1
00:00:13,240 --> 00:00:14,610
He-he sent...
He sent me an e-mail.

2
00:00:15,940 --> 00:00:17,820
Bryce sent me a whole dabase of government secrets.

3
00:00:17,820 --> 00:00:22,970
That are now locked in my brain, keeping me in a constant state of fear, danger and anxiety.

4
00:00:23,440 --> 00:00:24,300
Bryce larkin.

5
00:00:24,300 --> 00:00:28,080
Dude pretended to be his buddy, sexed up his girl, and then got him kicked out of stanford.

6
00:00:28,200 --> 00:00:31,060
??????

7
00:00:31,120 --> 00:00:33,610
Stanford was five years ago.
You need to move on.

8
00:00:42,060 --> 00:00:44,810
It's our subconscious mind that we're going to be talking about today.

9
00:00:45,220 --> 00:00:47,470
How can we penetrate the human mind?

10
00:00:48,050 --> 00:00:49,550
How can we understand it?

11
00:00:50,160 --> 00:00:51,510
How many images do you see?

12
00:00:52,680 --> 00:00:53,930
- Students: five.
- Ten.

13
00:00:53,930 --> 00:00:56,980
There are hundreds of images compressed inside this picture.

14
00:00:57,820 --> 00:00:59,550
The encoding is special.

15
00:01:06,730 --> 00:01:08,350
You only remember that one.

16
00:01:08,350 --> 00:01:10,730
Your subconscious, though, saw them all.

17
00:01:11,360 --> 00:01:12,900
We'll see how you do on the final exam.

18
00:01:12,900 --> 00:01:16,630
I include a section on subliminal image recognition, where you'll...

19
00:01:21,150 --> 00:01:23,550
Thank you.We'll, uh, 
we'll end early today.

20
00:01:23,550 --> 00:01:24,600
Class dismissed.

21
00:01:27,860 --> 00:01:29,710
Professor, how can we isolate...

22
00:01:38,430 --> 00:01:40,750
This is glass castle, reporting hostile contact.

23
00:01:41,260 --> 00:01:42,900
I made a mistake, black coat.

24
00:01:43,220 --> 00:01:45,460
I coed intel for myself onto a disc.

25
00:01:45,880 --> 00:01:48,320
They're after it.
I know i shouldn't have.

26
00:02:19,910 --> 00:02:21,250
Morgan: chuck, we have an emergency.

27
00:02:21,740 --> 00:02:22,530
We need to talk.

28
00:02:23,690 --> 00:02:24,350
I'm on the phone.

29
00:02:25,220 --> 00:02:28,130
Not here, not here.
There are spies at the buy more.

30
00:02:29,280 --> 00:02:30,200
Spies?
Really?

31
00:02:30,270 --> 00:02:31,480
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.

32
00:02:31,480 --> 00:02:32,440
Tang's minions, man.

33
00:02:32,440 --> 00:02:33,270
They're everywhere.

34
00:02:33,680 --> 00:02:36,470
He's like the dark lord sauron, from lord of the rings, only instead of the ring of power,  

35
00:02:36,470 --> 00:02:38,520
He's taken over control of the assistant managership.

36
00:02:38,700 --> 00:02:40,310
Yeah.
From me.

37
00:02:40,610 --> 00:02:41,760
Right.
Thanks for the reminder.

38
00:02:41,760 --> 00:02:43,830
Got it, man.
Listen, we need your help, chuck.

39
00:02:43,910 --> 00:02:45,200
Help?
What am i supposed to do?

40
00:02:45,200 --> 00:02:46,030
I'm, i'm just...
Just one...

41
00:02:46,030 --> 00:02:47,630
Small hobbit?

42
00:02:48,080 --> 00:02:50,110
So thought frodo baggins, my friend.

43
00:02:50,990 --> 00:02:52,820
So thought frodo baggins.

44
00:02:55,500 --> 00:02:58,440
"rules and regulations for the buy more break room.

45
00:02:58,440 --> 00:03:00,290
From the desk of harry tang"?

46
00:03:00,290 --> 00:03:01,470
He doesn't even have a desk.

47
00:03:01,840 --> 00:03:03,890
This is an affront to human decency.

48
00:03:03,890 --> 00:03:07,830
"no swearing, no expectorating, no fornicating.

49
00:03:08,310 --> 00:03:09,840
" wait, people been getting freaky in the break room?

50
00:03:09,840 --> 00:03:11,240
No.
No.

51
00:03:11,520 --> 00:03:13,070
But i liked to know that i had the option.

52
00:03:14,070 --> 00:03:15,440
Okay, so it's a little strict.

53
00:03:15,440 --> 00:03:17,490
It's torture...
Man.

54
00:03:18,090 --> 00:03:20,340
The no-drug policy includes red bull.

55
00:03:20,340 --> 00:03:21,640
Oh, ouch.

56
00:03:21,640 --> 00:03:23,590
I remember the last time you tried to detox.

57
00:03:23,590 --> 00:03:25,840
How am i supposed to move electronics with the sweaty shakes?

58
00:03:25,840 --> 00:03:28,940
I'm sorry, fellows, but is this the talk more?

59
00:03:29,550 --> 00:03:32,020
No, sir, it's the buy more.

60
00:03:32,020 --> 00:03:37,700
So why don't you get back to helping these nice 
customers buy more eleronics, mr.Grimes?

61
00:03:42,510 --> 00:03:45,850
I'm sorry, t is harry wearing a new assistant manager polo shirt?

62
00:03:46,170 --> 00:03:47,320
It's monogrammed.

63
00:03:49,240 --> 00:03:50,500
He must be stopped.

64
00:03:58,740 --> 00:04:01,070
That new hi-def screen sure shows every wrinkle.

65
00:04:02,190 --> 00:04:03,440
They can hear you.

66
00:04:03,750 --> 00:04:05,020
What?
Twinkle.

67
00:04:05,680 --> 00:04:06,700
Every twinkle...

68
00:04:07,370 --> 00:04:08,600
In her eye.

69
00:04:09,120 --> 00:04:09,900
Eyes.

70
00:04:11,360 --> 00:04:12,550
We have a situation.

71
00:04:12,870 --> 00:04:14,990
A cia asset has gone missing.

72
00:04:14,990 --> 00:04:17,660
We've had no communication from him for two days.

73
00:04:19,110 --> 00:04:20,060
No way.

74
00:04:20,250 --> 00:04:21,470
What, did you flash?

75
00:04:21,470 --> 00:04:22,590
No.I don't have to.


76
00:04:22,590 --> 00:04:24,430
That guy was my professor at stanford.

77
00:04:27,760 --> 00:04:30,610
Wait.Asset?He's cia?
My professor was a spy?

78
00:04:30,610 --> 00:04:33,260
The cia recruits on campuses across the country.

79
00:04:33,260 --> 00:04:36,320
Pressor fleming is a company scientist, not an operative.

80
00:04:36,320 --> 00:04:38,470
This is our last communication from him.

81
00:04:38,470 --> 00:04:40,560
This is glass castle reporting hostile contact.

82
00:04:41,140 --> 00:04:42,760
I made a mistake, black coat.

83
00:04:43,070 --> 00:04:45,310
I copied intel for myself onto a disc.

84
00:04:45,800 --> 00:04:48,350
They're after it.
I know i shouldn't have.

85
00:04:49,090 --> 00:04:50,630
Do we know what intel he copied?

86
00:04:50,630 --> 00:04:51,430
Beckman: we don't.

87
00:04:51,430 --> 00:04:54,140
He's handled many sensitive projects for us over the years.

88
00:04:54,140 --> 00:04:56,070
Any leak could prove devastating.

89
00:04:56,070 --> 00:04:56,780
How can wehelp?

90
00:04:56,780 --> 00:04:58,710
Fleming has contacts in la.

91
00:04:58,710 --> 00:05:00,730
????

92
00:05:00,730 --> 00:05:02,890
We'd like your help on this, chuck.

93
00:05:05,280 --> 00:05:07,850
Look, i-i-i really don't think i'm you're go-to guy on this one.

94
00:05:07,850 --> 00:05:10,450
Your knowledge of fleming and stanford is key here.

95
00:05:10,450 --> 00:05:14,220
We only have his official reports.
You have a rsonal connection.

96
00:05:14,220 --> 00:05:17,860
Yeah, i do have a personal connection, a very bad personal connection.

97
00:05:17,860 --> 00:05:19,620
Look, you guys have the file, okay?

98
00:05:19,620 --> 00:05:22,320
You know all about fleming and what happened to me.

99
00:05:22,320 --> 00:05:23,600
The guy kicked me out of school.

100
00:05:23,890 --> 00:05:25,850
Chuck, professor fleming is one of us.

101
00:05:26,310 --> 00:05:29,650
Maybe you can find somebody else to help you this time.

102
00:05:29,650 --> 00:05:30,720
Maybe just this once.

103
00:05:44,090 --> 00:05:46,350
* who invented the, uh, ucla brain trust?

104
00:05:46,350 --> 00:05:48,590
Those are devon's fraternity brothers.

105
00:05:48,590 --> 00:05:52,710
We are actually all caravanning up to stanford for the ucla game this weekend.

106
00:05:52,710 --> 00:05:54,760
Hey, chuck!
Go deep, brah.

107
00:05:58,200 --> 00:05:59,440
Right in the pills.

108
00:05:59,860 --> 00:06:02,150
Don't touch...Please-please don't...
Please don't touch me.

109
00:06:02,150 --> 00:06:03,090
Chuck.
Come on, man.

110
00:06:03,090 --> 00:06:05,470
Let me make it up to you, bro.
Get up.

111
00:06:05,880 --> 00:06:07,310
I got you a ticket for the game.

112
00:06:09,140 --> 00:06:10,050
Thanks.

113
00:06:10,370 --> 00:06:11,280
But, uh...

114
00:06:11,630 --> 00:06:13,550
Sarah and i already have plans.

115
00:06:13,990 --> 00:06:15,340
It's your alma mater, dude.

116
00:06:15,340 --> 00:06:20,650
Look, no offense, but i'd rather get hit in the produce section again

117
00:06:20,650 --> 00:06:22,190
 than go back to that   Place.

118
00:06:22,700 --> 00:06:23,600
Suit yourself.

119
00:06:24,150 --> 00:06:25,500
Let's go.
Game on, boys.

120
00:06:25,560 --> 00:06:26,300
Where's the ball?

121
00:06:27,460 --> 00:06:28,810
Uh, listen...

122
00:06:29,200 --> 00:06:32,690
I know that stanford doesn't hold a lot of good memories for you...

123
00:06:32,690 --> 00:06:33,980
Look, ellie.
Ellie.


124
00:06:34,820 --> 00:06:36,560
They kicked me out for something i didn't do.

125
00:06:37,310 --> 00:06:38,510
Okay?
So that's it.

126
00:06:38,510 --> 00:06:39,570
Me and stanford...

127
00:06:40,430 --> 00:06:41,570
We're officially done.

128
00:07:08,540 --> 00:07:10,440
stanford university

129
00:07:10,440 --> 00:07:14,900
stanford university
2003


130
00:07:34,190 --> 00:07:36,140
It sucks you have to leave, chuck.

131
00:07:44,210 --> 00:07:45,680
I don't get it, bryce.

132
00:07:46,750 --> 00:07:47,840
Why are you doing this?

133
00:07:50,350 --> 00:07:51,840
You did this to yourself.

134
00:08:32,360 --> 00:08:33,380
* what?

135
00:08:34,650 --> 00:08:36,440
I just flashed on myself.

136
00:08:37,900 --> 00:08:40,030
Why am i in the intersect?

137
00:08:40,760 --> 00:08:50,760
<font color="#4096d1">-==http://subland.5286.cn==-</font>

138
00:08:50,760 --> 00:09:01,770
<font color="#4096d1">sync:虾米</font>

139
00:09:01,770 --> 00:09:11,770
<font color="#4096d1">Chuck.S01E07</font>

140
00:09:12,060 --> 00:09:14,070
So you don't know why i'm in the intersect.

141
00:09:14,070 --> 00:09:18,060
Well, you didn't appear on the nsa radar until afterbryce sent you the intersect.

142
00:09:18,060 --> 00:09:20,870
- Same withthe cia
-  why don't i find that reassuring?

143
00:09:20,870 --> 00:09:23,830
So the files that you saw were of you in college, right?

144
00:09:23,830 --> 00:09:25,200
Yes.
Yes.

145
00:09:25,200 --> 00:09:25,810
Wait a minute, wait a minute.

146
00:09:25,810 --> 00:09:26,950
What about professor fleming?

147
00:09:26,950 --> 00:09:28,430
I was in his class.
He was cia.

148
00:09:28,430 --> 00:09:29,140
Could that be it?

149
00:09:29,140 --> 00:09:31,960
Well, if we can find fleming, maybe he can give us some answers.

150
00:09:31,960 --> 00:09:32,770
Okay.

151
00:09:33,180 --> 00:09:34,140
Let's do that.

152
00:09:34,140 --> 00:09:35,210
Sarah: it won't be easy.

153
00:09:35,210 --> 00:09:37,460
New intel suggests the professor is being hunted.

154
00:09:37,460 --> 00:09:41,370
The nsa interviewed one witness in fleming's class who id'd a magnus einersson.

155
00:09:41,370 --> 00:09:42,970
He's an icelandic spy.

156
00:09:42,970 --> 00:09:45,390
Chuck: i'm sorry.
Iceland does espionage?

157
00:09:45,390 --> 00:09:47,650
Magnus buys and sells intel to the highest bidder.

158
00:09:47,650 --> 00:09:50,980
Iceland isn't officially aware of his activities.

159
00:09:50,980 --> 00:09:53,770
Sarah: it says here the crossbow is his weapon of choice.

160
00:09:53,770 --> 00:09:55,910
Chuck: what, slingshots too ineffective?

161
00:09:58,460 --> 00:10:00,350
Hey, buddy, where you going?

162
00:10:00,940 --> 00:10:02,680
What's up?
My lunch break is over.

163
00:10:03,000 --> 00:10:04,000
You haven't seen?

164
00:10:04,000 --> 00:10:04,810
Seen what?

165
00:10:05,250 --> 00:10:07,190
New staggered lunch schedule.

166
00:10:07,190 --> 00:10:08,040
Dude.

167
00:10:09,260 --> 00:10:10,400
Single shifts.

168
00:10:10,400 --> 00:10:12,630
No more fraternization in the break room.

169
00:10:12,630 --> 00:10:14,670
We can't en eat lunch together anymore.

170
00:10:15,900 --> 00:10:18,200
No more wednesday-friday surf and turf?

171
00:10:19,020 --> 00:10:20,970
Harry tang is drunk with power.

172
00:10:20,970 --> 00:10:22,510
Anna: he could have an accident.

173
00:10:26,070 --> 00:10:29,000
I'm just saying.
I know a guy, very reasonable.

174
00:10:29,830 --> 00:10:31,230
His rates, i mean...

175
00:10:31,620 --> 00:10:32,510
Not him.

176
00:10:33,040 --> 00:10:36,890
Way to think outsideof the box, anna.
Me likey.

177
00:10:37,270 --> 00:10:38,230
What do you say, chuck?

178
00:10:38,230 --> 00:10:39,730
Are you two crazy?
What?

179
00:10:39,730 --> 00:10:43,680
No, i'm not gonna have a guy rubbed out just because he upsets our lunch routine.

180
00:10:43,680 --> 00:10:44,520
I see.

181
00:10:44,520 --> 00:10:46,230
So you've already thrown in the towel.

182
00:10:46,230 --> 00:10:47,030
Cool.

183
00:10:48,560 --> 00:10:49,740
Not me, chuck.

184
00:10:51,130 --> 00:10:54,010
I'm not getting pushed around anymore.
No way.

185
00:10:55,380 --> 00:10:58,500
I hope you were aiming for the recycling bin, grimes, 

186
00:10:58,500 --> 00:11:01,910
now that i'm instituting a new buy more  Green program.x

187
00:11:04,000 --> 00:11:06,600
Tree-hugging is all the rage these days.

188
00:11:08,030 --> 00:11:12,580
I plan on exploiting the burgeoning conscience of the american consumer.

189
00:11:13,560 --> 00:11:15,900
Well, that's very inspiring, harry.

190
00:11:22,550 --> 00:11:25,000
I'm gonna be the one who breaks you, grimes.

191
00:11:25,500 --> 00:11:26,540
You know why?

192
00:11:28,320 --> 00:11:29,730
Because you're soft...

193
00:11:30,550 --> 00:11:31,690
Like pudding.

194
00:11:40,890 --> 00:11:42,640
I've been doing all these crunches, man.

195
00:11:43,220 --> 00:11:44,560
I know, buddy.

196
00:11:53,630 --> 00:11:56,250
You didn't offer to kill harry for anna, did you?

197
00:11:56,780 --> 00:11:57,410
No.

198
00:11:57,670 --> 00:11:58,490
Why?
You want me to kill him?

199
00:11:58,490 --> 00:11:59,170
No.

200
00:12:00,120 --> 00:12:01,210
No, just curious.

201
00:12:01,210 --> 00:12:03,640
We just got a hit off a traffic camera in hollywood.

202
00:12:05,130 --> 00:12:05,920
That's fleming.

203
00:12:06,160 --> 00:12:08,860
Thanks.
You just saved me a lot of investigative work there, intersect.


204
00:12:08,860 --> 00:12:09,980
Dmv told me that.

205
00:12:09,980 --> 00:12:11,570
Wow, sarcasm.
What a surprise.

206
00:12:11,570 --> 00:12:13,250
We located the car fleming was driving.

207
00:12:13,250 --> 00:12:15,480
A local address.
We're bringing him in asap.

208
00:12:15,480 --> 00:12:16,470
So what do you need me for?

209
00:12:16,470 --> 00:12:17,680
Yours is a friendly face.

210
00:12:18,060 --> 00:12:20,600
Your professor sees you there, he'll be more inclined to cooperate.
Copy?

211
00:12:20,600 --> 00:12:23,500
Yeah, except that i wasn't exactly the professor's star pupil.

212
00:12:23,500 --> 00:12:24,430
We leave in three.

213
00:12:26,620 --> 00:12:30,140
Fleming: as you're aware, you scored perfectly on your midterm exam.

214
00:12:31,660 --> 00:12:33,560
Yeah, well, i was up all night studying.

215
00:12:33,560 --> 00:12:34,580
It was a monster.

216
00:12:34,580 --> 00:12:35,380
No offense.

217
00:12:35,380 --> 00:12:38,920
You even aced the last section-- encoded images.

218
00:12:39,640 --> 00:12:41,910
That, yeah, those were just kind of a shot in the dark.

219
00:12:42,470 --> 00:12:47,350
You may be aware, i keep an answer key to every exam locked inside this office.

220
00:12:48,250 --> 00:12:50,540
- No, no, i wasn't aware of that 
- really?

221
00:12:51,180 --> 00:12:56,680
Then how do you explain the midterm answer key being found in your fraternity room?

222
00:12:57,660 --> 00:12:59,100
I'm-i'm sorry.
Wha...


223
00:12:59,100 --> 00:13:00,270
You searched my room?

224
00:13:00,310 --> 00:13:02,450
We received a tip from a student this morning.

225
00:13:05,510 --> 00:13:06,410
What, you...

226
00:13:06,740 --> 00:13:08,750
You got a tip about my room?

227
00:13:08,750 --> 00:13:11,690
I need to know how you broke into this office and stole the answers, chuck.

228
00:13:11,920 --> 00:13:12,800
I...

229
00:13:13,130 --> 00:13:14,160
I didn't steal anything.

230
00:13:14,160 --> 00:13:14,800
I don't have to.

231
00:13:14,800 --> 00:13:15,960
I'm acing your class.

232
00:13:15,960 --> 00:13:16,960
Exactly.

233
00:13:16,960 --> 00:13:19,390
The student also claimed that you're selling copies.

234
00:13:19,390 --> 00:13:20,390
What?

235
00:13:20,390 --> 00:13:24,410
I know you're a scholarship student, and that stanford is a very expensive school...

236
00:13:24,410 --> 00:13:27,340
Look, look, who-whoever gave you your tip...

237
00:13:27,870 --> 00:13:29,020
Was lying.

238
00:13:30,800 --> 00:13:35,440
Our source was bryce larkin, your roommate.

239
00:13:47,440 --> 00:13:48,040
All right.

240
00:13:48,400 --> 00:13:49,380
We all know the game.

241
00:13:49,730 --> 00:13:51,160
We all know the rules.

242
00:13:51,160 --> 00:13:53,410
This is "fingers of fury.

243
00:13:53,410 --> 00:13:58,130
" the win goes to the contestant who can identify the most tv shows in a minute, all right?

244
00:13:58,130 --> 00:13:59,240
Who do you want next?

245
00:14:00,610 --> 00:14:01,950
I challenge...

246
00:14:03,140 --> 00:14:05,220
The ruling champion, morgan grimes.

247
00:14:05,220 --> 00:14:07,890
That's mr.Morgan grimes if you're nasty.

248
00:14:07,890 --> 00:14:08,610
Really.

249
00:14:08,780 --> 00:14:09,740
Ooh, the suspense.

250
00:14:09,740 --> 00:14:10,520
You don't want me, punk.

251
00:14:10,520 --> 00:14:11,440
Oh, yes, i do.

252
00:14:11,440 --> 00:14:12,670
Challenge accepted.

253
00:14:12,670 --> 00:14:13,700
Bang!

254
00:14:14,240 --> 00:14:15,450
On my mark!

255
00:14:15,800 --> 00:14:16,370
Three...

256
00:14:17,550 --> 00:14:18,100
Two...

257
00:14:18,750 --> 00:14:19,410
One!

258
00:14:19,410 --> 00:14:20,340
Mark!

259
00:14:21,640 --> 00:14:22,720
-dukes of hazzard.
- One tree hill.

260
00:14:22,720 --> 00:14:24,070
- Veronica mars.
- Gilmore girls.

261
00:14:24,070 --> 00:14:26,060
- Cold case.
- Animaniacs.

262
00:14:26,520 --> 00:14:27,510
- ???
- Smallville.

263
00:14:27,510 --> 00:14:29,530
- O.C., season 2.
- Underrated.

264
00:14:29,530 --> 00:14:30,760
Kung fu: the movie.

265
00:14:31,150 --> 00:14:32,660
Night court.
Night court.

266
00:14:33,610 --> 00:14:34,720
Um, they're not changing.

267
00:14:34,720 --> 00:14:35,970
Anna, the channels are not changing.

268
00:14:35,970 --> 00:14:36,980
Tang: it is now mine.

269
00:14:39,120 --> 00:14:42,030
The one remote that controls them all.

270
00:14:42,030 --> 00:14:43,720
The master remote.

271
00:14:44,220 --> 00:14:46,090
Your slacking days are over.

272
00:14:46,090 --> 00:14:47,930
Tang, there aren't even any customers.

273
00:14:47,930 --> 00:14:53,240
Three repair orders just came in, which you nerds would know if you were at your stations.

274
00:14:53,240 --> 00:14:57,020
And grimes, since there aren't any more customers, 

275
00:14:57,260 --> 00:14:59,860
i need a cleanup in the diaper-changing   Station.

276
00:15:00,910 --> 00:15:02,010
Wear a mask.

277
00:15:04,420 --> 00:15:06,870
We'll extract the professor as quickly as possible.

278
00:15:07,390 --> 00:15:08,120
You'll keep watch?

279
00:15:08,790 --> 00:15:10,910
If i flash on any bad guys, i'll call.

280
00:15:11,250 --> 00:15:12,580
Sarah: everything looks quiet, but...

281
00:15:12,580 --> 00:15:14,020
I know.
I know.

282
00:15:14,020 --> 00:15:15,210
Stay in the car.

283
00:15:15,490 --> 00:15:16,900
Okay, good.
????

284
00:15:50,620 --> 00:15:51,650
Professor fleming?

285
00:15:52,130 --> 00:15:52,720
Hey!

286
00:15:52,720 --> 00:15:54,550
No, no, no, no, wait, professor!
It's me, chuck!

287
00:15:55,130 --> 00:15:56,780
Professor, stop.
We're here to extract you!

288
00:15:56,780 --> 00:15:58,580
Glass castle!
Glass castle!


289
00:15:58,840 --> 00:15:59,730
I'm sorry, i didn't...

290
00:15:59,970 --> 00:16:01,170
I didn't mean to scare you.

291
00:16:01,170 --> 00:16:01,930
But it's...

292
00:16:02,580 --> 00:16:03,750
It's chuck.

293
00:16:05,090 --> 00:16:06,320
I wa...
I was in your...

294
00:16:06,320 --> 00:16:09,510
Your psychology and symbolism class at stanford.

295
00:16:09,510 --> 00:16:10,740
I don't know if you remember me, but...

296
00:16:10,740 --> 00:16:11,810
Chuck bartowski.

297
00:16:11,810 --> 00:16:13,340
Of course i remember you.

298
00:16:15,030 --> 00:16:18,120
Yeah, i guess it's not every day you kick a guy out of school, huh?

299
00:16:19,280 --> 00:16:20,320
At least i hope not.

300
00:16:21,210 --> 00:16:24,650
So you're, uh, with the agency now.

301
00:16:25,000 --> 00:16:25,950
Why didn't you say so?

302
00:16:26,320 --> 00:16:28,860
I don't think i'm supposed to, really.

303
00:16:28,860 --> 00:16:30,420
Well, we have code phrases.

304
00:16:31,380 --> 00:16:32,310
Didn't they train you?

305
00:16:32,310 --> 00:16:33,890
I-i mostly just stay in the car.

306
00:16:33,890 --> 00:16:38,890
Next time, if it's a dangerous situation, say, "are you coming to the toga party?

307
00:16:40,360 --> 00:16:41,780
" a real...
A real code phrase.

308
00:16:41,780 --> 00:16:43,180
I like it.
That's awesome.


309
00:16:43,180 --> 00:16:44,400
So, uh, so what are we doing now?

310
00:16:44,400 --> 00:16:45,370
Who's-who's bringing me in?

311
00:16:45,370 --> 00:16:48,420
Oh, right.
Yeah, so, uh, sarah and casey will...


312
00:16:48,420 --> 00:16:49,940
Will do that, but, um...

313
00:16:49,940 --> 00:16:52,400
I was wondering if i could ask you something first?

314
00:16:53,340 --> 00:16:55,820
Why did the cia have a file on me at stanford?

315
00:17:00,350 --> 00:17:01,300
I'm sorry.

316
00:17:04,230 --> 00:17:07,210
Oh, hey, hey...

317
00:17:07,210 --> 00:17:12,150
Hey, buddy, let's not beat ourselves up, you know.
The past is the past.

318
00:17:13,690 --> 00:17:17,460
Okay, look, uh, we didn't really know each other that well at college, 

319
00:17:17,460 --> 00:17:19,240
and this is a little  Awkward, what...

320
00:17:21,660 --> 00:17:23,330
Oh, boy!
Oh, boy!

321
00:17:23,330 --> 00:17:24,900
Hey, hey, hang in there.

322
00:17:24,900 --> 00:17:26,870
Hang...
Ha in there!

323
00:17:26,870 --> 00:17:29,220
Give this to bryce larkin.

324
00:17:29,930 --> 00:17:30,790
Bryce?

325
00:17:31,400 --> 00:17:32,540
Bryce larkin?

326
00:17:32,540 --> 00:17:34,300
What does bryce have to do with this?

327
00:17:49,400 --> 00:17:50,400
I'm nobody, i swear.

328
00:17:52,770 --> 00:17:54,430
????

329
00:17:54,940 --> 00:17:57,770
Man down!Man down!
Help me!help!

330
00:17:58,200 --> 00:18:00,880
Hey, hey, come on!
come on!

331
00:18:11,610 --> 00:18:13,710
I'm sorry, chuck, but we have to talk.

332
00:18:13,710 --> 00:18:14,690
Okay.

333
00:18:16,570 --> 00:18:17,850
So how was the hospital?

334
00:18:18,680 --> 00:18:20,000
Is the professor going to be okay?

335
00:18:20,000 --> 00:18:21,340
They putting him into surgery now.

336
00:18:21,340 --> 00:18:23,840
The problem is, we can't talk to him to sort this mess out.

337
00:18:23,840 --> 00:18:25,520
You sure it was magnus you saw?

338
00:18:25,520 --> 00:18:26,680
Gee, i don't know, casey.

339
00:18:26,680 --> 00:18:28,890
How many psycho archers do you know?

340
00:18:29,560 --> 00:18:30,830
I asked fleming about stanford.

341
00:18:30,830 --> 00:18:32,050
About why i was in the intersect.

342
00:18:32,050 --> 00:18:33,500
I should've brought him right to you, i'm sorry.

343
00:18:33,500 --> 00:18:35,020
Hey, it's not your fault, chuck.

344
00:18:35,020 --> 00:18:36,940
Yeah, well, i keep thinking about what he said.

345
00:18:37,350 --> 00:18:39,470
Why would he want me to bring those numbers to bryce?

346
00:18:39,470 --> 00:18:42,330
Bryce must have been one of his cia contacts, 

347
00:18:43,120 --> 00:18:45,560
and fleming was probably never told of his   Death.

348
00:18:45,560 --> 00:18:47,270
List off the numbers you remember.

349
00:18:47,270 --> 00:18:49,930
I don't know, there were, like ten of them.
A couple of nines, uh...

350
00:18:50,290 --> 00:18:52,140
A five...
Definitely started with a two.

351
00:18:52,140 --> 00:18:52,750
Casey: that's it?

352
00:18:52,750 --> 00:18:54,030
You have a computer for a brain...

353
00:18:54,030 --> 00:18:57,240
Look, it was a very stressful situation, okay, casey?

354
00:18:57,240 --> 00:18:59,570
I watched a guy get skewered by a crossbow.

355
00:19:00,880 --> 00:19:02,020
Look, fleming knew something.

356
00:19:02,020 --> 00:19:03,610
Right before he fell, he said, "i'm sorry.

357
00:19:03,610 --> 00:19:04,740
" why would he say that?

358
00:19:04,740 --> 00:19:05,910
I don't know, chuck.

359
00:19:06,790 --> 00:19:09,300
Yeah, well, i think he might know why i'm in the intersect.

360
00:19:12,360 --> 00:19:13,200
You okay?

361
00:19:14,190 --> 00:19:17,550
It's not too late for you to change your mind about revisiting the old alma mater.

362
00:19:18,400 --> 00:19:20,320
Spending some time with me and devon...

363
00:19:20,320 --> 00:19:21,250
Oh, please!

364
00:19:21,690 --> 00:19:25,110
U just don't want to be stuck in a car alone with awesome's frat buddies.

365
00:19:25,110 --> 00:19:31,250
Maybe, or maybe i'm your sister and i care abouyou and i think that going back to stanford  

366
00:19:31,250 --> 00:19:33,640
Would help you to move on.

367
00:19:34,120 --> 00:19:37,530
I love you, sis, an-and i take a lot of bullets for you, 

368
00:19:37,530 --> 00:19:41,780
but five hours in a car with awesome  
And his "brahs"?

369
00:19:42,250 --> 00:19:43,860
That is asking too much.

370
00:19:43,860 --> 00:19:48,740
Besides, if i came, you wouldn't have room for your fun, old foam finger!

371
00:19:48,740 --> 00:19:49,560
- Stop it.
- What is this?

372
00:19:49,560 --> 00:19:51,100
I don't know.
But look at what i found.

373
00:19:51,100 --> 00:19:53,370
You see this?
It was in my old college stuff.

374
00:19:54,970 --> 00:19:57,010
The decline and fall of t roman empire.

375
00:19:57,360 --> 00:20:00,160
You want me to return it to the stanford library for you?

376
00:20:00,440 --> 00:20:01,230
No.

377
00:20:01,230 --> 00:20:03,230
Well, i'd kind of like to finish it.

378
00:20:03,940 --> 00:20:04,720
Sehow it ends.

379
00:20:05,070 --> 00:20:06,970
Chuck, that book is, like, four years overdue.

380
00:20:06,970 --> 00:20:08,760
What do you think stanford's going to do, huh?

381
00:20:09,540 --> 00:20:10,290
Expel me?

382
00:20:19,460 --> 00:20:21,340
Bryce: you're a dead man, chuck bartowski.

383
00:20:24,030 --> 00:20:27,470
stanford university
2003


384
00:20:47,740 --> 00:20:48,310
* all right!

385
00:20:49,010 --> 00:20:49,810
Come on, bryce!

386
00:20:51,390 --> 00:20:52,100
Give it up, buddy.

387
00:20:52,100 --> 00:20:53,100
I know you're out of ammo.

388
00:20:53,100 --> 00:20:53,990
I've been counting.

389
00:20:55,940 --> 00:20:56,510
Buddy.

390
00:20:57,060 --> 00:20:57,890
Whoa, whoa, oh.

391
00:20:59,380 --> 00:21:01,150
You wouldn't fire at an unarmed guy.

392
00:21:01,770 --> 00:21:02,470
I might.

393
00:21:03,110 --> 00:21:04,490
It's hardly sportsmanlike.

394
00:21:06,090 --> 00:21:06,740
What's this?

395
00:21:08,880 --> 00:21:10,420
Gynecology for geeks.

396
00:21:11,840 --> 00:21:12,570
You read this?

397
00:21:12,570 --> 00:21:13,940
No.
Is it a good read?

398
00:21:15,520 --> 00:21:16,060
Gotcha.

399
00:21:16,420 --> 00:21:18,740
Larkin over bartowski again.

400
00:21:25,790 --> 00:21:26,920
Chuck: i know what the numbers mean.

401
00:21:27,480 --> 00:21:29,390
They're for a book in the stanford library.

402
00:21:29,390 --> 00:21:31,490
Bryce had a place where he would stash stuff, right?

403
00:21:31,490 --> 00:21:33,040
I bet he told fleming about it.

404
00:21:33,040 --> 00:21:35,560
The professor must have the intel there for bryce to find.

405
00:21:35,560 --> 00:21:39,310
Annow it's only a matter of time before magnus figures it out and beats us to the book.

406
00:21:39,310 --> 00:21:39,850
Bingo.

407
00:21:39,850 --> 00:21:40,910
Unless we can beat him to it.

408
00:21:40,910 --> 00:21:43,050
Well, bryce kept his stuff on the third floor.

409
00:21:43,050 --> 00:21:44,450
???

410
00:21:49,930 --> 00:21:51,000
I'd have to be there to remember.

411
00:21:53,750 --> 00:21:55,570
I can't believe i'm about to say this, 

412
00:21:57,110 --> 00:21:59,060
but i have to go back to stanford.

413
00:22:00,630 --> 00:22:01,310
Cool.

414
00:22:02,080 --> 00:22:04,590
stanford. university

415
00:22:15,410 --> 00:22:17,100
?????????Out.

416
00:22:17,950 --> 00:22:19,500
It's like nothing has changed.

417
00:22:19,970 --> 00:22:21,090
Is that good or bad?

418
00:22:21,710 --> 00:22:25,540
It's, uh, it's, uh, you know, yeah..
It's, yeah.

419
00:22:26,350 --> 00:22:29,900
* whoo, go, bruins!

420
00:22:34,080 --> 00:22:34,920
Put me down!

421
00:22:36,740 --> 00:22:37,830
You ladies ready to rock?

422
00:22:37,830 --> 00:22:40,130
Yeah, when you put it that way, maybe not.

423
00:22:41,460 --> 00:22:42,360
Nice barbecue.

424
00:22:44,780 --> 00:22:46,960
Uh, you want to meet us at the stadium?

425
00:22:46,960 --> 00:22:49,840
I think we're probably gonna hang out here until the game starts.

426
00:22:50,210 --> 00:22:54,210
Yeah, yeah, i'm gonna take sarah for the chk bartowski memorial tour.

427
00:22:54,210 --> 00:22:58,190
So call me if any rabid stanford fans decide to put awesome in the hospital.

428
00:23:06,000 --> 00:23:07,070
* plant a stanford tree.

429
00:23:07,620 --> 00:23:09,810
Create a renewable resource for your children's future.

430
00:23:10,310 --> 00:23:11,530
Oh, you want to save our environment?

431
00:23:13,410 --> 00:23:14,730
Take a shower, hippie.

432
00:23:17,940 --> 00:23:19,310
Nice job blending in with the crowd.

433
00:23:19,310 --> 00:23:20,520
Who you rooting for, death?

434
00:23:21,160 --> 00:23:22,400
Leave the quips to me.

435
00:23:22,990 --> 00:23:24,780
The library's this way, across the quad.

436
00:23:32,440 --> 00:23:33,070
What is it?

437
00:23:35,610 --> 00:23:36,120
I don't know.

438
00:23:36,120 --> 00:23:38,240
I mean, i figured this would be tough, but this placece i

439
00:23:38,940 --> 00:23:41,530
s just a lot to take in, you know?

440
00:23:42,220 --> 00:23:44,060
I used to have so much fun here, and then...

441
00:23:45,180 --> 00:23:45,880
And then?

442
00:23:47,050 --> 00:23:48,410
It was the worst day of my life...

443
00:23:49,250 --> 00:23:50,420
Getting kicked out of here.

444
00:23:50,780 --> 00:23:53,580
Having to hear ellie's voice when i told her i was coming home.

445
00:23:53,580 --> 00:23:57,150
Packing up all my stu and leaving as bryce just stood there.

446
00:23:58,300 --> 00:23:59,790
Said i brought it on myself.

447
00:24:02,190 --> 00:24:04,520
Why do you think that bryce betrayed you?

448
00:24:04,950 --> 00:24:05,610
I don't know.

449
00:24:06,180 --> 00:24:08,280
He's had four years to call and set the record straight.

450
00:24:08,280 --> 00:24:09,290
Now that he's gone...

451
00:24:12,170 --> 00:24:13,180
You know what?
Forget it.

452
00:24:13,690 --> 00:24:15,720
Bryce has betrayed a lot of people, hasn't he?

453
00:24:19,890 --> 00:24:20,540
Roger that.

454
00:24:23,760 --> 00:24:25,360
All right, we have to play this really cool.

455
00:24:25,360 --> 00:24:26,810
Magnus has the library book number.

456
00:24:26,810 --> 00:24:27,800
He could have beaten us here.

457
00:24:27,800 --> 00:24:28,590
You think he's in there?

458
00:24:28,590 --> 00:24:30,000
Look, maybe you should stay here.

459
00:24:30,000 --> 00:24:31,510
Yeah, 'cause that always works out well.

460
00:24:31,510 --> 00:24:33,260
Anyway, you can't find the book without me.

461
00:24:33,260 --> 00:24:33,950
I'm going in.

462
00:24:39,940 --> 00:24:41,360
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.

463
00:24:41,800 --> 00:24:42,610
You looking for this?

464
00:24:45,240 --> 00:24:46,670
You stole my id?

465
00:24:46,670 --> 00:24:48,570
I borrowed it to reactivate it.

466
00:24:48,810 --> 00:24:51,490
Sorry i couldn't wipe the idiot grin off your face with photoshop.

467
00:25:07,700 --> 00:25:08,990
We have a situation.

468
00:25:09,760 --> 00:25:11,280
We have a situation here.

469
00:25:12,190 --> 00:25:17,380
Harry tang is a control freak and his master remote is a symbol of that control.

470
00:25:17,380 --> 00:25:18,730
It's his totem.

471
00:25:19,630 --> 00:25:22,620
We steal the remote and we take control of the televisions in the store.

472
00:25:22,620 --> 00:25:24,840
Rendering harry impotent.

473
00:25:24,840 --> 00:25:27,410
That's totally curable, by the way.

474
00:25:29,660 --> 00:25:30,210
Here's the thing.

475
00:25:30,210 --> 00:25:31,640
He keeps the remote in his locker, does he not?

476
00:25:31,640 --> 00:25:34,110
He does, but it's padlocked-- harry has the only key, 

477
00:25:34,830 --> 00:25:36,390
- so...
- I can get it.

478
00:25:38,700 --> 00:25:42,280
Trust me, you do not want to know.

479
00:25:42,520 --> 00:25:43,670
I-i do want to know.

480
00:25:44,050 --> 00:25:44,770
I want to know.

481
00:25:44,770 --> 00:25:45,690
You guys want to know?

482
00:25:45,690 --> 00:25:46,870
You should make a judgment call.

483
00:25:53,490 --> 00:25:55,090
* assistant manager tang?

484
00:25:56,920 --> 00:25:57,640
I'm busy.

485
00:25:58,230 --> 00:26:01,640
I'd like your opinn about how we could streamline 

486
00:26:01,640 --> 00:26:04,580
our  standing work orders to operate more  Efficiently.

487
00:26:05,360 --> 00:26:07,630
That's a admirable goal, young lady.

488
00:26:08,030 --> 00:26:12,310
You know, your new position of authority has changed you.

489
00:26:12,830 --> 00:26:14,970
You look different.

490
00:26:15,920 --> 00:26:17,950
Maybe it's the new monogrammed shirt.

491
00:26:18,870 --> 00:26:22,090
Maybe it's just the cut of yr slacks.

492
00:26:22,850 --> 00:26:25,650
I hope you plan to make other changes around the buy more.

493
00:26:26,340 --> 00:26:31,830
In fact, i can't wait for your next massive...

494
00:26:32,360 --> 00:26:33,920
Invasive...

495
00:26:33,940 --> 00:26:35,070
Move.

496
00:26:36,850 --> 00:26:42,280
Well, uh, for starters, i-i think that the staff sits around too far...

497
00:26:42,280 --> 00:26:43,520
Far too often.

498
00:26:43,950 --> 00:26:44,710
Okay.

499
00:26:58,980 --> 00:27:00,470
There.
There, that row.x

500
00:27:01,070 --> 00:27:01,790
Oh, no.

501
00:27:02,900 --> 00:27:03,600
We're too late.

502
00:27:03,600 --> 00:27:05,350
Magnus beat us here.
He's got the book.

503
00:27:05,620 --> 00:27:06,440
Hold on.

504
00:27:09,010 --> 00:27:09,840
Got ya.

505
00:27:14,840 --> 00:27:15,670
Hold on a sec.

506
00:27:24,170 --> 00:27:25,050
Got ya.

507
00:27:25,590 --> 00:27:26,360
The intel.

508
00:27:26,800 --> 00:27:29,160
The book number was just a way to mark the spot for the professor.

509
00:27:29,160 --> 00:27:32,650
Okay, well, let's get out of re before magnus realizes that book he has is worthless.

510
00:27:33,010 --> 00:27:34,400
Man: hey, you, don't move!

511
00:27:34,400 --> 00:27:35,940
Charles bartowski...

512
00:27:36,810 --> 00:27:41,460
You still owe the library $294.68 in late fees.

513
00:27:42,450 --> 00:27:43,980
Do you...
Do you take credit cards?

514
00:27:44,060 --> 00:27:45,070
This isn't funny.

515
00:27:48,050 --> 00:27:49,320
Chuck, run.

516
00:27:50,470 --> 00:27:51,910
Chuck, this way.

517
00:27:54,780 --> 00:27:56,940
It's hard to hate stanford 'cause they suck so hard.

518
00:27:56,940 --> 00:27:59,030
I wish we were playing sc today, huh?

519
00:28:28,110 --> 00:28:28,840
There you are.

520
00:28:28,850 --> 00:28:30,280
Man: hey, you, freeze!

521
00:28:32,360 --> 00:28:33,790
????

522
00:28:34,130 --> 00:28:35,170
Okay, we have to go.

523
00:28:35,170 --> 00:28:36,650
I swear this school has it in for me.

524
00:28:36,650 --> 00:28:37,460
Come on.

525
00:28:59,320 --> 00:29:00,360
Jackpot, baby.

526
00:29:00,780 --> 00:29:04,240
Looking for something, mr.Grimes?

527
00:29:05,680 --> 00:29:07,410
Are you kidding me?
You betrayed us?

528
00:29:11,940 --> 00:29:14,310
Nice try, pudding.

529
00:29:14,920 --> 00:29:16,370
I'm not afraid of you, harry, okay?

530
00:29:16,370 --> 00:29:17,180
You can't fire me.

531
00:29:17,180 --> 00:29:19,240
No, but i can make you wish i did.

532
00:29:19,890 --> 00:29:21,880
I need fresh bodies in the hole.

533
00:29:21,880 --> 00:29:23,580
Come on, dude, not-not the hole.

534
00:29:24,550 --> 00:29:25,840
Harry, just let's...

535
00:29:34,240 --> 00:29:35,680
We're safe for now.

536
00:29:35,680 --> 00:29:37,290
I need to see what's on this disk.

537
00:29:37,290 --> 00:29:39,360
Hey, chuck, that is top secret.

538
00:29:39,360 --> 00:29:43,240
Yeah, well, so am i, and there could be answers on this disk about why i'm in the intersect.

539
00:29:48,700 --> 00:29:49,830
Sarah: that's testing data.

540
00:29:51,090 --> 00:29:53,520
And videotaped interviews.
These are all just students.

541
00:29:53,520 --> 00:29:56,410
Exactly.Students that were recruited into the cia by fleming.

542
00:29:56,410 --> 00:29:57,610
Ten years worth.

543
00:29:57,820 --> 00:29:59,290
It's all their current information.

544
00:29:59,290 --> 00:30:00,950
No wonder magnus wanted it so badly.

545
00:30:00,950 --> 00:30:02,620
Foreign governments pay a fortune for that.

546
00:30:02,710 --> 00:30:04,850
Chuck: look at this right next to 2002-- bryce larkin.

547
00:30:04,850 --> 00:30:06,950
Bryce joined the cia our junior year?

548
00:30:07,010 --> 00:30:07,600
That's enough.

549
00:30:07,600 --> 00:30:08,420
Now we know what he's after 

550
00:30:08,420 --> 00:30:10,600
no, wait, wait, wait! That's me.
That's me!I'm in here, too.

551
00:30:11,230 --> 00:30:12,230
- Click it.
- Don't click it.x

552
00:30:13,440 --> 00:30:14,890
I never applied with the cia.

553
00:30:15,410 --> 00:30:16,180
Sarah: chuck, get down!

554
00:30:25,450 --> 00:30:28,030
??????

555
00:30:39,950 --> 00:30:41,990
???
Get me out of here!

556
00:30:44,440 --> 00:30:46,990
Chuck, when i say go, run out the side door.

557
00:30:46,990 --> 00:30:47,870
Protect the disk.

558
00:30:48,100 --> 00:30:48,920
We'll cover you.

559
00:30:50,270 --> 00:30:50,810
Go!

560
00:31:00,930 --> 00:31:02,400
All right, computers.

561
00:31:02,780 --> 00:31:03,400
Here we go.

562
00:31:09,700 --> 00:31:12,590
Okay, okay.

563
00:31:13,770 --> 00:31:14,430
Come on.

564
00:31:22,010 --> 00:31:22,700
Excuse me.

565
00:31:23,880 --> 00:31:24,590
Hello?

566
00:31:24,590 --> 00:31:25,980
Hi.
Hi.

567
00:31:25,980 --> 00:31:26,830
Uh, is this...

568
00:31:26,830 --> 00:31:27,720
Is this glenda mitchell?

569
00:31:27,720 --> 00:31:29,600
We're in the science building lecture hall.

570
00:31:29,600 --> 00:31:31,780
It's an emergency.
Bring lots of big guns.

571
00:31:31,780 --> 00:31:32,340
I'm sorry.

572
00:31:32,340 --> 00:31:33,900
Whoever this is, you've got the wrong number.

573
00:31:34,170 --> 00:31:35,290
Crap, there's a code phrase.

574
00:31:37,610 --> 00:31:39,230
Are you coming to the toga party?

575
00:31:42,330 --> 00:31:44,000
There's a place you can plant it in the quad.

576
00:31:44,110 --> 00:31:45,260
Let me give you the directions.

577
00:31:48,760 --> 00:31:50,300
Listen we have a situation right now.

578
00:31:50,300 --> 00:31:54,340
Bring any ammunition and-or equipment you might have for killing bad guys.

579
00:31:54,340 --> 00:31:56,790
- Are you coming to the toga party?
- ?????

580
00:32:00,290 --> 00:32:02,200
Lots of bad guys are surrounding us.
Thank you very much.

581
00:32:02,200 --> 00:32:03,750
Are you coming to the toga party?
Bye-bye.

582
00:32:07,720 --> 00:32:09,890
- Agent katz?
- Yeah.Hey, frodo, is that you?

583
00:32:10,030 --> 00:32:11,710
I thought my code name was samwise gamgee?

584
00:32:11,710 --> 00:32:14,660
Hey, samwise, why don't you get your thumb out?

585
00:32:14,660 --> 00:32:17,360
Morgan, listen, this is really, really not a good time.

586
00:32:17,360 --> 00:32:19,020
Yeah, it's not a good time over here, either, dude.

587
00:32:19,020 --> 00:32:21,320
Okay, i'm stuck in the hole doing customer service.

588
00:32:22,290 --> 00:32:23,620
These kids are animals.

589
00:32:23,620 --> 00:32:25,370
Okay, buddy, i get that, but i'm at stanford.

590
00:32:25,370 --> 00:32:26,390
What do you want me to do about it?

591
00:32:26,390 --> 00:32:29,190
Do you have the code to harry tang's master remote?

592
00:32:29,190 --> 00:32:30,420
I think i can use it to bargain for my freedom.

593
00:32:31,730 --> 00:32:35,070
Okay, okay, the code is ou812#.

594
00:32:35,820 --> 00:32:38,230
Dude, this is why you're my hero.
Thank you so much.

595
00:32:39,580 --> 00:32:41,930
Throwing things at an adult's heads is not the way to...

596
00:32:41,930 --> 00:32:43,770
That's not gonna help you in life.

597
00:32:49,420 --> 00:32:50,090
Oh, no.

598
00:33:06,230 --> 00:33:07,460
I only got two rounds left.

599
00:33:08,930 --> 00:33:10,140
I got half a mag.

600
00:33:10,140 --> 00:33:11,750
Man: drop your weapons and stand up!

601
00:33:11,750 --> 00:33:13,320
Hands where we can see them!

602
00:33:14,900 --> 00:33:15,880
I'm gonna go for it.

603
00:33:16,450 --> 00:33:17,110
You in?

604
00:33:17,560 --> 00:33:18,290
You bet.

605
00:33:19,100 --> 00:33:20,310
I hate long good-byes.

606
00:33:25,070 --> 00:33:26,920
Actually, why don't you drop your weapons.

607
00:33:28,220 --> 00:33:30,090
- Looks like someone called the cavalry.
- Good.

608
00:33:30,670 --> 00:33:32,180
'Cause i only had one shot left.

609
00:33:35,400 --> 00:33:36,880
Aren't you in econ with me?

610
00:33:51,920 --> 00:33:55,110
Please don't.Please don't, please don't, 
please don't, please don't.

611
00:33:59,230 --> 00:33:59,880
Woman: don't.

612
00:34:00,560 --> 00:34:01,170
Hah!

613
00:34:05,160 --> 00:34:06,700
You must be chuck bartowski.

614
00:34:06,700 --> 00:34:08,090
I just got your message.

615
00:34:08,090 --> 00:34:08,940
Are you okay?

616
00:34:08,940 --> 00:34:10,970
I'm just glad you check your voice mail.

617
00:34:22,440 --> 00:34:24,210
Golf commentator: he's probay got a game plan.

618
00:34:29,430 --> 00:34:30,170
What's going on?

619
00:34:36,840 --> 00:34:37,720
What's happening?

620
00:34:40,510 --> 00:34:41,640
Grimes!

621
00:34:46,690 --> 00:34:47,760
- Hey, what's up, harry?
- What's going on?

622
00:34:47,760 --> 00:34:49,560
You reprogrammed my remote.

623
00:34:49,560 --> 00:34:50,440
Wow, you...

624
00:34:50,820 --> 00:34:51,730
You can do that?

625
00:34:51,730 --> 00:34:53,150
You've gone too far, grimes.

626
00:34:53,150 --> 00:34:54,290
I've done nothing of the sort.

627
00:34:54,290 --> 00:34:57,480
I've actually been here all day helping these lovely customers.

628
00:34:59,170 --> 00:35:01,160
But i may be able to fix it...

629
00:35:02,430 --> 00:35:03,440
For a price.

630
00:35:04,960 --> 00:35:06,280
I want out of the hole.

631
00:35:07,870 --> 00:35:10,510
I'd rather take a potato peeler to my groin.

632
00:35:10,900 --> 00:35:11,480
Okay.

633
00:35:12,220 --> 00:35:12,930
Fine with me.

634
00:35:13,130 --> 00:35:15,870
I hope that big mike doesn't get too upset though 

635
00:35:15,870 --> 00:35:18,430
if all the televisions just happeto change   To, i don't know...

636
00:35:19,950 --> 00:35:21,050
Passion cove.

637
00:35:22,540 --> 00:35:23,830
Quid pro quo, harry.

638
00:35:24,210 --> 00:35:25,700
Yes or no?

639
00:35:31,250 --> 00:35:32,070
That a boy.

640
00:35:32,490 --> 00:35:33,370
Nice and easy.

641
00:35:38,650 --> 00:35:39,570
Smart man.

642
00:35:40,810 --> 00:35:41,610
You're dismissed.

643
00:35:44,420 --> 00:35:46,030
Go ahead.
Yes!

644
00:35:47,520 --> 00:35:48,570
True leader.

645
00:35:48,570 --> 00:35:49,570
It's...

646
00:35:50,300 --> 00:35:51,560
The grimes.

647
00:35:54,180 --> 00:35:57,450
Ellie: i can't believe that game was such a wash.
What a blowout.

648
00:35:57,840 --> 00:35:59,660
Worst game ever.

649
00:36:00,760 --> 00:36:01,780
It's not coming off.

650
00:36:02,370 --> 00:36:03,940
I think i used the wrong kind of paint.

651
00:36:03,940 --> 00:36:04,960
Well, what brand was it?

652
00:36:05,470 --> 00:36:07,090
Brand?
I don't know.

653
00:36:07,090 --> 00:36:08,490
One of the guys picked it up.

654
00:36:08,490 --> 00:36:10,060
I'll get some stronger soap.

655
00:36:11,840 --> 00:36:12,560
So...

656
00:36:12,790 --> 00:36:15,960
How painful was it?
The game, i mean.

657
00:36:15,960 --> 00:36:20,030
Well, uh, do you rember the evening with morgan at the karaoke club?

658
00:36:20,030 --> 00:36:22,930
His cover of peter cetera's "glory of love" that he dedicated to you?

659
00:36:23,050 --> 00:36:25,060
That completely ruined karate kid ii.

660
00:36:25,060 --> 00:36:26,230
Seriously, though, thanks...

661
00:36:26,230 --> 00:36:27,460
Thanks for pushing me.

662
00:36:27,860 --> 00:36:29,720
After the initial shock and horror, 

663
00:36:29,720 --> 00:36:33,050
it was a relief to finally go back, you know, say good- Bye.

664
00:36:34,780 --> 00:36:36,120
Well, i'm proud of you.

665
00:36:36,120 --> 00:36:38,650
You know, you faced your past head on.

666
00:36:39,460 --> 00:36:40,880
Did you find what you were looking for?

667
00:36:43,030 --> 00:36:43,960
Almost.

668
00:36:45,140 --> 00:36:46,260
You'll get there.

669
00:36:56,790 --> 00:36:58,810
You didn't think we'd let you keep that, did you?

670
00:37:01,230 --> 00:37:02,660
I need to know, sarah.

671
00:37:03,350 --> 00:37:04,280
Okay, chuck.

672
00:37:11,910 --> 00:37:15,470
Test subject 0326.Bartowski.

673
00:37:15,470 --> 00:37:17,080
This will be his first interview.

674
00:37:19,510 --> 00:37:20,650
Send chuck in.

675
00:37:22,930 --> 00:37:23,760
Bryce...

676
00:37:25,110 --> 00:37:27,230
This isn't a good time.
I'm waiting for another student.

677
00:37:27,620 --> 00:37:28,670
Chuck bartowski?

678
00:37:29,710 --> 00:37:31,150
He neverot your message.

679
00:37:31,150 --> 00:37:32,420
What are you talking about?

680
00:37:33,090 --> 00:37:36,050
You put uck on the cia recruitment track.

681
00:37:36,050 --> 00:37:37,570
It's not up to me, bryce.

682
00:37:37,570 --> 00:37:39,240
They want him for the omaha project.

683
00:37:39,240 --> 00:37:40,790
But that's a military operation.

684
00:37:40,790 --> 00:37:41,650
They'll turn chuck into...

685
00:37:41,650 --> 00:37:44,950
I'm required to send all the top test results to the agency.

686
00:37:45,780 --> 00:37:47,020
I want my friend out of this.

687
00:37:47,020 --> 00:37:48,590
He's a perfect candidate.

688
00:37:48,590 --> 00:37:54,390
Keywords in his essay responses correlate to 98% of the subliminal images in the exam.

689
00:37:54,390 --> 00:37:55,470
You don't get it.

690
00:37:56,250 --> 00:37:57,610
Chuck's a good person.

691
00:37:58,660 --> 00:38:00,820
He's g too much heart for this kind of work.

692
00:38:00,820 --> 00:38:02,020
He's no operative.

693
00:38:03,020 --> 00:38:04,520
You can't put him out in the field.

694
00:38:04,520 --> 00:38:05,660
He won't survive.

695
00:38:05,980 --> 00:38:09,650
The agency is not gonna let go of a recruit this promising.

696
00:38:09,650 --> 00:38:12,470
The amount of information he can retain?

697
00:38:12,470 --> 00:38:14,220
They're not gonna give him a choice?

698
00:38:14,740 --> 00:38:16,590
He's in no matter what.

699
00:38:21,970 --> 00:38:26,150
If he cheated on the exam, copied all the answers...

700
00:38:26,710 --> 00:38:28,920
Then it would invalidate the results, wouldn't it?

701
00:38:29,420 --> 00:38:30,290
Yes.

702
00:38:31,080 --> 00:38:31,870
Good.

703
00:38:31,870 --> 00:38:34,000
Now you're going to help me, professor.

704
00:38:38,240 --> 00:38:40,050
Bryce framed me for cheating...

705
00:38:41,260 --> 00:38:42,560
To save me.

706
00:38:44,340 --> 00:38:46,260
Why didn't he just tell me that to begin with?

707
00:38:46,260 --> 00:38:47,310
He couldn't.

708
00:38:47,770 --> 00:38:49,560
They had already recruited him.

709
00:38:51,240 --> 00:38:53,180
Well, if he had good reason for tting me kicked out, 

710
00:38:53,180 --> 00:38:55,530
maybe he had a good reason to break into  The intersect, too.

711
00:38:57,080 --> 00:39:00,160
Maybe he had a good reason for sending it to you.

712
00:39:01,450 --> 00:39:03,050
I just wish i could talk to him.

713
00:39:05,240 --> 00:39:07,570
It must have tore him up to not be able to tell me.

714
00:39:08,630 --> 00:39:10,270
No one can know about this.

715
00:39:14,200 --> 00:39:15,510
For your own safety, okay?

716
00:39:15,510 --> 00:39:16,880
Sure.

717
00:39:18,170 --> 00:39:19,780
?????

718
00:40:03,420 --> 00:40:05,190
* * hey, are you in double-e 131?

719
00:40:07,860 --> 00:40:08,770
It's pretty brutal, huh?

720
00:40:10,030 --> 00:40:10,920
Oh, yeah.

721
00:40:11,440 --> 00:40:12,330
Yeah, i...

722
00:40:12,900 --> 00:40:16,090
The only reason i signed up is 'cause i'm building my own version of, uh...

723
00:40:18,260 --> 00:40:19,850
It's kind embarrassing actually.

724
00:40:19,850 --> 00:40:20,440
What?

725
00:40:21,800 --> 00:40:24,940
You don't remember that old computer game, zork, do you?

726
00:40:25,600 --> 00:40:27,280
You are likely to be eaten by a grue.

727
00:40:28,320 --> 00:40:29,850
Holy crap, you do remember zork.

728
00:40:29,850 --> 00:40:30,680
I love that game.

729
00:40:30,680 --> 00:40:32,650
I mean i haven't thought about in a while.

730
00:40:33,080 --> 00:40:34,590
Oh, it's probably a od thing.

731
00:40:35,360 --> 00:40:36,220
I disagree.

732
00:40:36,860 --> 00:40:38,040
It's 1999.

733
00:40:38,680 --> 00:40:40,410
The next millennium belongs to the geek.

734
00:40:40,650 --> 00:40:41,650
All right.

735
00:40:42,160 --> 00:40:47,600
But still, you know, text-based computer games don't exactly play with the chicks.

736
00:40:48,760 --> 00:40:51,360
This girl jill on my floor is nuts about everquest.

737
00:40:52,100 --> 00:40:53,000
Are you serious?

738
00:40:53,000 --> 00:40:54,080
If you want, you can meet her.

739
00:40:54,080 --> 00:40:55,320
Really?
Right now?

740
00:40:55,710 --> 00:40:56,740
She's over in the quad.

741
00:40:57,250 --> 00:40:59,110
Uh, yeah, i-i would...

742
00:40:59,110 --> 00:41:00,950
I would very much like to meet her.

743
00:41:01,090 --> 00:41:01,780
Need some help?

744
00:41:01,780 --> 00:41:03,090
No.
Oh, no, i'm fine.


745
00:41:03,090 --> 00:41:04,620
I just, uh...
You know...


746
00:41:06,100 --> 00:41:08,140
College...
I'm-i'm...

747
00:41:08,140 --> 00:41:09,800
Hi, i'm chuck, by the way.

748
00:41:09,800 --> 00:41:10,320
Bryce.

749
00:41:10,360 --> 00:41:12,300
- Nice to meet you, chuck.
- Hi.Yeah, nice to meet you.

750
00:41:14,000 --> 00:41:17,000
<font color="#4096d1">-==http://subland.5286.cn==-</font>

751
00:41:17,000 --> 00:41:20,000
<font color="#4096d1">sync:虾米</font>

752
00:41:20,000 --> 00:41:25,930
<font color="#4096d1">Welcome to join 5286 team]</font>

753
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


754
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


