1
00:00:00,700 --> 00:00:03,350
In my life lately:

2
00:00:03,350 --> 00:00:05,310
i'm a little worried about our cover.

3
00:00:05,310 --> 00:00:06,990
I think it's time for us to make love.

4
00:00:07,230 --> 00:00:10,480
I own a deli in the mall,
and i often think about meats and cheeses.

5
00:00:11,160 --> 00:00:14,140
You do know we're just spending
the night together for cover,right?

6
00:00:14,140 --> 00:00:18,090
By now,i'd say i'm pretty familiar 
with the concept of faking it,so...

7
00:00:18,090 --> 00:00:20,500
You're interested in that lou girl,aren't you?

8
00:00:20,500 --> 00:00:21,810
Sarah is my...

9
00:00:23,010 --> 00:00:24,680
Girlfriend.
mm-hmm.

10
00:00:24,680 --> 00:00:30,900
You and me,our thing under the undercover thing,
is this ever going anywhere?

11
00:00:32,160 --> 00:00:32,990
No.

12
00:00:33,110 --> 00:00:34,020
We need to break up.

13
00:00:34,120 --> 00:00:36,790
You know,like,fake break up our pretend relationship.

14
00:00:56,520 --> 00:00:57,750
Hey!

15
00:00:58,550 --> 00:01:00,070
careful,you idiot!

16
00:01:02,260 --> 00:01:03,950
this thing is live!

17
00:01:18,770 --> 00:01:20,510
excuse me.Can i please get some help?

18
00:01:21,060 --> 00:01:24,860
Three,two,one,bingo.

19
00:01:25,360 --> 00:01:27,330
I'm sorry.I'm on a break.

20
00:01:30,530 --> 00:01:31,700
Eat news,pal.

21
00:01:31,700 --> 00:01:33,590
I am free this evening for a meal.

22
00:01:33,770 --> 00:01:37,060
Thinking about a little surf and turf,right?
Half meatball,half tuna sub.

23
00:01:37,060 --> 00:01:39,820
Then boom!Call of duty 4,modern warfare.

24
00:01:39,960 --> 00:01:40,750
Me and you.

25
00:01:40,920 --> 00:01:43,350
Sniper on my back watching me.Oscar delta.

26
00:01:43,350 --> 00:01:45,770
I would love to,but i-i have plans tonight.

27
00:01:46,080 --> 00:01:47,820
Don't sweat it.
Me,too,slammed.

28
00:01:47,820 --> 00:01:48,700
What are you and the lady doing?

29
00:01:48,700 --> 00:01:53,230
Uh,actually,the lady and i are no mas.It's over.

30
00:01:53,550 --> 00:01:54,800
Ah,i knew this would happen.

31
00:01:54,800 --> 00:01:55,990
Dude,i'm sorry.Damn it!

32
00:01:55,990 --> 00:01:57,680
Women can be so cruel.

33
00:01:57,680 --> 00:02:01,490
You know,as a matter of fact,i'm the one who did the breaking up.

34
00:02:01,840 --> 00:02:03,150
She just wasn't the right girl for me.

35
00:02:03,150 --> 00:02:03,880
Right girl?

36
00:02:03,880 --> 00:02:05,410
Are you out of your mind,dude?

37
00:02:05,410 --> 00:02:07,000
She is the hottest piece we are ever gonna get!

38
00:02:07,000 --> 00:02:11,300
Listen,i didn't really see a future for sarah and i,ultimately,

39
00:02:11,300 --> 00:02:13,320
and so i didn't want to waste any more time.

40
00:02:19,290 --> 00:02:20,610
Beg for her back,charles.

41
00:02:27,520 --> 00:02:28,760
Go yeah.
Yeah.

42
00:02:28,760 --> 00:02:29,780
What's going on there?

43
00:02:29,780 --> 00:02:33,020
Uh,just a little thing i call "operation devastation.

44
00:02:33,130 --> 00:02:33,930
" explain.

45
00:02:33,930 --> 00:02:34,630
Okay.

46
00:02:34,630 --> 00:02:36,420
My boy about to dump the wiener chick.

47
00:02:36,420 --> 00:02:37,030
What?

48
00:02:37,030 --> 00:02:38,460
No way.
Don't lie.You liar.

49
00:02:38,560 --> 00:02:39,240
I'm not lying.

50
00:02:39,240 --> 00:02:40,510
All right?Relax.

51
00:02:40,510 --> 00:02:41,880
She wasn't the right girl.

52
00:02:42,150 --> 00:02:43,350
What?
Yeah.

53
00:02:46,400 --> 00:02:47,280
Right girl?

54
00:02:48,140 --> 00:02:48,960
What does that mean?

55
00:02:51,180 --> 00:02:56,520
Look,chuck,i've been thinking about our break up,
and i'm not so sure it's the best idea.

56
00:02:56,740 --> 00:02:57,840
Miss me already,huh?

57
00:02:58,290 --> 00:03:00,570
Well,just,you know,for the cover,
it makes things easier.

58
00:03:00,570 --> 00:03:02,490
Well,then i guess your job's gonna be a little bit harder.

59
00:03:03,070 --> 00:03:07,530
Look,i'm sorry if you thought there was something between us.

60
00:03:07,700 --> 00:03:12,040
It's very common in these situations to 
perceive a connection that isn't there.

61
00:03:12,040 --> 00:03:13,530
Of course.I get it.

62
00:03:13,530 --> 00:03:15,420
It's the old story,you know?

63
00:03:15,420 --> 00:03:19,240
Guy gets supercomputer in his brain,
beautiful cia agent is sent to protect him,

64
00:03:19,240 --> 00:03:22,100
and then she tells him,
while under the spell of truth serum,that she's t interested.

65
00:03:22,100 --> 00:03:22,840
I get it.

66
00:03:22,960 --> 00:03:25,810
But for me,the emotional roller 
coaster is a little much,

67
00:03:25,810 --> 00:03:30,690
so i think i'd rather find something a little less common, l
ike, say, i don't know, a, uh, 

68
00:03:30,690 --> 00:03:31,850
a real relationship.

69
00:03:31,950 --> 00:03:34,480
Okay,chuck,well,if that's what you want,
then i'm gonna have to sell it.

70
00:03:44,470 --> 00:03:45,360
You okay?

71
00:03:48,310 --> 00:03:49,220
Sarah?

72
00:03:53,360 --> 00:03:54,330
Heartbreaker.

73
00:03:54,330 --> 00:03:55,110
dream ker.

74
00:03:55,110 --> 00:03:55,940
Love taker.

75
00:03:55,940 --> 00:03:57,200
Don't you mess around with chuck.

76
00:03:57,200 --> 00:03:58,170
Check this out.

77
00:04:00,710 --> 00:04:01,410
Hey,buddy.

78
00:04:01,960 --> 00:04:03,070
Heard about what happened.

79
00:04:03,070 --> 00:04:04,270
Are you...Are you okay?

80
00:04:04,760 --> 00:04:06,180
Yeah,i'm-i'm fine,lester.

81
00:04:06,180 --> 00:04:07,330
Thanks for asking.Yeah,no problem.

82
00:04:07,330 --> 00:04:09,410
Now that you're done with sarah,
you mind if i take a crack at her?

83
00:04:10,580 --> 00:04:11,960
Hey,swing away,champ.

84
00:04:11,960 --> 00:04:12,940
You bet,brother.

85
00:04:14,100 --> 00:04:15,550
Where you going?
Don't run from me,all right?

86
00:04:15,660 --> 00:04:17,380
We need to talk about our emotions and all that crap.

87
00:04:17,480 --> 00:04:18,360
I'm sorry,buddy.

88
00:04:18,360 --> 00:04:20,390
You're gonna have to weep without me,i got a date.

89
00:04:20,640 --> 00:04:21,690
What?
Get out of here.

90
00:04:21,690 --> 00:04:24,260
Already?
Good for you,hotshot.With who?

91
00:04:24,260 --> 00:04:24,890
Just someone i met.

92
00:04:24,890 --> 00:04:26,830
Makes sandwiches.Deli owner.

93
00:04:27,640 --> 00:04:29,510
Okay,hold on a second.A pro?

94
00:04:33,930 --> 00:04:35,650
Who ordered the capracola?

95
00:04:46,370 --> 00:04:48,510
I don't like the idea of this break up at all.

96
00:04:48,510 --> 00:04:49,660
What the hell happened?

97
00:04:49,660 --> 00:04:50,770
She got dumped.

98
00:04:51,100 --> 00:04:53,940
We decided that it would be best 
for chuck to date a civilian.

99
00:04:54,200 --> 00:04:57,230
It will help secure his cover 
in the event that someone ids me.

100
00:04:57,230 --> 00:04:58,480
Yeah,because she got dumped.

101
00:04:58,480 --> 00:04:59,580
Let me get this straight.

102
00:04:59,750 --> 00:05:02,360
Some woman comes in off the street 
and starts dating the asset,

103
00:05:02,360 --> 00:05:04,500
and this doesn't strike either of you as suspicious.

104
00:05:04,500 --> 00:05:05,830
It's not completely unfeasible.

105
00:05:05,830 --> 00:05:07,590
He is a reasonably charming guy.

106
00:05:07,590 --> 00:05:08,960
I've heard enough.

107
00:05:08,960 --> 00:05:12,850
I want to know everything there is to 
know about this woman before she gets too close.

108
00:05:23,930 --> 00:05:24,690
Wait,wait.

109
00:05:28,610 --> 00:05:31,870
Wow,it's,uh,it's been a while since i've done that.

110
00:05:31,870 --> 00:05:32,600
Me,too.

111
00:05:32,820 --> 00:05:34,060
I think i tweaked my neck.

112
00:05:35,100 --> 00:05:38,130
Well,it,uh,it wouldn't be an official chuck bartowski date 

113
00:05:38,130 --> 00:05:40,130
if the woman didn't leave injured in some way.

114
00:05:45,950 --> 00:05:46,830
And i don't...

115
00:05:46,950 --> 00:05:50,120
Usually do this on first dates,
but you want to come inside?

116
00:05:51,230 --> 00:05:52,110
Yeah.

117
00:05:53,410 --> 00:05:56,020
I'm about to make you a very happy man.

118
00:06:05,640 --> 00:06:09,680
Oh,my god,you're so good.

119
00:06:10,280 --> 00:06:11,400
That is so amazing.

120
00:06:11,400 --> 00:06:12,200
Wow!

121
00:06:12,200 --> 00:06:13,290
Do you really like it?

122
00:06:13,570 --> 00:06:14,380
Oh!

123
00:06:14,690 --> 00:06:15,350
Oh!

124
00:06:15,350 --> 00:06:16,120
Like it?

125
00:06:16,280 --> 00:06:17,190
Yeah!

126
00:06:17,190 --> 00:06:18,230
Yeah,i like it.

127
00:06:18,230 --> 00:06:19,680
I-i love it.

128
00:06:30,380 --> 00:06:31,620
What's wrong?You don't like it?

129
00:06:31,730 --> 00:06:32,820
It's the chopped liver,isn't it?

130
00:06:32,820 --> 00:06:33,900
Huh?What?

131
00:06:34,540 --> 00:06:35,990
No,no,i...

132
00:06:36,080 --> 00:06:37,770
No,it's amazing.It's amazing.

133
00:06:37,770 --> 00:06:38,540
You're...

134
00:06:38,740 --> 00:06:39,800
You're...Amazing.

135
00:06:39,800 --> 00:06:42,240
What is,um,what is,what is that?

136
00:06:43,330 --> 00:06:45,200
What?The invite thing?

137
00:06:45,510 --> 00:06:48,190
Oh,it's nothing.

138
00:06:48,800 --> 00:06:51,310
Some invitation for a party at,uh...

139
00:06:51,660 --> 00:06:52,960
Club ares.

140
00:06:53,740 --> 00:06:55,860
Who is stavros demetrios?

141
00:06:56,320 --> 00:06:57,310
My ex.

142
00:06:57,410 --> 00:06:58,550
He owns the place.

143
00:06:58,800 --> 00:07:00,600
Why,do you know him?
No,not really,no.

144
00:07:00,600 --> 00:07:01,270
Good.

145
00:07:01,270 --> 00:07:02,610
You don't want to.

146
00:07:02,610 --> 00:07:04,920
He thought i was dating some guy and he trashed his car.

147
00:07:04,920 --> 00:07:05,940
Threatened to kill him.

148
00:07:06,750 --> 00:07:09,610
Believe me,the last thing you want 
is that lunatic swimming around in your head.

149
00:07:44,870 --> 00:07:49,730
stavros demetrios,a handsome playboy,
owns and operates a number of la clubs.

150
00:07:49,830 --> 00:07:51,060
I don't think he's that handsome.

151
00:07:51,490 --> 00:07:54,600
He's the son of yari demetrios,the shipping magnate.

152
00:07:55,320 --> 00:07:57,120
What do you mean by playboy?

153
00:07:57,120 --> 00:07:58,370
What kind of intel do we have on that?

154
00:07:58,370 --> 00:08:03,460
What we have is information that 
a volatile package is coming to los angeles.

155
00:08:03,460 --> 00:08:07,960
The cargo itself is time-sensitive,which,
knowing the demetrios family ties to the middle east,

156
00:08:07,960 --> 00:08:09,100
could mean a weapon.

157
00:08:09,100 --> 00:08:12,590
Chuck,we need you to get as close to stavros 
as possible and see if you flash on anything 

158
00:08:12,590 --> 00:08:13,820
related to the shipment.

159
00:08:13,820 --> 00:08:16,600
What?What?You want me to get close to my girlfriend's ex?

160
00:08:16,600 --> 00:08:17,480
W do you want me to do that?

161
00:08:17,480 --> 00:08:18,920
Plus,i don't want to get her involved in all this.

162
00:08:18,920 --> 00:08:21,460
why don't you and your girlfriend hit club ares tonight?

163
00:08:21,460 --> 00:08:23,260
I hear it's supposed to be all the rage.

164
00:08:28,810 --> 00:08:29,820
How's my breath?

165
00:08:29,920 --> 00:08:30,970
Like the ocean.

166
00:08:31,590 --> 00:08:32,570
Aye,aye,captain.

167
00:08:37,300 --> 00:08:38,370
Are you kidding me?

168
00:08:38,580 --> 00:08:40,170
Everybody in this place is scoring.

169
00:08:40,170 --> 00:08:41,370
Chuck's on to his second lady.

170
00:08:41,370 --> 00:08:42,210
What do we got?

171
00:08:42,330 --> 00:08:43,300
Nothing.

172
00:08:43,300 --> 00:08:47,220
I don't know about you,but i intend to 
make the most out of the seeds i've been planting.

173
00:08:48,690 --> 00:08:49,830
What are you talking about?

174
00:08:50,190 --> 00:08:52,030
I'm gonna tag anna.

175
00:08:52,030 --> 00:08:53,000
Are you kidding?

176
00:08:53,100 --> 00:08:54,300
You make me sick.

177
00:08:54,620 --> 00:08:56,060
I'd rather get with morgan.

178
00:09:04,400 --> 00:09:06,090
Hey,larry,what can i get for you?

179
00:09:06,090 --> 00:09:06,890
Lester.

180
00:09:06,890 --> 00:09:10,550
I want to say i was sorry to 
hear about you and chuck.

181
00:09:10,960 --> 00:09:15,500
And if you needed someone to talk to,
i'm here for you.

182
00:09:16,030 --> 00:09:17,150
That's very sweet.

183
00:09:17,490 --> 00:09:18,270
Thank you.

184
00:09:18,540 --> 00:09:19,710
Want to catch a movie?

185
00:09:20,280 --> 00:09:21,080
Grab a bite?

186
00:09:22,690 --> 00:09:25,870
You're asking me out a day after i broke up with your friend?

187
00:09:28,180 --> 00:09:30,420
All's fair in love and war,sarah.

188
00:09:32,870 --> 00:09:34,130
You know what you seem like to me?

189
00:09:34,130 --> 00:09:34,900
Hmm?

190
00:09:37,110 --> 00:09:38,250
A man who...

191
00:09:38,990 --> 00:09:40,370
Knows what he wants.

192
00:09:41,110 --> 00:09:47,490
Sure,you know,We could go through 
all the motions-- coffee,movie,dinner-- 

193
00:09:47,720 --> 00:09:52,920
or we could just skip all of that nonsense 
and i could just devour you right here.

194
00:09:55,010 --> 00:09:56,500
This should hold us.

195
00:09:57,280 --> 00:09:59,650
It's,it's an interesting,uh,thought.

196
00:09:59,650 --> 00:10:02,130
Let me think about that proposition.

197
00:10:02,140 --> 00:10:02,750
Whoops.

198
00:10:02,750 --> 00:10:04,610
Your feet seemed to have slipped...

199
00:10:04,610 --> 00:10:06,510
Is that jeff,uh,calling me?

200
00:10:06,510 --> 00:10:08,620
I-i will be right there,jeff!

201
00:10:08,990 --> 00:10:09,850
I'm just gonna...

202
00:10:10,950 --> 00:10:12,410
What about that movie?

203
00:10:15,600 --> 00:10:16,480
Hey,lou.

204
00:10:21,800 --> 00:10:22,530
Hi.

205
00:10:24,280 --> 00:10:25,110
Hi.

206
00:10:25,320 --> 00:10:26,550
Nice to see you again.

207
00:10:27,860 --> 00:10:29,170
You know,he's a great guy.

208
00:10:30,130 --> 00:10:32,710
Yeah,um,i've had the same opinion so far,too.

209
00:10:32,710 --> 00:10:34,390
It's not an opinion,it's a fact.

210
00:10:36,350 --> 00:10:37,240
Don't hurt him.

211
00:10:37,920 --> 00:10:38,700
Okay.

212
00:10:38,900 --> 00:10:40,220
Wasn't planning on it.

213
00:10:41,290 --> 00:10:42,600
Thanks for the heads up,though.

214
00:10:51,320 --> 00:10:52,090
Excuse me.

215
00:10:53,160 --> 00:10:54,740
Hi.
Do you know where i can find chuck?

216
00:10:55,350 --> 00:10:57,280
Ah,the sandwich maker.

217
00:10:57,280 --> 00:10:59,720
I have heard so much about you.

218
00:11:00,130 --> 00:11:00,880
Thank you.

219
00:11:01,100 --> 00:11:03,060
And i must be...

220
00:11:03,570 --> 00:11:05,440
A guy who works at the buy more?
Close.

221
00:11:05,440 --> 00:11:06,620
Morgan grimes.

222
00:11:06,620 --> 00:11:08,930
Chuck's best friend,soul mate.

223
00:11:09,030 --> 00:11:10,150
He hasn't mentioned me.

224
00:11:10,380 --> 00:11:11,050
Sorry.

225
00:11:11,050 --> 00:11:13,480
Probably means he doesn't think 
you're gonna be sticking around for a while.

226
00:11:14,410 --> 00:11:15,150
Hey.

227
00:11:15,250 --> 00:11:16,050
There you are.

228
00:11:16,050 --> 00:11:17,140
I'm glad you two finally met.

229
00:11:17,140 --> 00:11:17,970
Yeah.

230
00:11:17,970 --> 00:11:18,670
Hmm.

231
00:11:18,670 --> 00:11:19,980
I brought you some lunch.

232
00:11:19,980 --> 00:11:21,160
Oh,thank you.

233
00:11:22,160 --> 00:11:24,790
Mmm,i smell salami,black olives tapenade.

234
00:11:24,790 --> 00:11:28,180
Okay,this,this might actually have a shot at working out.

235
00:11:30,550 --> 00:11:32,800
Well,morgan approval,that's very big.

236
00:11:32,800 --> 00:11:35,350
I seem to be getting that from all angles today.

237
00:11:35,350 --> 00:11:36,990
Just had a moment with your ex.

238
00:11:36,990 --> 00:11:37,770
Did ya?

239
00:11:38,100 --> 00:11:42,470
Yeah,she's,uh,she can be a little overprotective sometimes.

240
00:11:42,470 --> 00:11:50,000
But speaking of exes,um,i was thinking maybe,
uh,we could go to that party thing at ares tonight.

241
00:11:50,100 --> 00:11:50,750
No.You know what?

242
00:11:50,750 --> 00:11:52,480
Trust me,bad plan.

243
00:11:52,480 --> 00:11:56,980
Look,sooner or later he's gonna 
find out about me,and i'd rather just...

244
00:11:56,980 --> 00:11:58,040
Make the peace now.

245
00:11:59,020 --> 00:12:00,880
Charming,handsome and brave.

246
00:12:00,880 --> 00:12:02,710
You know,that's a combination i'm not used to.

247
00:12:02,710 --> 00:12:05,560
Yeah,it's a little...

248
00:12:05,690 --> 00:12:07,060
Little new for me,too.

249
00:12:10,520 --> 00:12:13,080
We're only on our second official date,and already i'm lying to her.

250
00:12:13,080 --> 00:12:13,730
Relax.

251
00:12:13,730 --> 00:12:14,920
It's dating in la.

252
00:12:14,920 --> 00:12:15,870
Everyone lies.

253
00:12:16,470 --> 00:12:18,280
We're going to be tapped into the club's surveillance feed.

254
00:12:18,280 --> 00:12:19,140
All we need is the audio.

255
00:12:19,140 --> 00:12:21,850
This has an rk-7 mini mic that works up to 20 feet.

256
00:12:21,850 --> 00:12:24,770
I want you to keep it as close to stavros as possible.

257
00:12:25,990 --> 00:12:27,660
Are you kidding?
Are you kidding me with this?

258
00:12:28,210 --> 00:12:29,020
I can't wear this.

259
00:12:29,020 --> 00:12:29,970
This looks ridiculous.

260
00:12:29,970 --> 00:12:32,070
The alternative is we join you on your date.

261
00:12:32,910 --> 00:12:33,700
Fine.

262
00:12:37,510 --> 00:12:39,550
Ear wig.
It never stops with you people,does it?

263
00:12:43,570 --> 00:12:44,830
Aren't you forgetting something,romeo?

264
00:12:46,270 --> 00:12:47,590
Let me guess.

265
00:12:47,590 --> 00:12:49,990
This is equipped with some kind of microscopic,

266
00:12:49,990 --> 00:12:54,560
infrared tracking device that determines 
her mother's communist affiliations?

267
00:12:54,560 --> 00:12:55,430
No,idiot.

268
00:12:55,430 --> 00:12:56,580
It's so you can get laid.

269
00:13:15,700 --> 00:13:16,600
usually...I'm sorry.

270
00:13:16,600 --> 00:13:18,110
I usually get more respect at the door.

271
00:13:18,110 --> 00:13:19,590
You know,i-i come here a lot.

272
00:13:19,960 --> 00:13:21,900
Normally,it's here on monday,
on monday nights,and then...

273
00:13:22,020 --> 00:13:23,970
And then,uh,tuesdays at hyde.

274
00:13:23,970 --> 00:13:24,750
I'm on the circuit.

275
00:13:24,750 --> 00:13:26,060
You know,i do my thing.

276
00:13:26,700 --> 00:13:28,600
I can't hear a word that you're saying!

277
00:13:29,200 --> 00:13:30,010
What was that?

278
00:13:30,010 --> 00:13:31,060
i love this song.

279
00:13:31,060 --> 00:13:32,010
Do you want to dance?

280
00:13:32,480 --> 00:13:33,490
No.I normally,uh...

281
00:13:33,490 --> 00:13:37,000
I normally require some social 
lubricant before entering a dance floor.

282
00:13:37,000 --> 00:13:38,350
Hello,sweetheart.

283
00:13:39,150 --> 00:13:40,050
stavros.

284
00:13:40,550 --> 00:13:41,760
Uh,this is chuck.

285
00:13:41,980 --> 00:13:43,100
Chuck,stavros.

286
00:13:43,100 --> 00:13:43,810
Hi.

287
00:13:44,090 --> 00:13:44,820
Cool pin.

288
00:13:45,480 --> 00:13:47,670
I'd have worn mine,but i lost it in the '80s.

289
00:13:49,040 --> 00:13:50,170
I kept mine.

290
00:13:50,170 --> 00:13:51,130
Nice to see you.

291
00:13:51,820 --> 00:13:52,700
Whoa.Whoa.

292
00:13:52,700 --> 00:13:53,540
Where you going?

293
00:13:53,640 --> 00:13:55,300
At least let me buy your new friend a drink.

294
00:13:55,430 --> 00:13:56,810
No,thanks.Um...

295
00:13:57,770 --> 00:13:58,970
have the drink,chuck.

296
00:13:59,160 --> 00:14:00,240
Yeah,maybe...Maybe justne.

297
00:14:00,240 --> 00:14:03,070
Look,vip on me.

298
00:14:09,310 --> 00:14:11,130
Way to own the noobs,morgan!

299
00:14:11,840 --> 00:14:13,190
Use your deep impact perk.

300
00:14:13,190 --> 00:14:14,240
Don't-don't backseat perk me.

301
00:14:14,240 --> 00:14:15,680
I-i know when to use my perks.

302
00:14:16,390 --> 00:14:20,440
I have to tell you,morgan,i think you're 
one of the best call of duty 4 players in the store.

303
00:14:22,550 --> 00:14:23,250
Really?

304
00:14:27,120 --> 00:14:29,360
You know,i-i heard what you said to jeff.

305
00:14:29,780 --> 00:14:33,250
I think that you should not fight it anymore.

306
00:14:33,250 --> 00:14:36,510
You know,just sort of,um,
succumb to your desire,you know,just...

307
00:14:39,320 --> 00:14:40,790
Morgan,what are you doing?

308
00:14:41,520 --> 00:14:42,660
I thought you wanted me!

309
00:14:42,660 --> 00:14:44,280
Because i said i efer you to jeff?

310
00:14:44,500 --> 00:14:45,820
I'd take lester over jeff.

311
00:14:45,820 --> 00:14:47,560
Doesn't mean i'm into that loser.

312
00:14:48,360 --> 00:14:50,380
But you'd take me over lester,right?

313
00:14:51,700 --> 00:14:53,680
Okay,listen,can you keep this between me and you,please?

314
00:14:53,790 --> 00:14:55,280
You know,don't-don't tell anybody!

315
00:15:03,910 --> 00:15:06,040
That's aged ten years in oak.

316
00:15:09,290 --> 00:15:10,920
**

317
00:15:11,400 --> 00:15:12,910
Can yotaste it,jack?

318
00:15:14,480 --> 00:15:17,070
Chuck,and,uh,yes,i think i did...

319
00:15:17,070 --> 00:15:21,500
I think i did taste it,although,that-that also could have been a piece ofy liver.

320
00:15:22,380 --> 00:15:23,470
I love this guy!

321
00:15:23,650 --> 00:15:24,740
He's a charmer.

322
00:15:26,320 --> 00:15:27,650
Hey,you.

323
00:15:27,750 --> 00:15:28,510
Hey.
Hi.

324
00:15:28,510 --> 00:15:29,660
Can i get you something,anything?

325
00:15:29,660 --> 00:15:30,950
Can i get some more wine?

326
00:15:31,080 --> 00:15:32,950
Oh,don't do that,jack.

327
00:15:32,950 --> 00:15:34,410
You don't want to get on her bad side.

328
00:15:34,410 --> 00:15:35,660
Fiery italian.

329
00:15:35,840 --> 00:15:37,240
Stavros...
What?

330
00:15:37,240 --> 00:15:40,500
You think i'm going to tell him about the trip to mykonos where you threw a lamp at my head?

331
00:15:41,280 --> 00:15:42,420
Still have the scar.

332
00:15:44,340 --> 00:15:46,210
I thought...I thought you said she threw it at your head.

333
00:15:46,210 --> 00:15:47,020
She did.

334
00:15:47,290 --> 00:15:48,910
The scar is from the make-up sex.

335
00:15:49,320 --> 00:15:50,410
She's a tiger.

336
00:15:51,120 --> 00:15:52,270
get on with it,chuck!

337
00:15:52,270 --> 00:15:56,230
Um,so stavros,uh,you're in the,uh...

338
00:15:56,230 --> 00:15:57,240
You're in the club game?

339
00:15:58,020 --> 00:15:59,190
Don't worry about it.

340
00:16:00,270 --> 00:16:01,180
You seem nerus.

341
00:16:01,180 --> 00:16:02,080
I'm...
Relax.

342
00:16:02,080 --> 00:16:02,980
I'm not.

343
00:16:04,110 --> 00:16:06,270
Ooh,you got a small neck,huh?

344
00:16:06,380 --> 00:16:07,230
Thank you very much.

345
00:16:07,230 --> 00:16:08,230
Like a chicken.

346
00:16:09,970 --> 00:16:11,240
He does have a small neck.

347
00:16:12,340 --> 00:16:13,540
Maybe i should go in.

348
00:16:15,250 --> 00:16:16,540
Same bit with you,huh?

349
00:16:17,280 --> 00:16:18,500
What's that supposed to mean?

350
00:16:18,500 --> 00:16:19,690
You need me to spell it out?

351
00:16:20,440 --> 00:16:21,180
Fine.

352
00:16:21,460 --> 00:16:23,220
You fall for the guys you work with.

353
00:16:23,220 --> 00:16:25,100
First bryce,now our boy chuck.

354
00:16:25,230 --> 00:16:28,420
Bryce was a mistake,and i haven't fallen for chuck.

355
00:16:28,740 --> 00:16:29,770
Yeah,whatever you say.

356
00:16:30,250 --> 00:16:32,750
And just so we're clear,sister,not interested.

357
00:16:33,960 --> 00:16:36,600
have you ever snapped a chicken's neck,chuck?

358
00:16:36,700 --> 00:16:37,830
Can't say that i have.

359
00:16:38,790 --> 00:16:40,350
It's much easier than you would think.

360
00:16:40,350 --> 00:16:41,520
That's it.I'm going in.

361
00:16:42,110 --> 00:16:43,000
Hey,no.

362
00:16:43,380 --> 00:16:44,100
Hey!

363
00:16:44,250 --> 00:16:45,020
Walker!

364
00:16:48,630 --> 00:16:49,400
chuck?

365
00:16:51,090 --> 00:16:52,550
Isn't that your ex-girlfriend?

366
00:16:56,810 --> 00:16:57,520
Yes,it is.

367
00:16:57,520 --> 00:16:58,390
Yes.

368
00:16:58,920 --> 00:16:59,680
Sorry.

369
00:16:59,680 --> 00:17:01,980
Uh,she's having a hard time letting go.

370
00:17:02,770 --> 00:17:04,260
It's happened to me before.

371
00:17:04,260 --> 00:17:04,950
A lot,actually.

372
00:17:04,950 --> 00:17:06,490
I don't...You know,i better go talk to her.

373
00:17:06,490 --> 00:17:08,030
I'll be right back.I'm so sorry.

374
00:17:08,910 --> 00:17:10,040
Hey,i'm sorry.I'm sorry.

375
00:17:10,040 --> 00:17:10,850
Excuse me.Excuse me.

376
00:17:10,850 --> 00:17:12,350
Hey,what are you doing here?

377
00:17:12,350 --> 00:17:14,240
I wanted to make sure you're okay.

378
00:17:14,470 --> 00:17:15,470
i'm on a...

379
00:17:15,470 --> 00:17:17,410
I'm on a date,okay?

380
00:17:17,410 --> 00:17:19,240
Just,you're ruining it right now!

381
00:17:21,100 --> 00:17:22,710
I'm fine!I'm fine!

382
00:17:22,710 --> 00:17:23,910
Just...Just go!

383
00:17:23,910 --> 00:17:24,990
Okay,fine.

384
00:17:25,880 --> 00:17:27,590
But your girlfriend is leaving.

385
00:17:29,690 --> 00:17:30,730
Excuse me.I'm sorry.

386
00:17:30,730 --> 00:17:31,970
Excuse me.Excuse me.Excuse me.

387
00:17:31,970 --> 00:17:33,100
Hey,where are you going?

388
00:17:33,100 --> 00:17:36,470
You've spent the entire night either with my ex or yours.

389
00:17:36,470 --> 00:17:37,770
This date is over,okay?

390
00:17:37,770 --> 00:17:38,580
I'm out of here.

391
00:17:38,860 --> 00:17:39,920
Lou,wait.Excuse me.

392
00:17:39,920 --> 00:17:40,660
No,no.

393
00:17:41,030 --> 00:17:41,800
Lou?

394
00:17:41,800 --> 00:17:43,430
No,don't go!Don't go!Don't go!

395
00:17:54,180 --> 00:17:54,930
Excuse me...

396
00:17:56,050 --> 00:17:59,100
Casey?Casey,stavros' father yari just walked in!
I got it.

397
00:17:59,100 --> 00:18:00,040
He's heading towards his son.

398
00:18:00,040 --> 00:18:00,780
Get the mic closer.

399
00:18:00,780 --> 00:18:01,880
I need to hear what they're saying.

400
00:18:06,890 --> 00:18:08,420
Chuck,get over there!Now!

401
00:18:12,540 --> 00:18:14,210
Damn it,chuck,what are you waiting for?

402
00:18:15,070 --> 00:18:16,500
Okay.Excuse me.

403
00:18:16,610 --> 00:18:17,670
I beg your pardon.
I'm so sorry.I'm so sorry.

404
00:18:17,670 --> 00:18:18,970
Excuse me,i have to get...

405
00:18:19,220 --> 00:18:22,100
I was just...I literally was just in there,like,two seconds ago.

406
00:18:24,820 --> 00:18:25,660
Okay,chuck,this is it!

407
00:18:25,660 --> 00:18:26,570
Get the mic closer.

408
00:18:31,550 --> 00:18:32,150
Okay,you know what?

409
00:18:32,150 --> 00:18:34,060
I probably...Was over there,so i'm going to...

410
00:18:40,150 --> 00:18:41,030
Thank you.

411
00:18:41,450 --> 00:18:45,260
4:00 tomorrow afternoon,san pedro.

412
00:18:45,470 --> 00:18:48,670
The package is time sensitive,so,if it expires,we're all dead.

413
00:18:50,080 --> 00:18:50,890
Got you.

414
00:18:53,520 --> 00:18:54,870
Excuse me.Excuse me.Excuse me.

415
00:18:55,050 --> 00:18:55,810
Lou,wait!

416
00:18:55,810 --> 00:18:57,600
Wait,wait,wait,wait,wait,wait,wait!

417
00:18:57,740 --> 00:18:59,020
Great,great.

418
00:19:02,880 --> 00:19:03,880
Nice work,chuck.

419
00:19:04,100 --> 00:19:05,940
We know when and where the package is coming.

420
00:19:06,200 --> 00:19:07,480
Mission accomplished.

421
00:19:08,670 --> 00:19:09,600
How was the date?

422
00:19:10,820 --> 00:19:14,010
Is it me,or does our government never want me to have sex again?

423
00:19:17,010 --> 00:19:17,810
Second message.

424
00:19:17,810 --> 00:19:19,090
Look,i totally screwed up,okay?

425
00:19:19,090 --> 00:19:25,040
I'm more than comfortable blaming it on the alcohol,or global warming or my obscure allergy to neon...

426
00:19:25,040 --> 00:19:27,340
But,hey,hopefully,i'll-i'll talk to you soon.

427
00:19:27,340 --> 00:19:28,130
Okay.Thanks.

428
00:19:28,130 --> 00:19:28,870
Buh-bye.

429
00:19:29,620 --> 00:19:31,390
Damn it.You made me give her a buh-bye.

430
00:19:31,490 --> 00:19:32,750
She won't talk to you?

431
00:19:32,850 --> 00:19:34,540
You want us to cut her power,smoke her out?

432
00:19:34,540 --> 00:19:35,980
Wow.That's very romantic.

433
00:19:35,980 --> 00:19:38,630
Why don't you just club her over the head and drag her out by her foot?

434
00:19:38,910 --> 00:19:41,130
Look,i'll handle this one without the nsa,thank you.

435
00:19:41,300 --> 00:19:42,350
You did a good job last night.

436
00:19:42,350 --> 00:19:44,760
We're going down to the docks a few hours to intercept the package.

437
00:19:44,760 --> 00:19:45,580
You need me to go?

438
00:19:46,150 --> 00:19:48,880
Yeah,if the crap hits the fan,we could use you,chicken neck.

439
00:19:50,040 --> 00:19:51,490
chuck!Chuck!

440
00:19:51,650 --> 00:19:52,400
What did you hear about last night?

441
00:19:52,400 --> 00:19:53,340
And don't hold back.

442
00:19:53,540 --> 00:19:54,610
I don't know what you're talking about.

443
00:19:54,930 --> 00:19:57,630
I made a move on anna, and she shot me down, so, i...

444
00:19:57,630 --> 00:19:59,940
What?What?Anna?Anna?Really?
I didn't know you liked anna.

445
00:19:59,940 --> 00:20:01,150
What's like got to do with it?

446
00:20:01,150 --> 00:20:02,940
I figured you have a girl, i should have a girl, too.

447
00:20:02,940 --> 00:20:08,930
Uh, occasionally, on planet earth, men will consider their feelings for a woman before jumping atop them.

448
00:20:08,930 --> 00:20:13,430
You know, she's kind of cute in a freaky, little tigerish kind of way, you know?

449
00:20:14,470 --> 00:20:15,710
But that's not my problem, dude.

450
00:20:15,710 --> 00:20:16,850
Okay, what if she tells everyone?

451
00:20:16,850 --> 00:20:18,560
I was just starting to get some street cred around here.

452
00:20:18,560 --> 00:20:19,870
Anna is very cool.

453
00:20:19,870 --> 00:20:22,680
I'm sure that your rep is very secure, ese.

454
00:20:26,100 --> 00:20:27,200
No.They're talking about me.

455
00:20:27,200 --> 00:20:29,320
You see this?
I'm-i'm ruined, dude.

456
00:20:29,670 --> 00:20:31,520
Okay, you got me!

457
00:20:33,710 --> 00:20:35,060
Fun time at my expense.

458
00:20:35,060 --> 00:20:36,830
Look, i tried to kiss anna.

459
00:20:36,830 --> 00:20:38,390
She dissed me, all right?

460
00:20:40,310 --> 00:20:41,910
I feel like a fool.

461
00:20:42,590 --> 00:20:43,490
Are you happy now?

462
00:20:44,600 --> 00:20:49,960
Morgan, we were laughing about chuck getting dumped by the deli girl after he dumped the wiener girl.

463
00:20:52,020 --> 00:20:52,930
Kind of poetic?

464
00:20:54,060 --> 00:20:55,460
You tried to kiss anna?

465
00:20:56,040 --> 00:20:56,560
Why?

466
00:20:56,560 --> 00:20:57,730
Dude, how could you?

467
00:20:57,730 --> 00:20:58,930
I got dibs on anna.

468
00:20:58,930 --> 00:21:01,100
I'm right here, you disgusting pig!

469
00:21:05,570 --> 00:21:09,410
I realize that this is dangerously close to bordering on stalker status, 

470
00:21:09,410 --> 00:21:12,280
but, uh, look, i-i don't really care about that.

471
00:21:12,630 --> 00:21:14,530
Look, maybe-maybe you're...
Maybe you're calling me right now.

472
00:21:14,530 --> 00:21:17,010
I don't know.
And just give you the chance to...

473
00:21:18,000 --> 00:21:20,100
Okay, okay.Um, so, uh, you know, if you...

474
00:21:20,100 --> 00:21:23,500
If you get a sec, you can...You can call me back.Okay.Buh-bye.

475
00:21:25,200 --> 00:21:26,090
Won't call you back?

476
00:21:26,920 --> 00:21:29,320
I, uh...
Yeah, i think her voice-mail is broken.

477
00:21:29,970 --> 00:21:31,410
It's very, very common.

478
00:21:32,100 --> 00:21:33,880
I wanted to apologize for last night.

479
00:21:33,880 --> 00:21:37,780
I suppose i jumped the gun a little, and i didn't mean to interfere with your date.

480
00:21:37,780 --> 00:21:42,200
Yeah, not sure it qualifies as a date when you're bugged with cia mrophones 

481
00:21:42,200 --> 00:21:45,210
and infiltrating an arms importer, but, hey, i'm new at this.

482
00:21:45,730 --> 00:21:48,660
Well, it's hard to have a real relationship in this line of work.

483
00:21:49,330 --> 00:21:51,890
Apparently, it's hard to have a fake one, as well.

484
00:21:56,210 --> 00:22:00,850
Well, if it's any conciliation, i never felt like our time together was work.

485
00:22:03,460 --> 00:22:06,250
Oh, uh, gerber daises.
Lou's favorite.

486
00:22:06,460 --> 00:22:07,370
How do you know that?

487
00:22:07,790 --> 00:22:08,310
Cia.

488
00:22:08,310 --> 00:22:11,780
I had them check flower deliveries to her addresses from the last five years.

489
00:22:13,320 --> 00:22:13,940
Good tip.

490
00:22:23,670 --> 00:22:25,660
Wait, wait.Lou, can i talk to 
you just one second?One second?

491
00:22:26,170 --> 00:22:26,870
I'm busy.

492
00:22:27,350 --> 00:22:28,830
Uh, who had the parma prosciutto?

493
00:22:29,640 --> 00:22:30,330
There you go.

494
00:22:31,540 --> 00:22:32,480
Twenty-seven!

495
00:22:34,070 --> 00:22:36,030
You want to talk, get a number like everybody else.

496
00:22:36,580 --> 00:22:37,420
Man: who's got 28?

497
00:22:39,200 --> 00:22:41,270
28
28

498
00:22:42,230 --> 00:22:45,420
Who's holding 29?
29!Twenty-nine!

499
00:22:57,660 --> 00:22:59,090
Federal agent!
Down on the ground!

500
00:22:59,090 --> 00:22:59,720
Don't move!

501
00:23:01,960 --> 00:23:03,120
Get the bomb squad in here!

502
00:23:03,770 --> 00:23:04,610
Let's go!

503
00:23:15,760 --> 00:23:20,460
- 44!Who's holding 44?44?
- 44!I have 44.Yes, yes, yes, yes!

504
00:23:20,460 --> 00:23:22,000
Please, i'd like to speak to lou, please.

505
00:23:24,070 --> 00:23:26,390
Well, buddy, it looks like you're gonna have to te another number.

506
00:23:26,950 --> 00:23:28,800
45, who's got 45?

507
00:23:47,880 --> 00:23:48,970
You sure thas a good idea?

508
00:23:49,900 --> 00:23:50,690
Yeah, why not?

509
00:23:51,310 --> 00:23:52,700
If it's a bomb in there, we're all gonna go.

510
00:23:53,150 --> 00:23:54,740
Might as well enjoy a last smoke.

511
00:24:01,000 --> 00:24:01,840
It's all clear!

512
00:24:02,600 --> 00:24:04,630
Agent casey, you better take a look at this.

513
00:24:08,500 --> 00:24:09,150
What the hell...

514
00:24:10,130 --> 00:24:11,510
Sarah: someone knew we were coming.

515
00:24:17,900 --> 00:24:20,500
96?
Anybody got 96?

516
00:24:25,800 --> 00:24:28,900
I just wanted to apologize about last night and explain...

517
00:24:28,900 --> 00:24:30,690
I'm working.Do you want a sandwich?

518
00:24:32,630 --> 00:24:36,550
- Yeah.I'll take a sandwich.x
- Great.What'll you have?

519
00:24:36,570 --> 00:24:37,490
You guys carry wheat bread?

520
00:24:37,490 --> 00:24:37,990
We do.

521
00:24:37,990 --> 00:24:39,310
Why don't you grab a couple slices of that?

522
00:24:43,720 --> 00:24:45,500
Now, toss 'em and grab the seedless rye.

523
00:24:46,030 --> 00:24:47,920
And while you're at it, grab some pastrami.

524
00:24:47,920 --> 00:24:49,740
End cut, none of that lean crap.

525
00:24:49,740 --> 00:24:52,330
A man with high cholesterol.Se.

526
00:24:52,330 --> 00:24:53,010
Is that it?

527
00:24:53,010 --> 00:24:54,510
Oh, i'm just getting warmed up.

528
00:24:54,510 --> 00:24:55,240
Cole slaw.

529
00:24:55,240 --> 00:24:55,830
On the side?

530
00:24:55,830 --> 00:24:57,090
On the top, lather it on.

531
00:24:57,090 --> 00:24:57,890
Swiss?

532
00:25:00,070 --> 00:25:00,820
Muenster.

533
00:25:00,820 --> 00:25:01,550
Is that it?

534
00:25:01,550 --> 00:25:06,800
Well, after you shut itdown and gril this is a hot sandwich, sweetheart.
In the reuben family.

535
00:25:13,410 --> 00:25:14,390
These are for you.

536
00:25:15,460 --> 00:25:17,010
They were alive at one point.

537
00:25:19,350 --> 00:25:21,200
Gerber daisies, they're my favorite.

538
00:25:21,200 --> 00:25:23,240
I'm really sorry if i acted like a jerk last night.

539
00:25:23,240 --> 00:25:24,330
I was really nervous...

540
00:25:24,330 --> 00:25:25,220
Shut up, chuck.

541
00:25:29,340 --> 00:25:30,660
He had me at "pastrami.

542
00:25:40,460 --> 00:25:41,560
" who are these people?

543
00:25:41,560 --> 00:25:43,410
How did they find out about the shipment?

544
00:25:43,410 --> 00:25:44,430
I have no idea.

545
00:25:46,120 --> 00:25:48,940
If anything goes wrong with this shipment, we are dead.

546
00:25:48,940 --> 00:25:50,170
Katalabaini, stavros?

547
00:25:50,170 --> 00:25:51,230
These people will kill us.

548
00:25:51,230 --> 00:25:53,310
What the hell is coming in that's so important, eh?

549
00:25:53,310 --> 00:25:55,570
I don't know and i don't want to know.

550
00:25:55,570 --> 00:25:59,010
Our job is to make the delivery, not ask questions.

551
00:25:59,990 --> 00:26:04,310
Now, you find out who this belongs to and bring him to me.

552
00:26:16,480 --> 00:26:17,230
Morning, handsome.

553
00:26:18,420 --> 00:26:19,480
Nice work last night.

554
00:26:19,910 --> 00:26:20,510
Casey: hey, lover boy.

555
00:26:21,110 --> 00:26:22,940
Hasn't that mirror suffered enough already?

556
00:26:23,170 --> 00:26:24,400
I am in the bathroom.

557
00:26:24,750 --> 00:26:26,920
Okay, is there nothing sacred to you people?

558
00:26:26,920 --> 00:26:28,360
Just the right to bear arms.

559
00:26:31,230 --> 00:26:32,300
You two look terrible.

560
00:26:33,570 --> 00:26:35,510
Well, we were up all night explaining to our bosses 

561
00:26:35,510 --> 00:26:39,500
why we raided a cargo freighter filled with nothing but air and a surveillance camera.

562
00:26:40,070 --> 00:26:42,120
The tip you gave us was compromised.

563
00:26:42,120 --> 00:26:43,190
Someone set us up.

564
00:26:43,190 --> 00:26:44,610
I think it was your sandwich maker.

565
00:26:46,900 --> 00:26:49,070
Are you kidding me, lou?
Please.Come on.

566
00:26:49,070 --> 00:26:52,480
You don't want me to date for "national security" reasons, fine, just say that.

567
00:26:52,480 --> 00:26:54,030
But i think this is a little pathetic.

568
00:26:54,030 --> 00:26:55,650
And quite frankly, beneath you, sarah.

569
00:26:59,000 --> 00:27:01,590
This was taken at the docks after your date.

570
00:27:05,640 --> 00:27:08,340
I'm sure she has a perfectly reasonable explanation for this.

571
00:27:08,340 --> 00:27:08,860
Good.

572
00:27:08,860 --> 00:27:10,220
Can't wait to hear it.

573
00:27:11,820 --> 00:27:12,550
Keep it.

574
00:27:12,780 --> 00:27:14,060
We have plenty more.

575
00:27:19,360 --> 00:27:22,040
Everyone in the mall's talking about you trying to hook up with anna.

576
00:27:22,040 --> 00:27:25,190
Dude, the guys at the sbarro even named a pizza after you.

577
00:27:25,190 --> 00:27:28,970
No sauce, no toppings, nothing but pure cheese.
It's called "the loser.

578
00:27:28,970 --> 00:27:30,170
" hmm, let's grab a slice.

579
00:27:32,590 --> 00:27:33,290
I'm ruined.

580
00:27:40,850 --> 00:27:43,920
Casey: okay, chuck, our intel says lou should be meeting stavros behind the club.

581
00:27:44,540 --> 00:27:45,990
Chuck: you guys are being paranoid.

582
00:27:45,990 --> 00:27:47,470
There's no way lou's showing up here.

583
00:27:47,470 --> 00:27:48,500
Now you're mic'ed.

584
00:27:50,170 --> 00:27:52,840
Great.
Great, thanks a lot.

585
00:27:53,180 --> 00:27:56,460
And what will the sandwich police be doing on this stakeout?

586
00:27:58,710 --> 00:28:00,200
Here we go.
We got company.xx

587
00:28:11,520 --> 00:28:12,270
Casey: believe us now?

588
00:28:14,640 --> 00:28:15,230
No.

589
00:28:15,230 --> 00:28:17,100
As a matter of fact, i don't.

590
00:28:17,100 --> 00:28:17,910
Hey, chuck, wait...

591
00:28:18,370 --> 00:28:19,570
No, wait.No, damn it.
I'm going after him.x

592
00:28:19,570 --> 00:28:20,600
They have us on tape.

593
00:28:21,340 --> 00:28:23,720
They recognize either of us, we could blow the whole operation.

594
00:28:28,350 --> 00:28:29,430
Thank you, stavros.

595
00:28:29,430 --> 00:28:30,530
Oh, my pleasure.

596
00:28:31,960 --> 00:28:33,890
So your friend, chuck, where'd you meet him?

597
00:28:33,890 --> 00:28:36,560
He works at the buy more, across from the deli.

598
00:28:36,560 --> 00:28:37,810
I took my phone in to get fixed.

599
00:28:38,520 --> 00:28:39,020
Why?

600
00:28:40,540 --> 00:28:41,910
Just seems like a great guy.

601
00:28:42,600 --> 00:28:43,740
I'll be back with the rest.

602
00:28:48,300 --> 00:28:49,080
Well, hello, lou.

603
00:28:49,080 --> 00:28:50,670
If that is in fact your real name.

604
00:28:50,670 --> 00:28:52,250
Chuck, what are you doing here?

605
00:28:52,250 --> 00:28:54,160
I think the question is what are you doing here?

606
00:28:54,160 --> 00:28:55,250
None of your business.

607
00:28:55,250 --> 00:28:56,540
Were you following me?

608
00:28:57,020 --> 00:28:58,280
Have you been spying on me?

609
00:28:58,280 --> 00:29:00,660
Hold on a second, don't try and turn this around on me.

610
00:29:00,660 --> 00:29:02,660
Okay, i'm not the one-- i'm not the one smuggling...

611
00:29:02,660 --> 00:29:07,270
You know, what is this?What is this?
Illegal, illegal things with my boyfriend.

612
00:29:13,870 --> 00:29:15,340
Is that-- what is, what is that?

613
00:29:15,340 --> 00:29:17,160
Portuguese cured sopresseto?

614
00:29:17,380 --> 00:29:19,200
What'd you think was going to be in there?

615
00:29:20,670 --> 00:29:23,330
I, uh, i didn't quite know.

616
00:29:23,330 --> 00:29:25,430
I just saw you with stavros and i suspected the worst.

617
00:29:25,430 --> 00:29:27,240
Right, well, congratulations, chuck.

618
00:29:27,240 --> 00:29:30,430
Your suspicions have been confirmed.
I'm a smuggler.

619
00:29:31,800 --> 00:29:32,700
You should probably keep that down.

620
00:29:32,700 --> 00:29:33,570
Someone'll hear you, okay?

621
00:29:33,570 --> 00:29:34,850
I know it's illegal!

622
00:29:34,850 --> 00:29:36,750
There's no additives or preservatives in it.

623
00:29:36,750 --> 00:29:39,820
It takes ten days to clear customs and by then it's gone bad.

624
00:29:39,820 --> 00:29:43,930
Okay, don't get me started on the...
????

625
00:29:43,930 --> 00:29:45,380
I can't hear anything.
I'm going in.

626
00:29:45,380 --> 00:29:46,350
No, no, no, give him a minute.

627
00:29:46,350 --> 00:29:47,260
You can't go in every time he breaks a nail.

628
00:29:47,260 --> 00:29:48,850
Just cover the front.

629
00:29:53,190 --> 00:29:55,380
I'm sorry, lou.
I made a really big mistake.

630
00:29:55,380 --> 00:29:56,400
Looks like i did, too.

631
00:30:12,830 --> 00:30:13,430
Hey, what happened?

632
00:30:13,800 --> 00:30:14,470
I blew it...

633
00:30:15,420 --> 00:30:16,010
Again.

634
00:30:16,010 --> 00:30:17,170
Yes, you did, chuck.

635
00:30:18,140 --> 00:30:19,940
You most definitely blew it.

636
00:30:29,360 --> 00:30:30,170
Why did you come in?

637
00:30:30,170 --> 00:30:32,340
I had the situation entirely under control.

638
00:30:32,340 --> 00:30:33,520
Yeah, i can see that.

639
00:30:38,990 --> 00:30:39,870
Damn it.

640
00:30:46,820 --> 00:30:48,740
I assume you have a plan to get us out of this mess.

641
00:30:48,740 --> 00:30:51,360
Right now casey's tracking your gps device in your watch.

642
00:30:51,360 --> 00:30:52,980
A swat team will be here any minute.

643
00:30:54,370 --> 00:30:56,130
Yeah, about the watch...

644
00:31:01,520 --> 00:31:02,240
Idiot.

645
00:31:02,240 --> 00:31:04,830
Lou was incriminating herself 
and i didn't want her getting into trouble.

646
00:31:04,830 --> 00:31:06,240
Always the romantic, huh, chuck?

647
00:31:06,240 --> 00:31:06,830
Jealous?

648
00:31:06,830 --> 00:31:07,670
It was foolish.

649
00:31:07,670 --> 00:31:11,120
Do you really think the cia is interested in a deli meat smuggler?

650
00:31:11,120 --> 00:31:13,710
Well, excuse me if i'm not mr.Perfect spy.

651
00:31:13,710 --> 00:31:16,080
We can't all be bryce larkin, now can we?

652
00:31:16,080 --> 00:31:17,000
Who's jealous now?

653
00:31:17,000 --> 00:31:18,750
- Me, jealous of you and bryce?
- Never.

654
00:31:18,750 --> 00:31:19,830
You said everything you want to say?

655
00:31:19,830 --> 00:31:21,110
- More or less.
- Good.

656
00:31:21,110 --> 00:31:21,900
Now, shut up.

657
00:31:21,900 --> 00:31:23,270
You're sucking up all the air.

658
00:31:39,550 --> 00:31:41,610
Sorry i jammed my tongue down your throat.

659
00:31:42,180 --> 00:31:43,280
No worries, morgan.

660
00:31:45,350 --> 00:31:47,260
The lone wolf does it right.

661
00:31:47,260 --> 00:31:49,680
You know, just jump around from mate to mate.

662
00:31:49,680 --> 00:31:50,790
Never settles down.

663
00:31:50,790 --> 00:31:51,720
This way...

664
00:31:52,520 --> 00:31:53,510
He never gets hurt.

665
00:31:54,490 --> 00:31:57,710
Maybe, but lone wolves are also lonely.

666
00:32:21,790 --> 00:32:23,180
Food and drug administration.

667
00:32:25,920 --> 00:32:26,720
How can i help you?

668
00:32:27,790 --> 00:32:29,860
We know about the illegal meats you've been importing, miss.

669
00:32:30,770 --> 00:32:34,250
The fda's been running a task force 
against the demetrios family for the last few months.

670
00:32:34,250 --> 00:32:36,350
You're going dn for ten to 20 in a federal pen.

671
00:32:36,770 --> 00:32:37,480
For salami?

672
00:32:37,480 --> 00:32:38,240
For guns.

673
00:32:38,800 --> 00:32:41,640
- Guns?
- The demetrios family's been shipping guns into l.A.

674
00:32:41,640 --> 00:32:44,920
, which means technically we can 
nail you for aiding and abetting terrorists.

675
00:32:45,400 --> 00:32:46,780
Or you can help us.

676
00:32:49,330 --> 00:32:50,470
What would i have to do?

677
00:32:50,470 --> 00:32:53,240
Give me the dock number where you're 
receiving your shipments from stavros.

678
00:32:56,250 --> 00:32:58,710
- Dock 14b, the northwest pier.
- Thanks.

679
00:33:02,120 --> 00:33:04,900
By the way, miss, your pastrami is delicious.

680
00:33:08,060 --> 00:33:10,250
Time is of the essence, so i will cut to the chase.

681
00:33:11,670 --> 00:33:16,100
We have a very important delivery that is about 
to be picked up and we need to know who else knows about it.

682
00:33:17,820 --> 00:33:19,720
- Okay, i'll talk!I'll talk!
- No, chuck!

683
00:33:19,720 --> 00:33:21,540
We, we know all about...

684
00:33:21,540 --> 00:33:25,840
The imported salami and, and, 
and, we're cool with it, man.

685
00:33:25,840 --> 00:33:28,360
The real crime is that it's illegal to begin with.

686
00:33:28,360 --> 00:33:31,000
Honestly, there's no need for torture, yari.

687
00:33:31,940 --> 00:33:34,440
Mr.Bartowski, i'm not going to torture you.

688
00:33:34,440 --> 00:33:36,310
Great.Great, we're on the same page.

689
00:33:36,540 --> 00:33:37,540
I'm going to torture her.

690
00:33:37,540 --> 00:33:38,410
No, no, no, no, no, no.

691
00:33:38,410 --> 00:33:40,960
We're not on the same page anymore, yari, 
we're not even in the same chapter.

692
00:33:40,960 --> 00:33:42,000
No, no, no, please don't!

693
00:33:46,710 --> 00:33:48,950
You killed a whole family outside yerevan.

694
00:33:49,540 --> 00:33:52,530
You stole their heirlooms, and you sold 
all of them on the russian black market except for that watch.

695
00:33:52,530 --> 00:33:53,390
How do you know that?

696
00:33:59,090 --> 00:34:00,220
Your name is vladimir snell.

697
00:34:00,730 --> 00:34:03,680
Last year, you were paid $40,000 to kill a man named leo koloff.

698
00:34:04,670 --> 00:34:06,190
You told me we were paid 20.

699
00:34:06,340 --> 00:34:08,630
He's lying.
He'll say anything to get out of trouble.

700
00:34:08,630 --> 00:34:09,920
He knows about yerevan.

701
00:34:09,920 --> 00:34:11,070
He knows everything.

702
00:34:11,870 --> 00:34:12,620
And you...

703
00:34:13,380 --> 00:34:14,400
Owe me money.

704
00:34:18,010 --> 00:34:19,230
Well, that settles that.

705
00:34:19,660 --> 00:34:20,160
So...

706
00:34:20,620 --> 00:34:23,100
If you will kindly tell me 
who else knows about our shipment.

707
00:34:23,100 --> 00:34:24,100
Man: the package is here.

708
00:34:25,890 --> 00:34:26,850
Berth 19.

709
00:34:26,850 --> 00:34:28,850
We've got five minutes till it expires, sir.

710
00:34:32,990 --> 00:34:34,650
All right, let's go.

711
00:34:35,640 --> 00:34:36,940
We'll just have to kill them.

712
00:34:39,680 --> 00:34:41,160
Chuck: there's a weapon in the shipment.

713
00:34:41,160 --> 00:34:41,970
I think it's some kind of chemical bomb.

714
00:34:41,970 --> 00:34:43,580
We have to get to it before it blows.

715
00:35:01,710 --> 00:35:02,520
I'll hold the fort.

716
00:35:02,520 --> 00:35:03,950
You go get the bomb-- go!

717
00:35:06,900 --> 00:35:08,130
Sarah: the bomb's at berth 19.

718
00:35:08,130 --> 00:35:09,890
Chuck, i want you to get a
s far away from here as possible.

719
00:35:09,890 --> 00:35:11,050
-I'm coming with you.
-No.Chuck.

720
00:35:11,050 --> 00:35:13,150
You're not going anywhere near a live bomb.

721
00:35:13,150 --> 00:35:14,200
Do you know how to diffuse a bomb?

722
00:35:14,200 --> 00:35:15,440
Do you have an intersect in your head?

723
00:35:15,440 --> 00:35:16,270
I didn't think so.

724
00:35:16,270 --> 00:35:17,920
Hey!Chuck!
Wait!

725
00:35:31,240 --> 00:35:33,050
Go, dad, go!

726
00:35:42,960 --> 00:35:44,350
Go, dad, go!

727
00:35:55,290 --> 00:35:56,760
It's over, yari.Drop the weapon.

728
00:35:58,000 --> 00:35:58,720
Okay.
You got me.

729
00:36:08,610 --> 00:36:09,570
It's tommy.

730
00:36:09,950 --> 00:36:10,830
We have a problem.

731
00:36:11,280 --> 00:36:13,850
Thpackage has been intercepted.
We're going to have to clean things up.

732
00:36:20,590 --> 00:36:21,090
Here.

733
00:36:21,400 --> 00:36:22,000
Help me out.

734
00:36:46,510 --> 00:36:48,760
Okay...
Okay, intersect.

735
00:36:49,530 --> 00:36:50,270
Flash.

736
00:36:50,760 --> 00:36:51,830
Show me how to do this.

737
00:36:52,970 --> 00:36:53,710
Did you flash?

738
00:36:53,710 --> 00:36:54,680
No.
Nothing.

739
00:36:54,970 --> 00:36:55,670
Come on!

740
00:36:55,670 --> 00:36:58,080
Come on, come on, come on, baby, don't fail me now.

741
00:36:58,080 --> 00:37:00,070
Okay, chuck, that's enough.Run
.I'm going to try and stay and defuse it.

742
00:37:00,070 --> 00:37:01,480
No, i'm not leaving you.

743
00:37:01,480 --> 00:37:02,980
Go.That is an order.

744
00:37:02,980 --> 00:37:04,340
No.

745
00:37:06,150 --> 00:37:07,300
I said go.

746
00:37:07,300 --> 00:37:08,430
Oh, see.

747
00:37:08,430 --> 00:37:10,440
So you're going to shoot me to 
prevent me from getting blown up?

748
00:37:10,440 --> 00:37:11,400
That's a great plan.

749
00:37:11,400 --> 00:37:12,590
Why are you so stubborn?

750
00:37:12,590 --> 00:37:14,540
Actually, i consider this a rare moment of courage.

751
00:37:14,540 --> 00:37:17,230
I don't know where it's coming from, 
i guess you just bring out the worst in me.

752
00:37:17,230 --> 00:37:18,520
And you in me.

753
00:37:24,070 --> 00:37:25,190
It was nice knowing you.

754
00:37:55,850 --> 00:37:57,310
Well, the good news is, we're alive.

755
00:37:59,390 --> 00:38:01,580
And the bad news is that this is kind of...

756
00:38:01,980 --> 00:38:03,870
An uncomfortable moment right now.

757
00:38:05,560 --> 00:38:07,870
It's completely comfortable on my end.

758
00:38:09,520 --> 00:38:10,340
Just saying.

759
00:38:19,710 --> 00:38:20,270
* hey yeah * * under the sun * * you will find me * * under the sun * * nothing but blue skies * select ingredients combine for sophisticated flavours, like sun-dried tomato.

760
00:38:24,110 --> 00:38:24,740
Look, i...

761
00:38:24,740 --> 00:38:27,460
I know that you are so sick of hearing this, 

762
00:38:27,460 --> 00:38:32,760
but i'm really sorry if i've acted like a jerk.

763
00:38:33,250 --> 00:38:35,630
Chuck, i know who you really work for.

764
00:38:37,210 --> 00:38:39,000
That you're an undercover agent.

765
00:38:41,320 --> 00:38:42,210
How do you...

766
00:38:42,210 --> 00:38:44,900
That guy casey from the food 
and drug administration came to see me, 

767
00:38:45,280 --> 00:38:47,280
explained that you are an informant.

768
00:38:47,740 --> 00:38:50,070
Righ my cover has been blown.

769
00:38:50,410 --> 00:38:51,970
I'm an agent for the fda.

770
00:38:52,140 --> 00:38:55,490
Can i ask you a question?

771
00:38:56,100 --> 00:38:58,910
This whole time, did you ever really like me?

772
00:38:58,910 --> 00:38:59,650
Honestly?

773
00:38:59,650 --> 00:39:00,150
Yeah.

774
00:39:00,740 --> 00:39:04,350
Let's try that for the first time since we've met.

775
00:39:04,350 --> 00:39:06,740
Lou, you are everything that i'm looking for.

776
00:39:09,480 --> 00:39:11,040
I just can't look right now.

777
00:39:12,710 --> 00:39:13,300
Well...

778
00:39:13,300 --> 00:39:15,380
Thank you for being honest.

779
00:39:16,800 --> 00:39:19,160
The next time my phone breaks, 
i'm going to the large mart.

780
00:39:19,160 --> 00:39:21,300
Oh, that...That hurts.

781
00:39:21,300 --> 00:39:22,720
And the next time that you're hungry...

782
00:39:22,720 --> 00:39:23,530
No, no, no, no.

783
00:39:23,530 --> 00:39:24,840
Take it to the wienerlicious.

784
00:39:26,410 --> 00:39:28,300
I'm really going to miss the chuck bartowski.

785
00:39:29,660 --> 00:39:30,690
So am i.

786
00:39:33,140 --> 00:39:33,750
Hey, lou.

787
00:39:35,010 --> 00:39:35,560
Yeah?

788
00:39:36,520 --> 00:39:37,370
I'm sorry.

789
00:39:37,830 --> 00:39:38,650
Don't be.

790
00:39:39,120 --> 00:39:43,590
Secret agent or no that was 
the best kiss i've had in a long time.

791
00:39:50,690 --> 00:39:53,050
Hey, morgan, can i borrow a pen?

792
00:39:54,580 --> 00:39:55,780
He is so whipped.

793
00:39:55,780 --> 00:39:57,300
Pathetic.
Ridiculous.

794
00:39:58,350 --> 00:39:58,940
Whipped?

795
00:40:00,420 --> 00:40:02,130
Oh, yeah, i got a girlfriend now, chuck.

796
00:40:03,250 --> 00:40:04,080
Anna?

797
00:40:04,590 --> 00:40:06,340
She couldn't resist my animal magnetism.

798
00:40:07,530 --> 00:40:10,160
I almost feel bad for the kid.
She never stood a chance, you know?

799
00:40:10,960 --> 00:40:12,620
Anyway...
Hey!

800
00:40:12,980 --> 00:40:15,090
You and lou, this friday, we'll double date.

801
00:40:15,770 --> 00:40:16,890
Lou and i broke up.

802
00:40:16,890 --> 00:40:17,710
What?

803
00:40:17,710 --> 00:40:18,800
You're a free man?

804
00:40:21,020 --> 00:40:21,640
Anna.

805
00:40:22,040 --> 00:40:23,870
Hey, listen, it's, uh, it's morgan.

806
00:40:24,250 --> 00:40:25,060
It's over.

807
00:40:25,060 --> 00:40:29,400
We had a good run, but, uh, lone wolf has to run free.
Okay?x

808
00:40:30,200 --> 00:40:31,440
Chuck and morgan train is on...

809
00:40:31,440 --> 00:40:33,520
Track.Track.Track.

810
00:40:33,710 --> 00:40:35,730
Yeah, not really, though, 'cause, uh...

811
00:40:36,280 --> 00:40:38,300
I'm going to get back together with sarah i think.

812
00:40:38,300 --> 00:40:39,960
You couldn't say this ten seconds ago, huh?

813
00:40:41,230 --> 00:40:41,860
Anna.

814
00:40:42,480 --> 00:40:43,370
Honey?

815
00:40:43,720 --> 00:40:44,390
Sweetie.

816
00:40:55,110 --> 00:40:57,520
Whoever shot yari was here to pick up this package.

817
00:40:57,810 --> 00:40:59,570
Someone who didn't want yari to talk.

818
00:41:05,860 --> 00:41:06,620
All clear.

819
00:41:07,570 --> 00:41:09,110
Looks mean, but it's nonlethal.

820
00:41:09,490 --> 00:41:12,630
That timer wasn't a fuse, 
it was measuring an oxygen supply.

821
00:41:30,230 --> 00:41:32,080
This is sarah.
Please leave a message.

822
00:41:32,740 --> 00:41:33,930
Hi, it's chuck.

823
00:41:34,280 --> 00:41:36,230
Of course, it's me, it's me, it's chuck.

824
00:41:36,580 --> 00:41:39,290
Look, i-i was just wondering if 
you wanted to go out on a date tonight.

825
00:41:41,740 --> 00:41:47,220
And by "date" i mean no gps and no 
mikes and no chaperos-- it'd just be us.

826
00:41:55,150 --> 00:41:56,720
Oh, my god, bryce.

827
00:41:57,780 --> 00:41:58,690
Didn't i kill him?

828
00:42:04,160 --> 00:42:06,230
I'm thinking maybe we could hit up sbarro.

829
00:42:06,720 --> 00:42:12,080
They just named a new pizza after morgan,
 and, uh, you know, i kind of wanted to support him.

830
00:42:13,980 --> 00:42:14,730
So...

831
00:42:15,550 --> 00:42:16,360
Okay.

832
00:42:17,620 --> 00:42:18,450
Bye.

833
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


834
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


