1
00:00:00,960 --> 00:00:10,100
Michael I can say with virtual certainty

2
00:00:10,190 --> 00:00:11,100
that the man coming towards you

3
00:00:11,160 --> 00:00:14,100
is the same man who broke into the regional FBI office

4
00:00:13,960 --> 00:00:15,100
What about the drive?

5
00:00:15,160 --> 00:00:17,430
He appears to be carrying it.

6
00:00:17,500 --> 00:00:19,900
Michael,this man is armed and dangerous.

7
00:00:19,960 --> 00:00:21,460
You saying I can't take him?

8
00:00:21,530 --> 00:00:23,530
I'm merely saying,I'm available to assist you

9
00:00:23,600 --> 00:00:25,830
if necessary.

10
00:00:25,900 --> 00:00:27,730
How hard is it to find a black mustang?

11
00:00:41,800 --> 00:00:44,260
Michael,are you sure you don't need any help?

12
00:00:55,200 --> 00:00:57,960
See?

13
00:00:58,030 --> 00:00:58,960
I didn't need your help.

14
00:00:59,030 --> 00:01:00,000
Are you talking to me?

15
00:01:00,060 --> 00:01:01,030
Shut up.

16
00:01:06,230 --> 00:01:10,230
I'll take the drive and your gun.

17
00:01:14,600 --> 00:01:16,860
I believe the subject is playing possum.

18
00:01:21,830 --> 00:01:23,730
Okay,uncle.

19
00:01:23,800 --> 00:01:25,030
Black ice,Michael?

20
00:01:25,100 --> 00:01:26,230
Yeah,sure,why not?

21
00:01:26,300 --> 00:01:27,400
Initiating black ice.

22
00:01:35,600 --> 00:01:37,730
I would be happy to eliminate the fence with my laser.

23
00:01:37,800 --> 00:01:39,460
Okay,now you're just being annoying.

24
00:01:45,430 --> 00:01:46,860
Where's Rivai?

25
00:01:46,930 --> 00:01:48,530
Uh,interrogation one.

26
00:01:48,600 --> 00:01:50,030
Where's Torres?

27
00:01:50,100 --> 00:01:51,100
D.c.,back on wednesday,wouldn't talk about it.

28
00:01:51,160 --> 00:01:52,100
Graiman?

29
00:01:52,160 --> 00:01:53,260
Getting ready for the eco-audit.

30
00:01:53,330 --> 00:01:55,700
Green consultants coming from the pentagon.

31
00:01:55,760 --> 00:01:56,760
Nice eye.

32
00:01:56,830 --> 00:01:58,100
See the other guy.

33
00:01:58,160 --> 00:01:59,760
You got anything besides root beer?

34
00:01:59,830 --> 00:02:02,360
Who's this for?

35
00:02:02,430 --> 00:02:03,600
My p.c. needed an upgrade.

36
00:02:03,660 --> 00:02:05,930
How did you get past the FBI's secure perimeter?

37
00:02:06,000 --> 00:02:08,160
I'm persistent and goal-oriented.

38
00:02:10,200 --> 00:02:11,860
There are anti-terrorism files

39
00:02:11,930 --> 00:02:13,960
On this hard drive.

40
00:02:14,030 --> 00:02:15,360
Look,it was just a contract job I picked up

41
00:02:15,430 --> 00:02:16,660
On my way out of town.

42
00:02:16,730 --> 00:02:18,460
Do you know what messing with the bureau means?

43
00:02:18,530 --> 00:02:20,730
You ever heard of the patriot act?

44
00:02:20,800 --> 00:02:22,100
No lawyer.

45
00:02:22,160 --> 00:02:23,700
Do not pass go.

46
00:02:23,760 --> 00:02:25,330
Straight to guantanamo.

47
00:02:25,400 --> 00:02:27,800
Hope you like Cuban food.

48
00:02:31,530 --> 00:02:32,560
Anchorage.

49
00:02:32,630 --> 00:02:33,930
What?

50
00:02:34,000 --> 00:02:36,360
I said,"anchorage."

51
00:02:36,430 --> 00:02:37,730
I wanna make a deal.

52
00:02:40,730 --> 00:02:42,000
Kitt,analyze the ring cross reference

53
00:02:42,060 --> 00:02:43,830
With Anchorage,Alaska.

54
00:02:43,900 --> 00:02:47,000
It is a ring depicting virgo,the virgin.

55
00:02:47,060 --> 00:02:49,930
The sixth astrological sign in the zodiac.

56
00:02:50,000 --> 00:02:52,130
In astrology,virgo is considered a feminine sign.

57
00:02:52,200 --> 00:02:54,860
I didn't pick it,monotone guy.

58
00:02:54,930 --> 00:02:56,200
We were each given a sign and a ring.

59
00:02:56,260 --> 00:02:58,060
Nobody used real names.

60
00:02:58,130 --> 00:03:01,130
What was wrong with Mr. Pink,Mr. White,and Mr. Black?

61
00:03:01,200 --> 00:03:03,500
I guess capricorn never saw reservoir dogs?

62
00:03:03,560 --> 00:03:05,930
Actually,the names-as-colors motif

63
00:03:06,000 --> 00:03:09,000
was originally featured the film taking of pelham one two three.

64
00:03:09,060 --> 00:03:10,430
I knew that.

65
00:03:10,500 --> 00:03:12,000
Whatever.

66
00:03:12,060 --> 00:03:14,430
I ran security a payroll job up in Anchorage.

67
00:03:14,500 --> 00:03:15,860
Supposed to pick up my share.

68
00:03:15,930 --> 00:03:17,830
I can confirm the payroll robbery.

69
00:03:17,900 --> 00:03:21,200
Two security guard were killed.

70
00:03:21,260 --> 00:03:23,200
I didn't have nothing to do with murder.

71
00:03:23,260 --> 00:03:25,460
4 million dollar was stolen in what has the markings

72
00:03:25,530 --> 00:03:27,630
of a completely compartmentalized operation.

73
00:03:27,700 --> 00:03:29,330
six expert thieves.

74
00:03:29,400 --> 00:03:31,430
Reportedly,none knew the identities of the others.

75
00:03:31,500 --> 00:03:34,600
Each was known only by a sign of the zodiac.

76
00:03:34,660 --> 00:03:35,700
You hearing this?

77
00:03:35,760 --> 00:03:37,400
Alaska?

78
00:03:37,460 --> 00:03:38,600
None of the thieves were ever identified

79
00:03:38,660 --> 00:03:40,030
or apprehended.

80
00:03:40,100 --> 00:03:41,630
I hate the cold.

81
00:03:41,700 --> 00:03:42,930
I thought you hated water.

82
00:03:43,000 --> 00:03:44,760
Snow is frozen water,Sarah.

83
00:03:44,830 --> 00:03:48,360
Monotone guy's right,except he left something out.

84
00:03:48,430 --> 00:03:50,330
The lead of the crew's name's Capricorn.

85
00:03:50,400 --> 00:03:52,160
He's a big-time money launderer.

86
00:03:52,230 --> 00:03:53,830
If you give me immunity,

87
00:03:53,900 --> 00:03:56,530
On the payroll sco and on the hard drive...

88
00:03:58,060 --> 00:03:59,600
I'll give you the whole zodiac crew.

89
00:03:59,660 --> 00:04:01,330
None of you guys have ever seen each other,right?

90
00:04:01,400 --> 00:04:02,960
Not till later today.

91
00:04:03,030 --> 00:04:04,330
Supposed to finally meet up

92
00:04:04,400 --> 00:04:06,000
To discuss capricorn's new deal.

93
00:04:06,060 --> 00:04:07,630
I'll wear a wire.

94
00:04:11,400 --> 00:04:12,860
You're virgo.

95
00:04:12,930 --> 00:04:15,000
A virgin.

96
00:04:15,060 --> 00:04:16,430
Irony,thy name is Mike.

97
00:04:16,500 --> 00:04:18,760
The rendezvous point with capricorn and the others.

98
00:04:18,830 --> 00:04:20,830
Thought it was Alaska.

99
00:04:20,900 --> 00:04:23,400
Bet you wanna go now.

100
00:04:23,460 --> 00:04:24,700
I can't.

101
00:04:24,760 --> 00:04:25,900
We've got that eco-audit today.

102
00:04:25,960 --> 00:04:26,860
Looks like you lucked out.

103
00:04:26,930 --> 00:04:27,900
Take Billy as backup.

104
00:04:27,960 --> 00:04:29,500
Billy?

105
00:04:29,560 --> 00:04:31,060
Ow-ee,paper cut!

106
00:04:31,130 --> 00:04:33,200
Burns,burning,it burns.

107
00:04:33,260 --> 00:04:34,730
You don't deactivate sophisticated alarm systems

108
00:04:34,800 --> 00:04:36,200
With a pair wire cutters.

109
00:04:36,260 --> 00:04:37,500
You need computer skills.

110
00:04:37,560 --> 00:04:38,660
Do you have computer skills?

111
00:04:38,730 --> 00:04:40,300
I play Xbox.

112
00:04:40,360 --> 00:04:41,630
Yeah,you leave in 20.

113
00:04:47,630 --> 00:04:49,000
Dude,I will not disappoint.

114
00:04:49,060 --> 00:04:50,360
Promise.

115
00:04:50,430 --> 00:04:51,900
No offense,but I don't think

116
00:04:51,960 --> 00:04:53,900
There's a whole hell of a lot for you to do.

117
00:04:53,960 --> 00:04:55,330
I'm going deep cover on this one.

118
00:04:58,400 --> 00:05:00,500
Kitt,fingerprint generator.

119
00:05:03,930 --> 00:05:05,800
Michael,please place your hand directly on the hand mat.

120
00:05:05,860 --> 00:05:08,000
Transposing fingerprints now.

121
00:05:09,360 --> 00:05:12,260
I have overlaid virgo's fingerprints onto you.

122
00:05:12,330 --> 00:05:13,330
Look,I don't think I'm gonna need it.

123
00:05:13,400 --> 00:05:14,660
I got the ring.

124
00:05:14,730 --> 00:05:16,930
None of the zodiac crew's ever seen each other.

125
00:05:17,000 --> 00:05:19,060
Michael,may I ask you a question,why did the man in the interrogation room

126
00:05:19,130 --> 00:05:20,630
refer to me as "monotone guy"?

127
00:05:21,800 --> 00:05:23,430
'Cause he's a douche,kitt.

128
00:05:25,460 --> 00:05:27,230
Our aim is to recycle everything

129
00:05:27,300 --> 00:05:29,160
We used to ship out as refuse by the end of the year.

130
00:05:29,230 --> 00:05:30,660
What about top-secret files?

131
00:05:30,730 --> 00:05:31,760
Cross-cut,shredded,and burned.

132
00:05:31,830 --> 00:05:33,660
The FBI requires it.

133
00:05:33,730 --> 00:05:35,860
20th century solution to a 21st century problem.

134
00:05:35,930 --> 00:05:38,260
I've argued for an on-site,enzyme-activated

135
00:05:38,330 --> 00:05:40,030
Compost bi for all unrecyclable paper.

136
00:05:40,100 --> 00:05:43,300
No co2,no nitric oxide,no particulate emissions.

137
00:05:43,360 --> 00:05:45,030
Just methane.

138
00:05:45,100 --> 00:05:46,260
Which we could use to heat the entire floor.

139
00:05:46,330 --> 00:05:48,060
You talk like an engineer.

140
00:05:48,130 --> 00:05:49,560
Phd,mechanical.

141
00:05:49,630 --> 00:05:50,730
Me too,m.i.t.

142
00:05:50,800 --> 00:05:51,730
Where'd you get your doctorate?

143
00:05:51,800 --> 00:05:52,800
Stanford.

144
00:05:52,860 --> 00:05:53,760
Really? Yeah.

145
00:05:53,830 --> 00:05:54,760
I see you've met my daughter.

146
00:05:54,830 --> 00:05:56,230
Hello,Tess.

147
00:05:56,300 --> 00:05:57,460
Hello,Charles.

148
00:06:06,060 --> 00:06:09,000
We're entering a potentially hostile environment.

149
00:06:09,060 --> 00:06:11,330
Don't you think you're overstating things just a bit?

150
00:06:11,400 --> 00:06:12,800
Common difficulties,or a precipitous drop

151
00:06:12,860 --> 00:06:14,260
in blood-sugar,

152
00:06:14,330 --> 00:06:16,900
sleep deprivation,and encounters with dangers

153
00:06:16,960 --> 00:06:18,600
and unpredictable locals.

154
00:06:18,660 --> 00:06:20,360
We'll be careful,kitt,I promise.

155
00:06:22,600 --> 00:06:23,960
Vegas,baby.

156
00:06:24,030 --> 00:06:26,130
Vegas!

157
00:07:19,760 --> 00:07:21,360
Anybody sees us together,you're my little brother.

158
00:07:21,430 --> 00:07:23,200
We're just here to gamble,drink,

159
00:07:23,260 --> 00:07:24,800
and hunt for chicks.

160
00:07:24,860 --> 00:07:26,030
That's a good cover story,

161
00:07:26,100 --> 00:07:27,060
But don't take it too far.

162
00:07:27,130 --> 00:07:28,560
I may need some computer know-how.

163
00:07:28,630 --> 00:07:31,700
Dude,I can't get too wasted if I'm gonna try counting cards.

164
00:07:31,760 --> 00:07:33,360
May I remind you that all Las Vegas casinos

165
00:07:33,430 --> 00:07:35,300
will immediately eject you for counting cards?

166
00:07:35,360 --> 00:07:37,760
It's not illegal.

167
00:07:37,830 --> 00:07:39,700
Just try and stay relatively sober.

168
00:07:39,760 --> 00:07:41,930
Hey,I got your back.

169
00:07:42,000 --> 00:07:44,730
You know what they say about Vegas?

170
00:07:44,800 --> 00:07:48,260
Go on vacation,leave on probation.

171
00:07:49,930 --> 00:07:50,930
Yeah.

172
00:08:18,960 --> 00:08:20,460
Michael,I implore you.

173
00:08:20,530 --> 00:08:22,400
I know you don't like valet parking,Kitt,

174
00:08:22,460 --> 00:08:23,800
but I need you close by.

175
00:08:23,860 --> 00:08:24,860
Valets tend to be

176
00:08:24,930 --> 00:08:26,460
especially duplicitous humans.

177
00:08:26,530 --> 00:08:28,230
They often rummage through my interior

178
00:08:28,300 --> 00:08:30,900
or attempt to drive me in an erratic manner.

179
00:08:30,960 --> 00:08:32,430
Just don't hurt anybody,Okay?

180
00:08:32,500 --> 00:08:35,060
How do you plan on finding the zodiac gang?

181
00:08:35,130 --> 00:08:37,760
I imagine they'll be finding me.

182
00:08:37,830 --> 00:08:40,300
Welcome to the corsica.

183
00:08:40,360 --> 00:08:41,400
Wish me luck.

184
00:08:41,460 --> 00:08:42,500
Be careful,Michael.

185
00:08:45,100 --> 00:08:46,260
Just leave it up front.

186
00:08:46,330 --> 00:08:47,700
Yes,sir.

187
00:09:12,900 --> 00:09:15,130
Get a positive I.D. on the ring,all right?

188
00:09:15,200 --> 00:09:16,930
Michael,you are being followed.

189
00:09:17,000 --> 00:09:18,430
Kitt,give me options.

190
00:09:18,500 --> 00:09:20,200
There's a bathroom 30 feet ahead and then right.

191
00:09:22,060 --> 00:09:23,760
State law forbids the hotel from having cameras

192
00:09:23,830 --> 00:09:25,200
In its bathrooms.

193
00:09:25,260 --> 00:09:27,030
I cannot be your eyes if you enter.

194
00:09:27,100 --> 00:09:28,800
Got no choice.

195
00:09:28,860 --> 00:09:30,330
I got this.

196
00:09:30,400 --> 00:09:31,630
Stay here.

197
00:09:33,560 --> 00:09:35,630
I'm ditching the earwig.

198
00:09:40,560 --> 00:09:41,530
Hey.

199
00:09:42,560 --> 00:09:43,860
Look,easy,easy!

200
00:09:43,930 --> 00:09:45,300
Virgo,come on.

201
00:09:45,360 --> 00:09:47,130
I'm capricorn.

202
00:09:49,630 --> 00:09:51,260
I'm missing some vital information.

203
00:09:51,330 --> 00:09:52,460
Where's Kitt?

204
00:09:52,530 --> 00:09:54,630
Uh,officially,Kitt doesn't exist.

205
00:09:54,700 --> 00:09:56,700
So he's on a mission. When's he due back?

206
00:09:58,260 --> 00:09:59,460
I can't tell you that.

207
00:09:59,530 --> 00:10:01,560
Charles,there is a fax from the pentagon

208
00:10:01,630 --> 00:10:03,260
That has it in for knight industries.

209
00:10:03,330 --> 00:10:04,800
I can help.

210
00:10:07,200 --> 00:10:08,530
Sarah doesn't know about us,does she?

211
00:10:09,760 --> 00:10:10,830
No.

212
00:10:10,900 --> 00:10:12,260
She's a beautiful girl.

213
00:10:12,330 --> 00:10:13,760
And a first-rate scientist.

214
00:10:13,830 --> 00:10:14,760
You should be very proud.

215
00:10:14,830 --> 00:10:17,130
Yeah,isn't it unethical for you

216
00:10:17,200 --> 00:10:19,260
To exercise your full review authority

217
00:10:19,330 --> 00:10:23,360
Without disclosing the nature of our prior relationship?

218
00:10:23,430 --> 00:10:25,800
Oh,I already did.

219
00:10:25,860 --> 00:10:27,600
You told the pentagon we dated?

220
00:10:27,660 --> 00:10:29,560
Not in precisely that vernacular.

221
00:10:31,200 --> 00:10:33,660
I said we used to have sex,and lots of it.

222
00:10:33,730 --> 00:10:35,200
Let's get to work.

223
00:10:37,130 --> 00:10:39,160
Security chief was wearing the same ring.

224
00:10:39,230 --> 00:10:40,360
Mike's in.

225
00:10:40,430 --> 00:10:41,360
Mike okay?

226
00:10:41,430 --> 00:10:43,500
Billy says,"yes."

227
00:10:43,560 --> 00:10:44,560
He's out of audio contact,

228
00:10:44,630 --> 00:10:45,730
But we're tracking his earwig,

229
00:10:45,800 --> 00:10:47,500
It's still in the casino bathroom.

230
00:10:47,560 --> 00:10:48,600
He must've ditched it.

231
00:10:51,930 --> 00:10:53,100
What's up with that?

232
00:10:53,160 --> 00:10:54,560
What?

233
00:10:54,630 --> 00:10:56,660
Come on...

234
00:10:56,730 --> 00:10:57,900
You don't see it?

235
00:10:57,960 --> 00:10:59,960
Your dad and the green lady.

236
00:11:00,030 --> 00:11:01,530
Check out the body language.

237
00:11:02,960 --> 00:11:04,100
I'm pretty sure they used to,you know,

238
00:11:04,160 --> 00:11:05,130
Make waffles.

239
00:11:06,360 --> 00:11:08,760
Oh,Dr. G,pass the syrup.

240
00:11:08,830 --> 00:11:10,300
La,la,la,la,la...

241
00:11:10,360 --> 00:11:13,300
So gross. That's my dad.

242
00:11:23,900 --> 00:11:25,130
Everybody...

243
00:11:25,200 --> 00:11:26,960
Our final guest has arrived.

244
00:11:27,030 --> 00:11:28,960
I give you Virgo.

245
00:11:29,030 --> 00:11:30,800
Best second-story man in the business.

246
00:11:30,860 --> 00:11:31,900
Scorpio...

247
00:11:31,960 --> 00:11:33,600
Small-handed extraction.

248
00:11:35,060 --> 00:11:36,060
The pick-pocket.

249
00:11:36,130 --> 00:11:37,830
Yeah.

250
00:11:37,900 --> 00:11:38,860
We love to keep him around.

251
00:11:38,930 --> 00:11:39,930
Um,this is Gemini.

252
00:11:40,000 --> 00:11:40,930
Gemini.

253
00:11:41,000 --> 00:11:42,300
Weapons.

254
00:11:42,360 --> 00:11:44,130
Sorry about anchorage,nothing you could do about it.

255
00:11:44,200 --> 00:11:46,000
And of course,Leo.

256
00:11:46,060 --> 00:11:48,130
Communications and tech.

257
00:11:48,200 --> 00:11:49,130
Hey,you hungry?

258
00:11:49,200 --> 00:11:50,500
We got a whole buffet.

259
00:11:50,560 --> 00:11:51,530
Yes,we do.

260
00:11:51,600 --> 00:11:53,430
And the beautiful aquarius.

261
00:11:55,030 --> 00:11:56,530
Nice to finally meet you,Virgo.

262
00:11:56,600 --> 00:11:57,860
And what's your specialty?

263
00:11:57,930 --> 00:11:59,530
I'm the distraction.

264
00:11:59,600 --> 00:12:01,600
Trust me,she is.

265
00:12:01,660 --> 00:12:03,200
All right,listen up.

266
00:12:03,260 --> 00:12:04,530
Anybody wants out,

267
00:12:04,600 --> 00:12:06,100
Take your cut,hit the bricks.

268
00:12:06,160 --> 00:12:07,500
No hard feelings,okay?

269
00:12:12,560 --> 00:12:14,160
Well...

270
00:12:14,230 --> 00:12:15,230
With that said,

271
00:12:15,300 --> 00:12:16,730
To future endeavors.

272
00:12:18,730 --> 00:12:19,800
Cheers.

273
00:12:25,100 --> 00:12:27,330
Scanning fingerprints.

274
00:12:29,560 --> 00:12:32,730
Oh,very nice.

275
00:12:33,830 --> 00:12:35,200
Aquarius confirmed.

276
00:12:35,260 --> 00:12:36,260
Scorpio confirmed.

277
00:12:36,330 --> 00:12:38,500
Gemini confirmed.

278
00:12:38,560 --> 00:12:40,330
Leo confirmed.

279
00:12:43,230 --> 00:12:44,860
Virgo confirmed.

280
00:12:44,930 --> 00:12:46,600
Well,looks like we're all who we say we are.

281
00:12:46,660 --> 00:12:48,060
On to business...

282
00:12:48,130 --> 00:12:49,860
And now,it is time for us to divide our product

283
00:12:49,930 --> 00:12:52,130
From our last adventure as individuals.

284
00:12:52,200 --> 00:12:54,230
Because tomorrow,my friends,we embark

285
00:12:54,300 --> 00:12:55,760
On a new one as a team.

286
00:12:55,830 --> 00:12:57,130
One will enrich us.

287
00:12:57,200 --> 00:12:59,430
Beyond our wildest dreams.

288
00:12:59,500 --> 00:13:02,260
- But tonight,we drink.  - Absolutely.

289
00:13:18,330 --> 00:13:20,460
You want to go partner on the next hand?

290
00:13:20,530 --> 00:13:22,400
50 each?

291
00:13:22,460 --> 00:13:23,560
Me?

292
00:13:23,630 --> 00:13:24,700
Come on.

293
00:13:24,760 --> 00:13:26,600
You never know until you take a chance.

294
00:13:27,630 --> 00:13:29,360
All right.

295
00:13:29,360 --> 00:13:30,700
Yeah.

296
00:13:35,600 --> 00:13:37,300
Money play one hundred.

297
00:13:42,360 --> 00:13:43,700
21.

298
00:13:43,760 --> 00:13:45,030
Yeah!

299
00:13:50,660 --> 00:13:51,700
I'm Courtney.

300
00:13:51,760 --> 00:13:53,260
I'm Billy.

301
00:13:54,460 --> 00:13:56,400
- Wanna go again?  - Yeah.

302
00:13:56,460 --> 00:13:58,760
Now see,this is emblematic of my whole mission here.

303
00:13:58,830 --> 00:13:59,900
You can consider replacing some of this plastic

304
00:13:59,960 --> 00:14:00,930
With plain old paper.

305
00:14:01,000 --> 00:14:02,430
At least it biodegrades.

306
00:14:02,500 --> 00:14:04,330
Well,we kill 14 million trees every year

307
00:14:04,400 --> 00:14:06,500
To make the paper that's a major contributor

308
00:14:06,560 --> 00:14:09,430
To the increasing planetary surface temperature.

309
00:14:09,500 --> 00:14:12,300
Did you know that plastic consumes 12 million barrels

310
00:14:12,360 --> 00:14:13,500
Of oil a year in the u.s.

311
00:14:13,560 --> 00:14:14,700
Not to mention,it chokes the ocean

312
00:14:14,760 --> 00:14:16,160
And destroys sea life.

313
00:14:16,230 --> 00:14:18,000
Well,manufacturing paper bags

314
00:14:18,060 --> 00:14:20,030
Creates 70% more air pollution.

315
00:14:20,100 --> 00:14:21,500
Plastic creates four times the waste.

316
00:14:21,560 --> 00:14:23,230
Look,paper is bulkier.

317
00:14:23,300 --> 00:14:24,860
It takes seven times the number of trucks

318
00:14:24,930 --> 00:14:27,300
To ship the same number of...

319
00:14:29,260 --> 00:14:30,300
Carrie...

320
00:14:33,530 --> 00:14:34,660
Oh...

321
00:14:34,730 --> 00:14:35,760
My...

322
00:14:35,830 --> 00:14:37,830
God.

323
00:15:01,930 --> 00:15:03,730
Here's your cut.

324
00:15:03,800 --> 00:15:05,500
Washed clean.

325
00:15:05,560 --> 00:15:07,830
Courtesy of the Corsica hotel and casino.

326
00:15:07,900 --> 00:15:10,130
Oh,I do love this job.

327
00:15:11,900 --> 00:15:13,000
That's too bad,the gravy train's pulling

328
00:15:13,060 --> 00:15:14,030
Into its last station.

329
00:15:15,260 --> 00:15:16,230
What are you talking about?

330
00:15:18,530 --> 00:15:19,860
New ownership at the corsica.

331
00:15:19,930 --> 00:15:22,060
They're bringing in a new chief of security.

332
00:15:22,130 --> 00:15:23,100
- Are you kidding me?  - No.

333
00:15:23,160 --> 00:15:24,760
Seven years I spent as Steven Cordoba,

334
00:15:24,830 --> 00:15:26,430
Trusted chief of security.

335
00:15:26,500 --> 00:15:28,060
Now in ten days,I'm out on my ass.

336
00:15:28,130 --> 00:15:29,630
You can't catch a break these days.

337
00:15:29,700 --> 00:15:30,700
Yeah.

338
00:15:30,760 --> 00:15:31,900
The others know?

339
00:15:31,960 --> 00:15:34,760
No... You're the first.

340
00:15:34,830 --> 00:15:36,600
How're we going to wash the money from now on?

341
00:15:36,660 --> 00:15:37,760
We're not.

342
00:15:37,830 --> 00:15:39,760
We're gonna take down one more score.

343
00:15:39,830 --> 00:15:42,360
And this one's the mother lode,junior.

344
00:15:42,430 --> 00:15:44,230
And then we're all in the wind.

345
00:15:46,030 --> 00:15:47,900
Just seems to one little problem...

346
00:15:51,400 --> 00:15:53,260
Your fingerprints check out,

347
00:15:53,330 --> 00:15:54,430
But then that's the wrong I.D.

348
00:15:54,500 --> 00:15:57,100
And uh...

349
00:15:57,160 --> 00:16:00,060
Hold on.

350
00:16:00,130 --> 00:16:01,830
How do you think I stayed out of the joint this long?

351
00:16:01,900 --> 00:16:03,030
You tell me.

352
00:16:03,100 --> 00:16:04,630
Let me use your cell phone.

353
00:16:06,260 --> 00:16:07,330
This?

354
00:16:11,760 --> 00:16:13,530
Get me Kitt.

355
00:16:13,600 --> 00:16:14,700
It's Mike,From an unknown cell phone.

356
00:16:14,760 --> 00:16:17,130
- He wants Kitt.  - Patch him through.

357
00:16:17,200 --> 00:16:19,600
- Kitt?  - Michael,it's good to hear your voice.

358
00:16:19,660 --> 00:16:21,600
Put Steven Cordoba's Nevada driver's license

359
00:16:21,660 --> 00:16:24,100
On this computer.

360
00:16:28,930 --> 00:16:30,100
Impressive.

361
00:16:31,530 --> 00:16:32,700
Who do you want to be?

362
00:16:33,900 --> 00:16:35,100
What?

363
00:16:35,160 --> 00:16:36,760
Anybody. Living or dead.

364
00:16:36,830 --> 00:16:38,360
Who do you want to be?

365
00:16:44,060 --> 00:16:45,030
Him.

366
00:16:52,630 --> 00:16:54,130
Insert.

367
00:17:00,400 --> 00:17:01,400
That's good.

368
00:17:04,230 --> 00:17:05,300
That's very good.

369
00:17:06,660 --> 00:17:07,700
All right,all right.

370
00:17:07,760 --> 00:17:09,160
Hey,come on.

371
00:17:09,230 --> 00:17:10,330
Let's all go get rich,huh?

372
00:17:10,400 --> 00:17:11,700
Let's party.

373
00:17:19,500 --> 00:17:21,230
So where's the next score?

374
00:17:21,300 --> 00:17:24,060
I'll show you at the pool. We'll talk then.

375
00:17:32,030 --> 00:17:33,100
I missed you,Michael.

376
00:17:33,160 --> 00:17:34,100
Likewise.

377
00:17:34,160 --> 00:17:35,960
Can you analyze these bills for me?

378
00:17:36,030 --> 00:17:38,200
Of course,Michael.

379
00:17:39,560 --> 00:17:41,060
The bills are genuine.

380
00:17:41,130 --> 00:17:42,630
Get me the SSC.

381
00:17:43,700 --> 00:17:44,660
You okay?

382
00:17:44,730 --> 00:17:46,200
I'm fine.

383
00:17:46,260 --> 00:17:48,000
Capricorn is Steve Cordoba.

384
00:17:48,060 --> 00:17:49,500
He's the head of security at the Corsica.

385
00:17:49,560 --> 00:17:50,530
And he's using his position

386
00:17:50,600 --> 00:17:51,930
To run a massive money laundering operation

387
00:17:52,000 --> 00:17:53,100
Through the casino.

388
00:17:53,160 --> 00:17:54,660
But that's coming to an end.

389
00:17:54,730 --> 00:17:56,100
And now he's planning something big.

390
00:17:56,160 --> 00:17:58,460
We'll do some more digging on his Cordoba alias.

391
00:17:58,530 --> 00:18:00,100
And check with our informants on the street.

392
00:18:00,160 --> 00:18:01,760
Oh,and,Carrie...

393
00:18:01,830 --> 00:18:04,160
Don't make any deals with the real Virgo.

394
00:18:04,230 --> 00:18:06,500
He killed those two guards in anchorage.

395
00:18:06,560 --> 00:18:09,000
Michael,do not forget your earwig.

396
00:18:09,060 --> 00:18:11,700
I went all the way out to the room

397
00:18:11,760 --> 00:18:12,900
To meet my friend.

398
00:18:12,960 --> 00:18:14,830
And it turns out,she ditched me.

399
00:18:14,900 --> 00:18:16,260
I think she met a dude.

400
00:18:16,330 --> 00:18:17,260
That's so random.

401
00:18:17,330 --> 00:18:19,130
I...I kind of got ditched too.

402
00:18:22,660 --> 00:18:23,700
Ouch.

403
00:18:23,760 --> 00:18:25,460
Eh,it's okay.

404
00:18:25,530 --> 00:18:27,600
My parents are ridiculously wealthy.

405
00:18:27,660 --> 00:18:28,600
Really?

406
00:18:28,660 --> 00:18:30,230
Really.

407
00:18:30,300 --> 00:18:31,330
What do you do?

408
00:18:31,400 --> 00:18:32,600
Uh...

409
00:18:32,660 --> 00:18:33,700
I'm in I.T.

410
00:18:33,760 --> 00:18:34,930
Oh...

411
00:18:35,000 --> 00:18:36,260
You mean you're no an undercover agent,

412
00:18:36,330 --> 00:18:38,300
Like every other guy I've met this weekend?

413
00:18:39,530 --> 00:18:40,630
Nope.

414
00:18:40,700 --> 00:18:42,500
Just a regular old computer guy.

415
00:18:42,560 --> 00:18:44,430
You?

416
00:18:44,500 --> 00:18:45,800
Dental school.

417
00:18:45,860 --> 00:18:47,500
My last year.

418
00:18:47,560 --> 00:18:48,660
Wow.

419
00:18:48,730 --> 00:18:49,900
You've got great teeth,by the way.

420
00:18:49,960 --> 00:18:51,430
Thanks.

421
00:18:51,500 --> 00:18:54,060
You've got great...

422
00:18:55,960 --> 00:18:57,600
Everything.

423
00:19:00,900 --> 00:19:02,230
She's trying to get to Kitt,I know it.

424
00:19:02,300 --> 00:19:03,630
Well,then you'd think she'd show up

425
00:19:03,700 --> 00:19:04,760
When he's here.

426
00:19:04,830 --> 00:19:06,730
Well,Mike took Kitt on an unscheduled mission,

427
00:19:06,800 --> 00:19:09,330
And now she's treading water till they get back.

428
00:19:09,400 --> 00:19:10,500
What do you think she wants with him?

429
00:19:11,800 --> 00:19:13,700
Tess and I were fierce rivals.

430
00:19:13,760 --> 00:19:15,260
I hear you were more than that.

431
00:19:17,130 --> 00:19:19,760
You know,it's okay to tell me about your girlfriends,dad.

432
00:19:19,830 --> 00:19:20,930
She wasn't my girlfriend.

433
00:19:37,130 --> 00:19:38,400
Well...

434
00:19:38,460 --> 00:19:40,430
That's it for me.

435
00:19:40,500 --> 00:19:42,030
Yeah,i'm kind of tapped out too.

436
00:19:43,500 --> 00:19:44,860
Well,You lost quite a bit.

437
00:19:47,760 --> 00:19:49,230
Well,it was nice meeting you.

438
00:19:49,300 --> 00:19:50,860
Yeah.

439
00:19:52,700 --> 00:19:54,330
You too.

440
00:19:56,430 --> 00:19:57,500
Well...

441
00:19:58,730 --> 00:19:59,930
Bye.

442
00:20:01,030 --> 00:20:02,030
Bye.

443
00:20:05,660 --> 00:20:07,460
Oh,come on.

444
00:20:08,760 --> 00:20:10,400
Idiot.

445
00:20:10,460 --> 00:20:11,730
Hey,zoe,where's mike?

446
00:20:11,800 --> 00:20:13,400
Mike's with kitt. He's fine.

447
00:20:13,460 --> 00:20:14,430
Where are you?

448
00:20:14,500 --> 00:20:15,630
I'm in the casino.

449
00:20:15,700 --> 00:20:16,800
I need some advice.

450
00:20:16,860 --> 00:20:18,030
Did you lose all your money?

451
00:20:18,100 --> 00:20:19,500
Don't go to the ATM.

452
00:20:19,560 --> 00:20:21,300
Just go to bed and start over in the morning.

453
00:20:21,360 --> 00:20:22,530
I met a girl.

454
00:20:22,600 --> 00:20:24,860
They're called hookers,Billy.

455
00:20:24,930 --> 00:20:26,930
No,a real girl.

456
00:20:27,000 --> 00:20:29,030
Does she have two heads?

457
00:20:29,100 --> 00:20:30,660
No,only one and it's beautiful.

458
00:20:30,730 --> 00:20:32,330
Oh,what's wrong with her?

459
00:20:32,400 --> 00:20:34,260
Nothing,except she split.

460
00:20:34,330 --> 00:20:35,660
Of course she did.

461
00:20:35,730 --> 00:20:37,300
You were being you.

462
00:20:37,360 --> 00:20:40,530
Look,I think she really liked me.

463
00:20:40,600 --> 00:20:42,800
I just...I couldn't close.

464
00:20:42,860 --> 00:20:46,100
You screwed up vacation sex? That's pathetic.

465
00:20:46,160 --> 00:20:48,060
Is she staying at the hotel?

466
00:20:48,130 --> 00:20:49,700
- I think so.  - What's her name?

467
00:20:49,760 --> 00:20:51,130
- Courtney.  - Courtney what?

468
00:20:51,200 --> 00:20:53,630
I don't know. Never mind.

469
00:20:53,700 --> 00:20:55,400
Courtney Harshberger,2902.

470
00:20:55,460 --> 00:20:57,830
Courtney Rosenthal,717.

471
00:20:57,900 --> 00:21:00,560
There's a courtney flynn. In poolside 16.

472
00:21:00,630 --> 00:21:02,900
Yeah,she said something about going out to her room.

473
00:21:02,960 --> 00:21:04,100
Yeah,I think that's her.

474
00:21:04,160 --> 00:21:05,330
Getting her driver's license

475
00:21:05,400 --> 00:21:06,660
And credit card info now.

476
00:21:06,730 --> 00:21:08,100
Zoe,that's illegal.

477
00:21:08,160 --> 00:21:11,200
Since when has that been an issue?

478
00:21:11,260 --> 00:21:12,960
Dude,she is hot.

479
00:21:13,030 --> 00:21:14,960
I know!

480
00:21:15,030 --> 00:21:16,930
You listen to me,Billy morgan,

481
00:21:17,000 --> 00:21:18,730
You go find this Courtney Flynn,

482
00:21:18,800 --> 00:21:20,000
And you go make it happen.

483
00:21:40,300 --> 00:21:41,260
Hey.

484
00:21:41,330 --> 00:21:43,100
I was just coming back to look for you.

485
00:21:43,160 --> 00:21:45,100
I was just going to your room.

486
00:21:45,160 --> 00:21:47,130
How'd you know where my room was?

487
00:21:47,200 --> 00:21:49,060
I...

488
00:21:49,130 --> 00:21:50,260
I don't.

489
00:21:50,330 --> 00:21:51,530
I guess I was just gonna roam the halls

490
00:21:51,600 --> 00:21:52,800
Looking for dental floss

491
00:21:52,860 --> 00:21:54,330
On the discarded room service trays.

492
00:21:54,400 --> 00:21:55,600
Dental joke.

493
00:21:55,660 --> 00:21:57,160
That's lame.

494
00:21:57,230 --> 00:21:59,300
Yeah.

495
00:21:59,360 --> 00:22:02,400
So I gotta take a break from the tables for a while.

496
00:22:02,460 --> 00:22:03,900
Yeah,me too.

497
00:22:03,960 --> 00:22:05,330
Can you believe my big move

498
00:22:05,400 --> 00:22:06,830
Was to come to Vegas and count cards

499
00:22:06,900 --> 00:22:08,300
And I chickened out?

500
00:22:08,360 --> 00:22:10,260
Well,isn't that illegal anyway?

501
00:22:10,330 --> 00:22:11,800
Uh,it's like going to a restaurant

502
00:22:11,860 --> 00:22:13,160
With no shirt on.

503
00:22:13,230 --> 00:22:15,400
It's not illegal,but they can kick you out.

504
00:22:15,460 --> 00:22:18,260
No shirt,no shoes,

505
00:22:18,330 --> 00:22:19,660
No dice.

506
00:22:19,730 --> 00:22:21,030
Fast times at ridgemont high.

507
00:22:21,100 --> 00:22:22,000
It's my favorite movie.

508
00:22:22,060 --> 00:22:23,700
Mine too.

509
00:22:25,860 --> 00:22:27,630
So...

510
00:22:27,700 --> 00:22:29,730
I was thinking...

511
00:22:29,800 --> 00:22:33,000
You wanna hang out?

512
00:22:33,060 --> 00:22:34,260
Okay.

513
00:22:53,460 --> 00:22:56,160
We had a bet.

514
00:22:56,230 --> 00:22:57,730
Who?

515
00:22:57,800 --> 00:22:59,200
Me and Aquarius.

516
00:22:59,260 --> 00:23:01,600
I bet that you'd ask her to dance first.

517
00:23:01,660 --> 00:23:04,030
You lost.

518
00:23:10,460 --> 00:23:13,500
You guys get cable in here?

519
00:23:16,530 --> 00:23:18,930
Dork,what are you doing?

520
00:23:19,000 --> 00:23:21,800
I'm easing into it.

521
00:23:21,860 --> 00:23:23,400
Answer the door. I sent you something.

522
00:23:23,460 --> 00:23:24,760
Are you on the phone?

523
00:23:24,830 --> 00:23:28,430
Uh,uhh...

524
00:23:28,500 --> 00:23:30,060
I just called room service.

525
00:23:30,130 --> 00:23:32,130
I had them send some things over.

526
00:23:35,400 --> 00:23:36,760
Whoa.

527
00:23:41,500 --> 00:23:43,300
You sure got here quick.

528
00:23:47,060 --> 00:23:49,300
A little strawberries and champagne.

529
00:23:49,360 --> 00:23:51,700
And,uh,some chocolate sauce.

530
00:23:51,760 --> 00:23:52,960
And...

531
00:23:53,030 --> 00:23:56,530
Whip-whipped cream.

532
00:23:56,600 --> 00:23:57,830
Whoa.

533
00:23:57,900 --> 00:23:58,930
Mmm.

534
00:24:02,260 --> 00:24:05,330
I've been waiting all day for this.

535
00:24:26,330 --> 00:24:27,260
Virgo.

536
00:24:27,330 --> 00:24:28,360
What's up?

537
00:24:28,430 --> 00:24:29,660
Hey,your friend Kitt,

538
00:24:29,730 --> 00:24:31,000
The one who pulled the driver's license thing?

539
00:24:31,060 --> 00:24:32,300
Yeah,what about kitt?

540
00:24:32,360 --> 00:24:34,300
If she's single,I'm available.

541
00:24:34,360 --> 00:24:36,160
If you only knew,Leo.

542
00:24:40,100 --> 00:24:41,760
You all right?

543
00:24:41,830 --> 00:24:43,360
Uh,yeah,you know,I'm fine.

544
00:24:43,430 --> 00:24:44,830
I'm just,uh...

545
00:24:44,900 --> 00:24:47,060
Just thinking about the next score,that's all.

546
00:24:47,130 --> 00:24:48,930
So am I.

547
00:24:49,000 --> 00:24:51,760
You ready to tell me?

548
00:24:51,830 --> 00:24:53,630
You're looking at it.

549
00:24:53,700 --> 00:24:55,160
we're gonna hit the casino.

550
00:24:58,560 --> 00:24:59,600
He's gonna rob his own casino.

551
00:24:59,660 --> 00:25:00,630
That doesn't make sense.

552
00:25:00,700 --> 00:25:01,660
He's about to lose his job.

553
00:25:01,730 --> 00:25:02,900
He robs the place,

554
00:25:02,960 --> 00:25:04,300
the cops are bound to look at him hard.

555
00:25:04,360 --> 00:25:06,230
it is possible he's trying to solidify

556
00:25:06,300 --> 00:25:07,700
his current position.

557
00:25:07,760 --> 00:25:09,060
Explain,Kitt.

558
00:25:09,130 --> 00:25:11,060
If a robbery was to take place in the casino,

559
00:25:11,130 --> 00:25:13,030
and capricorn arrived in time to foil it,

560
00:25:13,100 --> 00:25:14,530
his supervisors would be more likely

561
00:25:14,600 --> 00:25:16,030
to trust him

562
00:25:16,100 --> 00:25:18,000
and possibly keep him on in his current position.

563
00:25:18,060 --> 00:25:20,460
But if he busts the zodiac crew in the process,

564
00:25:20,530 --> 00:25:22,560
The whole plan falls apart.

565
00:25:22,630 --> 00:25:23,660
Interesting scenario,

566
00:25:23,730 --> 00:25:25,230
But there has to be more to it.

567
00:25:25,300 --> 00:25:26,900
Regardless,why don't we jus take the whole gang down now?

568
00:25:26,960 --> 00:25:28,030
Not enough evidence.

569
00:25:28,100 --> 00:25:29,500
What about the anchorage job?

570
00:25:29,560 --> 00:25:30,800
No witnesses,no fingerprints.

571
00:25:30,860 --> 00:25:33,560
We have to catch them in the act.

572
00:25:33,630 --> 00:25:36,200
So tell me about Kitt's propulsion system.

573
00:25:36,260 --> 00:25:38,460
Well,I'd love to,Tess,but I can't.

574
00:25:38,530 --> 00:25:40,700
Is it a conventional internal combustion engine

575
00:25:40,760 --> 00:25:42,000
Or something new?

576
00:25:42,060 --> 00:25:43,330
Come on.

577
00:25:43,400 --> 00:25:45,460
Right now the SSC has the potential

578
00:25:45,530 --> 00:25:47,400
To look like another major boondoggle.

579
00:25:47,460 --> 00:25:51,060
You gotta give me something to work with here.

580
00:25:51,130 --> 00:25:52,400
What about oil?

581
00:25:52,460 --> 00:25:54,200
Uh,transmission fluid brake fluid,

582
00:25:54,260 --> 00:25:55,800
Where are those disposed of?

583
00:25:55,860 --> 00:25:57,430
Well,fluids that we use for kitt

584
00:25:57,500 --> 00:25:59,100
are specially designed to withstand

585
00:25:59,160 --> 00:26:00,760
Infinitely higher tolerances

586
00:26:00,830 --> 00:26:02,460
Than the ordinary automobile product

587
00:26:02,530 --> 00:26:04,100
And last up to

588
00:26:04,160 --> 00:26:06,100
1,000% longer.

589
00:26:06,160 --> 00:26:09,160
Doesn't answer my question.

590
00:26:09,230 --> 00:26:12,200
Well,that'll have to do.

591
00:26:12,260 --> 00:26:14,860
Charles...

592
00:26:14,930 --> 00:26:17,630
What's happening between us aside,

593
00:26:17,700 --> 00:26:20,760
Things don't look good for you here.

594
00:26:20,830 --> 00:26:22,600
Now,until I get the full picture,

595
00:26:22,660 --> 00:26:26,700
The SSC is in major carbon deficit.

596
00:26:28,960 --> 00:26:30,900
Okay.

597
00:26:30,960 --> 00:26:34,060
Let me tell you about Kitt.

598
00:27:02,900 --> 00:27:04,530
No,no,no,this isn't your toothbrush.

599
00:27:04,600 --> 00:27:06,200
I carry one with me at all times.

600
00:27:06,260 --> 00:27:07,960
See,red.

601
00:27:08,030 --> 00:27:09,960
That's not why I'm crying.

602
00:27:10,030 --> 00:27:12,500
Oh,I thought last nig was wonderful.

603
00:27:12,560 --> 00:27:14,900
It's not you,it's me.

604
00:27:14,960 --> 00:27:16,860
Not the first time I've heard that.

605
00:27:16,930 --> 00:27:20,300
I owe over $100,000 in student loans.

606
00:27:20,360 --> 00:27:21,430
I got a check

607
00:27:21,500 --> 00:27:23,060
For $20,000 last week,

608
00:27:23,130 --> 00:27:27,200
And I blew it all at the blackjack table.

609
00:27:27,260 --> 00:27:30,100
it was supposed to be for tuition.

610
00:27:30,160 --> 00:27:32,200
Wow.

611
00:27:32,260 --> 00:27:33,660
That was dumb.

612
00:27:35,960 --> 00:27:39,860
You know how I told you my dad was really rich?

613
00:27:39,930 --> 00:27:42,460
He's a bus driver.

614
00:27:44,560 --> 00:27:46,660
Last night was probably...

615
00:27:46,730 --> 00:27:49,260
No,last night was definitely

616
00:27:49,330 --> 00:27:52,830
The best night of my life.

617
00:27:52,900 --> 00:27:55,500
If you... if you're scamming me,Courtney,

618
00:27:55,560 --> 00:27:57,530
I swear I can't take it,it'll break my heart.

619
00:27:57,600 --> 00:27:59,900
No.

620
00:27:59,960 --> 00:28:03,030
I just screwed up,that's all.

621
00:28:03,100 --> 00:28:05,600
I promise.

622
00:28:08,500 --> 00:28:11,300
You remember yesterday when I said I was an I.T. Guy?

623
00:28:13,660 --> 00:28:15,700
I'm actually a secre government operative.

624
00:28:18,600 --> 00:28:21,030
Hmm,I have ways of checking.

625
00:28:25,160 --> 00:28:28,360
Where are you going?

626
00:28:28,430 --> 00:28:30,430
I'm going to get your money back.

627
00:28:33,700 --> 00:28:35,260
Corsica casino.

628
00:28:35,330 --> 00:28:37,100
40,000 square feet of gaming space.

629
00:28:37,160 --> 00:28:39,900
160 armed personnel,

630
00:28:39,960 --> 00:28:41,230
422 surveillance cameras.

631
00:28:41,300 --> 00:28:42,530
Now on a normal day,

632
00:28:42,600 --> 00:28:44,160
there's a million dollars cash

633
00:28:44,230 --> 00:28:45,960
In the cage at any given time.

634
00:28:46,030 --> 00:28:47,560
If you look behind you,

635
00:28:47,630 --> 00:28:48,830
this beautiful gentleman,

636
00:28:48,900 --> 00:28:51,830
this sad-looking man is Artie Yamtov.

637
00:28:51,900 --> 00:28:53,200
He used to be a big-time hack

638
00:28:53,260 --> 00:28:54,530
Who's actually a pretty good little thief.

639
00:28:54,600 --> 00:28:56,660
He fell on some hard times,

640
00:28:56,730 --> 00:28:58,260
but hey,he loves his kids.

641
00:28:58,330 --> 00:29:00,160
So in exchange for taking the fall for us in this job,

642
00:29:00,230 --> 00:29:01,730
We're gonna pay out his family

643
00:29:01,800 --> 00:29:03,830
$250,000.

644
00:29:03,900 --> 00:29:05,560
So we rob your casino

645
00:29:05,630 --> 00:29:08,200
And nice guy Artie there becomes a convenient patsy,

646
00:29:08,260 --> 00:29:09,560
goes to state prison.

647
00:29:09,630 --> 00:29:10,530
Pretty much.

648
00:29:10,600 --> 00:29:11,760
I mean,you said yourself,

649
00:29:11,830 --> 00:29:12,800
There's only a million dollars in there.

650
00:29:12,860 --> 00:29:14,630
Yeah,how is that the score of a lifetime?

651
00:29:14,700 --> 00:29:16,030
Excellent question.

652
00:29:16,100 --> 00:29:17,060
My friends,

653
00:29:17,130 --> 00:29:18,430
Meet Mr. Shepherd Wong.

654
00:29:18,500 --> 00:29:21,360
Mr. Wong owns a factor in shanghai

655
00:29:21,430 --> 00:29:22,800
that makes boxes,

656
00:29:22,860 --> 00:29:25,600
The boxes that everything we buy from china comes in.

657
00:29:25,660 --> 00:29:26,930
Now,Mr. Wong

658
00:29:27,000 --> 00:29:28,560
is a very wealthy man,

659
00:29:28,630 --> 00:29:30,960
But unfortunately,he has a very serious Jones.

660
00:29:31,030 --> 00:29:32,900
He plays baccarat exclusively.

661
00:29:32,960 --> 00:29:34,460
Now by law,the cage has to have

662
00:29:34,560 --> 00:29:36,160
A dollar for dollar on hand

663
00:29:36,230 --> 00:29:37,560
To match his bets.

664
00:29:37,630 --> 00:29:38,760
How much?

665
00:29:38,830 --> 00:29:39,760
30 million.

666
00:29:39,830 --> 00:29:40,860
Now you're talking.

667
00:29:40,930 --> 00:29:42,430
Absolutely.

668
00:29:42,500 --> 00:29:44,330
Leo,I need you to disable the wired

669
00:29:44,400 --> 00:29:46,130
and wireless communication systems

670
00:29:46,200 --> 00:29:49,100
Both here and here.

671
00:29:49,160 --> 00:29:50,430
Done and done

672
00:29:50,500 --> 00:29:52,300
The security guards here and here at bay.

673
00:29:52,360 --> 00:29:53,800
Copy.

674
00:29:53,860 --> 00:29:55,900
All right,Scorpio,we need that key from the cage guard,okay?

675
00:29:55,960 --> 00:29:56,960
Can you handle that?

676
00:29:57,030 --> 00:29:58,330
Why can't you get that for us?

677
00:29:58,400 --> 00:29:59,630
Because it's a magnetic lock with rotating codes.

678
00:29:59,700 --> 00:30:01,400
I mean,the matching key

679
00:30:01,460 --> 00:30:03,160
Is given to the appropriate cage guard

680
00:30:03,230 --> 00:30:05,500
At the beginning of every shift.

681
00:30:05,560 --> 00:30:06,960
Aquarius,darling,I need you to load up the car,

682
00:30:07,030 --> 00:30:09,260
Put all the money in,and make sure you distract

683
00:30:09,330 --> 00:30:10,600
all these guards.

684
00:30:10,660 --> 00:30:12,430
Ooh,I dropped a contact lens,

685
00:30:12,500 --> 00:30:15,160
And this floor is so confusing.

686
00:30:16,530 --> 00:30:17,800
And last but not least,Virgo,

687
00:30:17,860 --> 00:30:18,830
I need you to cut the power,

688
00:30:18,900 --> 00:30:20,260
snag the key from Scorpio,

689
00:30:20,330 --> 00:30:22,530
Take down the cage,load up the cart,

690
00:30:22,600 --> 00:30:24,130
And exit through this side door right here.

691
00:30:24,200 --> 00:30:25,630
Piece of cake.

692
00:30:25,700 --> 00:30:27,260
When's all this go down?

693
00:30:27,330 --> 00:30:30,460
At shift change,1600 hours.

694
00:30:30,530 --> 00:30:32,460
Today?

695
00:30:32,530 --> 00:30:34,630
Today.

696
00:30:45,030 --> 00:30:46,900
This is gonna be tough.

697
00:30:46,960 --> 00:30:49,260
but you said,"piece of cake."

698
00:30:49,330 --> 00:30:51,960
Yeah,I had to make it look good in front of the others.

699
00:30:52,030 --> 00:30:53,100
It's called Bravado,Kitt.

700
00:30:53,160 --> 00:30:56,700
What's this area next to the slots?

701
00:30:56,760 --> 00:31:00,560
It is a game of chance called,"win this car."

702
00:31:00,630 --> 00:31:01,830
a new automobile is presented

703
00:31:01,900 --> 00:31:03,430
to the winner of a slot machine jackpot.

704
00:31:03,500 --> 00:31:05,560
It's got a straight line of sight to the cage.

705
00:31:05,630 --> 00:31:07,030
Hey,what's up?

706
00:31:07,100 --> 00:31:09,600
Courtney lost all of her student loan money playing blackjack.

707
00:31:09,660 --> 00:31:10,600
I'm getting it back for her.

708
00:31:10,660 --> 00:31:12,160
- How?  - Counting cards.

709
00:31:12,230 --> 00:31:14,660
I need to win 100 grand. Can I borrow some money?

710
00:31:14,730 --> 00:31:16,430
you meet a girl in vegas,

711
00:31:16,500 --> 00:31:17,700
She takes you home,

712
00:31:17,760 --> 00:31:18,830
And in the morning she tells you she needs 100 grand?

713
00:31:18,900 --> 00:31:19,930
Come on,Billy.

714
00:31:20,000 --> 00:31:21,560
Oh,you think she's grifting me.

715
00:31:21,630 --> 00:31:22,760
Why,because no girl could ever

716
00:31:22,830 --> 00:31:23,960
Like Billy Morgan that much,right?

717
00:31:24,030 --> 00:31:27,160
I'm not saying that.

718
00:31:27,230 --> 00:31:28,400
Just have Kitt run a check on her,is all.

719
00:31:28,460 --> 00:31:29,500
I don't want you to check her out.

720
00:31:29,560 --> 00:31:31,400
I believe her. Okay?

721
00:31:31,460 --> 00:31:33,630
- Okay.  - What's happening on your end?

722
00:31:33,700 --> 00:31:35,000
Michael is going to rob the casino.

723
00:31:35,060 --> 00:31:36,460
Whoa.

724
00:31:36,530 --> 00:31:39,000
Yeah,so you'd better hurry up and win.

725
00:31:48,160 --> 00:31:50,530
what do you have to say about this?

726
00:31:50,600 --> 00:31:52,100
I think somebody's wasting paper.

727
00:31:52,160 --> 00:31:54,030
It was stuffed under my pod room door.

728
00:31:54,100 --> 00:31:55,500
Oh,what can I tell you?

729
00:31:55,560 --> 00:31:57,700
Heart wants what the heart wants.

730
00:31:57,760 --> 00:32:02,330
You're acting like a little boy.

731
00:32:02,400 --> 00:32:04,230
Well,the problem around here is there's too much science,

732
00:32:04,300 --> 00:32:05,230
Not enough chemistry.

733
00:32:05,300 --> 00:32:09,000
Dad?

734
00:32:09,060 --> 00:32:10,730
Do you trust tess enough

735
00:32:10,800 --> 00:32:12,260
To show her Kitt's propulsion schematics?

736
00:32:12,330 --> 00:32:15,560
Sometimes you gotta take a chance.

737
00:32:44,560 --> 00:32:46,560
New vehicle going on casino floor!

738
00:32:46,630 --> 00:32:49,060
Let's go!

739
00:32:49,130 --> 00:32:55,100
Oh.

740
00:32:59,230 --> 00:33:00,300
Kitt.

741
00:33:00,360 --> 00:33:02,030
I have 50,000 in chips. I need your help.

742
00:33:02,100 --> 00:33:04,160
I have to win this hand.

743
00:33:04,230 --> 00:33:05,160
I need you to...

744
00:33:05,230 --> 00:33:06,630
I need you to access...

745
00:33:06,700 --> 00:33:08,060
Casino's surveillance camera

746
00:33:08,130 --> 00:33:09,360
And tell me what the dealer's hole card is.

747
00:33:09,430 --> 00:33:11,530
I am sorry,Billy,but I cannot assist you

748
00:33:11,600 --> 00:33:13,000
in cheating a legitimate business.

749
00:33:13,060 --> 00:33:14,830
But if it is any consolation,

750
00:33:14,900 --> 00:33:17,460
I believin you.

751
00:33:32,330 --> 00:33:36,760
Check's play.

752
00:33:39,630 --> 00:33:40,530
Hey,what's your name?

753
00:33:40,600 --> 00:33:42,000
Uh,Clarence.

754
00:33:42,060 --> 00:33:44,060
Clarence,your personal car. What do you drive?

755
00:33:44,130 --> 00:33:45,630
Uh,it's blue and it's old.

756
00:33:45,700 --> 00:33:47,760
I'll give you 20 grand for it.

757
00:33:47,830 --> 00:33:49,400
Sure.

758
00:33:49,460 --> 00:33:51,600
Leave it running by the side entrance in 15 minutes.

759
00:33:51,660 --> 00:33:54,060
Okay.

760
00:33:54,130 --> 00:33:55,530
I'm gonna need your jacket as well.

761
00:33:55,600 --> 00:33:56,630
Sure.

762
00:33:56,700 --> 00:33:58,600
Sir,you have 16.

763
00:33:58,660 --> 00:34:00,100
Hit or stand?

764
00:34:00,160 --> 00:34:01,960
You have 16.

765
00:34:08,530 --> 00:34:11,760
Hit or stand?

766
00:34:11,830 --> 00:34:13,930
- Hit.   - 21.

767
00:34:25,230 --> 00:34:30,100
Kitt I'm in position,Michael.

768
00:34:30,160 --> 00:34:32,360
Make sure your cameras are rolling on the entire crew.

769
00:34:32,430 --> 00:34:34,530
Carrie needs complete video documentation.

770
00:34:34,600 --> 00:34:36,530
I have a perfectline of sight,Michael.

771
00:34:36,600 --> 00:34:40,160
On my mark,fire your E.M.P. And zap the casino's power grid.

772
00:34:40,230 --> 00:34:41,760
Michael,the hotel has

773
00:34:41,830 --> 00:34:43,160
an off-site redundant backup system.

774
00:34:43,230 --> 00:34:45,500
You will only have 30 seconds of darkness.

775
00:34:45,560 --> 00:34:47,660
That's all I'm gonna need.

776
00:34:47,730 --> 00:34:48,830
Is that bravado again,Michael?

777
00:34:48,900 --> 00:34:50,100
my contact.

778
00:34:50,160 --> 00:34:55,130
No,Kitt. It's a fact.

779
00:34:55,200 --> 00:34:56,200
Excuse me.

780
00:34:56,260 --> 00:34:57,600
I dropped a contact. Can you help me?

781
00:34:57,660 --> 00:34:59,130
You new here?

782
00:34:59,200 --> 00:35:01,030
Yeah,it's my first day. I'm already losing things.

783
00:35:01,100 --> 00:35:02,000
Where do you think you lost it?

784
00:35:02,060 --> 00:35:03,060
Um,I think it's like,

785
00:35:03,130 --> 00:35:09,100
in this area.

786
00:35:16,960 --> 00:35:22,100
Michael,communication lines have been disabled.

787
00:35:23,600 --> 00:35:24,830
Grab some floor now!

788
00:35:24,900 --> 00:35:27,660
Get down!

789
00:35:27,730 --> 00:35:29,800
Kitt,it's showtime. E.M.P.

790
00:35:29,860 --> 00:35:31,560
Yes,Michael.

791
00:35:34,960 --> 00:35:36,660
Please remain calm.

792
00:35:36,730 --> 00:35:39,200
Backup systems will be coming on line momentarily.

793
00:35:39,260 --> 00:35:42,100
Please stay at your tables.

794
00:35:44,930 --> 00:35:47,030
Kitt?

795
00:35:47,100 --> 00:35:49,700
The E.M.P. may have demagnetized the key.

796
00:35:49,760 --> 00:35:51,330
Re-magnetize it,then.

797
00:35:51,400 --> 00:35:52,830
I am unable.

798
00:35:52,900 --> 00:35:54,130
22 seconds.

799
00:35:54,200 --> 00:35:55,560
Blow the cage,Kitt.

800
00:36:28,260 --> 00:36:28,330
What a rush.

801
00:36:40,700 --> 00:36:42,030
I was driving a '92 civic.

802
00:36:42,100 --> 00:36:47,800
You know the,uh,real virgo was really never that good.

803
00:36:52,700 --> 00:36:58,460
There's a radio signal coming from his left ear.

804
00:37:00,160 --> 00:37:01,700
Sorry,man.

805
00:37:01,760 --> 00:37:04,600
I really liked you.

806
00:37:04,660 --> 00:37:05,600
Everybody out.

807
00:37:05,660 --> 00:37:06,560
Come on,man.

808
00:37:06,630 --> 00:37:07,560
Everybody out!

809
00:37:07,630 --> 00:37:12,060
Let's go. Get out.

810
00:37:12,130 --> 00:37:14,260
Come on,man.

811
00:37:14,330 --> 00:37:18,100
How are you gonna explain all this?

812
00:37:18,160 --> 00:37:22,200
Explain what?

813
00:37:26,300 --> 00:37:28,560
I cannot contact Mike.

814
00:37:28,630 --> 00:37:31,800
Yeah,me neither.

815
00:37:31,860 --> 00:37:33,960
What's going on?

816
00:37:33,960 --> 00:37:39,900
Sorry,baby. I gotta go.

817
00:37:39,960 --> 00:37:44,730
I love you.

818
00:37:49,530 --> 00:37:50,630
Kitt.

819
00:37:50,700 --> 00:37:51,830
I think Mike's in trouble.

820
00:37:51,900 --> 00:37:53,900
If he's not with you,how did he get away?

821
00:37:53,960 --> 00:37:55,460
Michael drove off from the robbery

822
00:37:55,530 --> 00:37:58,000
in a blue '92 civic.

823
00:37:58,060 --> 00:37:59,130
Zoe,into vegas metro traffic.

824
00:37:59,200 --> 00:38:00,630
On it.

825
00:38:00,700 --> 00:38:01,830
Searching video for a blue '92ivic.

826
00:38:01,900 --> 00:38:03,700
Cross-reference with any vehicles

827
00:38:03,760 --> 00:38:06,460
With a corsica hotel logo.

828
00:38:06,530 --> 00:38:07,500
Got him.

829
00:38:07,560 --> 00:38:08,900
Industrial park,west of the city,

830
00:38:08,960 --> 00:38:10,460
Off desert inn road.

831
00:38:10,530 --> 00:38:12,600
Kitt?

832
00:38:12,660 --> 00:38:16,130
Attack mode.

833
00:38:16,200 --> 00:38:18,030
The police are on their way.

834
00:38:18,100 --> 00:38:19,630
Police.

835
00:38:19,700 --> 00:38:20,630
Yeah.

836
00:38:20,700 --> 00:38:21,660
I mean,I'm holding the man

837
00:38:21,730 --> 00:38:23,530
Who robbed the Corsica hotel and Casino

838
00:38:23,600 --> 00:38:24,730
till they arrive.

839
00:38:24,800 --> 00:38:27,230
Here's how it went down:

840
00:38:27,300 --> 00:38:29,060
You robbed the casino,

841
00:38:29,130 --> 00:38:30,460
You fled here to this empty warehouse

842
00:38:30,530 --> 00:38:32,760
to hide the cash until... What?

843
00:38:32,760 --> 00:38:34,530
Heat died down,am I right?

844
00:38:34,600 --> 00:38:38,060
But the brave chief of security followed the bad guy here,

845
00:38:38,130 --> 00:38:40,560
And surprised me while I was stashing the loot.

846
00:38:40,630 --> 00:38:44,560
And the would-be robber was... Fatally wounded.

847
00:38:44,630 --> 00:38:46,660
- Not a big fan of the fatal part.  - Really?

848
00:38:45,730 --> 00:38:48,130
Chief of security becomes stuff of local legend.

849
00:38:48,200 --> 00:38:49,930
I mean,who knows?

850
00:38:50,000 --> 00:38:51,000
Might be able to keep my job.

851
00:38:51,060 --> 00:38:54,030
Sorry.

852
00:38:54,100 --> 00:38:56,100
There's really no other way.

853
00:39:03,860 --> 00:39:08,230
All right. Oh,that's much better.

854
00:39:08,300 --> 00:39:10,330
Must feel pretty cool robbin a casino like this,huh,pal?

855
00:39:15,730 --> 00:39:17,700
Come to daddy.

856
00:39:17,760 --> 00:39:19,660
Marco!

857
00:39:19,730 --> 00:39:20,730
What,no polo?

858
00:39:22,030 --> 00:39:23,760
Come on.

859
00:39:23,830 --> 00:39:25,700
There you are.

860
00:39:30,400 --> 00:39:32,530
Kitt,xenons!

861
00:39:32,600 --> 00:39:34,460
Ahh,my eyes!

862
00:39:41,860 --> 00:39:43,300
Hey.

863
00:39:43,360 --> 00:39:45,000
Did you win?

864
00:39:45,060 --> 00:39:45,960
What?

865
00:39:46,030 --> 00:39:48,400
Blackjack. Did you win?

866
00:39:49,460 --> 00:39:52,600
I got pretty lucky.

867
00:39:54,600 --> 00:39:58,500
I'm the latest iteration of the knight industries 3000.

868
00:39:58,560 --> 00:40:01,200
It's a Kitt 2.0.

869
00:40:01,260 --> 00:40:03,430
Next-generation shell,

870
00:40:03,500 --> 00:40:07,060
Combination hydrogen-electric hybrid propulsion system,

871
00:40:07,130 --> 00:40:09,000
Integrated neural network,

872
00:40:09,060 --> 00:40:11,160
64 core processor.

873
00:40:11,230 --> 00:40:14,500
Ultimately efficient,completely self-contained.

874
00:40:14,560 --> 00:40:20,030
Eminently green. Full specs. On paper.

875
00:40:20,100 --> 00:40:23,860
Well,he is marvelous,Charles,absolutely beautiful.

876
00:40:23,930 --> 00:40:26,000
Thank you,Dr. Landafly.

877
00:40:26,060 --> 00:40:28,760
My report.

878
00:40:28,830 --> 00:40:29,860
Oh.

879
00:40:29,930 --> 00:40:31,560
Due to Kitt' extreme efficiency,

880
00:40:31,630 --> 00:40:34,360
the ssc actually registers a carbon credit.

881
00:40:34,430 --> 00:40:36,460
Well,if this data ends up in popular science,

882
00:40:36,530 --> 00:40:38,330
I'll know where to find you.

883
00:40:38,400 --> 00:40:39,960
You can find me at the marriott.

884
00:40:40,030 --> 00:40:43,160
Room 1706. I'll see you tonight.

885
00:40:50,330 --> 00:40:51,730
Great job,Kitt.

886
00:40:51,800 --> 00:40:53,360
Thank you,Dr. Graiman.

887
00:40:53,430 --> 00:40:56,100
But the specifications you presented to Dr. Landafly

888
00:40:56,160 --> 00:40:58,100
were completely inaccurate.

889
00:40:58,160 --> 00:40:59,930
Absolutely correct,Kitt.

890
00:41:00,000 --> 00:41:01,600
That means you do not trust her.

891
00:41:01,660 --> 00:41:05,030
Yet you plan to meet her at her hotel.

892
00:41:05,100 --> 00:41:06,260
Correct again.

893
00:41:06,330 --> 00:41:08,230
I do not understand.

894
00:41:08,300 --> 00:41:13,130
One day,Kitt. One day you will.

895
00:41:13,200 --> 00:41:17,930
So? Tell you about the girl.

896
00:41:18,000 --> 00:41:19,660
Who? Courtney?

897
00:41:19,730 --> 00:41:22,200
Yes,Courtney.

898
00:41:22,260 --> 00:41:24,630
There's really not that much to tell.

899
00:41:24,700 --> 00:41:26,230
Suffice to say

900
00:41:26,300 --> 00:41:28,230
Billy played a few hands,downed a couple beers,

901
00:41:28,300 --> 00:41:29,700
And saved my butt when it needed saving.

902
00:41:29,760 --> 00:41:32,500
Mission accomplished.

903
00:41:35,100 --> 00:41:36,630
We figured you'd say that.

904
00:41:36,700 --> 00:41:40,200
Kitt,play back video of Billy leaving the casino.

905
00:41:40,260 --> 00:41:42,830
I am afraid I cannot. It has been password-protected.

906
00:41:42,900 --> 00:41:46,130
Oh...

907
00:41:46,200 --> 00:41:47,700
Rats.

908
00:41:47,760 --> 00:41:48,930
Oh,come on.

909
00:41:49,000 --> 00:41:51,130
See,ladies,what happens in Vegas stays in...

910
00:41:51,200 --> 00:41:52,130
Kitt.

911
00:41:52,200 --> 00:41:53,430
Aww. Come