1
00:00:01,490 --> 00:00:03,000
why do we fight? 

2
00:00:03,000 --> 00:00:05,000
what is that thing deep within each of us,

3
00:00:05,000 --> 00:00:08,080
that compels us to settle this disagreements with our fists?

4
00:00:08,380 --> 00:00:11,000
<i>Whatever it is,it's there</i> <i>right from the beginning.</i>

5
00:00:11,100 --> 00:00:13,100
Okay,okay,okay.Stop fighting!

6
00:00:13,430 --> 00:00:13,810
Why?

7
00:00:14,480 --> 00:00:16,750
Because it's stupid  and juvenile.

8
00:00:16,750 --> 00:00:19,210
We're six. We are stupid and juvenile.

9
00:00:22,740 --> 00:00:25,280
<i>Kids,I've only been</i> <i>in one fight in my life.</i>

10
00:00:25,280 --> 00:00:27,200
<i>And this is the story</i> <i>of how it happened.</i>

11
00:00:27,400 --> 00:00:30,160
<i>Now,as you know,I recently</i> <i>had been left at the altar.</i>

12
00:00:30,160 --> 00:00:32,290
<i>And the worst thing about</i> <i>getting left at e altar?</i>

13
00:00:32,290 --> 00:00:34,770
<i>I mean,aside from actually</i> <i>getting left at the altar,</i>

14
00:00:34,770 --> 00:00:36,400
<i>was what came next.</i>

15
00:00:36,400 --> 00:00:40,220
<i>A steady unrelenting</i> <i>unbearable stream of pity.</i>

16
00:00:40,220 --> 00:00:42,150
Vodka cranberry. Gin and tonic.

17
00:00:44,730 --> 00:00:46,010
Scotch and soda.

18
00:00:48,330 --> 00:00:49,520
Um,thank you.

19
00:00:52,730 --> 00:00:54,140
Could I see a menu?

20
00:00:54,140 --> 00:00:57,820
Ted,I'm going to go get you a menu...

21
00:00:58,120 --> 00:01:01,450
but I promise you i will come back.

22
00:01:04,600 --> 00:01:07,060
Okay,we have to start  going someplace else.

23
00:01:07,060 --> 00:01:10,010
At this bar,I'm always going to be the guy who got left at the altar.

24
00:01:10,010 --> 00:01:11,280
That sucks!

25
00:01:11,280 --> 00:01:13,520
Good times.

26
00:01:13,520 --> 00:01:14,930
Uh-oh. We lost Barney.

27
00:01:14,930 --> 00:01:15,750
What do you mean?

28
00:01:15,750 --> 00:01:18,140
There's a girl over there in a tight red sweater.

29
00:01:18,140 --> 00:01:20,400
So he's not listening  to a word anyone's saying.

30
00:01:20,400 --> 00:01:21,210
Right,Barney?

31
00:01:21,210 --> 00:01:22,770
Give me a break!

32
00:01:22,770 --> 00:01:23,880
See,he out a while back

33
00:01:23,880 --> 00:01:25,780
he could fake an entire  conversation just by saying

34
00:01:25,780 --> 00:01:28,860
titles of black sitcoms from the 70's and 80's.

35
00:01:28,860 --> 00:01:30,470
What's happening?

36
00:01:30,470 --> 00:01:31,210
Hey,Barney,

37
00:01:31,500 --> 00:01:33,430
want to go upstairs  and do stuff to me

38
00:01:33,430 --> 00:01:35,110
that I won't even let Marshall do?

39
00:01:35,390 --> 00:01:37,400
Huh-- different strokes.

40
00:01:39,740 --> 00:01:41,330
What the hell is this?!

41
00:01:41,330 --> 00:01:43,130
<i>I've told you kids </i> <i>about Doug,right?</i>

42
00:01:43,130 --> 00:01:44,570
<i>I haven't? Oh,well...</i>

43
00:01:45,580 --> 00:01:47,690
<i>Doug Martin was a</i> <i>bartender at MacLaren's.</i>

44
00:01:47,900 --> 00:01:49,520
<i>He was always</i> <i>kind of around.</i>

45
00:01:49,720 --> 00:01:50,960
Have... you met Ted?

46
00:01:51,130 --> 00:01:52,710
What? No,no,no. We're not  playing "Have you met Ted?"

47
00:01:52,900 --> 00:01:53,310
Am I dead?

48
00:01:54,850 --> 00:01:55,400
Am I dead?

49
00:01:56,010 --> 00:01:56,380
Tonight...

50
00:01:58,000 --> 00:01:58,850
I pick up a lesbian.

51
00:01:59,690 --> 00:02:01,900
<i>Anyway，three things you</i> <i>need to know about Doug.</i>

52
00:02:02,570 --> 00:02:05,260
<i>The first thing is that Doug</i>,  <i>had a bit of a violent streak.</i>

53
00:02:05,260 --> 00:02:06,880
...just crumbled,so he's on the ground,right?

54
00:02:06,880 --> 00:02:08,440
And we're just kicking him! 

55
00:02:08,440 --> 00:02:10,740
He's making that face,all shaking.

56
00:02:11,390 --> 00:02:14,200
So,anyway,what we did was we left him there.

57
00:02:14,200 --> 00:02:15,670
Top you off?

58
00:02:17,220 --> 00:02:20,070
<i>The second thing is that</i> <i>he was weird about his hair.</i>

59
00:02:21,270 --> 00:02:22,250
What?

60
00:02:22,250 --> 00:02:23,630
What?

61
00:02:23,630 --> 00:02:25,790
Are you looking at my hair?

62
00:02:25,790 --> 00:02:28,440
Uh,no,sir. I-I was not.

63
00:02:28,440 --> 00:02:29,360
It's a toupee.

64
00:02:31,190 --> 00:02:33,190
Is that funny? You want to laugh it up? 

65
00:02:33,190 --> 00:02:34,390
Is it funny,guy? Is it?

66
00:02:34,630 --> 00:02:36,580
I'll tell you what,why don't you,why don't you grab it?

67
00:02:36,580 --> 00:02:37,590
-Excuse me? -Go ahead,grab it.

68
00:02:37,590 --> 00:02:40,260
Grab it right off my head. Go ahead.

69
00:02:40,460 --> 00:02:41,770
Huh,you don't want grab it? come on.

70
00:02:42,420 --> 00:02:44,190
Come on,go ahead and grab it

71
00:02:44,190 --> 00:02:45,290
Want to grab it off my head?

72
00:02:45,290 --> 00:02:46,790
Grab my toupee right off my head.

73
00:02:53,240 --> 00:02:54,430
I like you guys!

74
00:02:55,030 --> 00:02:57,760
<i>But the third thing is that he</i> <i>was very loyal to his regulars.</i>

75
00:02:57,970 --> 00:02:59,850
Hey-hey! There they are!

76
00:02:59,850 --> 00:03:00,910
Hey,you guys want your booth?

77
00:03:00,910 --> 00:03:02,710
Oh,no. We're fine over here.

78
00:03:02,710 --> 00:03:03,570
Yeah? Yeah? Yeah.

79
00:03:03,570 --> 00:03:04,870
<i>Maybe a little too loyal.</i>

80
00:03:04,870 --> 00:03:06,530
Oh,no,it's fine,it's fine.

81
00:03:06,530 --> 00:03:07,950
Okay,you two lovebirds!

82
00:03:07,950 --> 00:03:09,890
Let's take this somewhere else, this booth's reserved.

83
00:03:10,690 --> 00:03:12,720
Let's go! Now! Come on!

84
00:03:12,720 --> 00:03:14,160
Let's see some hustle,Father.up you get.

85
00:03:14,160 --> 00:03:16,030
Okay,guys, here we are

86
00:03:16,230 --> 00:03:17,830
<i>So,that's Doug.</i>

87
00:03:18,610 --> 00:03:19,520
What the hell is this?!

88
00:03:19,850 --> 00:03:21,510
Oh,um,well,some guys are sitting in our booth.

89
00:03:21,510 --> 00:03:22,780
But you know what? this is fine.

90
00:03:26,980 --> 00:03:28,380
Let's go, i'll take care of it.

91
00:03:29,760 --> 00:03:31,300
Oh,boy,there he goes.

92
00:03:38,560 --> 00:03:40,780
Ladies,if you'll please adjourn to your usual booth.

93
00:03:40,780 --> 00:03:43,130
Gentlemen,I will require your assistance outside.

94
00:03:43,130 --> 00:03:44,610
Our assistance with what?

95
00:03:44,610 --> 00:03:46,520
We're going to go out in the  alley and fight those guys.

96
00:03:47,750 --> 00:03:49,140
What's happening now?

97
00:04:03,600 --> 00:04:04,770
I'm sorry,did you just  say we were gonna...

98
00:04:04,770 --> 00:04:07,750
Look,those guys are being inconsiderate,okay?

99
00:04:07,750 --> 00:04:09,030
So we're going to go outside

100
00:04:09,030 --> 00:04:10,650
and cave in their skulls,okay?

101
00:04:10,650 --> 00:04:12,170
This will be fun!

102
00:04:14,870 --> 00:04:19,200
He wants us to fight? like,with our hands and stuff?

103
00:04:19,200 --> 00:04:21,950
And feet maybe? I don't know what the rules are.

104
00:04:21,950 --> 00:04:24,900
wow,a fight.should we go out there?

105
00:04:24,900 --> 00:04:25,830
Come on,Ted.

106
00:04:25,830 --> 00:04:28,230
There's only three things you'll ever see me fight

107
00:04:28,230 --> 00:04:30,200
the stubborn clasp of a bra,

108
00:04:30,200 --> 00:04:32,200
Sexual harassment charges-- nine for nine--

109
00:04:34,240 --> 00:04:36,820
And the urge to vomit when I see someone wearing 

110
00:04:37,080 --> 00:04:39,040
brown shoes with a black suit.

111
00:04:40,920 --> 00:04:41,510
Marshall?

112
00:04:41,730 --> 00:04:42,850
Dude,fighting is for losers

113
00:04:42,850 --> 00:04:44,360
We're civilized guys.

114
00:04:44,360 --> 00:04:46,150
Civilized guys don't fight.

115
00:04:46,150 --> 00:04:47,650
Unless it's with lightsabers.

116
00:04:47,650 --> 00:04:49,330
But that's l to five years away,so...

117
00:04:49,330 --> 00:04:50,510
Well,that not true.

118
00:04:51,010 --> 00:04:52,670
Robin,I'm on the forums every day.

119
00:04:52,880 --> 00:04:54,310
Three to five Thanksgiving from now,

120
00:04:54,500 --> 00:04:56,260
I'm going to be carving the turkey with Old Green.

121
00:04:58,130 --> 00:05:01,720
No,I'm saying there are  plenty of legitimate reasons to get in a fight

122
00:05:01,720 --> 00:05:03,920
It might not be pretty,but in certain situations,

123
00:05:03,920 --> 00:05:05,740
you gotta do what you gotta do.

124
00:05:05,740 --> 00:05:08,580
Right,I forgot.she thinks fighting's sexy.

125
00:05:08,580 --> 00:05:11,150
No,I do not! a lot...

126
00:05:12,470 --> 00:05:14,430
Look,I come from a culture of hockey players.

127
00:05:14,430 --> 00:05:18,500
If a guy can throw down,it's somewhat way hot.

128
00:05:19,000 --> 00:05:21,120
And scars,hello!

129
00:05:21,120 --> 00:05:23,530
If a guy's got a scar, he's got a Robin.

130
00:05:23,530 --> 00:05:26,020
And if he's missing teeth?  I'm missing my pants.

131
00:05:27,940 --> 00:05:29,890
I'm missing my wisdom teeth.

132
00:05:30,690 --> 00:05:32,440
Outpatient procedure.

133
00:05:32,440 --> 00:05:33,940
Local anesthesia.

134
00:05:33,940 --> 00:05:35,550
Whatever.It ain't a thing.

135
00:05:37,230 --> 00:05:38,630
Look,maybe we should  go out there.

136
00:05:38,630 --> 00:05:41,900
I can't believe we're even having this discussion.

137
00:05:41,900 --> 00:05:45,030
Ted you're 30, you're too old to act like this.

138
00:05:45,030 --> 00:05:48,800
I was 30 and in those 30 years  I'd been punched once.

139
00:05:48,800 --> 00:05:51,380
There's a very simple explana...

140
00:05:51,380 --> 00:05:53,320
There was that thing at camp.

141
00:05:53,320 --> 00:05:56,140
Today we're going to braid friendship bracelets.

142
00:05:57,810 --> 00:05:59,590
In college I studied some Kung Fu.

143
00:06:05,840 --> 00:06:07,160
And well there  was some other stuff.

144
00:06:12,240 --> 00:06:14,280
The thing with the goat wasn't for another few months.

145
00:06:14,640 --> 00:06:16,330
The point is I had never been in a fight.

146
00:06:16,330 --> 00:06:17,550
I'm going out there.

147
00:06:17,550 --> 00:06:18,400
No!

148
00:06:18,760 --> 00:06:20,080
Listen to me,please trust me

149
00:06:20,080 --> 00:06:21,340
I've been in plenty of fights.

150
00:06:21,340 --> 00:06:23,210
It's really nothing to be proud of.

151
00:06:23,210 --> 00:06:25,830
Who did you get in a fight with?

152
00:06:25,930 --> 00:06:27,600
My brothers.

153
00:06:29,400 --> 00:06:30,990
Yes I'm sure that was quite a rumble

154
00:06:30,990 --> 00:06:33,340
in the Eriksen rums room.

155
00:06:34,000 --> 00:06:35,710
I love brotherly horseplay!

156
00:06:35,710 --> 00:06:36,660
Here comes the tickle monster!

157
00:06:37,630 --> 00:06:38,860
Noogie patrol!

158
00:06:40,000 --> 00:06:41,990
Wait,wait,wait! Timesies! Timesies!

159
00:06:43,450 --> 00:06:44,120
Cocoa break.

160
00:06:47,800 --> 00:06:49,360
Oh,cocoa break.

161
00:06:51,310 --> 00:06:53,630
Okay it's clobbering time.

162
00:06:53,630 --> 00:06:56,100
Ted don't do this, you're a nice guy.

163
00:06:56,350 --> 00:06:57,900
That's your best quality.

164
00:06:57,900 --> 00:06:58,930
Is it?

165
00:06:58,930 --> 00:07:00,490
'Cause I seem to remember this nice guy

166
00:07:00,490 --> 00:07:03,340
getting dumped by his fiance for a Tae Kwon Do instructor.

167
00:07:03,340 --> 00:07:06,120
Look this may sound crazy but I think I need to do this.

168
00:07:06,300 --> 00:07:08,700
I-I think this is an experience I need to have.

169
00:07:09,980 --> 00:07:10,570
I'm going.

170
00:07:15,070 --> 00:07:15,770
Me too!

171
00:07:18,690 --> 00:07:19,120
Guys...

172
00:07:19,830 --> 00:07:21,050
take a good look at this face

173
00:07:21,560 --> 00:07:22,700
because the next time you see it

174
00:07:22,890 --> 00:07:26,780
it will be disfigured in the hottest possible way.

175
00:07:26,780 --> 00:07:29,890
Because that's who I am, I'm a man.

176
00:07:29,890 --> 00:07:34,230
I like to fight and mix it up and get all dirty.

177
00:07:34,730 --> 00:07:36,210
Can you find a wood hanger for this?

178
00:07:41,230 --> 00:07:42,410
Whoa, what happened here?

179
00:07:42,700 --> 00:07:43,870
I know, right?

180
00:07:43,870 --> 00:07:46,710
Who's not looking at my toupee now huh?!

181
00:07:46,710 --> 00:07:47,960
Look what we did to these guys!

182
00:07:47,960 --> 00:07:49,500
-"We?"  -Yeah  "we."

183
00:07:49,500 --> 00:07:51,410
Come on, man. we're a good team.

184
00:07:51,710 --> 00:07:53,160
Nice work boys! We did it!

185
00:07:53,460 --> 00:07:54,810
No, no, no, you did it.

186
00:07:54,810 --> 00:07:56,090
We didn't do anything.

187
00:07:57,000 --> 00:07:59,850
Okay, yeah, yeah, sure. I just beat up three guys by myself.

188
00:08:00,950 --> 00:08:02,180
You guys. That's good.

189
00:08:02,180 --> 00:08:03,980
You and you--

190
00:08:04,980 --> 00:08:06,420
free drinks for life.

191
00:08:11,390 --> 00:08:13,300
He thinks we were in this fight with him.

192
00:08:13,300 --> 00:08:15,110
We were, in this fight with him.

193
00:08:15,920 --> 00:08:18,040
And now we are going to go in there and tell everyone

194
00:08:18,040 --> 00:08:20,800
the legendary tale of how we beat up some guys.

195
00:08:21,150 --> 00:08:22,900
And everyone is going to think it's great

196
00:08:22,900 --> 00:08:24,810
and everyone is going to sleep with me again.

197
00:08:24,810 --> 00:08:26,510
Dude come on,no one is gonna

198
00:08:26,510 --> 00:08:28,360
believe we were in a fight-- look at us.

199
00:08:28,360 --> 00:08:29,000
Oh that's a good...

200
00:08:31,090 --> 00:08:31,820
What are you doing?!

201
00:08:32,020 --> 00:08:33,200
What I should've done a long time ago.

202
00:08:33,680 --> 00:08:34,090
What?

203
00:08:34,300 --> 00:08:36,210
I don't know I just hit myself in the eye!

204
00:08:36,410 --> 00:08:38,020
I don't even know what I'm saying

205
00:08:39,630 --> 00:08:41,370
I throw an awesome right hook by the way.

206
00:08:41,840 --> 00:08:42,620
Okay are you ready?

207
00:08:43,050 --> 00:08:43,790
To go back in?

208
00:08:43,820 --> 00:08:44,610
No,for this.

209
00:08:47,630 --> 00:08:49,650
God! You just punched me in the nose!

210
00:08:49,650 --> 00:08:50,580
Are you crying?

211
00:08:50,580 --> 00:08:53,100
Yes I'm crying! You just punched me in the nose!

212
00:08:54,050 --> 00:08:55,470
Oh that's going to swell up real good.

213
00:08:55,470 --> 00:08:56,730
You're going to look like Owen Wilson.

214
00:08:56,730 --> 00:08:57,860
Okay let's get back in there.

215
00:08:57,860 --> 00:09:00,660
but just let's just play this down, okay?

216
00:09:00,660 --> 00:09:02,670
I don't want this to turn into a big thing.

217
00:09:04,080 --> 00:09:05,710
And Ted comes and takes his shoe off!

218
00:09:05,710 --> 00:09:06,690
Hits him in the mouth...

219
00:09:06,690 --> 00:09:09,280
Hey there they are! The guys that got my back!

220
00:09:22,980 --> 00:09:25,110
You two got in a fight.

221
00:09:25,110 --> 00:09:25,650
Really?

222
00:09:26,090 --> 00:09:28,100
Uh, no, Barney punched me and himself in the face

223
00:09:28,310 --> 00:09:29,640
to make it look like we got in a fight.

224
00:09:29,850 --> 00:09:30,750
Come on, Marshall!

225
00:09:31,940 --> 00:09:37,150
Wow look at your eye. you look like a badass.

226
00:09:37,450 --> 00:09:39,110
I'm surprised to see you had it in me.

227
00:09:39,110 --> 00:09:41,570
You. Had it in you.

228
00:09:42,780 --> 00:09:45,400
Do you... want to touch it?

229
00:09:49,790 --> 00:09:51,240
Oh my God, it's warm!

230
00:09:53,110 --> 00:09:55,490
Hey! Victory drinks!  Huh?

231
00:09:56,080 --> 00:10:00,080
Free! Free! Free! Free!

232
00:10:00,080 --> 00:10:01,620
$7.50.

233
00:10:02,130 --> 00:10:03,750
Why do I have to pay?

234
00:10:04,170 --> 00:10:06,020
'Cause you don't got my back.

235
00:10:06,520 --> 00:10:07,120
These guys got my back.

236
00:10:07,500 --> 00:10:09,770
You know what Doug? I will gladly pay.

237
00:10:09,770 --> 00:10:11,840
And you know why? Because that's what grownups do.

238
00:10:11,840 --> 00:10:14,530
They pay for their drinks and they don't get into fights.

239
00:10:14,530 --> 00:10:15,550
You know what I was doing while you guys

240
00:10:15,550 --> 00:10:16,740
were out there being immature?

241
00:10:16,740 --> 00:10:17,590
I'll tell you what I was doing.

242
00:10:17,590 --> 00:10:18,560
Your nails?

243
00:10:19,860 --> 00:10:21,360
No. I was doing...

244
00:10:21,360 --> 00:10:23,480
The relationship quiz in this month's Cosmo?

245
00:10:23,870 --> 00:10:25,230
No. I was doing...

246
00:10:25,230 --> 00:10:27,630
Your best not to cry when Big came back for Carrie

247
00:10:27,630 --> 00:10:29,210
at the end of the  Sex and the City movie?

248
00:10:29,210 --> 00:10:31,570
No. Spoilers much? No.

249
00:10:31,570 --> 00:10:33,050
I'll tell you what I was doing--

250
00:10:33,050 --> 00:10:34,230
The captain of the football team

251
00:10:34,420 --> 00:10:36,440
Because he gave you his promise ring and you

252
00:10:36,440 --> 00:10:38,470
looking so pretty in your open back homecoming dress?

253
00:10:41,010 --> 00:10:42,120
Sorry.

254
00:10:44,220 --> 00:10:46,000
I hate those guys!

255
00:10:46,000 --> 00:10:48,320
Acting like they're the manliest guys in the universe

256
00:10:48,320 --> 00:10:51,860
like they're Crocodile Dundee and David Hasselhoff.

257
00:10:51,860 --> 00:10:53,840
Those are the manliest guys in the universe?

258
00:10:53,840 --> 00:10:55,750
I don't understand why they're getting all this attention.

259
00:10:55,970 --> 00:10:58,330
I mean I'm threal hero here.

260
00:10:58,330 --> 00:10:59,710
yeah, you are.

261
00:10:59,710 --> 00:11:03,000
I'm serious woman.Put it back in your pants.

262
00:11:03,800 --> 00:11:07,580
Marshall u're the man every  boy should grow up to become

263
00:11:07,580 --> 00:11:09,110
and every girl should marry.

264
00:11:10,900 --> 00:11:11,720
You know what?

265
00:11:12,200 --> 00:11:14,640
I have two kids in my class who won't stop fighting.

266
00:11:14,640 --> 00:11:17,620
If you come to school tomorrow and tell them your story

267
00:11:17,620 --> 00:11:19,470
of choosing the path of nonviolence

268
00:11:19,470 --> 00:11:21,600
it might really set them straight.

269
00:11:21,600 --> 00:11:24,670
And save me having to get up early to make a lesson plan.

270
00:11:25,760 --> 00:11:26,920
All right.

271
00:11:27,120 --> 00:11:29,230
Okay. I'll set them straight.

272
00:11:29,430 --> 00:11:30,500
You're a wuss.

273
00:11:30,500 --> 00:11:32,280
What? No!

274
00:11:33,250 --> 00:11:36,040
Mahatma Panda and Martin Luther Koala are telling you kids

275
00:11:36,040 --> 00:11:37,050
this story to illustrate...

276
00:11:37,050 --> 00:11:39,170
To illustrate that you're a wuss?

277
00:11:39,870 --> 00:11:42,130
Why didn't you just fight those guys?

278
00:11:42,130 --> 00:11:43,850
Were you scared?

279
00:11:43,850 --> 00:11:45,660
What?

280
00:11:45,660 --> 00:11:48,520
No! I wasn't scared!

281
00:11:48,520 --> 00:11:50,390
I've been in plenty of fights okay?

282
00:11:50,390 --> 00:11:53,930
You're huge! You must weigh like a thousand pounds.

283
00:11:55,050 --> 00:11:59,060
Okay. First of all, I'm wearing a baggy sweater  

284
00:11:59,060 --> 00:12:01,630
and it has horizontal stripes.

285
00:12:01,630 --> 00:12:03,750
And I also-- and I had a salty lunch...

286
00:12:03,750 --> 00:12:05,870
And so I'm retain...You know what? Shut up!

287
00:12:05,870 --> 00:12:07,730
Wuss! Wuss! Wuss!

288
00:12:07,730 --> 00:12:09,830
Wuss! Wuss! Wuss!

289
00:12:14,400 --> 00:12:18,040
Wow. So you just beat those guys up?

290
00:12:18,540 --> 00:12:19,140
Just?

291
00:12:20,490 --> 00:12:22,720
Oh, Amanda were it so simple.

292
00:12:22,970 --> 00:12:26,400
You see, hand to hand combat is about so much more than just

293
00:12:26,400 --> 00:12:29,280
administering brute force on your opponent, right B?

294
00:12:29,280 --> 00:12:30,770
You know it!

295
00:12:30,770 --> 00:12:31,530
It's a science.

296
00:12:32,810 --> 00:12:35,210
The sweet science as it were.

297
00:12:35,210 --> 00:12:38,100
Wait. I'm confused what did those guys do to deserve it?

298
00:12:38,700 --> 00:12:40,690
Well. this may sound petty  

299
00:12:42,230 --> 00:12:43,990
-but they sat in our booth. -They sat in our booth.

300
00:12:44,480 --> 00:12:46,380
- And nobody...   - Nobody.

301
00:12:46,380 --> 00:12:47,450
sits in our booth.

302
00:12:51,300 --> 00:12:53,360
Are you going to beat those guys up?

303
00:12:58,530 --> 00:13:00,210
Yes ,we are going to beat those guys up.

304
00:13:00,210 --> 00:13:01,300
Ted, come on.

305
00:13:04,890 --> 00:13:05,570
You two.

306
00:13:05,570 --> 00:13:06,920
Our booth.

307
00:13:06,920 --> 00:13:08,680
Get out. Now!

308
00:13:08,810 --> 00:13:10,880
-What are you doing? -Relax. we got Doug.

309
00:13:10,880 --> 00:13:12,230
Big Doug's got our backs.

310
00:13:12,230 --> 00:13:13,230
Yeah. But Doug's not here tonight

311
00:13:13,630 --> 00:13:15,430
Can I get you guys something?

312
00:13:15,670 --> 00:13:17,530
Drinks? Cash? Those two girls over there?

313
00:13:17,530 --> 00:13:19,770
Are you Ted Mosby?

314
00:13:19,770 --> 00:13:21,920
um,yeah,I am.

315
00:13:21,920 --> 00:13:23,520
And u're Barney Stinson?

316
00:13:24,040 --> 00:13:24,800
They've heard of us.

317
00:13:25,650 --> 00:13:26,610
It's cool,guys.

318
00:13:26,610 --> 00:13:30,160
I let you leave with your asses unkicked.

319
00:13:30,160 --> 00:13:30,960
This time.

320
00:13:34,980 --> 00:13:36,390
What's, uh, what's this?

321
00:13:36,390 --> 00:13:37,580
You've been served.

322
00:13:37,580 --> 00:13:38,870
You're being sued for assault.

323
00:13:40,130 --> 00:13:41,330
Enjoy your booth.

324
00:13:47,350 --> 00:13:49,050
That was close.

325
00:13:52,850 --> 00:13:53,630
Assault!

326
00:13:53,840 --> 00:13:55,300
They're suing us for assault!

327
00:13:55,300 --> 00:13:57,780
Okay well. What's the penalty for assault?

328
00:13:57,780 --> 00:13:59,370
What do I have to pay a fine? 

329
00:13:59,370 --> 00:14:01,180
Pick up trash on the highway?

330
00:14:01,180 --> 00:14:03,710
'Cause I've done that before know what I mean?

331
00:14:03,710 --> 00:14:04,230
I don't know.

332
00:14:04,980 --> 00:14:07,080
Actually he did know that the worst we we looking at

333
00:14:07,080 --> 00:14:08,420
was a small civil settlement  

334
00:14:08,420 --> 00:14:10,050
and probably no criminal charges.

335
00:14:10,050 --> 00:14:12,150
But he was really pissed at us.

336
00:14:12,170 --> 00:14:13,960
I mean you guys could be looking at

337
00:14:13,960 --> 00:14:15,070
some serious prison time.

338
00:14:15,070 --> 00:14:17,150
-Prison?! -I can't go to prison!

339
00:14:18,260 --> 00:14:20,040
I mean I could get a lot of reading done  

340
00:14:20,040 --> 00:14:22,240
finally write some short stories.

341
00:14:22,240 --> 00:14:23,750
Work out all the time.

342
00:14:23,750 --> 00:14:25,570
Seriously if I don't come out of there completely ripped--

343
00:14:25,570 --> 00:14:28,280
Ted, we can't go to prison!

344
00:14:28,280 --> 00:14:29,880
People get shivved in the joint!

345
00:14:31,460 --> 00:14:33,170
Plus the meals are really starchy.

346
00:14:34,080 --> 00:14:36,240
Well,you guys should have thought of that

347
00:14:36,240 --> 00:14:37,530
before you beat up those guys.

348
00:14:40,030 --> 00:14:41,500
What if we didn't?

349
00:14:41,500 --> 00:14:42,170
Didn't what, Ted?

350
00:14:42,170 --> 00:14:43,680
Didn't beat up those guys .

351
00:14:43,680 --> 00:14:45,320
What if Doug beat up those guys all by himself

352
00:14:45,320 --> 00:14:46,280
and we didn't do anything?

353
00:14:46,280 --> 00:14:48,290
I knew it! I knew it!  I knew it! I knew it!

354
00:14:49,620 --> 00:14:51,520
You guys didn't throw a single punch.

355
00:14:51,520 --> 00:14:54,210
Well. I hit Ted and myself so...

356
00:14:54,210 --> 00:14:56,450
Well, who's the wuss now? 

357
00:14:56,450 --> 00:14:58,450
Answer: You guys.

358
00:14:58,450 --> 00:15:00,560
Look, can you just help us get out of this?

359
00:15:00,560 --> 00:15:02,020
You know the old expression:

360
00:15:02,020 --> 00:15:03,530
If you're not prepared to do the time

361
00:15:03,530 --> 00:15:04,930
don't pretend to do the crime

362
00:15:04,930 --> 00:15:07,060
and laugh and get free drinks 

363
00:15:07,060 --> 00:15:08,560
and not stand up for your friend

364
00:15:08,560 --> 00:15:12,550
who incidentally,has been in plenty of fights with his brothers.

365
00:15:14,280 --> 00:15:16,400
Look you've got to help us out. Marshall.

366
00:15:17,000 --> 00:15:19,290
We're the Three Musketeers!

367
00:15:19,590 --> 00:15:22,210
If I give up Ted, how much time am I looking at?

368
00:15:22,910 --> 00:15:23,980
Hey guys! 

369
00:15:26,400 --> 00:15:28,930
Barney, I've been looking for you.

370
00:15:30,270 --> 00:15:32,470
I got, uh, tickets to this hockey game tonight.

371
00:15:32,470 --> 00:15:34,940
It's stupid. You want to go?

372
00:15:34,940 --> 00:15:36,340
It might go kind of late  

373
00:15:36,340 --> 00:15:38,180
so maybe after the game we can grab a drink.

374
00:15:38,180 --> 00:15:40,030
Oh, hey, Robin. get this.

375
00:15:40,030 --> 00:15:41,100
You know that fight?

376
00:15:42,130 --> 00:15:43,420
These guys faked the whole thing.

377
00:15:50,180 --> 00:15:53,620
Oh, I forgot! Tonight is no good.

378
00:15:53,620 --> 00:15:58,790
I,uh, I can't go to that hockey game tonight. I got that  uh...

379
00:15:58,790 --> 00:16:02,580
That uh... that uh...

380
00:16:04,840 --> 00:16:06,040
That uh...

381
00:16:08,520 --> 00:16:09,530
That uh...

382
00:16:09,530 --> 00:16:12,570
That uh...

383
00:16:16,570 --> 00:16:18,980
Good news..I talked to the guys.

384
00:16:18,980 --> 00:16:21,010
-What guys? -The guys you didn't beat up.

385
00:16:21,010 --> 00:16:22,580
They agreed to drop the lawsuit.

386
00:16:22,580 --> 00:16:24,470
Boom! Lawyered.

387
00:16:24,470 --> 00:16:26,040
What? They agreed to drop it?

388
00:16:26,040 --> 00:16:29,550
Yeah. I just explained that you two are wusses.

389
00:16:29,550 --> 00:16:30,470
We had a good laugh about that.

390
00:16:30,470 --> 00:16:32,090
A good long laugh actually.

391
00:16:32,090 --> 00:16:35,310
I explained how you get a mani/pedi once a month.

392
00:16:35,310 --> 00:16:37,610
Weekly Wolverine-- some of us care.

393
00:16:38,200 --> 00:16:40,710
And how you played the hammer dulcimer

394
00:16:40,920 --> 00:16:43,510
in the Pre-Reformation Dance Society at Wesleyan.

395
00:16:43,510 --> 00:16:45,500
Did you at least tell them we were one of

396
00:16:45,500 --> 00:16:48,210
the premier Medieval chamber groups in the Little Ivies?

397
00:16:48,210 --> 00:16:48,960
Oh, I did.

398
00:16:49,440 --> 00:16:51,300
And we all agreed it was much more likely that

399
00:16:51,300 --> 00:16:52,690
one guy beat up the three of them

400
00:16:52,690 --> 00:16:54,660
than that you two had anything to do with it so...

401
00:16:56,300 --> 00:16:58,890
Wait so... so now they're only suing Doug.

402
00:16:58,890 --> 00:16:59,750
Affirmative.

403
00:17:00,830 --> 00:17:04,320
Angry, irrational, violent Doug  

404
00:17:04,320 --> 00:17:07,090
who now knows we were the ones who threw him under the bus.

405
00:17:08,730 --> 00:17:09,520
They what?!

406
00:17:10,630 --> 00:17:12,310
Look, Doug we can explain...

407
00:17:12,310 --> 00:17:12,880
Explain what?

408
00:17:13,980 --> 00:17:16,630
Explain how you stabbed me in the back right to my face?

409
00:17:16,630 --> 00:17:17,880
Robin,i'm scared.

410
00:17:17,880 --> 00:17:19,760
Yeah,is Doug seeing anyone?

411
00:17:19,760 --> 00:17:22,550
Are you seeing anyone? you really should.

412
00:17:22,550 --> 00:17:24,680
Doug, look,you don't understand  

413
00:17:24,680 --> 00:17:27,040
you beat up those guys all by yourself.

414
00:17:27,040 --> 00:17:28,390
It's true,all right?

415
00:17:28,390 --> 00:17:29,800
They had nothing to do with it.

416
00:17:29,800 --> 00:17:33,080
I mean,look at these two.

417
00:17:34,680 --> 00:17:36,070
It was all Ted!

418
00:17:37,910 --> 00:17:38,980
Look at this guy.

419
00:17:38,980 --> 00:17:40,060
Yeah,look at me!

420
00:17:40,060 --> 00:17:41,760
He wouldn't last five minutes in a fight.

421
00:17:41,760 --> 00:17:43,570
Well,I think I could  last at least five

422
00:17:43,570 --> 00:17:46,090
He's got the muscle definition of linguini.

423
00:17:46,090 --> 00:17:49,270
Yeah  linguini with meatballs maybe, check it.

424
00:17:49,670 --> 00:17:52,120
-Ted, Ted, don't. -Look!

425
00:17:53,020 --> 00:17:53,750
Okay,you know what?

426
00:17:53,750 --> 00:17:55,660
maybe it was just me.

427
00:17:55,660 --> 00:17:57,090
Actually,you know what that makes a lot of sense.

428
00:17:57,090 --> 00:17:58,220
I tend to black out a lot.

429
00:17:58,220 --> 00:18:01,440
Anyway,look,i always got your back.

430
00:18:02,040 --> 00:18:03,540
All I ask in return is that you got mine.

431
00:18:03,540 --> 00:18:06,380
But you know what? you don't.

432
00:18:06,380 --> 00:18:08,800
You can't be counted on.

433
00:18:10,130 --> 00:18:11,570
No wonder your fiance left you.

434
00:18:12,800 --> 00:18:13,700
And here it is,kids  

435
00:18:13,980 --> 00:18:15,320
the only fight I've ever been in.

436
00:18:15,320 --> 00:18:18,020
So what can I share about the experience?

437
00:18:20,880 --> 00:18:23,250
Well,for starters,when you punch someone in the face,

438
00:18:24,910 --> 00:18:25,820
it hurts your hand...

439
00:18:27,360 --> 00:18:28,280
a lot.

440
00:18:30,470 --> 00:18:33,490
But what hurts even more than that?

441
00:18:33,490 --> 00:18:34,110
This.

442
00:18:35,670 --> 00:18:37,910
And the next thing i remember was waking up.

443
00:18:38,780 --> 00:18:40,520
Okay,i'm all warmed up.

444
00:18:40,520 --> 00:18:41,850
Let's do this thing.

445
00:18:42,870 --> 00:18:45,570
Turns out getting in a fight was a terrible idea.

446
00:18:46,350 --> 00:18:47,330
And that's my story.

447
00:18:47,330 --> 00:18:49,270
And what did you learn?

448
00:18:49,270 --> 00:18:53,060
Well,i learned that fighting is bad

449
00:18:54,060 --> 00:18:56,090
and you shouldn't do it ever.

450
00:18:56,960 --> 00:18:58,060
Any questions?

451
00:18:59,160 --> 00:19:02,140
Yeah,where do you find these people?

452
00:19:02,140 --> 00:19:05,760
I know! Was there a big sale at the wuss market?

453
00:19:05,760 --> 00:19:07,900
Wuss! Wuss! Wuss!

454
00:19:08,990 --> 00:19:10,430
Of course,I didn't tell those kids what really happened.

455
00:19:12,790 --> 00:19:14,480
Okay,I'm all warmed up.

456
00:19:14,480 --> 00:19:15,370
Let's do this thing.

457
00:19:17,810 --> 00:19:18,790
What happened?

458
00:19:19,660 --> 00:19:21,160
This happened.

459
00:19:24,670 --> 00:19:26,350
Holy crap!

460
00:19:26,930 --> 00:19:29,010
Yeah,turns out Uncle Marshall and his brothers

461
00:19:29,010 --> 00:19:30,880
did a little more than just roughhouse.

462
00:19:37,600 --> 00:19:39,030
Cocoa break!

463
00:19:48,200 --> 00:19:49,310
Marshall looks good.

464
00:19:49,310 --> 00:19:50,290
Has he lost weight?

465
00:19:50,290 --> 00:19:52,050
Bitch,don't even.

466
00:19:53,450 --> 00:19:55,610
Kids,I'd love to leave you with the message

467
00:19:55,610 --> 00:19:57,400
that figing is bad and you shouldn't do it  

468
00:19:57,400 --> 00:19:59,110
but I know that's pointless.

469
00:19:59,310 --> 00:20:00,350
So i'll leave you with this

470
00:20:01,250 --> 00:20:03,100
don't ever get in a fight with Uncle Marshall.

471
00:20:03,100 --> 00:20:05,220
That guy's freaking crazy.

472
00:20:10,900 --> 00:20:12,470
It is so good to be home.

473
00:20:12,920 --> 00:20:15,040
Mom,Lily,fantastic job.

474
00:20:15,690 --> 00:20:18,070
"Good food ,good meat,good God ,let's eat." Right?

475
00:20:18,470 --> 00:20:19,750
Okay,here we go.

476
00:20:19,750 --> 00:20:20,640
Goggles on.

477
00:20:26,260 --> 00:20:28,710
All right,so you guys pass the plates.

478
00:20:28,970 --> 00:20:30,660
Lily,you want white or dark meat?

479
00:20:30,900 --> 00:20:32,790
Dark! Honey,please be careful.

480
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


481
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000

਍਍㤹㤹਍〰〺㨰ⰰ〵‰ⴭ‾〰〺㨰ⰲ〰਍昼湯⁴潣潬㵲⌢晦晦〰•楳敺ㄽ㸴睷⹷癴畳瑢瑩敬⹳敮㱴是湯㹴਍