1
00:00:00,420 --> 00:00:03,450
it was a quiet november afternoon in 2007.

2
00:00:03,460 --> 00:00:04,700
i was working from home,

3
00:00:04,710 --> 00:00:06,920
because, you know, no distractions.

4
00:00:06,930 --> 00:00:08,480
-this is incredible! -oh, my god!

5
00:00:08,480 --> 00:00:09,550
i can't believe it!

6
00:00:09,550 --> 00:00:11,160
-i have big news. -oh, my god!

7
00:00:11,160 --> 00:00:12,330
okay, my thing's pretty huge.

8
00:00:12,330 --> 00:00:14,060
-but fine, you can go first. -okay, i just

9
00:00:14,060 --> 00:00:17,530
-found out... -i found a porno starring ted mosby!

10
00:00:17,850 --> 00:00:18,370
what are you...

11
00:00:18,370 --> 00:00:19,540
what are you, what you're talking about?

12
00:00:19,550 --> 00:00:23,300
i'm talking about welcome to the sex plane,

13
00:00:23,310 --> 00:00:25,670
and look who plays the navigator,

14
00:00:25,680 --> 00:00:27,800
ted mosby.

15
00:00:28,760 --> 00:00:30,760
it is the same exact spelling as my name.

16
00:00:30,770 --> 00:00:31,740
okay, you know,

17
00:00:31,750 --> 00:00:33,010
cute coincidence, barney.

18
00:00:33,010 --> 00:00:34,280
whatever.

19
00:00:34,290 --> 00:00:36,090
i just got off the phone with the nr...

20
00:00:36,090 --> 00:00:37,970
oh, my god, this totally explains the thing

21
00:00:37,970 --> 00:00:39,700
at my doctor's the other day.

22
00:00:39,710 --> 00:00:41,040
open wide.

23
00:00:41,050 --> 00:00:42,430
i guess you're more used to saying that

24
00:00:42,430 --> 00:00:45,410
than hearing it, huh, ted mosby?

25
00:00:47,660 --> 00:00:49,370
who is this guy?

26
00:00:49,720 --> 00:00:51,140
and why's my doctor watching porn?

27
00:00:51,150 --> 00:00:53,730
all right, let's meet your new doppelganger.

28
00:00:53,740 --> 00:00:56,400
or should i say doppelbanger?

29
00:00:56,410 --> 00:00:57,560
guys, guys, guys!

30
00:00:57,560 --> 00:00:59,260
can i tell my news?

31
00:00:59,260 --> 00:01:01,490
-it's pretty... -this is really bizarre.

32
00:01:01,490 --> 00:01:02,810
the only other famous mosby i know

33
00:01:02,810 --> 00:01:04,990
was a confederate general during the civil war.

34
00:01:05,000 --> 00:01:06,160
probably not the same guy.

35
00:01:06,160 --> 00:01:08,140
i got the job at the nrdc!

36
00:01:08,150 --> 00:01:10,530
you got the job! oh! yeah.

37
00:01:10,530 --> 00:01:13,620
the nrdc, or national resources defense council,

38
00:01:13,620 --> 00:01:15,800
fought for clean water,

39
00:01:15,810 --> 00:01:18,180
air and to preserve america's wilderness.

40
00:01:18,190 --> 00:01:20,010
it was marshall's dream job.

41
00:01:20,020 --> 00:01:21,620
-congrats, buddy! -thanks.

42
00:01:21,630 --> 00:01:23,230
it's kind of weird hugging with porn on.

43
00:01:23,240 --> 00:01:25,090
yeah, it really is.

44
00:01:25,170 --> 00:01:26,330
hey, hey-o!

45
00:01:26,330 --> 00:01:27,740
new guy entering the cockpit.

46
00:01:27,740 --> 00:01:30,460
could it be the navigator, ted mosby?

47
00:01:30,470 --> 00:01:31,620
uh... no.

48
00:01:31,630 --> 00:01:33,370
no, navigators have three stripes on their hats.

49
00:01:33,370 --> 00:01:34,690
captains have four.

50
00:01:34,700 --> 00:01:36,170
that guy's a captain.

51
00:01:36,180 --> 00:01:38,240
yeah, and i'm sure complete accuracy

52
00:01:38,240 --> 00:01:41,670
in all those details was very important to the directors...

53
00:01:41,680 --> 00:01:44,600
"dirt and skank, the raunch brothers."

54
00:01:47,760 --> 00:01:50,130
baby, i have some exciting news!

55
00:01:50,130 --> 00:01:53,730
i hope it's not that you just won some sort of race here.

56
00:01:54,390 --> 00:01:56,030
i got the job at the nrdc!

57
00:01:56,040 --> 00:01:58,440
and i found a porno starring ted mosby!

58
00:01:58,450 --> 00:02:00,110
oh my god, that's amazing!

59
00:02:00,110 --> 00:02:01,480
i know, right?

60
00:02:01,490 --> 00:02:03,170
oh, congratulations, marshall!

61
00:02:03,180 --> 00:02:04,280
congratulation to us all!

62
00:02:04,280 --> 00:02:05,890
oh, let's go celebrate!

63
00:02:05,890 --> 00:02:08,760
the fact that i found a porno starring a guy named ted mosby--

64
00:02:08,760 --> 00:02:10,470
let's do it!

65
00:02:10,590 --> 00:02:11,620
oh, is that him?

66
00:02:11,620 --> 00:02:14,380
cause that ted mosby really knows what he's doing.

67
00:02:14,390 --> 00:02:16,330
no, that's not him.

68
00:02:16,450 --> 00:02:17,210
what do you mean,

69
00:02:17,210 --> 00:02:19,430
"that" ted mosby really knows what he's doing.

70
00:02:19,440 --> 00:02:20,430
oh, no.

71
00:02:20,430 --> 00:02:22,710
no, i meant, that ted mosby,

72
00:02:22,710 --> 00:02:24,400
he really knows what he's doing.

73
00:02:24,410 --> 00:02:26,350
like all ted mosbys.

74
00:02:26,870 --> 00:02:27,850
wow, nrdc!

75
00:02:27,850 --> 00:02:29,720
way to go, marshall.

76
00:02:30,200 --> 00:02:30,870
but you're

77
00:02:30,870 --> 00:02:33,030
still gonna go to your job interview today, right, baby?

78
00:02:33,040 --> 00:02:33,840
marshall had an interview

79
00:02:33,840 --> 00:02:36,690
at a firm called nicholson, hewitt and west.

80
00:02:36,700 --> 00:02:37,510
they represented

81
00:02:37,510 --> 00:02:39,880
pretty much everybody marshall was going to sue

82
00:02:39,890 --> 00:02:41,550
once he started at the nrdc.

83
00:02:41,560 --> 00:02:43,080
i'm not doing that interview.

84
00:02:43,080 --> 00:02:44,810
those people are evil.

85
00:02:44,820 --> 00:02:47,280
marshall, your dad went through a lot of trouble to set this up.

86
00:02:47,280 --> 00:02:49,780
you can't just pull out at the last second.

87
00:02:49,790 --> 00:02:51,680
apparently you can.

88
00:02:52,380 --> 00:02:54,460
ted, ted, ted, guy in the hat!

89
00:02:54,460 --> 00:02:55,170
three stripes!

90
00:02:55,170 --> 00:02:58,810
ladies and gentlemen, i give you ted mosby, porn star.

91
00:03:01,250 --> 00:03:02,410
i know what kind of plane this is.

92
00:03:02,410 --> 00:03:04,800
it's a "boing."

93
00:03:05,040 --> 00:03:05,580
see.

94
00:03:05,580 --> 00:03:07,990
this is way better than marshall's internship.

95
00:03:08,000 --> 00:03:10,020
it's a real job.

96
00:03:10,140 --> 00:03:11,740
who is this guy?

97
00:03:11,750 --> 00:03:13,030
are we related?

98
00:03:13,040 --> 00:03:14,880
do, do i look like him?

99
00:03:15,970 --> 00:03:16,550
it's hard to tell.

100
00:03:16,550 --> 00:03:18,400
go, go like this.

101
00:03:20,940 --> 00:03:22,920
-oh, yeah, a little bit. -yeah.

102
00:03:22,930 --> 00:03:23,990
more aroud the eyes. oh, i do see that.

103
00:03:38,660 --> 00:03:39,550
and here's your water, 

104
00:03:39,550 --> 00:03:42,790
in case you're dehydrated, ted mosby.

105
00:03:43,240 --> 00:03:44,350
very funny, wendy.

106
00:03:44,350 --> 00:03:46,470
now we know you watch porn.

107
00:03:46,990 --> 00:03:49,200
this ted mosby must be getting kind of famous.

108
00:03:49,210 --> 00:03:50,400
mm. you're not wrong.

109
00:03:50,410 --> 00:03:51,300
according to the web site,

110
00:03:51,300 --> 00:03:54,220
of the far superior ted mosby...

111
00:03:54,230 --> 00:03:55,580
...he's been in the business three months,

112
00:03:55,580 --> 00:03:59,090
and he's made 125 movies.

113
00:03:59,470 --> 00:04:02,010
that's 42 movies a month.

114
00:04:02,020 --> 00:04:04,270
who is he, jude law?

115
00:04:04,350 --> 00:04:05,630
right?

116
00:04:05,640 --> 00:04:08,040
he makes a lot of movies.

117
00:04:08,050 --> 00:04:08,750
i mean,

118
00:04:08,760 --> 00:04:10,100
not so much lately,

119
00:04:10,100 --> 00:04:12,210
but maybe, like, two years ago,

120
00:04:12,210 --> 00:04:14,780
-you couldn't go to a movie without... -shh...

121
00:04:16,060 --> 00:04:17,040
oh, hey, look, check it out.

122
00:04:17,040 --> 00:04:20,250
ted mosby did an interview in adult video weekly.

123
00:04:20,260 --> 00:04:23,130
adult video weekly?

124
00:04:23,140 --> 00:04:24,760
oh, no.

125
00:04:26,990 --> 00:04:27,870
hello?

126
00:04:27,880 --> 00:04:29,390
hi, i'm looking for ted mosby.

127
00:04:29,400 --> 00:04:31,600
it's leonard ross from avw.

128
00:04:31,610 --> 00:04:32,520
oh, my god!

129
00:04:32,530 --> 00:04:33,610
A.V.W?

130
00:04:33,620 --> 00:04:36,450
it's architecture vision weekly!

131
00:04:37,010 --> 00:04:38,400
wow, i have been reading your magazine

132
00:04:38,400 --> 00:04:39,820
since i was a little kid.

133
00:04:39,830 --> 00:04:41,630
well, that's a bummer.

134
00:04:41,640 --> 00:04:44,450
anyway, i'm calling to interview you about your latest project.

135
00:04:44,460 --> 00:04:46,070
well, i don't want to say it's my project.

136
00:04:46,070 --> 00:04:48,080
i mean, i'll be working with at least three partners.

137
00:04:48,090 --> 00:04:50,130
oh! group scene. always fun.

138
00:04:50,140 --> 00:04:52,510
yeah, yeah, i'm really looking forward to it.

139
00:04:52,520 --> 00:04:55,010
i mean, i know they're gonna ride me pretty hard

140
00:04:55,020 --> 00:04:56,640
but they're great guys.

141
00:04:56,650 --> 00:04:57,780
guys?

142
00:04:57,790 --> 00:05:00,670
whoa, there's a scoop.

143
00:05:01,060 --> 00:05:03,860
that interview went on for 20 more minutes.

144
00:05:03,870 --> 00:05:05,760
"this project was so demanding,

145
00:05:05,760 --> 00:05:07,300
"i can't tell you how many nights

146
00:05:07,300 --> 00:05:10,170
i spent bent over a table."

147
00:05:11,340 --> 00:05:13,700
oh, hey, baby, how'd the interview go?

148
00:05:13,710 --> 00:05:15,760
um, interesting.

149
00:05:15,770 --> 00:05:18,360
there i am in the office of jefferson coatsworth,

150
00:05:18,360 --> 00:05:20,020
and i figure i'm not gonna take this job anyway,

151
00:05:20,020 --> 00:05:23,310
i might as well give this old bastard a piece of my mind.

152
00:05:23,690 --> 00:05:24,680
jefferson coatsworth

153
00:05:24,680 --> 00:05:26,630
wasn't what i expected.

154
00:05:26,640 --> 00:05:28,130
marshall,

155
00:05:28,580 --> 00:05:30,290
jeff coatsworth.

156
00:05:31,220 --> 00:05:32,170
hello.

157
00:05:32,180 --> 00:05:35,890
dude, i am so, so psyched that you're here.

158
00:05:35,900 --> 00:05:37,000
can i beer ya?

159
00:05:37,010 --> 00:05:38,240
marshall was thrown.

160
00:05:38,250 --> 00:05:39,890
this guy seemed nice.

161
00:05:39,900 --> 00:05:40,910
of course, he wasn't.

162
00:05:40,910 --> 00:05:42,760


163
00:05:42,760 --> 00:05:44,310
go-go to hell!

164
00:05:44,320 --> 00:05:45,740
i'd do it again!

165
00:05:45,750 --> 00:05:46,850
i'm innocent.

166
00:05:46,860 --> 00:05:48,510
i'm innocent.

167
00:05:48,920 --> 00:05:50,360
marshall,

168
00:05:50,390 --> 00:05:51,440
why do you want to work

169
00:05:51,450 --> 00:05:53,510
at nicholson, hewitt & west?

170
00:05:53,510 --> 00:05:55,080
right, um, okay, jeff,

171
00:05:55,080 --> 00:05:56,240
i've actually given this a lot of thought...

172
00:05:56,240 --> 00:05:58,050
i'm sorry. stop.

173
00:05:58,060 --> 00:06:00,430
i can't do this with a straight face.

174
00:06:00,690 --> 00:06:02,460
you don't want to work here.

175
00:06:02,470 --> 00:06:04,040
you're only here 'cause your dad went to high school

176
00:06:04,040 --> 00:06:05,500
with joe hewitt.

177
00:06:05,510 --> 00:06:06,740
fact is,

178
00:06:06,750 --> 00:06:08,980
you just got a sweet job at the nrdc.

179
00:06:08,990 --> 00:06:11,900
and it's awesome.

180
00:06:11,910 --> 00:06:12,360
man, i could

181
00:06:12,360 --> 00:06:14,270
have gone the non-profit route.

182
00:06:14,280 --> 00:06:15,330
i didn't.

183
00:06:15,340 --> 00:06:18,180
and it eats me up inside every day.

184
00:06:18,300 --> 00:06:20,130
i hate myself.

185
00:06:21,510 --> 00:06:23,490
i hate myself.

186
00:06:24,280 --> 00:06:26,020
oh, he's good.

187
00:06:26,030 --> 00:06:28,210
classic seduction technique.

188
00:06:28,220 --> 00:06:29,270
what do you mean?

189
00:06:29,280 --> 00:06:30,590
oh, i use it all the time.

190
00:06:30,600 --> 00:06:33,940
first i buy her-- and by her i mean you-- a drink.

191
00:06:33,950 --> 00:06:34,890
now, i'm the guy who gets her

192
00:06:34,890 --> 00:06:35,750
what she wants.

193
00:06:35,760 --> 00:06:37,000
then i pretend to care

194
00:06:37,000 --> 00:06:39,140
about whatever idiotic thing she cares about.

195
00:06:39,140 --> 00:06:41,820
for you, that would be the environment.

196
00:06:41,830 --> 00:06:42,680
now, i'm the great

197
00:06:42,680 --> 00:06:44,230
guy who shares her interests.

198
00:06:44,240 --> 00:06:46,620
and before you know it, you're naked in my apartment

199
00:06:46,620 --> 00:06:50,050
shouting, "oh, oh, bar-r-r-ne-e-ey!"

200
00:06:50,060 --> 00:06:50,600
and by you,

201
00:06:50,600 --> 00:06:52,330
i mean her.

202
00:06:52,500 --> 00:06:54,590
he is not trying to seduce me.

203
00:06:54,600 --> 00:06:56,240
he didn't even offer me the job.

204
00:06:56,250 --> 00:06:57,330
that comes later.

205
00:06:57,340 --> 00:06:58,530
at dinner.

206
00:06:58,540 --> 00:07:01,020
he did invite you to dinner, didn't he?

207
00:07:01,760 --> 00:07:03,260
let me buy you dinner

208
00:07:03,270 --> 00:07:04,460
tomorrow night

209
00:07:04,470 --> 00:07:06,080
as a thank you, okay?

210
00:07:06,080 --> 00:07:08,230
you'll tell me all about the nrdc,

211
00:07:08,240 --> 00:07:10,940
and we'll charge it all to one of my evil clients.

212
00:07:11,060 --> 00:07:12,090
i, you know, i don't know,

213
00:07:12,090 --> 00:07:13,410
-i don't know if... -marshall,

214
00:07:14,200 --> 00:07:16,320
you know what kobe beef is?

215
00:07:17,510 --> 00:07:20,080
the most expensive beef in the world.

216
00:07:20,240 --> 00:07:24,000
the place i'm taking you has kobe lobster.

217
00:07:24,010 --> 00:07:28,460
that is lobster fed with kobe beef.

218
00:07:29,120 --> 00:07:32,160
oh, my god, he's trying to seduce me.

219
00:07:32,170 --> 00:07:33,990
so are you gonna go to dinner with him?

220
00:07:34,000 --> 00:07:35,710
no. no way.

221
00:07:35,720 --> 00:07:38,170
i promised myself to the nrdc.

222
00:07:38,180 --> 00:07:39,490
i'm not that kind of lawyer.

223
00:07:39,500 --> 00:07:40,740
oh, you should go.

224
00:07:40,750 --> 00:07:41,910
i mean, you're not gonna take the job,

225
00:07:41,910 --> 00:07:42,580
but you might as well

226
00:07:42,580 --> 00:07:44,720
get a great meal out of the deal.

227
00:07:44,730 --> 00:07:46,350
don't wait up.

228
00:07:47,020 --> 00:07:48,230
guys, guys, guys, check this out.

229
00:07:48,230 --> 00:07:49,980
ted mosby porn star's bio

230
00:07:49,980 --> 00:07:51,990
says his hometown is your hometown.

231
00:07:51,990 --> 00:07:53,360
shaker heights, ohio.

232
00:07:53,370 --> 00:07:54,320
what?

233
00:07:54,330 --> 00:07:55,720
okay, this is getting creepy.

234
00:07:55,720 --> 00:07:57,160
who, who is this guy?

235
00:07:57,170 --> 00:07:58,270
i gotta find him.

236
00:07:58,280 --> 00:07:59,180
well, it's your lucky day.

237
00:07:59,180 --> 00:07:59,980
he's gonna be signing

238
00:07:59,980 --> 00:08:01,770
autographs tomorrow night in manhattan

239
00:08:01,770 --> 00:08:04,360
at something called the adult video expo.

240
00:08:04,370 --> 00:08:04,970
mm. wait.

241
00:08:04,980 --> 00:08:05,780
are you telling me

242
00:08:05,780 --> 00:08:08,230
that they actually have conventions for porn?

243
00:08:08,240 --> 00:08:09,070
affirmative.

244
00:08:09,080 --> 00:08:10,810
or to put it another way...

245
00:08:10,820 --> 00:08:13,160
god bless america.

246
00:08:16,200 --> 00:08:18,440
you can really taste the beef in that lobster.

247
00:08:18,440 --> 00:08:19,930
right.

248
00:08:20,540 --> 00:08:22,050
listen,

249
00:08:22,060 --> 00:08:23,940
i know we're only here to screw over my client,

250
00:08:23,940 --> 00:08:26,260
who quite frankly deserves it...

251
00:08:26,650 --> 00:08:28,530
but i gotta be able to tell the guys upstairs

252
00:08:28,530 --> 00:08:30,550
i gave you the spiel, okay?

253
00:08:30,560 --> 00:08:32,110
so, first up,

254
00:08:32,230 --> 00:08:33,710
starting salary.

255
00:08:33,720 --> 00:08:35,000
okay.

256
00:08:35,010 --> 00:08:36,290
here we go.

257
00:08:36,300 --> 00:08:39,860
this is the big number that's supposed to impress me and--

258
00:08:40,520 --> 00:08:43,720
that is a big number.

259
00:08:44,060 --> 00:08:45,610
there's also a signing bonus,

260
00:08:45,620 --> 00:08:47,380
uh, use of a company car,

261
00:08:47,390 --> 00:08:49,050
expense account, blah blah blah.

262
00:08:49,050 --> 00:08:52,260
hey, by the way, turn around and wave to patrick swayze.

263
00:08:52,270 --> 00:08:53,670


264
00:08:56,070 --> 00:08:58,430
i'm going to, uh, try to remain cool.

265
00:08:58,440 --> 00:09:00,980
but you know patrick swayze?!

266
00:09:00,990 --> 00:09:01,720
he's a client.

267
00:09:01,730 --> 00:09:02,890
who do you think bought us this wine.

268
00:09:02,890 --> 00:09:04,790
crazy swayze.

269
00:09:04,800 --> 00:09:06,400
cheers, buddy.

270
00:09:07,600 --> 00:09:08,610
okay. no.

271
00:09:08,620 --> 00:09:10,410
jeff, this is all very impressive,

272
00:09:10,410 --> 00:09:11,960
-but i just don't think that... -listen, i know,

273
00:09:11,970 --> 00:09:13,370
i know.

274
00:09:13,390 --> 00:09:16,740
you're gonna be tempted by big numbers and fancy perks.

275
00:09:16,750 --> 00:09:18,520
you're gonna do the noble thing,

276
00:09:18,530 --> 00:09:21,030
take the low-paying job at the nrdc,

277
00:09:21,040 --> 00:09:22,970
live off your family money.

278
00:09:22,980 --> 00:09:24,600
family money?

279
00:09:24,680 --> 00:09:26,320
you do have family money, don't you?

280
00:09:26,330 --> 00:09:28,280
no, um, not that i know of.

281
00:09:28,290 --> 00:09:33,150
i do have an uncle who owns a, a pretty successful bait shop.

282
00:09:33,360 --> 00:09:34,900
nrdc.

283
00:09:34,910 --> 00:09:37,610
no family money.

284
00:09:39,660 --> 00:09:41,650
so you don't plan on having kids?

285
00:09:41,660 --> 00:09:44,360
actually, i, i want to have four kids.

286
00:09:46,800 --> 00:09:48,950
new york public schools make a lot of parents nervous,

287
00:09:48,950 --> 00:09:53,520
but the kids who walk out, walk out proud.

288
00:09:54,340 --> 00:09:56,190
he was surely doing a tough decision

289
00:09:56,200 --> 00:09:58,110
now, kids, when i'm faced with a tough decision

290
00:09:58,120 --> 00:10:01,600
i like to make a list of pros and cons.

291
00:10:01,610 --> 00:10:03,140
marshall knew all cons

292
00:10:03,150 --> 00:10:04,900
but that is one thing he didn't konw

293
00:10:04,910 --> 00:10:07,110
a big guy live in a pros con

294
00:10:07,120 --> 00:10:08,760
lily, you're a kindergarten teacher.

295
00:10:08,770 --> 00:10:10,070
-yeah. -cause robin

296
00:10:10,070 --> 00:10:12,660
was about to ask lily the one question...

297
00:10:12,670 --> 00:10:15,660
an-and you make a kindergarten teacher's salary, right?

298
00:10:15,670 --> 00:10:16,580
yeah.

299
00:10:16,590 --> 00:10:18,620
...that lily had been dreading for years.

300
00:10:18,630 --> 00:10:21,500
well, how do you afford all of these expensivelothes?

301
00:10:21,830 --> 00:10:23,950
i shop the sales.

302
00:10:23,970 --> 00:10:26,500
they were in the closet when we moved in.

303
00:10:26,840 --> 00:10:28,170
i steal.

304
00:10:28,180 --> 00:10:29,530
i'm a criminal.

305
00:10:29,540 --> 00:10:32,560
i once shot a man just to watch him die.

306
00:10:33,190 --> 00:10:33,820
lily?

307
00:10:33,820 --> 00:10:36,130
okay.

308
00:10:36,140 --> 00:10:39,060
that's when lily showed robin her box of shame.

309
00:10:40,870 --> 00:10:42,740
lily, this is nuts.

310
00:10:42,750 --> 00:10:44,300
how many credit cards do you have?

311
00:10:44,310 --> 00:10:45,030
i don't know.

312
00:10:45,030 --> 00:10:46,750
well, how much do you owe?

313
00:10:46,760 --> 00:10:48,470
i don't know!

314
00:10:52,090 --> 00:10:55,500
i can't believe this many people love porn this much,

315
00:10:55,660 --> 00:10:58,690
including that guy who works in human resources at my firm.

316
00:10:58,700 --> 00:11:01,560
let's just wave at each other awkwardly.

317
00:11:01,570 --> 00:11:03,190
that'll make it better.

318
00:11:03,790 --> 00:11:05,760
dude, come on, let's just find bizarro me

319
00:11:05,760 --> 00:11:07,330
and get out of here.

320
00:11:07,490 --> 00:11:09,030
oh, i get it.

321
00:11:09,040 --> 00:11:10,610
ted mosby, non-porn star,

322
00:11:10,610 --> 00:11:13,060
thinks this is all crude and disgusting.

323
00:11:13,070 --> 00:11:14,010
you know wholse was considered

324
00:11:14,010 --> 00:11:15,470
crude and disgusting?

325
00:11:15,480 --> 00:11:17,030
shakespeare.

326
00:11:17,040 --> 00:11:18,010
hmm. but his themes--

327
00:11:18,020 --> 00:11:21,290
love, lust, forbidden desire-- were universal,

328
00:11:21,290 --> 00:11:24,320
which is why his work has stood the test of time.

329
00:11:24,330 --> 00:11:26,020
and so will all this.

330
00:11:26,030 --> 00:11:29,800
400 years from now, some high school drama class

331
00:11:29,800 --> 00:11:32,910
will be doing a plucky, spirited production

332
00:11:32,920 --> 00:11:35,560
of beef party vii.

333
00:11:36,120 --> 00:11:38,940
oh, my god, lily, that is a lot of debt.

334
00:11:38,950 --> 00:11:41,390
how did you get yourself into this situation?

335
00:11:41,400 --> 00:11:42,840
i don't know what it is.

336
00:11:42,850 --> 00:11:45,860
when i feel down about something, i shop.

337
00:11:47,330 --> 00:11:48,650
ma'am, is everything okay? oh,

338
00:11:48,660 --> 00:11:51,160
i just had a huge fight with my mother.

339
00:11:51,170 --> 00:11:53,600
she doesn't understand me at all.

340
00:11:55,020 --> 00:11:57,040
i swore that teaching would be a way

341
00:11:57,040 --> 00:11:58,420
to support my painting career,

342
00:11:58,420 --> 00:12:01,210
but i never paint anymore.

343
00:12:02,560 --> 00:12:05,750
i just got a huge credit card bill.

344
00:12:06,730 --> 00:12:07,430
does marshall know?

345
00:12:07,430 --> 00:12:08,630
no.

346
00:12:08,640 --> 00:12:09,890
but you guys are the couple

347
00:12:09,890 --> 00:12:11,670
who tell each other everything.

348
00:12:11,680 --> 00:12:12,660
and for god's sakes, lily,

349
00:12:12,660 --> 00:12:15,110
you text him while he's on the can.

350
00:12:15,120 --> 00:12:18,100
well, i just want him to know i'm rooting for him.

351
00:12:18,440 --> 00:12:20,980
wait, okay, this all makes sense.

352
00:12:20,990 --> 00:12:22,220
so when you said...

353
00:12:22,230 --> 00:12:23,250
but you're still going to go

354
00:12:23,250 --> 00:12:25,160
to your job interview today, right, baby?

355
00:12:25,170 --> 00:12:26,030
and then...

356
00:12:26,040 --> 00:12:27,180
oh, you should go.

357
00:12:27,190 --> 00:12:28,260
i mean, you're not going to take the job,

358
00:12:28,260 --> 00:12:30,740
but you might as well get a great meal out of the deal.

359
00:12:30,750 --> 00:12:31,600
you were pushing him

360
00:12:31,600 --> 00:12:34,020
into taking that high- paying corporate job.

361
00:12:34,030 --> 00:12:34,700
i know.

362
00:12:34,700 --> 00:12:37,580
it's terrible that i was trying to get him to do that.

363
00:12:37,590 --> 00:12:38,480
terrible

364
00:12:38,490 --> 00:12:39,720
he has to take it

365
00:12:39,730 --> 00:12:42,520
i mean, how else are you going to pay off all that debt?

366
00:12:42,530 --> 00:12:43,060
lily, you have

367
00:12:43,060 --> 00:12:46,170
to tell him about this before he turns down that job.

368
00:12:46,510 --> 00:12:47,570
you're right.

369
00:12:47,580 --> 00:12:49,510
i feel awful.

370
00:12:50,900 --> 00:12:53,630
-you know there is a sale...-we're not going to shopping

371
00:12:59,910 --> 00:13:02,070
ooh, there he is. come on, let's go.

372
00:13:02,680 --> 00:13:05,200
why do i get so nervous around celebrities?

373
00:13:05,950 --> 00:13:07,660
hi, ted mosby.

374
00:13:07,730 --> 00:13:10,040
i'm ted mosby.

375
00:13:10,050 --> 00:13:11,650
ted mosby, it's you.

376
00:13:11,660 --> 00:13:12,620
have we met?

377
00:13:12,630 --> 00:13:15,260
mr. mosby, it is an honor to meet you, sir.

378
00:13:15,270 --> 00:13:15,940
starney binson.

379
00:13:15,940 --> 00:13:17,430
barney stinson.

380
00:13:17,440 --> 00:13:18,540
damn it.

381
00:13:18,550 --> 00:13:19,840
we have met.

382
00:13:19,850 --> 00:13:21,830
my real name is steve biel.

383
00:13:22,020 --> 00:13:24,310
when i was in fourth grade, you were in ninth,

384
00:13:24,410 --> 00:13:25,080
one day i was behind the school

385
00:13:25,180 --> 00:13:26,450
and a bunch of seventh graders

386
00:13:26,460 --> 00:13:28,530
were just beating the crap out of me.

387
00:13:28,540 --> 00:13:30,270
oh, yeah, i remember. that was you?

388
00:13:30,280 --> 00:13:32,550
yeah, but you pulled them off me.

389
00:13:32,560 --> 00:13:35,660
you told them to go pick on someone their own size.

390
00:13:35,950 --> 00:13:39,480
i vowed right then that when i made something of myself,

391
00:13:39,490 --> 00:13:41,540
i would honor you somehow.

392
00:13:41,550 --> 00:13:44,270
so you took my name and starred

393
00:13:44,280 --> 00:13:46,540
in welcometo the sex truck?

394
00:13:47,060 --> 00:13:48,770
yeah.

395
00:13:49,470 --> 00:13:52,250
um, yeah, listen, ted, you got to stop using my name.

396
00:13:52,250 --> 00:13:55,280
i-i'm trying to make a career as an architect.

397
00:13:55,290 --> 00:13:56,760
architect, huh?

398
00:13:56,770 --> 00:13:59,710
you mean like a sex architect?

399
00:13:59,720 --> 00:14:01,780
-what? -yeah, you know, you're on to something.

400
00:14:01,780 --> 00:14:04,110
that would make a great title of a film.

401
00:14:04,120 --> 00:14:07,470
ted mosby, sex architect.

402
00:14:07,500 --> 00:14:09,960
you know, i'm actually looking for a new project

403
00:14:09,960 --> 00:14:12,210
to shoot next friday afternoon.

404
00:14:12,590 --> 00:14:14,640
yeah, listen, isn't, isn't there some other way

405
00:14:14,650 --> 00:14:16,200
you could honor me?

406
00:14:16,210 --> 00:14:17,900
with all due respect.

407
00:14:17,910 --> 00:14:20,100
wait, you're not mad, are you?

408
00:14:20,440 --> 00:14:22,400
oh, man, i knew it.

409
00:14:22,410 --> 00:14:25,870
my father said, "just plant a tree in israel."

410
00:14:25,890 --> 00:14:27,260
i'm such an idiot.

411
00:14:27,270 --> 00:14:29,610
i guess i thought you'd be psyched.

412
00:14:31,160 --> 00:14:32,680
i am.

413
00:14:32,690 --> 00:14:33,270
i am; it's just

414
00:14:33,270 --> 00:14:35,510
i feel a little guilty beuse i'm not

415
00:14:35,510 --> 00:14:37,550
the one who saved you that day.

416
00:14:37,560 --> 00:14:40,620
the guy who actually saved you was...

417
00:14:40,630 --> 00:14:46,090
named... lance hardwood.

418
00:14:46,750 --> 00:14:49,110
lance hardwood, yeah.

419
00:14:49,120 --> 00:14:51,100
really? mm.

420
00:14:51,350 --> 00:14:52,940
you know, you might not know this,

421
00:14:52,950 --> 00:14:56,220
but in my business, that's kind of a killer name.

422
00:14:57,100 --> 00:14:59,110
yeah, i guess, i guess it is.

423
00:14:59,120 --> 00:15:00,670
i can see the poster now.

424
00:15:00,680 --> 00:15:03,310
lance hardwood, sex architect.

425
00:15:03,320 --> 00:15:03,850
starring...

426
00:15:03,850 --> 00:15:05,360
ted mosby.

427
00:15:05,370 --> 00:15:07,030
i love it.

428
00:15:08,860 --> 00:15:11,220
marshall and jeff stayed pretty late at the restaurant.

429
00:15:11,230 --> 00:15:12,070
they stayed so late

430
00:15:12,070 --> 00:15:14,070
that marshall crashed on jeff's couch,

431
00:15:14,080 --> 00:15:15,000
and the next day,

432
00:15:15,010 --> 00:15:17,210
marshall took part in a sunday morning 

433
00:15:17,310 --> 00:15:19,520
tradition as old as the city itself

434
00:15:19,530 --> 00:15:21,250
the walk of shame,

435
00:15:21,260 --> 00:15:23,730
the long journey home after doing something you regret

436
00:15:23,740 --> 00:15:24,780
the night before.

437
00:15:24,790 --> 00:15:26,040
i'll take the job.

438
00:15:26,040 --> 00:15:28,430
that's awesome!

439
00:15:29,750 --> 00:15:31,640
great time last night.

440
00:15:31,720 --> 00:15:33,340
i'll call you later.

441
00:15:33,770 --> 00:15:35,620
he's not going to call you.

442
00:15:39,820 --> 00:15:41,570
um, did you get my message?

443
00:15:41,570 --> 00:15:42,960
i just, i crashed uptown. yeah, yeah.

444
00:15:42,970 --> 00:15:47,170
listen, i have, uh, something to tell you.

445
00:15:47,180 --> 00:15:49,810
uh, i have something i need to tell you also.

446
00:15:49,820 --> 00:15:51,760
mine's pretty huge.

447
00:15:51,920 --> 00:15:53,560
you go first.

448
00:15:53,570 --> 00:15:55,310
-well... -i took

449
00:15:55,310 --> 00:15:56,850
the job.

450
00:15:57,050 --> 00:15:57,630
i'm sorry.

451
00:15:57,630 --> 00:15:58,610
i'm so sorry.

452
00:15:58,610 --> 00:15:59,760
i was drunk,

453
00:15:59,770 --> 00:16:04,190
and it was a haze of cigars and scotch and swayze,

454
00:16:04,200 --> 00:16:06,120
and they offered me, like,

455
00:16:06,130 --> 00:16:09,230
like, like, like, a lot of money.

456
00:16:09,400 --> 00:16:11,330
oh, marshall.

457
00:16:12,170 --> 00:16:13,790
how much money?

458
00:16:17,420 --> 00:16:18,900
here.

459
00:16:26,700 --> 00:16:27,910
it's completely despicable.

460
00:16:27,910 --> 00:16:29,830
i know, i know, i sold out

461
00:16:29,830 --> 00:16:34,300
for a huge pile of disgusting money,

462
00:16:34,310 --> 00:16:38,780
disgusting money that could help our future family

463
00:16:38,790 --> 00:16:40,410
have some financial security

464
00:16:40,420 --> 00:16:42,200
and could help pay for law school.

465
00:16:42,210 --> 00:16:43,740
law school.

466
00:16:43,860 --> 00:16:46,170
law school that i went to to help protect the environment,

467
00:16:46,170 --> 00:16:47,330
not help destroy it.

468
00:16:47,330 --> 00:16:48,180
and for what?

469
00:16:48,180 --> 00:16:51,870
for, for... a lot of money.

470
00:16:56,220 --> 00:16:58,180
okay, okay, you've got to stop screaming.

471
00:16:58,190 --> 00:16:58,720
listen, marshall,

472
00:16:58,720 --> 00:17:00,850
you know what i like to do in situations like this?

473
00:17:00,860 --> 00:17:03,510
ted, if you say make a list of pros and cons,

474
00:17:03,510 --> 00:17:04,910
i'm going to smack you.

475
00:17:04,920 --> 00:17:06,280
i wasn't going to say that.

476
00:17:06,290 --> 00:17:08,020
okay, two beers,

477
00:17:08,030 --> 00:17:10,590
and ted, here's that yellow legal pad you asked for.

478
00:17:10,590 --> 00:17:12,210
yellow legal pad?

479
00:17:12,220 --> 00:17:13,250
i ordered fries.

480
00:17:13,250 --> 00:17:16,280
maybe you should use this to write down people's orders.

481
00:17:18,960 --> 00:17:21,550
guys, i, i don't know what to do.

482
00:17:21,560 --> 00:17:22,470
take the money.

483
00:17:22,480 --> 00:17:25,830
money is good, money is happiness.

484
00:17:25,840 --> 00:17:26,550
if i work there,

485
00:17:26,550 --> 00:17:30,030
i'll be representing the most evil corporations in the world.

486
00:17:30,040 --> 00:17:32,380
kind of sounds like a pro and con list to me.

487
00:17:32,950 --> 00:17:34,100
lily, you have to tell him.

488
00:17:34,100 --> 00:17:35,990
you can help him make this decision.

489
00:17:36,000 --> 00:17:38,930
oh, i think he's doing fine on his own.

490
00:17:39,230 --> 00:17:42,280
@#$%^&*@#$%^&*

491
00:17:43,780 --> 00:17:45,490
all right.

492
00:17:49,070 --> 00:17:50,510
marshall,

493
00:17:51,480 --> 00:17:52,760
i have something to say,

494
00:17:52,770 --> 00:17:54,680
and it's going to help you make your decision.

495
00:17:54,690 --> 00:17:58,110
oh, of course, you know my heart better than i do.

496
00:17:58,120 --> 00:18:00,170
you know what's best for me and for us.

497
00:18:00,180 --> 00:18:03,030
please, please tell me what to do.

498
00:18:07,820 --> 00:18:11,260
i think you should take the job at the nrdc.

499
00:18:11,270 --> 00:18:14,070
of course i should, of course i should.

500
00:18:14,180 --> 00:18:15,290
guys,

501
00:18:15,300 --> 00:18:17,880
i'm going to save the planet earth.

502
00:18:17,890 --> 00:18:19,640
i got to go call jeff.

503
00:18:23,810 --> 00:18:25,090
what is the matter with you?

504
00:18:25,100 --> 00:18:27,040
i can't ask him to make himself miserable

505
00:18:27,040 --> 00:18:29,190
because of a mistake i made.

506
00:18:29,200 --> 00:18:31,760
it's my problem; i'll figure it out.

507
00:18:32,200 --> 00:18:33,860
that's really sweet.

508
00:18:34,610 --> 00:18:35,300
are those new earrings?

509
00:18:35,300 --> 00:18:37,190
what are you, my mom?

510
00:18:37,980 --> 00:18:41,040
jeff, hey, um, it's marshall.

511
00:18:41,050 --> 00:18:42,470
hey, marshall.

512
00:18:42,480 --> 00:18:44,480
i have something that i need to tell you.

513
00:18:44,490 --> 00:18:47,160
i feel really weird about doing this over the phone.

514
00:18:47,170 --> 00:18:48,660
then don't.

515
00:18:50,530 --> 00:18:51,540
before you say anything,

516
00:18:51,550 --> 00:18:54,830
come take a ride in this awesome limo with me.

517
00:18:55,130 --> 00:18:56,590
where are we going?

518
00:18:56,600 --> 00:18:58,560
tuckahoe funland.

519
00:18:58,900 --> 00:18:59,960
i'm sorry.

520
00:18:59,970 --> 00:19:02,250
it sounded like you said tuckahoe funland,

521
00:19:02,250 --> 00:19:05,100
the magic factory where dreams are made.

522
00:19:05,110 --> 00:19:06,600
get in.

523
00:19:11,570 --> 00:19:14,270
man, i-i love this place.

524
00:19:14,280 --> 00:19:15,860
me, too, buddy.

525
00:19:16,400 --> 00:19:18,120
so what did you want to tell me?

526
00:19:19,810 --> 00:19:21,660
i can't work for you.

527
00:19:21,730 --> 00:19:23,100
i know, dude.

528
00:19:23,110 --> 00:19:24,610
it's fine.

529
00:19:24,620 --> 00:19:27,390
marshall eriksen wants to preserve the environment,

530
00:19:27,400 --> 00:19:29,390
so that our children can enjoy it as we have.

531
00:19:29,390 --> 00:19:30,970
i get it.

532
00:19:31,600 --> 00:19:33,900
good. thank you.

533
00:19:34,380 --> 00:19:38,470
i look down and see children enjoying this place.

534
00:19:39,220 --> 00:19:42,280
yeah, because somebody fought to preserve it.

535
00:19:42,690 --> 00:19:45,140
if they ever shut this place down, it would be a tragedy.

536
00:19:45,150 --> 00:19:48,700
well, the good news is, that'll never happen.

537
00:19:48,950 --> 00:19:50,670
you won't let it.

538
00:19:51,100 --> 00:19:52,720
because when you work for us,

539
00:19:52,730 --> 00:19:56,420
your only client will be this place--

540
00:19:56,580 --> 00:19:59,010
tuckahoe funland.

541
00:20:02,410 --> 00:20:03,870
i'm taking the job.

542
00:20:03,880 --> 00:20:04,730
hey! all right.

543
00:20:04,730 --> 00:20:05,530
and the best part is

544
00:20:05,530 --> 00:20:06,520
i'm not even going to be representing

545
00:20:06,520 --> 00:20:07,810
some sort of evil corporation.

546
00:20:07,810 --> 00:20:11,390
i will be representing tuckahoe funland,

547
00:20:11,400 --> 00:20:13,460
the least evil place in the world.

548
00:20:13,470 --> 00:20:14,880
or so marshall thought.

549
00:20:14,890 --> 00:20:16,360


550
00:20:16,370 --> 00:20:17,760


551
00:20:17,760 --> 00:20:21,030


552
00:20:26,800 --> 00:20:28,730
oh, i'd better check on him.

553
00:20:29,330 --> 00:20:35,230


554
00:20:40,560 --> 00:20:42,110
lance hardwood,

555
00:20:42,120 --> 00:20:44,660
sex architect starring ted mosby.

556
00:20:44,670 --> 00:20:45,930
terrific.

557
00:20:45,940 --> 00:20:47,990
you'll notice i'm in the credits.

558
00:20:48,000 --> 00:20:50,300
i did some location scouting.

559
00:20:57,500 --> 00:21:01,320
here are the plans for the new international sex building.

560
00:21:01,620 --> 00:21:05,060
wow, that really looks like our apartment.

561
00:21:05,070 --> 00:21:05,810
it is.

562
00:21:05,820 --> 00:21:08,160
oh, i should return these.

563
00:21:09,230 --> 00:21:12,800
sex architect, you've done it again.

564
00:21:12,810 --> 00:21:16,050
let's go celebrate on the couch.

565
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


566
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000

