1
00:00:00,820 --> 00:00:02,360
Previously
On "Private Practice"...

2
00:00:02,360 --> 00:00:04,690
You've Been Downgraded
To Acquaintance. I'm Moving On.

3
00:00:04,690 --> 00:00:05,610
||
I Was Wondering

4
00:00:05,610 --> 00:00:08,650
If You Would Be Interested
In Having A Drink With Me.

5
00:00:08,650 --> 00:00:11,230
- Oh.
- What We DidThe Other Night? Not A Sin.

6
00:00:11,230 --> 00:00:13,660
You Do A Lot For The Practice.
But I Do It For You.

7
00:00:13,660 --> 00:00:15,510
I Am Not Having Sex With You
Just Because

8
00:00:15,510 --> 00:00:18,470
I Wrote Some Things
On The Internet.

9
00:00:18,470 --> 00:00:20,140
Thank You So Much.

10
00:00:20,140 --> 00:00:22,720
Uh, Uh, Pete Helped.

11
00:00:22,720 --> 00:00:27,380
They Saved A Marriage.

12
00:00:29,750 --> 00:00:33,900
- It's Not Erupting.
- It'll Erupt. Just Wait.

13
00:00:33,900 --> 00:00:38,170
It's Not Erupting.Just Wait.

14
00:00:38,170 --> 00:00:39,690
- It's Not Erupting.
- Told You.

15
00:00:39,690 --> 00:00:41,610
Why Didn't Your Daughter
Do Her Own Science Project?

16
00:00:41,610 --> 00:00:44,950
Because When Maya's Happy,
Naomi's Happy.

17
00:00:44,950 --> 00:00:46,200
I Thought The Point
Of Getting Divorced

18
00:00:46,200 --> 00:00:48,320
Is You Stop Being The Keeper
Of Your Ex-Wife's Happiness.

19
00:00:48,320 --> 00:00:49,700
Yeah, Right.

20
00:00:49,700 --> 00:00:51,430
Are You Trying To Get
Back In Naomi's Pants?

21
00:00:51,430 --> 00:00:54,800
N-No. I Am Not.

22
00:00:54,800 --> 00:00:56,620
Her Pants Are Her Pants.

23
00:00:56,620 --> 00:00:59,260
Do Not Sleep With Naomi.
I Am--Why?

24
00:00:59,260 --> 00:01:01,610
Office Drama. We Don't Need
Any More Office Drama.

25
00:01:01,610 --> 00:01:03,730
Just Because You Couldn't
Seal The Deal With Addison

26
00:01:03,730 --> 00:01:06,020
And You Couldn't
Seal The Deal With Viot...

27
00:01:06,020 --> 00:01:11,090
I Seal The Deal.
Okay, I... Seal The Deal.

28
00:01:11,090 --> 00:01:13,640
Not That I'm Sealing
Anything With Naomi,

29
00:01:13,640 --> 00:01:18,290
'Cause I'm Not Sealing...
With Naomi.

30
00:01:18,290 --> 00:01:22,280
Casual Sex
With Virtual Strangers,

31
00:01:22,280 --> 00:01:23,310
That's The Way To Go.

32
00:01:23,310 --> 00:01:25,640
Yeah, How's That
Working Out For You?

33
00:01:25,640 --> 00:01:28,260
Actually, It's Working Out
Just Fine. I Gotta Go.

34
00:01:28,260 --> 00:01:31,950
W-Wait...
Gotta Go.

35
00:01:31,950 --> 00:01:38,800
- I Think He May Be Smarter Than Us.
- Me, Too.

36
00:01:40,120 --> 00:01:42,760
Next Time,I Wanna Be Bad Cop.
Pardon Me?

37
00:01:42,760 --> 00:01:44,810
You Know, The Whole Dirty,
Bossy Thing You Got Going.

38
00:01:44,810 --> 00:01:46,150
Don't Get Me Wrong,
I Like It.

39
00:01:46,150 --> 00:01:48,190
But I Wanna, You Know,
As A Male Of The Species, I--

40
00:01:48,190 --> 00:01:52,160
Understood.Still Not Gonna Happen.
Okay.

41
00:01:52,160 --> 00:01:53,700
Now Unlike
You Oceanside People,

42
00:01:53,700 --> 00:01:56,910
I Still Have A Busy Y--
Patients, Uh, Meetings.

43
00:01:56,910 --> 00:01:58,460
I Have To Find
A New Instructor

44
00:01:58,460 --> 00:02:01,010
For This Parenting Class
For Tads Tonight.

45
00:02:01,010 --> 00:02:04,540
||
So Unless You Are Applying
To Be My Assistant,

46
00:02:04,540 --> 00:02:06,900
Enough With The Questions.

47
00:02:06,900 --> 00:02:11,800
God. I Almost Forget I'm Having Sex
With Charlotte King.

48
00:02:11,800 --> 00:02:13,630
Isn't Finding A Teacher
For Dad's Class

49
00:02:13,630 --> 00:02:15,520
Kinda Small Potatoes
For A Chief Of Sff?

50
00:02:15,520 --> 00:02:18,080
I Mean, A-A Dirty,
Bossy Chief Of||Taff.

51
00:02:18,080 --> 00:02:20,430
No, Sir. Big Potatoes.

52
00:02:20,430 --> 00:02:22,760
One Of The Hospital's
Biggest Moneymakers.

53
00:02:22,760 --> 00:02:25,210
We Wipe The Floor
With The Oer Classes In Town.

54
00:02:25,210 --> 00:02:27,630
You Have To Be Competitive
About Everything, Right?

55
00:02:27,630 --> 00:02:30,610
You Always Have To Win.
You Want Me Back TonightOr Not?

56
00:02:30,610 --> 00:02:31,950
I Wanna Be B

57
00:02:31,950 --> 00:02:40,280
You're Not The Bad Cop Type.Now Yes Or No?

58
00:02:40,280 --> 00:02:46,700
Okay, Fine, Yes.

59
00:02:59,960 --> 00:03:02,270
I Am Not Afraid Of Being
In A Relationship With Sam.

60
00:03:02,270 --> 00:03:04,500
We Are Not
Getting Back Together.

61
00:03:04,500 --> 00:03:06,870
You're Afraid Of Talking To Sam
About Being In A Relationship?

62
00:03:06,870 --> 00:03:09,540
Y-You Want To Be?
I'm Just Saying Sam IsOne Of The Good Ones.

63
00:03:09,540 --> 00:03:11,390
Do You Know How Hard It Is
To Find A Good One?

64
00:03:11,390 --> 00:03:15,560
I Was Married To S.
I-I Know How Good He Is.

65
00:03:15,560 --> 00:03:18,130
He--He Is Good.
You Mean "Good" Good?

66
00:03:18,130 --> 00:03:19,780
You--You Mean--
You Mean Bed "Good"?

67
00:03:19,780 --> 00:03:24,020
No.
A-Absolutely Not. No.
Mm-Hmm.

68
00:03:24,020 --> 00:03:26,320
Okay, I'm--I'm Missing--
What Are We Talking About Here?

69
00:03:26,320 --> 00:03:28,560
Just Talk To Sam
About Where You're Going.

70
00:03:28,560 --> 00:03:29,590

You Won't Talk To Pete.

71
00:03:29,590 --> 00:03:31,680
Well, I'm NotIn A Relationship With Pete.
And She Won't TalkTo Cooper, So--

72
00:03:31,680 --> 00:03:34,950
We're Sort Of Taing.
I'm--I'm Trying To Get Over It.

73
00:03:34,950 --> 00:03:36,730
He's Not Over It.
He's Avoiding Me.

74
00:03:36,730 --> 00:03:40,530
What--What Are We
Talking About?

75
00:03:40,530 --> 00:03:41,570
Hello.
Good Morning.

76
00:03:41,570 --> 00:03:44,700
Good Morning.
Morning.

77
00:03:44,700 --> 00:03:46,200
See? Avoiding Me.

78
00:03:46,200 --> 00:03:50,980
I'm Gonna Go Talk To Pete
Right Now.

79
00:03:50,980 --> 00:03:52,620
Hey. Where's The Honey?

80
00:03:52,620 --> 00:03:55,450
Uh--All We Have Is This
Artificial Sweetener Crap.

81
00:03:55,450 --> 00:03:57,130
Food Should Weigh More
Than This.

82
00:03:57,130 --> 00:04:01,670
Can We... I've Been Thinking
About Things Between Us.

83
00:04:01,670 --> 00:04:02,680
Yeah. They've Been Weird.

84
00:04:02,680 --> 00:04:04,860
Just Because We Were Bad
At The Dating Thing

85
00:04:04,860 --> 00:04:08,350
Doesn't Mean That
We Have To Be UncomfortableAround Each Other.

86
00:04:08,350 --> 00:04:11,390
I Think That We ShouldBe Friends.
Friends?

87
00:04:11,390 --> 00:04:14,840
Yeah. I Hear Grown-Ups
Do It All The Time.

88
00:04:14,840 --> 00:04:16,910
Done.

89
00:04:16,910 --> 00:04:19,740
So...

90
00:04:19,740 --> 00:04:21,360
Oh, No. We Don't
Have To Start Right Now.

91
00:04:21,360 --> 00:04:24,910
Good.

92
00:04:24,910 --> 00:04:28,230
Hey,
My Officis Freezing.It's Frozen In There.

93
00:04:28,230 --> 00:04:30,590
I Need My Labs
For My 10:00.

94
00:04:30,590 --> 00:04:33,460
All Right. I'll Go Get Them.
Wait, Something Is Off Today.

95
00:04:33,460 --> 00:04:36,500
What Is--What Is Off?
Um...

96
00:04:36,500 --> 00:04:38,640
Jusbecause
Addison Found Out About ||,

97
00:04:38,640 --> 00:04:41,570
You Didn't Tell Her, Like,
Every Little Detail, Did You?

98
00:04:41,570 --> 00:04:44,200
And She Didn't TellEverybody Else, Right?
Well, No.

99
00:04:44,200 --> 00:04:45,450
Okay.
Why?

100
00:04:45,450 --> 00:04:47,680
No, It's Jus Uh,
Cooper Was Acting Like Maybe

101
00:04:47,680 --> 00:04:50,140
He Knew--
My Office Smells LikeA Dead Rat.

102
00:04:50,140 --> 00:04:52,280
Excuse Me?
No One Took Out The Trash.

103
00:04:52,280 --> 00:04:55,240
What Is Going On Today?

104
00:04:55,240 --> 00:04:56,640
I'm Here. I'm Here.

105
00:04:56,640 --> 00:04:57,970
Is Everything All Right?

106
00:04:57,970 --> 00:05:01,830
Yeah, It's Fine.
Uh, Sort Of.

107
00:05:01,830 --> 00:05:04,370
Is Ipossible You Could
Help Me With Something Medical?

108
00:05:04,370 --> 00:05:05,580
Yeah, Sure. What Is It?

109
00:05:05,580 --> 00:05:08,120
Um, It's My Pa Pa.
Something's Wrong.

110
00:05:08,120 --> 00:05:12,290
Your Pa Pa?
Yeah.

111
00:05:12,290 --> 00:05:13,260
Please Tell Me That

112
00:05:13,260 --> 00:05:14,840
That's Not
What You Call Your--

113
00:05:14,840 --> 00:05:16,680
N-No, No.
Okay.

114
00:05:16,680 --> 00:05:20,460
Um, My--My Grandfather.
Um, And His Friend Nate.

115
00:05:20,460 --> 00:05:25,260
I Think They're Being Abused
At Their Nursing Home.

116
00:05:25,260 --> 00:05:27,480
The Vaginismus--
Is It Recurring?

117
00:05:27,480 --> 00:05:28,680
No, Not At All.

118
00:05:28,680 --> 00:05:31,060
Once You Got Us Going,
Our Sex Has Been--

119
00:05:31,060 --> 00:05:33,640
Unbelievable||
I Mean, Really...

120
00:05:33,640 --> 00:05:36,550
We've Been Doing It Like Crazy
For The Last Two Months.

121
00:05:36,550 --> 00:05:40,720
I've Peed On I Don't Know
How Many Sticks. Nothing.

122
00:05:40,720 --> 00:05:42,570
Something's Just Not Right.
I Just Know It.

123
00:05:42,570 --> 00:05:44,250
I'm Just A Mess Down There.

124
00:05:44,250 --> 00:05:46,620
Cathleen, Two Mont--

125
00:05:46,620 --> 00:05:49,980
I Mean, It Tes
Couples Time To Conceive,

126
00:05:49,980 --> 00:05:51,640
Sometimes Up To A Year.

127
00:05:51,640 --> 00:05:54,860
I Know. I Just...
We Really Want To Have A Baby.

128
00:05:54,860 --> 00:05:56,370
And It's Not Like
I'm A Spring Chicken.

129
00:05:56,370 --> 00:05:58,240
It Took Me A Long Time
To Find Geoffrey.

130
00:05:58,240 --> 00:06:00,630
I Just Want To Know
That We Can.

131
00:06:00,630 --> 00:06:03,650
Okay. I'll, Uh,
Check Your F.S.H.

132
00:06:03,650 --> 00:06:05,980
And Get A Sample
From Geoffrey

133
00:06:05,980 --> 00:06:08,320
If That'll Make You
Feel Better.

134
00:06:08,320 --> 00:06:10,670
This Grandson Of Mine
Worries Too Much.

135
00:06:10,670 --> 00:06:13,720
Ever Since He Was A Boy--
Worry, Worry.

136
00:06:13,720 --> 00:06:16,460
No, He's Just Concerned
About You.

137
00:06:16,460 --> 00:06:18,060
Do--Do You See Those?

138
00:06:18,060 --> 00:06:19,960
Every Time I Go
To The Nursing He,There's Another One.

139
00:06:19,960 --> 00:06:21,900
And Look--
Look, Look, Look.

140
00:06:21,900 --> 00:06:26,710
Those Are Liver Spots, Kid.
You Have Lollipops Here?

141
00:06:26,710 --> 00:06:28,710
They're Just For The Kids.

142
00:06:28,710 --> 00:06:31,370
So, Uh, Where Are
These Bruises Coming From?

143
00:06:31,370 --> 00:06:33,990
I Don't Know.
He Says ThisEvery Time I Ask.

144
00:06:33,990 --> 00:06:35,550
Has Anyone Who Works
At The Nursing Home

145
00:06:35,550 --> 00:06:38,160
Hurt You In Any Way?
They Wouldn't Have The Nerve.

146
00:06:38,160 --> 00:06:39,980
I Spent Ten Years
In Thearine Corps,

147
00:06:39,980 --> 00:06:41,380
Fought In Korea--

148
00:06:41,380 --> 00:06:45,900
I'd Beat Them Down.
What About Dementia?

149
00:06:45,900 --> 00:06:48,750
What About Sleepwalking?
You, Uh, Bumping Into Things?

150
00:06:48,750 --> 00:06:50,220
What Am I, An Idiot?

151
00:06:50,220 --> 00:06:52,230
You Are Kind Of A Klutz.
Watch It.

152
00:06:52,230 --> 00:06:54,280
Or What, You'll Come Over Here
And Fall On Me?

153
00:06:54,280 --> 00:06:58,380
Look, My Memory Iss Sharp
As A Swiss Army Knife.

154
00:06:58,380 --> 00:07:01,820
Ask Me Anything From 1945 On,
And I'll Tell You.

155
00:07:01,820 --> 00:07:05,240
Okay.

156
00:07:05,240 --> 00:07:08,160
Your Grandfather Claims
He's Not Being Abused.

157
00:07:08,160 --> 00:07:09,320
I'm Inclined To Believe Him.

158
00:07:09,320 --> 00:07:11,380
Well, I'm Not.

159
00:07:11,380 --> 00:07:15,220
Look, He--He Would Never Say
If Something Like ThatWas Happening.

160
00:07:15,220 --> 00:07:17,980
What Am I Supposed To Do, Just
Wait Around And Hope I'm Wrong?

161
00:07:17,980 --> 00:07:21,000
Dell, I'm Ready.
Let's Go.

162
00:07:21,000 --> 00:07:26,290
- All Right.
- So Long. So Long.All Right. So Long.

163
00:07:28,920 --> 00:07:32,580
Oh.Hey.

164
00:07:32,580 --> 00:07:34,460
Dr. Montgomery.

165
00:07:34,460 --> 00:07:37,230
You're, Uh... Yore Dry.

166
00:07:37,230 --> 00:07:40,440
Uh...Last Time I Saw You,
You Were All Wet

167
00:07:40,440 --> 00:07:41,500
From The Birthing Tub.

168
00:07:41,500 --> 00:07:42,970
Yet You Still Recognize Me.

169
00:07:42,970 --> 00:07:46,550
Yes. Well, My Cop-Honed
Powers Of Deduction.

170
00:07:46,550 --> 00:07:49,480
I'm Waiting R Dr. Bennett.
I'm Having Him Do My Physical.

171
00:07:49,480 --> 00:07:51,890
Oh, You're A Patient Here?
Yeah, I HeardHe Delived A Baby

172
00:07:51,890 --> 00:07:54,470
Next To A Slurpee Machine.
Th Hdid.

173
00:07:54,470 --> 00:07:57,420
So He Must Be Good.
You Are In Good Hands.

174
00:07:57,420 --> 00:07:58,930
Officer Nelson?
Dr. Bennett.

175
00:07:58,930 --> 00:07:59,450
Yes.

176
00:07:59,450 --> 00:08:02,480
I'm Sorry. Uh, Dr. Montgomery
Was Just Distracting Me.

177
00:08:02,480 --> 00:08:05,090
Well, She Often Has
That Affect On People.

178
00:08:05,090 --> 00:08:08,610
Come On. Let's Do This.

179
00:08:10,210 --> 00:08:12,010
Here's The Pitch--
You And Me,

180
00:08:12,010 --> 00:08:14,150
2-Day Intensive Parenting Class
For New Fathers.

181
00:08:14,150 --> 00:08:15,710
You Do
Your Holistic Baby Thing.

182
00:08:15,710 --> 00:08:17,300
I Got A List Odad's
That Are Already On Board.

183
00:08:17,300 --> 00:08:20,820
All We Gotta DoIs Make The Call.
Did YouCome Up With This Yourself?

184
00:08:20,820 --> 00:08:22,870
Yes, Sir. It's Time We Got
More Aggressive And Competitive

185
00:08:22,870 --> 00:08:25,630
With Other Institutions,
Show Them Who's On Top.

186
00:08:25,630 --> 00:08:27,460
You Know What?
We're Guys Talking To Guys.

187
00:08:27,460 --> 00:08:30,460
We--We Can Handle This.
We Can Totally Handle It.

188
00:08:30,460 --> 00:08:33,480
Cooper And I Are Gonna
Teach A Parenting ClassTo Expectant Dads.

189
00:08:33,480 --> 00:08:35,810
You Never Told Me About
A Dad's Class. I Could--

190
00:08:35,810 --> 00:08:37,870
Oh, No, No, No. We're Gonna Go
Twosies On It, Do It Our Way.

191
00:08:37,870 --> 00:08:39,540
Wait A Minute, Wait A Minute,
The Insurance On That,

192
00:08:39,540 --> 00:08:40,880
That Could Cost A Lot Of--
It's Not A Problem.

193
00:08:40,880 --> 00:08:45,140
It's Gonna Bring In $20,000In 2 Days.
Everybody Needs ToLeave Cooper Alone.

194
00:08:45,140 --> 00:08:47,980
That's A Gat Idea.
Godspeed.

195
00:08:49,230 --> 00:08:52,620
So, So, Hey. What--What Were
You Up To Last Night?

196
00:08:52,620 --> 00:08:54,350
I Called You,
But Got No Answer.

197
00:08:54,350 --> 00:08:57,670
Ah, I Crashed Early.

198
00:08:57,670 --> 00:08:59,780
Hey, Pete.
Hey.

199
00:08:59,780 --> 00:09:03,910
Have Fun At Your Class.

200
00:09:03,910 --> 00:09:05,360
Have Fun At Your Class.

201
00:09:05,360 --> 00:09:08,750
I Am Being A Friend, Okay?
We Are Doing Friendship.

202
00:09:08,750 --> 00:09:09,770
Yeah, I'm Your Friend,

203
00:09:09,770 --> 00:09:11,710
And You Have Never Been
That Nice To Me, Ever.

204
00:09:11,710 --> 00:09:14,870
We're Adjusting, All Right.
Just--Thank You.

205
00:09:14,870 --> 00:09:16,570
Whenever We Give Each Other
A Hard Time

206
00:09:16,570 --> 00:09:20,030
Or We Start To Fight,I Mean, That's When...
Yeah, That's When

207
00:09:20,030 --> 00:09:22,580
The Two Of YouGet Hot For Each Other.
Yes, I Know.It's Twisted. But--

208
00:09:22,580 --> 00:09:25,100
Okay, And See That's WhyI Don't Know 
What To DoAbout My Cop, You Know?

209
00:09:25,100 --> 00:09:26,830
I Mean, I Think Maybe
He's Interested,

210
00:09:26,830 --> 00:09:28,780
But Then Maybe
I Shouldn't Inflict Myself

211
00:09:28,780 --> 00:09:31,550
On A Decent, Unsuspecting
Officer Of The Peace.

212
00:09:31,550 --> 00:09:34,510
Well, Maybe--Maybe That's
What You Need.

213
00:09:34,510 --> 00:09:37,020
Oh, I Don't Know.My Track Record
With Men Lately,

214
00:09:37,020 --> 00:09:43,750
He's Probably A Crazy.

215
00:09:45,200 --> 00:09:48,150
We Checked Your L.H. Levels,
And They're Normal.

216
00:09:48,150 --> 00:09:50,660
You're Ovulating.
Good.That's Good, Right?

217
00:09:50,660 --> 00:09:52,240
Well, We Did Find
Some Fibroids,

218
00:09:52,240 --> 00:09:54,960
So We Should Monitor ThemJust To-
-I Knew It. It's Always Me.

219
00:09:54,960 --> 00:09:56,930
First My Vagina Was Locked,
And Now--

220
00:09:56,930 --> 00:09:59,150
You Should Get Your Money Back.
I Am A Dud.

221
00:09:59,150 --> 00:10:02,640
The Fertility Issue
Doesn't Lie With You.

222
00:10:02,640 --> 00:10:04,580
Geoffrey, We Checked
Your Sperm Count,

223
00:10:04,580 --> 00:10:07,350
And Unfortunately,
It Was Very Low.

224
00:10:07,350 --> 00:10:10,170
H-How Low?

225
00:10:10,170 --> 00:10:12,950
There Are No Viable Sperm
In Your Specimen.

226
00:10:12,950 --> 00:10:21,800
I'm Sorry, Geoffrey.You're Sterile.

227
00:10:27,300 --> 00:10:29,040
I Know This Isn't
What You Want To Hear,

228
00:10:29,040 --> 00:10:30,040
But There Is Hope.

229
00:10:30,040 --> 00:10:31,940
When You're Ready,
There Are Other Options.

230
00:10:31,940 --> 00:10:34,450
There's Sperm Donation,
Adoption--

231
00:10:34,450 --> 00:10:38,230
The Main Thing Is, You Can
Have A Child, A Family.

232
00:10:38,230 --> 00:10:39,290
No Adoption.

233
00:10:39,290 --> 00:10:42,140
Wait. I Don't Know If We
Should Be Ruling That Out.

234
00:10:42,140 --> 00:10:44,030
We're GoingWith A Sperm Donor.
But, Honey--

235
00:10:44,030 --> 00:10:46,270
No. You've Always Wanted
To Be Pregnant.

236
00:10:46,270 --> 00:10:48,010
You've Always Wanted
A Baby Oyour Own.

237
00:10:48,010 --> 00:10:51,480
Do We Have To Decide Now?
Is There A Reason To Rush?

238
00:10:51,480 --> 00:10:54,410
Not To Rush, But, Uh,
Fertility Does Decline

239
00:10:54,410 --> 00:10:57,500
Every Year For A Woman
After The Age Of 35.

240
00:10:57,500 --> 00:11:00,660
And The Fibroids
Could Eventually Interfere--

241
00:11:00,660 --> 00:11:05,480
All Ght. We Get It.
We've Gotta Go For It Now.

242
00:11:05,480 --> 00:11:07,340
Look, They Said
You're Ovulating.

243
00:11:07,340 --> 00:11:10,110
Doesn't That Mean
We're In The Zone To Try?

244
00:11:10,110 --> 00:11:13,390
That's--That's Right. Yes.

245
00:11:13,390 --> 00:11:15,660
Are You Sure
You're Okay With This?

246
00:11:15,660 --> 00:11:17,750
Cathleen, I Love You.

247
00:11:17,750 --> 00:11:23,250
It's What You Want,
What I Want.

248
00:11:23,250 --> 00:11:26,350
I'm Sure.

249
00:11:26,350 --> 00:11:28,180
So What's Wrong
With Dell's Granddad?

250
00:11:28,180 --> 00:11:31,130
Oh, It's Just Some
Minor Bumps And Bruises.

251
00:11:31,130 --> 00:11:33,650
Dell's Concerned That There
Might Be Some Abuse Going On,

252
00:11:33,650 --> 00:11:36,290
But Nate And Wendell Are Adamant
That That's Not Happening.

253
00:11:36,290 --> 00:11:39,310
Well, Dell's Grandfather
Is A War Vet.

254
00:11:39,310 --> 00:11:41,270
I Think He'd Be Too Proud
To Admit Something Like That.

255
00:11:41,270 --> 00:11:42,440
Where's The Mom?

256
00:11:42,440 --> 00:11:44,210
Dell's Always Getting
Those Postcards From India

257
00:11:44,210 --> 00:11:46,290
And ChinaAnd All Over The Place?
Yeah, I Asked Him Once.

258
00:11:46,290 --> 00:11:49,430
He Said ThatShe Was A Rolling Stone.
Yeah, She Ro長Ed Right Off

259
00:11:49,430 --> 00:11:50,900
And Left Dell
With His Grandparents.

260
00:11:50,900 --> 00:11:52,770
Wendell Went Into A Home
After His Wife Died.

261
00:11:52,770 --> 00:11:56,360
Wow. You Sure Know
A Lot About Dell.
Seriously,

262
00:11:56,360 --> 00:11:58,050
If Dell Suspects Something,
Then Maybe You Should--

263
00:11:58,050 --> 00:12:00,010
I Just Read A Paper
About Der Abuse.

264
00:12:00,010 --> 00:12:02,350
-It's Way Underreported.
-All Right,I'll Call The Nursing Home,

265
00:12:02,350 --> 00:12:06,440
See If I Can Get Ahold
Of His Medical Records.

266
00:12:06,440 --> 00:12:08,250
Hey, Sam.

267
00:12:08,250 --> 00:12:10,720
Tell Me What That
Was About Earlier.

268
00:12:10,720 --> 00:12:14,570
Oh. Uh...

269
00:12:14,570 --> 00:12:16,270
I Just Think
Th It Would Be Nice

270
00:12:16,270 --> 00:12:18,000
If We Kept
This Thing Private.

271
00:12:18,000 --> 00:12:20,150
Well, Somebody Already
Found Out, Sam.

272
00:12:20,150 --> 00:12:22,660
And Honestly, I Don't Think
It's That Big Of A Deal.

273
00:12:22,660 --> 00:12:23,210
Oh.

274
00:12:23,210 --> 00:12:25,430
What, Are--A You Afraid That
This Is Gonna Mean Commitment?

275
00:12:25,430 --> 00:12:26,530
What? Because If, You Know,

276
00:12:26,530 --> 00:12:28,500
You're Ashamed Of Having S
With Your Ex-Wife--
Naomi--

277
00:12:28,500 --> 00:12:30,120
- Um, Naomi, 
- I Got These LabsFor Your Patient--

278
00:12:30,120 --> 00:12:36,150
- Just Leave It On My Desk.Excuse Me.
- All Right. Sorry.

279
00:12:36,150 --> 00:12:37,710
Jeez.

280
00:12:37,710 --> 00:12:38,890
They're Really
Going At It Lately.

281
00:12:38,890 --> 00:12:41,980
One Minute, They're Grinning,
Then The Next Minute They're--

282
00:12:41,980 --> 00:12:44,460
You Think They're
"Going At It"?

283
00:12:44,460 --> 00:12:46,000
Sex?
Yeah.

284
00:12:46,000 --> 00:12:49,060
No. No.
You Think So?

285
00:12:49,060 --> 00:12:51,910
As Much As They Argue?

286
00:12:51,910 --> 00:12:58,630
Angry Sex Is Hot.

287
00:12:58,630 --> 00:12:59,880
So I Called The Nursing Home,

288
00:12:59,880 --> 00:13:02,790
And They Sent Over Wendell
And Nate's Medical Recor.

289
00:13:02,790 --> 00:13:04,900
There Are A Bunch
Of Injury Reports

290
00:13:04,900 --> 00:13:08,750
In The Past Few Months--
Minor Scrapes, Bruises.

291
00:13:08,750 --> 00:13:10,150
So I Was Right
To Be Concerned.

292
00:13:10,150 --> 00:13:12,140
Well, It's Not Proof
Of Anything, But, Yeah,

293
00:13:12,140 --> 00:13:17,000
You Were Right
To Be Concerned.

294
00:13:17,000 --> 00:13:18,790
I'm Gonna Go Over ThereAnd Check This Out.
I'll Go With You.

295
00:13:18,790 --> 00:13:20,700
No, I Can Handle This, Okay?
No, You Brought Them To Me,

296
00:13:20,700 --> 00:13:22,130
So Technically,
They're My Patients,

297
00:13:22,130 --> 00:13:24,620
Which Means Legally,
I'm As Obligated To Them

298
00:13:24,620 --> 00:13:26,540
As Anyone Else.
I Told You, I-I Don't--

299
00:13:26,540 --> 00:13:32,980
Dell, I'm Going.

300
00:13:32,980 --> 00:13:37,570
All Right, Let's Start
By Picking Up Our Babies.

301
00:13:37,570 --> 00:13:39,810
But With Two Hands.

302
00:13:39,810 --> 00:13:42,910
My Baby Looks Like Chucky.
Do You Want To Trade?

303
00:13:42,910 --> 00:13:44,940
No Way.
All Right,No Trading Babies.

304
00:13:44,940 --> 00:13:46,350
One Of The Things We're Trying
To Teach You In ||Is Class

305
00:13:46,350 --> 00:13:50,490
Is How To BondWith Your Newborn.
I Don't Want To BondWith Chucky.

306
00:13:50,490 --> 00:13:51,980
These Babies Are Gonna
Come Into Your Life,

307
00:13:51,980 --> 00:13:54,730
And They're Gonna Seem
So Small And Fragi||

308
00:13:54,730 --> 00:13:57,940
That You're Gonna Be Afraid
To Touch Them.

309
00:13:57,940 --> 00:14:00,780
Don't Be.
Uh, They Need Toe Held,

310
00:14:00,780 --> 00:14:01,980
And They're A Lot Tougher
Than They Look.

311
00:14:01,980 --> 00:14:03,400
Yeah, I Heard A Baby Can Eat,

312
00:14:03,400 --> 00:14:06,510
Like, Half A Cup Of SandAnd Be Fine.
That's Not--

313
00:14:06,510 --> 00:14:09,330
And What About That Baby
That Fell 11 Stories,

314
00:14:09,330 --> 00:14:10,800
Crawled Away
Without A Scratch?

315
00:14:10,800 --> 00:14:14,010
It's What You Said, Man.
You Can't Break A Baby.Yeah, You--You Can.

316
00:14:14,010 --> 00:14:16,760
From 11 Stories,
Totally Breakable.

317
00:14:16,760 --> 00:14:18,500
Um, Who--
Who's Your Pediatrician?

318
00:14:18,500 --> 00:14:21,580
You Know What? Why Don't We
Start With The Basics?

319
00:14:21,580 --> 00:14:25,570
Yes. Um...
Changing A Diaper.

320
00:14:25,570 --> 00:14:32,060
Who Wants To Give It
A Try?

321
00:14:32,060 --> 00:14:33,410
I'd Like To Try.

322
00:14:33,410 --> 00:14:35,450
Adam--Our First Volunteer.

323
00:14:35,450 --> 00:14:37,030
Let's Do This.
Dr. Pete?

324
00:14:37,030 --> 00:14:38,800
Okay, Gentlemen,
Put Your Babies Down.

325
00:14:38,800 --> 00:14:43,160
Support The Head. Support--
Next Time, Support The Head.

326
00:14:43,160 --> 00:14:44,660
He's Probably
With Nate Or Arthur.

327
00:14:44,660 --> 00:14:50,820
They Play Bingo Together.
Where Is Everybody?

328
00:14:52,030 --> 00:14:54,500
We're Looking For Wendell.
He's In Room 310.

329
00:14:54,500 --> 00:14:56,330
Yeah.
Do You Know Where He Is?

330
00:14:56,330 --> 00:14:58,300
Uh, If He's Not In His Room,
I Don't--

331
00:14:58,300 --> 00:15:00,160
No, We Checked His Room.
He's Not There, Okay?

332
00:15:00,160 --> 00:15:03,920
Aren't You Supposed To Be
Watching Them?

333
00:15:03,920 --> 00:15:06,560
They Give Me
$5 An Hour Not To.

334
00:15:06,560 --> 00:15:11,000
If You Can Do Better...

335
00:15:11,000 --> 00:15:13,000
You Think That Guy
Was Just Messing With Us?

336
00:15:13,000 --> 00:15:18,280
I Should--I Should've
Given Him A 20.

337
00:15:18,280 --> 00:15:19,960
You Hear That?

338
00:15:19,960 --> 00:15:24,270
Yeah, I Hear It.

339
00:15:43,970 --> 00:15:47,450
Stop, Stop! You Two
Are Gonna Kill Each Other.

340
00:15:49,230 --> 00:15:50,030
Pa Pa!

341
00:15:50,030 --> 00:15:52,580
Stay Outta This.
This Is A Championship Match.

342
00:15:52,580 --> 00:15:54,200
And I Don't Want Him
Making Excuses

343
00:15:54,200 --> 00:15:56,890
When I Kick S Butt.
First Time For Everything.

344
00:15:56,890 --> 00:15:59,890
Except You
Growing A Pair.

345
00:16:03,010 --> 00:16:06,260
Come On. Get Up.
Is That All You Got?

346
00:16:06,260 --> 00:16:07,830
Oh, No.
His Heart Rate's Down To 30.

347
00:16:07,830 --> 00:16:09,330
I Can Barely Feel His Pulse.
He's Hurt.

348
00:16:09,330 --> 00:16:12,320
Sure He Is. Come On.
Get Up, You Old Geezer.

349
00:16:12,320 --> 00:16:15,960
Get Some M||E Of This.
No, No, Game Over.He's Really Hurt.

350
00:16:15,960 --> 00:16:16,850
We Gotta Get Him
An Ambulance.

351
00:16:16,850 --> 00:16:20,430
I Need To Get Him
To A Hospital Now.

352
00:16:20,430 --> 00:16:21,680
Good First Day,
You Guys.

353
00:16:21,680 --> 00:16:25,230
Check Your Babies
At The Door.

354
00:16:25,230 --> 00:16:26,830
Guys, Uh, That Was Amazing.

355
00:16:26,830 --> 00:16:28,990
Um, I Was Just Wondering
If There's Any Homework.

356
00:16:28,990 --> 00:16:29,900
No, Homework.

357
00:16:29,900 --> 00:16:32,430
You Know, Adam, Your Energy
Is Great For This Class,

358
00:16:32,430 --> 00:16:33,820
And It's Okay To Be Nervous.

359
00:16:33,820 --> 00:16:35,690
That's Totally Normal
For A First-Time Dad.

360
00:16:35,690 --> 00:16:38,180
Oh, Thanks,
But I'm Actually Not A Dad.

361
00:16:38,180 --> 00:16:40,430
I'm Just Here For Jack.
Jack Is Your Partner?

362
00:16:40,430 --> 00:16:43,110
Oh, No, No. Well, He's A Partner
At The Firm, Of Course,

363
00:16:43,110 --> 00:16:44,340
But I'm Just His Assistant.

364
00:16:44,340 --> 00:16:47,010
That's Why I'm HereTang The Class.
Jack Is Your Boss?

365
00:16:47,010 --> 00:16:49,430
Yeah.He Sent--
He Sent His Assistant.

366
00:16:49,430 --> 00:16:52,900
Well, Second Assistant,
Actually, But, Uh, Not For Long,

367
00:16:52,900 --> 00:16:55,630
Thanks To This Class.
You Need To Tell HimTo Be Here.

368
00:16:55,630 --> 00:16:57,820
Oh, No. No, No,
I Couldn't Tell Him That.

369
00:16:57,820 --> 00:16:59,790
He'll Destroy Me
Or Have Me Destroyed.

370
00:16:59,790 --> 00:17:00,890
Look, Please J--

371
00:17:00,890 --> 00:17:02,990
Adam, The Only Requirement
For This Dad's Class

372
00:17:02,990 --> 00:17:04,130
Is You're Actually
Gonna Be A Dad,

373
00:17:04,130 --> 00:17:05,870
So If Your Boss
Wants To Take The Class,

374
00:17:05,870 --> 00:17:11,050
He Has To Attend Himself.

375
00:17:16,360 --> 00:17:18,850
Hey, You're Still Here?

376
00:17:18,850 --> 00:17:19,550
Cathleen Went Back

377
00:17:19,550 --> 00:17:21,460
For One More Look
At The Sperm Donor Book.

378
00:17:21,460 --> 00:17:25,110
She's Hoping Something
Will Click.

379
00:17:25,110 --> 00:17:27,690
I'm Gonna Give Her
This Baby.

380
00:17:27,690 --> 00:17:29,330
I Believe You.

381
00:17:29,330 --> 00:17:32,710
You're Determined.But...

382
00:17:32,710 --> 00:17:36,950
Why So Determined?

383
00:17:36,950 --> 00:17:39,850
Cathleen Never Asks
For Much.

384
00:17:39,850 --> 00:17:41,770
I Promised Her A Happy Life.

385
00:17:41,770 --> 00:17:43,040
Sometimes You Have To
Get Over Yourself

386
00:17:43,040 --> 00:17:44,410
In Order To Do Tha

387
00:17:44,410 --> 00:17:47,160
Well, I Wonder How Cathleen
Would Feel About That--

388
00:17:47,160 --> 00:17:48,830
You Disregarding
Your Own Feelings

389
00:17:48,830 --> 00:17:53,390
To Give Her
What She Wants.

390
00:17:53,390 --> 00:17:54,450
She Doesn't
Talk About It Much,

391
00:17:54,450 --> 00:17:55,940
But Cathleen Was Adopted.

392
00:17:55,940 --> 00:17:59,430
I Mean, She's Got
Great Parents, But...

393
00:17:59,430 --> 00:18:01,100
I Wanted To Give Her
What I Had,

394
00:18:01,100 --> 00:18:05,680
You Know, My Family.They're Crazy, But...

395
00:18:05,680 --> 00:18:06,940
It's Only Fair
That She Gets To Have

396
00:18:06,940 --> 00:18:09,030
One Person In Her Life
That Looks Like Her.

397
00:18:09,030 --> 00:18:12,750
But What About
What You Want, Geoffrey?

398
00:18:12,750 --> 00:18:15,390
I'll Tell You What,
Why Don't You...

399
00:18:15,390 --> 00:18:18,370
Go Home, Get Some Sleep,
Think About It,

400
00:18:18,370 --> 00:18:25,320
And Then Start Over
Tomorrow?

401
00:18:30,310 --> 00:18:31,910
H-How Is He?

402
00:18:31,910 --> 00:18:34,490
Well, He, Uh, He Had
A Heart Attack.

403
00:18:34,490 --> 00:18:36,720
We're Trying To Reopen
His Blocked Vessels.

404
00:18:36,720 --> 00:18:39,630
I Did That?
I-I Did That To Him?

405
00:18:39,630 --> 00:18:42,520
Well, I'm Sure It Didn't Help
That You Decked Him,

406
00:18:42,520 --> 00:18:46,670
But, Uh, We Can't Say
Right Now.

407
00:18:46,670 --> 00:18:48,640
I Don't Believe This.

408
00:18:48,640 --> 00:18:50,820
We--We Didn't Mean
For Anyone To Get Hurt.

409
00:18:50,820 --> 00:18:52,300
Okay, Then Why
Did You Hit Each Other?

410
00:18:52,300 --> 00:18:54,270
We Had To Do Something.

411
00:18:54,270 --> 00:18:56,440
The Days There...

412
00:18:56,440 --> 00:18:59,290
You-Ou Can't
Tell One From Another.

413
00:18:59,290 --> 00:19:02,420
Me, Nate--
We Were All Going Crazy.

414
00:19:02,420 --> 00:19:03,710
Yeah, Well,
That Part's Obvious.

415
00:19:03,710 --> 00:19:06,100
Dell, Maybe Your Granddad,
He--He Just Needs A Minute--

416
00:19:06,100 --> 00:19:07,710
I Got It.

417
00:19:07,710 --> 00:19:11,940
I Need You To Swear, Okay?
No More Of This.

418
00:19:11,940 --> 00:19:19,900
You Think I Don't Know
It's Over?

419
00:19:20,970 --> 00:19:25,680
Dell...

420
00:19:35,560 --> 00:19:36,850
Old Man Fight Club?

421
00:19:36,850 --> 00:19:39,180
, Yeah.

422
00:19:39,180 --> 00:19:41,060
Wendell Was
The Ringleader, Too.

423
00:19:41,060 --> 00:19:42,490
Knocked The Hell
Out Of His Friend,

424
00:19:42,490 --> 00:19:44,980
Who's Actually Not Doing
Too Well Now.

425
00:19:44,980 --> 00:19:45,630
Well, It's Amazing

426
00:19:45,630 --> 00:19:47,960
What Some People Will Do
To Entertain Themselves.

427
00:19:47,960 --> 00:19:49,390
Yeah. Come Here.

428
00:19:49,390 --> 00:19:50,290
What? Oh.

429
00:19:50,290 --> 00:19:54,380
Ooh. Ooh.
What Are You Doing?

430
00:19:54,380 --> 00:19:56,930
Hmm? I'm Just
Entertaining Myself.

431
00:19:56,930 --> 00:19:58,980
And You.Trying At Least.
No.

432
00:19:58,980 --> 00:19:59,930
Come Here.
No.

433
00:19:59,930 --> 00:20:02,450
Shh, Shh, Shh.
Sam, No, No.

434
00:20:02,450 --> 00:20:08,340
- What?
- No.

435
00:20:08,340 --> 00:20:11,100
I'm Not Gonna Be Your...
Secret Lover.

436
00:20:11,100 --> 00:20:14,540
Oh, Come On, Naomi.

437
00:20:14,540 --> 00:20:17,470
You're Mad Because I'm Trying
To Spice Things Up

438
00:20:17,470 --> 00:20:21,610
Now That We're...
Atever We Are?

439
00:20:21,610 --> 00:20:23,260
Okay, Everybody Around Here,

440
00:20:23,260 --> 00:20:25,110
They Already Went Through
Our Divorce.

441
00:20:25,110 --> 00:20:27,730
Do We Really Have To Drag Them
Through Every Little Detail Now?

442
00:20:27,730 --> 00:20:30,160
This Is Not About Them.

443
00:20:30,160 --> 00:20:32,510
This Is About Things
Being Different

444
00:20:32,510 --> 00:20:35,080
The Second Time Around...

445
00:20:35,080 --> 00:20:39,930
If There Is
A Second Time Around.

446
00:20:39,930 --> 00:20:43,100
I Need To Know You're Not
Just Gonna Give Up This Time.

447
00:20:43,100 --> 00:20:45,100
Oh.
Forget It. I--

448
00:20:45,100 --> 00:20:46,380
I Gotta Go. I-I Have To Get--
Wait, Listen.

449
00:20:46,380 --> 00:20:50,860
I Have A Patient.
Naomi, Wait.

450
00:20:50,860 --> 00:20:52,710
Naomi, Uh...

451
00:20:52,710 --> 00:20:57,290
Your Patient's He.
Yeah, I Know

452
00:20:57,290 --> 00:21:00,080
Oh, Uh, Dell, Listen,
I Was Looking Over

453
00:21:00,080 --> 00:21:02,570
Some Of These Medical Reports
From The Nursing Home--

454
00:21:02,570 --> 00:21:05,970
What Did You Do To Her?

455
00:21:05,970 --> 00:21:06,810
Excuse Me?

456
00:21:06,810 --> 00:21:08,700
You Heard Me.
What Did You Do?

457
00:21:08,700 --> 00:21:10,310
I Don't Think That's
Any Of Your Business.

458
00:21:10,310 --> 00:21:12,880
No. It Is, Okay?
No, It's Not.

459
00:21:12,880 --> 00:21:14,860
Dell, I Know That You're
Upset About Wendell--

460
00:21:14,860 --> 00:21:16,530
This Has Nothing To Do
With Him, Okay?

461
00:21:16,530 --> 00:21:18,590
Every Time She Walks Away
From You, She's Miserable.

462
00:21:18,590 --> 00:21:21,000
And I Care About How
She Feels, Okay? I Care.

463
00:21:21,000 --> 00:21:22,310
-Dell-
-No, I Know What You Think,

464
00:21:22,310 --> 00:21:24,670
But This Isn't
Just A Crush, Okay?

465
00:21:24,670 --> 00:21:27,560
Maybe After So Many Years,
You Just Don't See It.

466
00:21:27,560 --> 00:21:30,290
You Know How Many Women Think
Like And--And Look Like That

467
00:21:30,290 --> 00:21:32,760
And Laugh Like That
And Care?

468
00:21:32,760 --> 00:21:34,980
One.
So Far I've Met One.

469
00:21:34,980 --> 00:21:37,290
And Yeah, She's--She's Out Of
My League In Every Possible Way,

470
00:21:37,290 --> 00:21:40,860
But I Don't Care.
She Dazzles Me.

471
00:21:40,860 --> 00:21:42,660
And I'm Not Stupid Enough
To Hope That One Day I'll Meet

472
00:21:42,660 --> 00:21:44,580
Someone Like Her When The Time
Is Right, Because I Won't.

473
00:21:44,580 --> 00:21:47,070
I Love Her. Okay?

474
00:21:47,070 --> 00:21:50,820
And I Guarantee You
I Wouldn't Make Her Cry.

475
00:21:50,820 --> 00:21:53,430
Okay, Uh... Dell,
I Know That

476
00:21:53,430 --> 00:21:55,770
You're Under
A Lot Of Stress Right Now,

477
00:21:55,770 --> 00:21:57,190
So I'm Gonna Pretend

478
00:21:57,190 --> 00:22:02,950
You Didn't Just Say
Those Things About My Wife.

479
00:22:02,950 --> 00:22:09,290
Ex-Wife.

480
00:22:12,360 --> 00:22:13,850
Uh, I Just Wanted
To Let You Know,

481
00:22:13,850 --> 00:22:16,630
I'm Gonna Do My Job,
But I'm Done With Dell.

482
00:22:16,630 --> 00:22:17,860
What--Hey, What Happened?

483
00:22:17,860 --> 00:22:22,130
Dell Is A...
Dell's A Child.

484
00:22:22,130 --> 00:22:23,870
Sam, Will You Cut Him
A Break?

485
00:22:23,870 --> 00:22:26,490
Oh, You Have No Idea.

486
00:22:26,490 --> 00:22:29,240
I'm Cutting Him A Break...

487
00:22:29,240 --> 00:22:35,760
A Big Damn Break.

488
00:22:39,790 --> 00:22:41,790
We Put A Lock
On The Basement Door.

489
00:22:41,790 --> 00:22:43,700
They Were Taking Bets.
Okay.

490
00:22:43,700 --> 00:22:45,370
The Winner Would Walk Around
All Puffed Up.

491
00:22:45,370 --> 00:22:47,380
It's...
What A Thing, Huh?

492
00:22:47,380 --> 00:22:52,510
G-49.

493
00:22:56,620 --> 00:23:01,570
Hey, Pa Pa.

494
00:23:01,570 --> 00:23:04,810
- Nate?
- Uh, The Same.

495
00:23:04,810 --> 00:23:08,070
The Doctors Put
A Pacemaker In.

496
00:23:08,070 --> 00:23:10,420
Yoshouldn't
Blame Yourself.

497
00:23:10,420 --> 00:23:13,130
He Didn't
Have To Fight You.

498
00:23:13,130 --> 00:23:21,020
I Should've Known Better.

499
00:23:21,300 --> 00:23:22,970
Hey.

500
00:23:22,970 --> 00:23:24,480
Still No Click.

501
00:23:24,480 --> 00:23:26,130
Where's Geoffrey?
On His Way.

502
00:23:26,130 --> 00:23:27,810
It's Not Like We Haven't
Gone Over These Guys

503
00:23:27,810 --> 00:23:29,960
A Million Times.
Hmm.

504
00:23:29,960 --> 00:23:32,440
Hey.
Hey, I ThinkI've Solved Our Problem.

505
00:23:32,440 --> 00:23:34,030
I Have Found
The Perfect Donor.

506
00:23:34,030 --> 00:23:36,830
You--Mark.

507
00:23:36,830 --> 00:23:38,890
Drmontgomery, I'd Like You
To Meet My Brother.

508
00:23:38,890 --> 00:23:40,100
Your Brother?

509
00:23:40,100 --> 00:23:46,620
Hey, Yeah.
Let's Make A Kid.

510
00:23:46,620 --> 00:23:50,210
So It's True.

511
00:23:50,210 --> 00:23:53,260
I Had To See It
For Myself.

512
00:23:53,260 --> 00:23:56,370
You Stole My Dads.
You Took My Class Roster.

513
00:23:56,370 --> 00:23:58,640
I Just Had To Refund
$27,000.

514
00:23:58,640 --> 00:24:00,240
You Know How That Looks
For The Chief Of Staff?

515
00:24:00,240 --> 00:24:02,630
See How It Feels
To Be Someone's Bitch?

516
00:24:02,630 --> 00:24:05,800
I See.
This Is A Game To You.

517
00:24:05,800 --> 00:24:08,080
Oh, And It's Not For You?
Come On.

518
00:24:08,080 --> 00:24:14,860
You Know What?
We're Off For Tonight.Game Over.

519
00:24:14,860 --> 00:24:17,820
I Know It's A Little Close,
But Cathleen Said Rself,

520
00:24:17,820 --> 00:24:19,090
She Doesn't Settle.

521
00:24:19,090 --> 00:24:23,620
- She Has Her IdeaOf What She Wants.
- And I'm The Next Best ThingTo Being There.

522
00:24:23,620 --> 00:24:25,320
Are You Sure You're Okay
With This, Mark?

523
00:24:25,320 --> 00:24:28,410
I Mean, You'd Be Making
A Child.

524
00:24:28,410 --> 00:24:30,290
Whoa.
I'm Not Having The Baby.

525
00:24:30,290 --> 00:24:32,230
I'm Just Gonna Be Doing
The Uncle Thing.

526
00:24:32,230 --> 00:24:34,530
It--It Sounds Simple Now,
But Sometimes

527
00:24:34,530 --> 00:24:37,460
Donations FromFamily Members Can...
It Gets--

528
00:24:37,460 --> 00:24:39,050
Be--
It Gets Complicated.

529
00:24:39,050 --> 00:24:41,390
Yeah.
Well, Mark's Not Complicated.

530
00:24:41,390 --> 00:24:42,420
I'm Not Complicated.

531
00:24:42,420 --> 00:24:46,040
I Mean, He Won'tThink Twice About This.
You Won't?

532
00:24:46,040 --> 00:24:48,540
Nope. I Probably Have
A Few Kids Out There

533
00:24:48,540 --> 00:24:53,740
I Don't Know About Already.It's A Joke.

534
00:24:53,740 --> 00:24:55,620
It's Probably A Joke.

535
00:24:55,620 --> 00:24:57,050
This--This Is Good,
Right?

536
00:24:57,050 --> 00:24:59,100
I Mean,
Maybe Not Us Exactly,

537
00:24:59,100 --> 00:25:02,960
But, Uh, You Know,I'll Be In The Mix.

538
00:25:02,960 --> 00:25:04,600
Yes. It's Just A Little--

539
00:25:04,600 --> 00:25:07,250
I-I Know, And--And We Don't
Have To At All.

540
00:25:07,250 --> 00:25:08,250
It's Just...

541
00:25:08,250 --> 00:25:10,890
No. I Want To.
You're Right.

542
00:25:10,890 --> 00:25:18,460
You'll Be In The M,
And That's What Matters.

543
00:25:18,460 --> 00:25:20,710
Have You Seen, Uh,
Dr. Montgomery?

544
00:25:20,710 --> 00:25:23,180
Not Lately.
Did You Ask At Reception?

545
00:25:23,180 --> 00:25:24,800
Yeah.

546
00:25:25,810 --> 00:25:28,690
- You're Back.
- Yeah.

547
00:25:28,690 --> 00:25:31,760
And You Met, Uh, Pete.
My Friend.

548
00:25:31,760 --> 00:25:34,690
Kevin Nelson. Hi.

549
00:25:34,690 --> 00:25:37,070
I Came To Pick Up
My Medical Report...

550
00:25:37,070 --> 00:25:38,030
For Work.
Uh-Huh.

551
00:25:38,030 --> 00:25:46,010
You Know, Theyan Just
E-Mail That To You.

552
00:25:46,010 --> 00:25:50,280
They Can Kind Of...
E-Mail You.

553
00:25:50,280 --> 00:25:56,340
Okay. Uh, I Thought
I Might See You And...

554
00:26:00,180 --> 00:26:01,840
I've Gotta Take This.

555
00:26:01,840 --> 00:26:08,150
Okay. It Was Nice
To See You Again.

556
00:26:12,920 --> 00:26:14,260
Please.

557
00:26:14,260 --> 00:26:15,830
Look, I Won't Be
A Disturbance.

558
00:26:15,830 --> 00:26:21,540
And If You Can, Uh,
Just Talk Into The Mike.

559
00:26:21,540 --> 00:26:23,310
Yeah, No. Sorry, Dude.

560
00:26:23,310 --> 00:26:24,740
What Am I
Supposed To Tell Jack?

561
00:26:24,740 --> 00:26:26,060
He'll Fire Me.

562
00:26:26,060 --> 00:26:28,360
Look, And After All Those
Prenatal Classes With His Wife

563
00:26:28,360 --> 00:26:31,650
And Decorating The Nursery,I Just--
Hey, How About I Tell Him Something?

564
00:26:31,650 --> 00:26:35,470
No, Don't.
Your Wife Is About To HaveA Baby, Jack.

565
00:26:35,470 --> 00:26:37,260
So Put Down The Blackberry,

566
00:26:37,260 --> 00:26:39,280
Stop Sending Adam
To Do Your Dirty Work

567
00:26:39,280 --> 00:26:45,740
And Get Over Here.Got That, Jackass?

568
00:26:47,840 --> 00:26:50,090
Okay, Using A Speculum,

569
00:26:50,090 --> 00:26:51,600
I'm Going To Insert
A Catheter

570
00:26:51,600 --> 00:26:53,020
Into Your Uterus,

571
00:26:53,020 --> 00:26:55,790
Where The Sperm
Will Be Released.

572
00:26:55,790 --> 00:26:57,240
Mark's Stuff--

573
00:26:57,240 --> 00:27:00,090
It Was Really Okay?
Oh, Yeah, It Was Excellent.

574
00:27:00,090 --> 00:27:01,900
Millions And Millions
Of Little Guys.

575
00:27:01,900 --> 00:27:06,200
So With Any Luck, The "Stuff"
Will Swim Right To Your Egg,

576
00:27:06,200 --> 00:27:09,860
And Presto--
You Should Have An Embryo.

577
00:27:09,860 --> 00:27:11,310
-Yay.
-All Right.

578
00:27:11,310 --> 00:27:15,330
And Here We Go.

579
00:27:15,330 --> 00:27:17,960
No!
No!

580
00:27:17,960 --> 00:27:20,310
I Can't.
I Can't Have Mark Inside Me,

581
00:27:20,310 --> 00:27:22,260
This Brother Sperm Traveling
To My Uterus.

582
00:27:22,260 --> 00:27:23,420
I Know, I Know.

583
00:27:23,420 --> 00:27:26,210
Honestly,I Loveour Brother, But--
He's Kind Of A Jerk.

584
00:27:26,210 --> 00:27:29,760
He Kind Of A Jerk.
Why Would You Even Suggest This?

585
00:27:29,760 --> 00:27:31,860
I'm Trying Here, Okay?I Just--
Listen,Both Of You,

586
00:27:31,860 --> 00:27:34,520
This Isn't Right For You,
And That's Okay.

587
00:27:34,520 --> 00:27:37,590
I Don't Want Anybody's Baby
But Yours.

588
00:27:37,590 --> 00:27:38,530
I'm Sorry.

589
00:27:38,530 --> 00:27:39,970
So What Do We Do?

590
00:27:39,970 --> 00:27:42,790
Just Give Up,
Not Have A Kid?

591
00:27:42,790 --> 00:27:45,850
I Just Can't Do This.
I Can't.

592
00:27:45,850 --> 00:27:48,670
There's Gotta Be
Another Way.

593
00:27:48,670 --> 00:27:51,500
Please.Please...

594
00:27:51,500 --> 00:27:58,390
Help Us Make Our Baby.

595
00:27:58,690 --> 00:28:01,010
I Actually Thought That
The Brother Was Our Solution.

596
00:28:01,010 --> 00:28:03,000
No, They Were Right.
He's A Jerk.

597
00:28:03,000 --> 00:28:07,300
I ||S Momentarily Attracted
To Him, So He Must Be.

598
00:28:07,300 --> 00:28:09,280
The Sweet Brother
Can't Make Babies.

599
00:28:09,280 --> 00:28:11,520
What Does That Say
About Natural Selection?

600
00:28:11,520 --> 00:28:12,730
What Were
His Levels Again?

601
00:28:12,730 --> 00:28:16,170
Uh, F.S.H. And Prolactin
Were Within Normal Limits.

602
00:28:16,170 --> 00:28:17,440
How About Testosterone?

603
00:28:17,440 --> 00:28:19,670
Borderline.
Borderline Low.

604
00:28:19,670 --> 00:28:20,990
Yeah, But Not 鞳Nexistent,

605
00:28:20,990 --> 00:28:22,250
Which Means
There Might Be A Way,

606
00:28:22,250 --> 00:28:27,300
And If There Is,
We Should Find It.

607
00:28:27,300 --> 00:28:28,940
Screw Natural Selection.

608
00:28:28,940 --> 00:28:32,910
Gentlemen, Prepare To Have
Your Lives Transformed.

609
00:28:32,910 --> 00:28:36,940
I Present To You...
Diap|| B. Gone.

610
00:28:36,940 --> 00:28:38,930
I'm Jack Grossman.

611
00:28:38,930 --> 00:28:42,570
Which One Of You Jerks
Called Me A Jackass?

612
00:28:42,570 --> 00:28:43,700
That'd Be Me.

613
00:28:43,700 --> 00:28:46,600
Um, Your Name's Jack And...

614
00:28:46,600 --> 00:28:48,450
You Were Acting
Like An Ass.

615
00:28:48,450 --> 00:28:51,820
You Don't Know Anything
About Me

616
00:28:51,820 --> 00:28:55,420
My Wife, My Work,

617
00:28:55,420 --> 00:28:57,510
My Life, Nothing.

618
00:28:57,510 --> 00:28:59,070
Mr. Grossman, He W Just
Trying To Help. He--

619
00:28:59,070 --> 00:29:00,310
I Know That
You Pawned Off A Class

620
00:29:00,310 --> 00:29:01,440
That Could Help Save
Your Baby's Life

621
00:29:01,440 --> 00:29:04,100
On A Guy That Makes YouLunch Reservations.
Oh, You ThinkYou're Clever, Huh?

622
00:29:04,100 --> 00:29:05,650
I Know.
You're A Tough Guy, Okay?

623
00:29:05,650 --> 00:29:08,190
But The Tough-Guy Act Is Not
Gonna Work With Being A Father.

624
00:29:08,190 --> 00:29:10,750
It's Just Not.
I'm Doing This My Way.

625
00:29:10,750 --> 00:29:12,660
My Wife Is Gonna Stay Home
With Our Kid, And I'm--

626
00:29:12,660 --> 00:29:14,980
Okay, But Your Wife
Is Not There To Do Your Job.

627
00:29:14,980 --> 00:29:17,370
You N't Check Out, Jack.
You Gotta Show Up.

628
00:29:17,370 --> 00:29:19,580
In Fact, You Have Gotta
Screw Things Up

629
00:29:19,580 --> 00:29:22,930
Before You Even Have
The First Clue Ab--

630
00:29:22,930 --> 00:29:24,320
How Many Of You Guys
Have Figured Out

631
00:29:24,320 --> 00:29:27,550
What It Means To Be A Father?
Not Me.

632
00:29:27,550 --> 00:29:33,290
Well, I-I Don't Know Much,
But I Know Morthan This Guy.

633
00:29:33,290 --> 00:29:34,640
This Kid Is Coming,

634
00:29:34,640 --> 00:29:36,370
Whether You're Ready For It
Or Not.

635
00:29:36,370 --> 00:29:38,830
You Think I Don't Know That?

636
00:29:38,830 --> 00:29:41,990
You Think It Doesn't
Keep Me Up At Night?

637
00:29:41,990 --> 00:29:46,930
All I Want For That Kid
Is To Be Safe And To Be Happy,

638
00:29:46,930 --> 00:29:49,080
And I'm Doing Everything
That I Know How To Do.

639
00:29:49,080 --> 00:29:51,840
I Believe You.
Now Do More.

640
00:29:51,840 --> 00:29:53,920
I Mean, You Came Down Here
To Yell At A Pediatrician,

641
00:29:53,920 --> 00:30:00,760
So Don't Tell Me
You Don't Care Enough.

642
00:30:03,760 --> 00:30:07,310
-I Got This.
-Am I, Uh...

643
00:30:07,310 --> 00:30:11,200
-I'm Not Fired?
-No.

644
00:30:11,200 --> 00:30:15,640
But There's No Way
You're Watching Me Do This.

645
00:30:15,640 --> 00:30:17,000
Well, Come On.

646
00:30:17,000 --> 00:30:19,320
Let's Show This Guy
How To Rock This, Right?

647
00:30:19,320 --> 00:30:26,040
Come On.Okay, Yes.
Show Him How It's Done.

648
00:30:26,040 --> 00:30:31,480
So Did Officer Manly
Make A Move?

649
00:30:31,480 --> 00:30:34,050
You Rely Want
To Hear About This?

650
00:30:34,050 --> 00:30:36,740
This Is What Friends Do.
Right?

651
00:30:36,740 --> 00:30:39,250
No Sex Talk.
That's Off-Limits.

652
00:30:39,250 --> 00:30:41,000
Uh, I Don't Usually
Talk About It.

653
00:30:41,000 --> 00:30:42,160
I'm More Of A Do-It Guy.

654
00:30:42,160 --> 00:30:44,690
Oh, Yeah. Good To Know.

655
00:30:44,690 --> 00:30:49,320
And The Officer Did Not Get
A Chance To Move.

656
00:30:49,320 --> 00:30:50,780
My Man Choices Lately--

657
00:30:50,780 --> 00:30:56,030
-Have Been Me?
-And Trk.

658
00:30:56,030 --> 00:30:58,270
Say Yes.

659
00:30:58,270 --> 00:30:59,460
It's That Simple?

660
00:30:59,460 --> 00:31:01,780
It's Not Your Fault
There Have Been Misfires.

661
00:31:01,780 --> 00:31:03,060
Dating Is A Numbers Game.

662
00:31:03,060 --> 00:31:06,200
You Get Out There As Much
As You Can And See What Works.

663
00:31:06,200 --> 00:31:07,840
Volume Dating,
That's Your Philosophy?

664
00:31:07,840 --> 00:31:09,380
My Point Is,
Most Of The Time,

665
00:31:09,380 --> 00:31:10,760
You're Not Gonna Find
A Right Fit.

666
00:31:10,760 --> 00:31:13,360
And Sometimes,
It's The Last Person You'd Think

667
00:31:13,360 --> 00:31:15,790
Who Makes You Happy.

668
00:31:15,790 --> 00:31:21,360
And... Yeah, I'm Out There.

669
00:31:21,360 --> 00:31:26,460
Good.Good Advice...For Us.

670
00:31:26,460 --> 00:31:33,040
I Gotta Go...take Care Of
Cathleen And Geoffrey.

671
00:31:33,040 --> 00:31:34,800
So We Think
We Found Something.

672
00:31:34,800 --> 00:31:38,050
It's A New Procedure Called
Testicular Sperm Extraction.

673
00:31:38,050 --> 00:31:40,760
Okay, What's That?
Sperm Search And Rescue.

674
00:31:40,760 --> 00:31:42,360
We Go Inside The Testicle

675
00:31:42,360 --> 00:31:44,610
To Look For
A Few Viable Sperm,

676
00:31:44,610 --> 00:31:46,570
Which We Then Implant
Into Cathleen's Eggs

677
00:31:46,570 --> 00:31:49,000
To Make A Child.
You Can Do That?

678
00:31:49,000 --> 00:31:50,570
Yes. We Use
A Surgical Microscope

679
00:31:50,570 --> 00:31:52,450
To Isolate
Sperm-Producing Tissue.

680
00:31:52,450 --> 00:31:54,990
If We Find Even One Sperm,
You Have A Shot.

681
00:31:54,990 --> 00:31:56,820
Wow.
This Is So Friggin' Cool.

682
00:31:56,820 --> 00:32:00,510
It's Like Rambo Time.

683
00:32:00,510 --> 00:32:02,430
I-Inside My Testicles?

684
00:32:02,430 --> 00:32:08,070
Yes.
Yeah.

685
00:32:10,090 --> 00:32:11,930
I Know Why, Why You've
Been Avoiding Me. It--

686
00:32:11,930 --> 00:32:14,700
What? What?

687
00:32:14,700 --> 00:32:18,320
I...

688
00:32:18,320 --> 00:32:20,030
Owe You An Apology.

689
00:32:20,030 --> 00:32:21,610
You Do?
Yes!

690
00:32:21,610 --> 00:32:24,900
I Was Stupid To Think
We Could Have Unemotional Sex,

691
00:32:24,900 --> 00:32:27,400
Or Attempted Sex.

692
00:32:27,400 --> 00:32:30,570
We--We Care About Ea Other.
We're Friends.

693
00:32:30,570 --> 00:32:32,970
Friends With Benefits
Never Works.

694
00:32:32,970 --> 00:32:37,140
- I Was Wrong.
- Thank You.

695
00:32:37,140 --> 00:32:40,010
So It Was The Sex? That's Why
U've Been Avoiding Me?

696
00:32:40,010 --> 00:32:43,480
It Was The Sex.
Good.

697
00:32:43,480 --> 00:32:46,690
- So We're Good?
- We're Good.

698
00:32:46,690 --> 00:32:50,330
Good.

699
00:32:50,330 --> 00:32:52,110
Okay, Geoffrey,

700
00:32:52,110 --> 00:32:53,360
Once I Get Inside,

701
00:32:53,360 --> 00:32:57,490
You Might Feel
A Slight||Ulling,Some Discomfort.

702
00:32:57,490 --> 00:33:00,130
If It Gets Too Bad,
We Can Stop.

703
00:33:00,130 --> 00:33:02,440
And Then If Dr. Montgomery
Locates Any Sperm,

704
00:33:02,440 --> 00:33:04,570
I'll Extract Cathleen's Eggs.

705
00:33:04,570 --> 00:33:06,920
You Can Do This, Honey.

706
00:33:06,920 --> 00:33:09,120
I Love You, Babe.

707
00:33:09,120 --> 00:33:12,530
Okay, On Three.

708
00:33:12,530 --> 00:33:14,120
One...

709
00:33:14,120 --> 00:33:16,260
Two...

710
00:33:16,260 --> 00:33:22,740
Three.

711
00:33:22,740 --> 00:33:24,110
Okay...

712
00:33:24,110 --> 00:33:26,240
I'm Going Inside,

713
00:33:26,240 --> 00:33:28,390
Taking A Look Around,

714
00:33:28,390 --> 00:33:31,790
Trying To Find That...

715
00:33:31,790 --> 00:33:34,900
One Swimmer.

716
00:33:34,900 --> 00:33:36,880
What If
She Doesn't Find Anything?

717
00:33:36,880 --> 00:33:38,020
What If
There's Nothing There?

718
00:33:38,020 --> 00:33:45,500
I Love You No Matter What.

719
00:33:45,500 --> 00:33:48,530
What's Going On?

720
00:33:48,530 --> 00:33:49,810
The Hospital Just Called.

721
00:33:49,810 --> 00:33:53,560
I've--I've Gotta Go Get,
Uh, Wendell.

722
00:33:53,560 --> 00:34:00,400
Nate's Not Going To Make It.

723
00:34:02,870 --> 00:34:06,730
Anything?

724
00:34:06,730 --> 00:34:10,920
No, Not...

725
00:34:10,920 --> 00:34:13,740
Wait. What's That?

726
00:34:13,740 --> 00:34:15,450
I Have One?
You Found It?

727
00:34:15,450 --> 00:34:19,300
Maybe.
I Just Need To Grab This.

728
00:34:19,300 --> 00:34:23,670
Come On, You Bastard.

729
00:34:23,670 --> 00:34:30,160
Sorry.

730
00:34:30,160 --> 00:34:32,220
Got It.

731
00:34:32,220 --> 00:34:37,610
You--You Did?Hold On A Minute.
We're Checking.

732
00:34:37,610 --> 00:34:40,680
Yeah. There You Go.

733
00:34:40,680 --> 00:34:44,650
- That's My Kid.
- That's Your Kid.

734
00:34:49,000 --> 00:34:52,160
Nateas Right About His Heart.
It Was Shot.

735
00:34:52,160 --> 00:34:53,220
It Wasn't Me?

736
00:34:53,220 --> 00:35:00,480
No, No. He Was Living
On Borrowed Time.

737
00:35:00,480 --> 00:35:02,520
I'm Sorry.

738
00:35:02,520 --> 00:35:04,980
I Know He Was Your Friend.

739
00:35:04,980 --> 00:35:07,660
Nate Lost His Wife, Too.

740
00:35:07,660 --> 00:35:10,770
And Then...
He Was At The Home.

741
00:35:10,770 --> 00:35:13,760
You Want To Know Why
We Fight? I'll Tell You Why.

742
00:35:13,760 --> 00:35:16,180
On Those Days,
You Wake Up Thinking,

743
00:35:16,180 --> 00:35:23,230
Today Something Happens
Besides This... Death March.

744
00:35:23,230 --> 00:35:25,340
Our Lives...

745
00:35:25,340 --> 00:35:27,430
They Change.

746
00:35:27,430 --> 00:35:30,590
Fair Enough, We're Old.

747
00:35:30,590 --> 00:35:34,010
But They Don't
Have To Be Over.

748
00:35:34,010 --> 00:35:38,590
Damn... It Felt Good.

749
00:35:38,590 --> 00:35:42,140
To Fight?

750
00:35:42,140 --> 00:35:44,710
I Hate Bingo.

751
00:35:44,710 --> 00:35:46,620
So Did Nate.

752
00:35:46,620 --> 00:35:49,340
Your Grandma...

753
00:35:49,340 --> 00:35:53,500
She Was What I Lived For.

754
00:35:53,500 --> 00:35:56,580
You'll See,
When You're Like Me,

755
00:35:56,580 --> 00:36:00,250
You'll Wish You'd Fought More
Your Whole Life.

756
00:36:00,250 --> 00:36:09,800
You'll Miss Caring That Much
About Anything.

757
00:36:44,730 --> 00:36:52,230
I Think
We Just Made A Baby.

758
00:36:54,880 --> 00:36:57,100
Hey.
You Want To Grab A Bite?

759
00:36:57,100 --> 00:36:59,830
I Can Come To Your House,
Get A Pizza, Movie?

760
00:36:59,830 --> 00:37:01,330
I Have Plans, Actually.

761
00:37:01,330 --> 00:37:03,930
Oh, Okay.
But We're Good?

762
00:37:03,930 --> 00:37:09,900
We're Good. We're Good.

763
00:37:09,900 --> 00:37:12,300
You Have A Girlfriend.

764
00:37:12,300 --> 00:37:13,930
What?

765
00:37:13,930 --> 00:37:16,840
No. You Have No Idea How...
No.

766
00:37:16,840 --> 00:37:21,000
Cooper, If This Is Why You've
Been Avoiding Me, Don't.

767
00:37:21,000 --> 00:37:23,200
I'm Happy For You.
I Am.

768
00:37:23,200 --> 00:37:26,910
God. One Of Us
Has To Act Like A Grown-Up.

769
00:37:26,910 --> 00:37:30,260
I'm Hardly...

770
00:37:30,260 --> 00:37:31,980
I Still Want To Hang Out
With You.

771
00:37:31,980 --> 00:37:32,860
It's Not A Big Thing.

772
00:37:32,860 --> 00:37:36,970
Exactly.
So Don't Be A Freak.

773
00:37:36,970 --> 00:37:41,070
Right.You're Right.

774
00:37:41,070 --> 00:37:43,340
Go.

775
00:37:43,340 --> 00:37:52,520
Don't Stand Her Up.

776
00:37:53,210 --> 00:37:54,100
Just Relax.

777
00:37:54,100 --> 00:37:57,390
Give That One Guy
A Chance To Settle In.

778
00:37:57,390 --> 00:37:59,640
I'm Gonna Be
A Big Old Lump.

779
00:37:59,640 --> 00:38:04,590
- Thanks For Everything.
- Yeah.

780
00:38:05,000 --> 00:38:07,680
Is It Too Soon
To Feel Pregnant?

781
00:38:07,680 --> 00:38:10,020
Maybe Just A Little.
Just--

782
00:38:10,020 --> 00:38:13,680
Taking It Easy.
Bye.

783
00:38:13,680 --> 00:38:15,460
- Hey.
- Hey.

784
00:38:15,460 --> 00:38:17,150
I Heard You Did
A Great Job In There.

785
00:38:17,150 --> 00:38:19,410
Yeah. God, Those Two,
They Make You Think

786
00:38:19,410 --> 00:38:21,230
That It's Worth
Slugging It Out, You Know,

787
00:38:21,230 --> 00:38:22,460
If You Can Find Somebody

788
00:38:22,460 --> 00:38:27,400
That Makes You Feel
Half That Good.

789
00:38:27,400 --> 00:38:29,420
Thank You...

790
00:38:29,420 --> 00:38:31,420
For Your Advice Earlier.

791
00:38:31,420 --> 00:38:36,370
You're Welcome.

792
00:38:39,370 --> 00:38:41,430
Who Kicked Your Dog?

793
00:38:41,430 --> 00:38:42,660
I Think I'm Helping
Some Other Guy

794
00:38:42,660 --> 00:38:47,400
Win Over Addison.
Good Job.

795
00:38:47,400 --> 00:38:50,350
It'd Be Weird
To Punch Him Out Now, Right?

796
00:38:50,350 --> 00:38:55,240
Yeah, A Little Bit.

797
00:39:01,150 --> 00:39:03,490
You Said
You Weren't Coming Over.

798
00:39:03,490 --> 00:39:06,740
And Then, Uh...

799
00:39:06,740 --> 00:39:10,650
That's "Game Over"?

800
00:39:10,650 --> 00:39:16,990
Sex Is BestWhen You Feel Like You Want
To Kill The Other Person.

801
00:39:16,990 --> 00:39:18,990
You Stole My Dads.

802
00:39:18,990 --> 00:39:22,850
Yeah. And That Makes Me
A Bad Guy.

803
00:39:22,850 --> 00:39:24,730
Yeah, A Bad,
Dirty Cop Kind Of Guy.

804
00:39:24,730 --> 00:39:26,990
Little Bit.

805
00:39:30,000 --> 00:39:32,740
So Are We Dating?

806
00:39:32,740 --> 00:39:35,370
If...

807
00:39:35,370 --> 00:39:37,840
Dirty Sex
On A Regular Basis Is Dating,

808
00:39:37,840 --> 00:39:40,640
Then, Yeah.

809
00:39:40,640 --> 00:39:42,860
Okay, Good.

810
00:39:42,860 --> 00:39:45,160
Does That Mean
I Get To Be On Top?

811
00:39:45,160 --> 00:39:50,020
Never.

812
00:39:52,570 --> 00:39:54,960
Oh.
Hey.Hi, Dell.

813
00:39:54,960 --> 00:39:56,180
What Is--
Oh, Here.

814
00:39:56,180 --> 00:40:06,430
Oh. Thank You.Thanks.Oh, Here We Go.

815
00:40:10,540 --> 00:40:15,540
Look, I-I Don't Have It
All Together, Okay?

816
00:40:15,540 --> 00:40:20,410
But I'm Not A Kid.I'm A Man...

817
00:40:20,410 --> 00:40:30,450
Who Loves You,
Who's Going To FightFor You.

818
00:40:36,940 --> 00:40:48,160
Hey.
H-Have You Seen Addison?I Need To...

819
00:40:57,890 --> 00:41:09,590
Okay? I Don't Care.Let Everybody Know.

820
00:41:09,590 --> 00:41:13,360
What Was That?

821
00:41:13,360 --> 00:41:22,660
He's Fighting For Her.She's Worth It.

822
00:41:31,320 --> 00:41:32,990
- Hello.
- Hi.

823
00:41:32,990 --> 00:41:35,480
I Am Here
To See Officer Nelson.

824
00:41:35,480 --> 00:41:38,140
Kevin Nelson.I'm A Friend.

825
00:41:38,140 --> 00:41:45,490
I'll See If I Can Find Him.

826
00:41:56,380 --> 00:42:01,560
Addison?


