1
00:00:00,030 --> 00:00:01,300
Oh, look,  <i>Saturn 3</i> is on.

2
00:00:01,360 --> 00:00:02,630
I don't want to watch  <i>Saturn 3.</i>

3
00:00:02,700 --> 00:00:04,030
 <i>Deep Space Nine</i> is better.

4
00:00:04,100 --> 00:00:07,800
How is <i>Deep Space Nine</i> better than <i>Saturn 3?</i>

5
00:00:07,860 --> 00:00:11,560
Simple subtraction will tell you it's six better.

6
00:00:13,760 --> 00:00:16,460
Compromise. Watch <i>Babylon 5.</i>

7
00:00:16,530 --> 00:00:19,530
In what sense is that a compromise?

8
00:00:19,600 --> 00:00:24,230
Well, five is partway between three... Never mind.

9
00:00:24,300 --> 00:00:25,360
I'll tell you what.

10
00:00:25,430 --> 00:00:27,060
How about we go rock-paper-scissors?

11
00:00:27,130 --> 00:00:28,300
Ooh, I don't think so.

12
00:00:28,360 --> 00:00:30,130
Anecdotal evidence suggests

13
00:00:30,200 --> 00:00:31,730
that in the game of rock-paper-scissors,

14
00:00:31,800 --> 00:00:35,100
players familiar with each other will tie 75 to 80% of the time

15
00:00:35,160 --> 00:00:37,530
due to the limited number of outcomes.

16
00:00:37,600 --> 00:00:41,900
I suggest rock-paper-scissors- lizard-Spock.

17
00:00:42,860 --> 00:00:43,530
What?

18
00:00:43,600 --> 00:00:45,330
It's very simple.

19
00:00:45,400 --> 00:00:47,900
Scissors cuts paper. Paper covers rock.

20
00:00:47,960 --> 00:00:49,260
Rock crushes lizard.

21
00:00:49,330 --> 00:00:50,530
Lizard poisons Spock.

22
00:00:50,600 --> 00:00:53,430
Spock smashes scissors. Scissors decapitates lizard.

23
00:00:53,500 --> 00:00:55,960
Lizard eats paper. Paper disproves Spock.

24
00:00:56,030 --> 00:00:57,700
Spock vaporizes rock.

25
00:00:57,760 --> 00:01:00,860
And as it always has, rock crushes scissors.

26
00:01:02,360 --> 00:01:04,500
Okay, I think I got it.

27
00:01:07,800 --> 00:01:09,500
Rock-paper-scissors- lizard-Spock!

28
00:01:10,530 --> 00:01:12,700
Oh!

29
00:01:17,600 --> 00:01:19,930
Hello, boys.

30
00:01:20,000 --> 00:01:22,830
Ahoy, matey.

31
00:01:22,900 --> 00:01:24,960
Noticed the eye patch, did you?

32
00:01:25,030 --> 00:01:27,060
It's all part of a technique I've been studying

33
00:01:27,130 --> 00:01:28,660
for picking up women.

34
00:01:28,730 --> 00:01:30,460
You employ a visual display (thud)

35
00:01:30,530 --> 00:01:32,300
designed to make yourself

36
00:01:32,360 --> 00:01:35,300
distinctive and memorable.

37
00:01:35,360 --> 00:01:37,930
Oh, yes, like the male peacock with brilliant plumage

38
00:01:38,000 --> 00:01:41,530
or the rutting baboon with engorged hindquarters.

39
00:01:42,860 --> 00:01:45,360
Or in this case, the bar mitzvah boy with pinkeye.

40
00:01:45,430 --> 00:01:48,060
Mock me if you will, but it works.

41
00:01:48,130 --> 00:01:50,130
You show up at a club in something distinctive,

42
00:01:50,200 --> 00:01:52,860
scope out your target and toss out some negs.

43
00:01:52,930 --> 00:01:53,860
What are negs?

44
00:01:53,930 --> 00:01:55,330
A neg is a negative compliment

45
00:01:55,400 --> 00:01:57,300
that throws a pretty woman off her game,

46
00:01:57,360 --> 00:02:00,700
like "Normally, I'm not turned on by big teeth,

47
00:02:00,760 --> 00:02:03,530
but on you, they work."

48
00:02:03,600 --> 00:02:06,660
I got a whole list of 'em. Who wants to be my wingman?

49
00:02:06,730 --> 00:02:08,000
You're not gonna need wingman.

50
00:02:08,060 --> 00:02:10,860
You're gonna need a paramedic.

51
00:02:10,930 --> 00:02:12,800
Howard, your scooter's blocking my car.

52
00:02:13,830 --> 00:02:16,700
Aw, did you get pinkeye again?

53
00:02:17,630 --> 00:02:20,660
Step one: she notices the eye patch.

54
00:02:20,730 --> 00:02:23,030
May I say, Penny,

55
00:02:23,100 --> 00:02:26,000
not a lot of women could look as hot as you do

56
00:02:26,060 --> 00:02:28,160
with such greasy hair?

57
00:02:33,960 --> 00:02:36,130
Yeah, just move your stupid scooter

58
00:02:36,200 --> 00:02:38,500
before I pick it up and throw it in the mpster.

59
00:02:42,130 --> 00:02:43,530
Ow.

60
00:02:44,900 --> 00:02:48,330
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *

61
00:02:48,400 --> 00:02:51,730
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *

62
00:02:51,830 --> 00:02:53,400
* The Earth began to cool *

63
00:02:53,460 --> 00:02:55,730
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *

64
00:02:55,800 --> 00:02:58,230
* We built the Wall * * <i>We built the pyramids</i> *

65
00:02:58,300 --> 00:03:01,200
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *

66
00:03:01,260 --> 00:03:03,260
* That all started with a big bang *

67
00:03:03,330 --> 00:03:04,930
* <i>Bang!</i> *

68
00:03:11,700 --> 00:03:14,600
I'm sorry, but I'm not going to watch <i>The Clone Wars</i> TV series

69
00:03:14,660 --> 00:03:17,830
until I've seen  <i>The e Clone Wars</i> movie.

70
00:03:17,900 --> 00:03:19,660
I prefer to let George Lucas disappoint me

71
00:03:19,730 --> 00:03:22,330
in the order he intended.

72
00:03:23,600 --> 00:03:25,200
Well, I want to watch it now.

73
00:03:25,260 --> 00:03:28,160
Then I believe we've arrived at another quintessential

74
00:03:28,230 --> 00:03:31,400
rock-paper-scissors- lizard-Spock moment.

75
00:03:36,730 --> 00:03:38,730
Watch whatever you want.

76
00:03:39,630 --> 00:03:40,930
I saw what you did there.

77
00:03:41,000 --> 00:03:43,460
What'd I do?

78
00:03:43,530 --> 00:03:47,460
(phone rings)

79
00:03:47,530 --> 00:03:50,500
Hello. Hey, Howard.

80
00:03:50,560 --> 00:03:51,730
What's wrong?

81
00:03:52,830 --> 00:03:55,030
Okay. Okay, we'll be right there.

82
00:03:55,100 --> 00:03:57,200
What happened?

83
00:03:57,260 --> 00:03:59,260
Howard's at the Mars Rover lab. He says he's in trouble.

84
00:03:59,330 --> 00:04:00,330
Defcon 5.

85
00:04:00,400 --> 00:04:01,800
Defcon 5?

86
00:04:01,860 --> 00:04:04,400
Well, there's no need to rush.

87
00:04:04,460 --> 00:04:05,560
What?

88
00:04:05,630 --> 00:04:07,200
Defcon 5 means "no danger."

89
00:04:07,260 --> 00:04:09,400
Defcon 1 is a crisis.

90
00:04:09,460 --> 00:04:11,560
How can 5 not be worse than 1?

91
00:04:11,630 --> 00:04:15,300
Yeah, <i>Star Trek V</i> worse than <i>I.</i>

92
00:04:15,360 --> 00:04:17,900
Okay, first of all, that's a comparison of quality,

93
00:04:17,960 --> 00:04:19,260
not intensity.

94
00:04:19,330 --> 00:04:21,730
Secondly, <i>Star Trek I</i> is orders-of-magnitude worse

95
00:04:21,800 --> 00:04:23,430
than <i>Star Trek V.</i>

96
00:04:23,500 --> 00:04:25,860
Are you joking?  <i>Star Trek V</i> is the standard

97
00:04:25,930 --> 00:04:27,900
against which all badness is measured.

98
00:04:27,960 --> 00:04:29,060
No, no.

99
00:04:29,130 --> 00:04:31,600
 <i>Star Trek V</i> has specific failures

100
00:04:31,660 --> 00:04:32,860
in writing and direction,

101
00:04:32,930 --> 00:04:34,530
while <i>Star Trek I</i> fails across the board:

102
00:04:34,600 --> 00:04:38,330
art direction, costuming, music, sound editing.

103
00:04:38,400 --> 00:04:40,660
Can we just forget I said Defcon and go?

104
00:04:42,330 --> 00:04:45,130
(scoffs):  <i>Star Trek V.</i>

105
00:04:46,460 --> 00:04:48,060
All right, will you at least stipulate

106
00:04:48,130 --> 00:04:51,130
that <i>Star Trek IV:</i>  <i>The Voyage Home</i> is inarguably the best?

107
00:04:51,200 --> 00:04:53,330
I have three words for you:

108
00:04:53,400 --> 00:04:54,830
 <i>Wrath of Khan.</i>

109
00:04:54,900 --> 00:04:56,830
Oh, thank God, you're here.

110
00:04:56,900 --> 00:04:58,060
What's the emergency?

111
00:04:58,130 --> 00:05:01,330
I got the Mars Rover stuck in a ditch.

112
00:05:01,400 --> 00:05:02,530
Where?

113
00:05:02,600 --> 00:05:04,700
On a dusty highway just outside Bakersfield.

114
00:05:04,760 --> 00:05:06,600
Where do you think? On Mars!

115
00:05:08,030 --> 00:05:09,300
Howard, is everything okay?

116
00:05:09,360 --> 00:05:11,800
Yeah, baby, I'll be right in.

117
00:05:13,700 --> 00:05:15,960
You brought a girl to the Mars Rover control room?

118
00:05:16,030 --> 00:05:18,300
Yeah, I picked her up in the bar. She's a doctor.

119
00:05:18,360 --> 00:05:20,130
One free barium enema,

120
00:05:20,200 --> 00:05:22,500
and my mother won't care she's not Jewish.

121
00:05:22,560 --> 00:05:24,630
Wait a minute.

122
00:05:24,700 --> 00:05:26,600
So the eye patch and e insults worked?

123
00:05:26,660 --> 00:05:28,960
No, there were three other guys with eye patches.

124
00:05:29,030 --> 00:05:30,260
It was a fiasco.

125
00:05:31,800 --> 00:05:34,330
What did work was, "How'd you like to visit

126
00:05:34,400 --> 00:05:35,760
a secret government facility?"

127
00:05:35,830 --> 00:05:37,930
So what exactly do you want us to do?

128
00:05:38,000 --> 00:05:40,160
I need you and Raj to help me get the Rover out of the ditch

129
00:05:40,230 --> 00:05:41,460
and I need you to get Stephanie out

130
00:05:41,530 --> 00:05:42,530
before somebody notices she's here.

131
00:05:42,600 --> 00:05:44,100
She doesn't exactly have clearance.

132
00:05:44,160 --> 00:05:46,830
Really? They don't let strange women from honky-tonks come in

133
00:05:46,900 --> 00:05:49,060
and play with $200 million government projects

134
00:05:49,130 --> 00:05:50,260
on distant planets?

135
00:05:50,330 --> 00:05:52,930
Yes, I was bad. Maybe she'll spank me.

136
00:05:53,000 --> 00:05:54,460
Can we please move on?

137
00:05:55,730 --> 00:05:57,660
Hey, Howard, you know, it's getting late,

138
00:05:57,730 --> 00:05:59,830
so do I get to drive this thing or what?

139
00:05:59,900 --> 00:06:02,700
Yeah. No. I'm sorry, but something's come up.

140
00:06:02,760 --> 00:06:05,700
Kind of a Mars Rover... Mars Rover

141
00:06:05,760 --> 00:06:10,060
can Howard come over...

142
00:06:10,130 --> 00:06:11,930
situation.

143
00:06:13,500 --> 00:06:16,600
So my friend Leonard is gonna take you home.

144
00:06:16,660 --> 00:06:19,260
Oh, okay. Let's go, friend Leonard.

145
00:06:19,330 --> 00:06:20,230
Okay.

146
00:06:20,300 --> 00:06:21,300
I'll call ya.

147
00:06:21,360 --> 00:06:23,360
Yeah. So are you a scientist like Howard?

148
00:06:23,430 --> 00:06:26,760
No one's a scientist like Howard.

149
00:06:26,830 --> 00:06:29,930
My mother is so gonna love her.

150
00:06:30,000 --> 00:06:31,600
How nice. Maybe they can carpool

151
00:06:31,660 --> 00:06:33,200
when they visit you in federal prison.

152
00:06:41,030 --> 00:06:43,130
I'm sorry. I totally interrupted you.

153
00:06:43,200 --> 00:06:44,530
What, what, what were you saying?

154
00:06:44,600 --> 00:06:46,130
Just said Howard's a terrific guy.

155
00:06:48,230 --> 00:06:51,300
He's got a great sense of humor.

156
00:06:51,360 --> 00:06:52,930
He loves his mother...

157
00:06:53,000 --> 00:06:54,200
a lot.

158
00:06:54,260 --> 00:06:55,960
People say "too much."

159
00:06:56,030 --> 00:06:58,860
I really like that you're such a loyal friend.

160
00:06:58,930 --> 00:07:00,660
Yeah, I am loyal.

161
00:07:00,730 --> 00:07:03,460
You know, if you look at the big picture.

162
00:07:08,400 --> 00:07:09,760
Out of curiosity,

163
00:07:09,830 --> 00:07:11,500
did he ever have a shot with you?

164
00:07:11,560 --> 00:07:12,500
Are you insane?

165
00:07:12,560 --> 00:07:15,030
The guy was wearing an eye patch.

166
00:07:15,100 --> 00:07:16,400
Then why did you...?

167
00:07:16,460 --> 00:07:19,900
He said that I cou drive a car on Mars.

168
00:07:19,960 --> 00:07:22,030
Got it.

169
00:07:24,360 --> 00:07:26,330
So, can I see you again?

170
00:07:26,400 --> 00:07:28,730
You're not gonna see me now.

171
00:07:31,460 --> 00:07:33,760
Cool.

172
00:07:35,130 --> 00:07:37,460
(typing)

173
00:07:38,630 --> 00:07:39,830
Anything?

174
00:07:39,900 --> 00:07:42,530
Actually, I was just checking my e-mail.

175
00:07:44,000 --> 00:07:46,900
But, uh, no, the Rover is not responding.

176
00:07:46,960 --> 00:07:48,900
I believe the appropriate metaphor here

177
00:07:48,960 --> 00:07:50,430
involves a river of excrement

178
00:07:50,500 --> 00:07:52,130
and a Native American water vessel

179
00:07:52,200 --> 00:07:54,730
without any means of propulsion.

180
00:07:54,800 --> 00:07:55,700
Hang on.

181
00:07:55,760 --> 00:07:57,330
There's got to be other options.

182
00:07:57,400 --> 00:07:59,830
You could try calling Triple-A.

183
00:07:59,900 --> 00:08:01,830
But based on NASA's latest timetable,

184
00:08:01,900 --> 00:08:03,800
they won't get there for 35 years.

185
00:08:05,230 --> 00:08:06,800
Plus I understand you have to be standing

186
00:08:06,860 --> 00:08:09,560
next to the vehicle with your card when they arrive.

187
00:08:09,630 --> 00:08:11,800
Oh, snap.

188
00:08:11,860 --> 00:08:14,100
Snap what?

189
00:08:14,160 --> 00:08:16,500
Okay, I guess we have to turn to Plan B.

190
00:08:16,560 --> 00:08:17,760
What's Plan B?

191
00:08:17,830 --> 00:08:19,360
Erase all the hard drives, scrap the surveillance tapes,

192
00:08:19,430 --> 00:08:22,160
wipe our fingerprints off every surface and run.

193
00:08:22,230 --> 00:08:24,060
Why wasn'that Plan A?

194
00:08:26,600 --> 00:08:29,800
REPORTER: A NASA spokesman states that due to the loss of data,

195
00:08:29,860 --> 00:08:32,460
they will most likely be unable to determine the cause

196
00:08:32,530 --> 00:08:34,560
of the Mars Rover's malfunction.

197
00:08:34,630 --> 00:08:37,360
This is not the first time an exploratory mission to Mars

198
00:08:37,430 --> 00:08:38,660
has ended in disappointment.

199
00:08:38,730 --> 00:08:41,900
Thank God for Plan B.

200
00:08:41,960 --> 00:08:43,860
Howard, didn't you say you worked on the Mars Rover?

201
00:08:43,930 --> 00:08:46,400
No, you're mistaken.

202
00:08:46,460 --> 00:08:47,760
Yeah, when we first met,

203
00:08:47,830 --> 00:08:49,260
you said that if I went out with you,

204
00:08:49,330 --> 00:08:51,160
I could drive a car on Mars.

205
00:08:52,760 --> 00:08:56,630
I don't know what you're talking about.

206
00:08:56,700 --> 00:08:58,460
Psst! Psst!

207
00:08:59,930 --> 00:09:00,960
Will you all excuse me?

208
00:09:01,030 --> 00:09:02,260
Leonard is subtly signaling

209
00:09:02,330 --> 00:09:04,800
that he'd like to talk to me in private.

210
00:09:05,700 --> 00:09:08,600
No. Yeah, I remember specifically.

211
00:09:08,660 --> 00:09:10,530
You started by asking if I was from Mars

212
00:09:10,600 --> 00:09:13,830
because my ass was out of this world.

213
00:09:15,230 --> 00:09:18,430
Well, that does sound like me, but no.

214
00:09:19,530 --> 00:09:20,760
Is there some problem?

215
00:09:20,830 --> 00:09:21,930
Yeah.

216
00:09:22,000 --> 00:09:24,960
Listen, I have to kinda sneak out for a while.

217
00:09:25,030 --> 00:09:26,530
All right, good-bye.

218
00:09:26,600 --> 00:09:28,430
No, wait!

219
00:09:28,500 --> 00:09:30,700
If anyone asks you where I went, you don't know.

220
00:09:30,760 --> 00:09:32,700
Where <i>are</i> you going?

221
00:09:32,760 --> 00:09:34,260
I can't tell you that.

222
00:09:34,330 --> 00:09:36,760
Who would ask me?

223
00:09:36,830 --> 00:09:40,000
I can't tell you that, either.

224
00:09:40,060 --> 00:09:42,130
So you brought me in here to inform me

225
00:09:42,200 --> 00:09:43,900
that you can't tell me where you're going

226
00:09:43,960 --> 00:09:46,760
and you can't tell me who might ask?

227
00:09:46,830 --> 00:09:51,030
Yeah, I really didn't think this through.

228
00:09:52,360 --> 00:09:53,400
Leonard, a moment.

229
00:09:53,460 --> 00:09:54,960
What?

230
00:09:55,030 --> 00:09:57,900
If someone-- and of course, we don't know who this would be--

231
00:09:57,960 --> 00:10:00,060
does ask where you've gone, what should I say?

232
00:10:00,130 --> 00:10:02,460
I don't know. Just tell 'em I went to the office.

233
00:10:02,530 --> 00:10:04,400
Are you going to the office? No.

234
00:10:04,460 --> 00:10:06,400
Then how can I say it convincingly?

235
00:10:06,460 --> 00:10:08,760
Just say, "Leonard went totheoffice."

236
00:10:08,830 --> 00:10:13,160
All right. Leonard went to <i>the office.</i>

237
00:10:16,830 --> 00:10:19,130
What is...? No, not like that!

238
00:10:19,200 --> 00:10:21,560
Just, "Leonard went to the office."

239
00:10:21,630 --> 00:10:22,960
This would have worked out a lot better

240
00:10:23,030 --> 00:10:25,060
if you'd just told me you were going tthe office.

241
00:10:25,130 --> 00:10:26,430
I'm going to the office.

242
00:10:26,500 --> 00:10:29,230
See? Why don't I believe you?

243
00:10:32,100 --> 00:10:33,860
(TV playing)

244
00:10:33,930 --> 00:10:35,630
I'm going out for a while.

245
00:10:35,700 --> 00:10:37,500
Okay.

246
00:10:45,930 --> 00:10:49,760
Doesn't anyone want to know where he's going?

247
00:10:49,830 --> 00:10:53,100
Okay, where is he going?

248
00:10:53,160 --> 00:10:55,460
Leonard is going to <i>the office.</i>

249
00:11:10,200 --> 00:11:11,300
So how was work today?

250
00:11:11,360 --> 00:11:12,830
Busy.

251
00:11:12,900 --> 00:11:14,430
I removed an appendix, a gall bladder

252
00:11:14,500 --> 00:11:16,510
and about a foot and a half of bowel.

253
00:11:18,130 --> 00:11:21,230
I'm hoping that's three different guys.

254
00:11:21,300 --> 00:11:23,830
No, just the one.

255
00:11:24,860 --> 00:11:26,000
He didn't make it.

256
00:11:28,300 --> 00:11:29,730
So, how was your day?

257
00:11:29,800 --> 00:11:32,600
Oh, you know, I'm a physicist, so...

258
00:11:32,660 --> 00:11:35,130
I thought about stuff.

259
00:11:35,200 --> 00:11:36,800
That's it?

260
00:11:36,860 --> 00:11:39,400
Well, I wrote some of it down.

261
00:11:39,460 --> 00:11:42,000
Are you done eating?

262
00:11:42,060 --> 00:11:44,030
Uh, yeah. Oh, good.

263
00:11:47,060 --> 00:11:48,830
If I knew you were waiting,

264
00:11:48,900 --> 00:11:51,260
I would've swallowed that lasagna whole.

265
00:11:51,330 --> 00:11:52,830
(phone ringing)

266
00:11:52,900 --> 00:11:55,660
You've reached Dr. Stephanie Barnett.

267
00:11:55,730 --> 00:11:57,830
Leave a message. (beep)

268
00:11:57,900 --> 00:11:59,330
WOLOWITZ: Hey, Steph,

269
00:11:59,400 --> 00:12:00,360
it's me again, Howard.

270
00:12:00,430 --> 00:12:01,900
Listen, if you're free Friday,

271
00:12:01,960 --> 00:12:04,700
maybe we could have a little something to eat at my place.

272
00:12:04,760 --> 00:12:07,100
My mom cooks a hell of a brisket.

273
00:12:07,160 --> 00:12:08,930
Let me know.

274
00:12:09,000 --> 00:12:11,430
It's Howard. (beep)

275
00:12:11,500 --> 00:12:14,830
I've had her brisket. Melts in your mouth.

276
00:12:20,330 --> 00:12:22,860
Maybe we should think about going to the bedroom.

277
00:12:22,930 --> 00:12:24,100
That's a good idea.

278
00:12:24,160 --> 00:12:25,930
There's a bed in there, and I'm very...

279
00:12:26,000 --> 00:12:27,960
very, very pro-bed.

280
00:12:28,030 --> 00:12:29,860
(phone rging)

281
00:12:29,930 --> 00:12:32,100
You've reached Dr. Stephanie Barnett.

282
00:12:32,160 --> 00:12:34,700
Leave a message. (beep)

283
00:12:34,760 --> 00:12:36,800
WOLOWITZ: Hey, it's me again.

284
00:12:36,860 --> 00:12:38,660
Just want to let you know

285
00:12:38,730 --> 00:12:41,500
the head count for dinner Friday has gone up.

286
00:12:41,560 --> 00:12:46,230
My Aunt Betty and Uncle Elliot are coming in from Palm Springs.

287
00:12:45,300 --> 00:12:47,930
Oh, and if anybody should ask,

288
00:12:48,000 --> 00:12:50,800
you're half-Jewish on your mother's side.

289
00:12:50,860 --> 00:12:53,000
Okay, call me.

290
00:12:53,060 --> 00:12:55,530
It's Howard. (beep)

291
00:12:55,600 --> 00:12:58,800
Don't you think we should tell him you're not interested?

292
00:12:58,860 --> 00:13:02,700
Do you want me to stop and call him back right now?

293
00:13:02,760 --> 00:13:04,260
Dear God, no!

294
00:13:06,960 --> 00:13:09,160
(Stephanie laughing): Oh, Leonard...

295
00:13:09,230 --> 00:13:11,860
(phone ringing)

296
00:13:11,930 --> 00:13:14,100
You've reached Dr. Stephanie Barnett.

297
00:13:14,160 --> 00:13:16,000
Leave a message. (beep)

298
00:13:16,060 --> 00:13:19,430
WOLOWITZ: Hey, it's me again. Howard.

299
00:13:19,500 --> 00:13:22,560
Listen, my cousins from Fort Lauderdale

300
00:13:22,630 --> 00:13:24,400
are flying in to meet you

301
00:13:24,460 --> 00:13:26,400
so that means we're gonna have to move the dinner

302
00:13:26,460 --> 00:13:28,500
to a restaurant.

303
00:13:28,560 --> 00:13:32,000
WOMAN (shrieking): Tell her we're going to the Olive Garden!

304
00:13:32,060 --> 00:13:35,360
I have a coupon from the paper.

305
00:13:35,430 --> 00:13:40,660
WOLOWITZ: We're not going to the Olive Garden, Mom!

306
00:13:40,730 --> 00:13:44,660
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Oh, Mr. Bigshot with his Red Lobster.

307
00:13:44,730 --> 00:13:49,560
WOLOWITZ: I'll call you back when we firm up the details.

308
00:13:49,630 --> 00:13:52,100
It's Howard.

309
00:13:57,060 --> 00:13:58,100
Oh, hey. Hey.

310
00:13:58,160 --> 00:13:59,300
New shirts?

311
00:13:59,360 --> 00:14:00,460
Yeah, a couple.

312
00:14:00,530 --> 00:14:02,160
Nice. Thank you.

313
00:14:02,230 --> 00:14:04,130
So, who's the girl?

314
00:14:04,200 --> 00:14:06,300
I'm sorry?

315
00:14:06,360 --> 00:14:09,230
Well, last time you bought a new shirt was when we were dating.

316
00:14:09,300 --> 00:14:12,530
So what we did was in fact dating?

317
00:14:12,600 --> 00:14:16,100
Well, yeah, we did have a date.

318
00:14:16,160 --> 00:14:18,400
Exactly. Thank you.

319
00:14:18,460 --> 00:14:22,830
Do me a favor. Tell Koothrappali that next time you see him.

320
00:14:22,900 --> 00:14:25,100
So, who is she?

321
00:14:25,160 --> 00:14:27,330
Oh, she's a doctor.

322
00:14:27,400 --> 00:14:28,730
Oh, nice.

323
00:14:28,800 --> 00:14:32,300
A doctor doctor, or a you kind of doctor?

324
00:14:32,360 --> 00:14:33,400
Doctor doctor.

325
00:14:33,460 --> 00:14:35,130
Surgical resident.

326
00:14:35,200 --> 00:14:36,630
Smart, pretty.

327
00:14:38,960 --> 00:14:40,300
Let me ask you something.

328
00:14:40,360 --> 00:14:44,330
If your friend thinks he's dating someone,

329
00:14:44,400 --> 00:14:47,260
but he's not because, in fact, you're dating her,

330
00:14:47,330 --> 00:14:48,930
does that make you a bad person?

331
00:14:49,000 --> 00:14:50,230
Well, that depends.

332
00:14:50,300 --> 00:14:51,230
On what?

333
00:14:51,300 --> 00:14:53,500
Is that friend Wolowitz?

334
00:14:53,560 --> 00:14:55,860
Yeah.

335
00:14:55,930 --> 00:14:57,360
Screw him. You're fine.

336
00:14:59,560 --> 00:15:01,330
Are you sure?

337
00:15:01,400 --> 00:15:03,660
Well, have you slept with her yet?

338
00:15:05,860 --> 00:15:08,330
You dog!

339
00:15:08,400 --> 00:15:10,130
Good for you.

340
00:15:10,200 --> 00:15:11,930
Does that change things?

341
00:15:12,000 --> 00:15:13,200
No.

342
00:15:13,260 --> 00:15:15,460
So why'd you ask?

343
00:15:15,530 --> 00:15:17,930
I'm nosy. See ya.

344
00:15:23,000 --> 00:15:25,960
MRS. WOLOWITZ (shrieking): Howard, get the door!

345
00:15:26,030 --> 00:15:30,200
WOLOWITZ (shouting): Really? Is that what you dohen someone knocks?!

346
00:15:30,260 --> 00:15:33,630
Thank you. I had no idea!

347
00:15:33,700 --> 00:15:38,760
Hey, buddy. What brings you to my little slice of hell?

348
00:15:38,830 --> 00:15:40,730
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Who is it?!

349
00:15:40,800 --> 00:15:42,400
It's Leonard!

350
00:15:42,460 --> 00:15:45,460
MRS. WOLOWITZ: You're gonna have to play outside!

351
00:15:45,530 --> 00:15:48,630
I'm not dressed to receive!

352
00:15:48,700 --> 00:15:51,200
No one cares, Ma!

353
00:15:51,260 --> 00:15:53,260
(softly): So, what's up?

354
00:15:53,330 --> 00:15:56,100
Listen, I need to talk to you about something.

355
00:15:56,160 --> 00:15:58,730
(ringtone playing "She Blinded Me with Science")

356
00:15:58,800 --> 00:16:00,060
 <i>Momentito.</i>

357
00:16:00,130 --> 00:16:02,030
Yello.

358
00:16:02,100 --> 00:16:03,330
Oh, Stephanie,

359
00:16:03,400 --> 00:16:05,800
thanks for calling me back. I was worried...

360
00:16:07,060 --> 00:16:09,630
Oh...

361
00:16:09,700 --> 00:16:11,530
Uh-huh.

362
00:16:12,900 --> 00:16:15,660
Uh-huh.

363
00:16:15,730 --> 00:16:18,000
Uh-huh...

364
00:16:18,060 --> 00:16:20,060
No, I understand.

365
00:16:20,130 --> 00:16:22,000
Sure, we can be friends. Absolutely.

366
00:16:22,060 --> 00:16:24,030
Thanks for calling.

367
00:16:24,100 --> 00:16:25,860
Yeah, you have a nice day, too.

368
00:16:27,430 --> 00:16:29,160
You are dead to me.

369
00:16:34,930 --> 00:16:37,360
Okay, who gets the extra dumpling?

370
00:16:42,130 --> 00:16:44,630
ALL: Rock-paper-scissors- lizard-Spock.

371
00:16:48,000 --> 00:16:52,530
Okay, one of us is going to have to stop putting up Spock.

372
00:16:52,600 --> 00:16:55,560
lizard-Spock.

373
00:16:55,630 --> 00:16:57,200
(yelling)

374
00:16:57,260 --> 00:16:58,900
Oh, hey, guys.

375
00:16:58,960 --> 00:17:00,260
Hello. He

376
00:17:00,330 --> 00:17:02,730
Hi, Howard.

377
00:17:04,960 --> 00:17:06,560
Howard?

378
00:17:06,630 --> 00:17:07,960
Sheldon.

379
00:17:08,030 --> 00:17:09,700
Howard is employing

380
00:17:09,760 --> 00:17:12,060
a schoolyard paradigm in which you are,

381
00:17:12,130 --> 00:17:14,530
for all intents and purposes, deceased.

382
00:17:14,600 --> 00:17:15,660
He intends

383
00:17:15,730 --> 00:17:18,560
to act on this by not speaking to you,

384
00:17:18,630 --> 00:17:21,100
feigning an inability to hear you when you speak

385
00:17:21,160 --> 00:17:24,000
and otherwise refusing to acknowledge your existence.

386
00:17:24,060 --> 00:17:25,360
That's just ridiculous.

387
00:17:25,430 --> 00:17:27,000
Why are you cooperating with him?

388
00:17:27,060 --> 00:17:30,000
I don't make the rules, Leonard.

389
00:17:30,060 --> 00:17:33,660
Howard, come on. I didn't plan on this.

390
00:17:33,730 --> 00:17:35,530
These things just happen.

391
00:17:35,600 --> 00:17:38,230
Usually not to me, but they do happen.

392
00:17:38,300 --> 00:17:42,230
Did someone just feel a cold breeze?

393
00:17:42,300 --> 00:17:45,160
I believe this is an extension of the death metaphor.

394
00:17:46,530 --> 00:17:49,000
The cold breeze is the so-called ectoplasmic issue

395
00:17:49,060 --> 00:17:50,600
of a disembodied soul passing by.

396
00:17:51,960 --> 00:17:55,630
You know, screw it. I'm just gonna eat the dumpling.

397
00:17:55,700 --> 00:17:58,500
(knocking)

398
00:17:58,560 --> 00:18:00,700
Hey. Oh, hi, Steph.

399
00:18:00,760 --> 00:18:02,760
Come on in. Is this a bad time?

400
00:18:02,830 --> 00:18:05,100
Yeah, but I don't see a better one on the horizon, so...

401
00:18:06,730 --> 00:18:10,130
Oh, if it isn't Mrs. Dead to Me.

402
00:18:10,200 --> 00:18:11,730
Hello, Howard.

403
00:18:11,800 --> 00:18:13,260
Sheldon?

404
00:18:13,330 --> 00:18:15,560
I'm sorry, you violated the terms of your metaphor

405
00:18:15,630 --> 00:18:18,200
by acknowledging her existence. I'm out.

406
00:18:18,260 --> 00:18:20,800
He just won't listen to me.

407
00:18:20,860 --> 00:18:23,660
Okay, I guess it'll just be the three of us then.

408
00:18:23,730 --> 00:18:25,530
Lisa's gonna be disappointed. Yeah.

409
00:18:25,600 --> 00:18:28,460
Lisa?

410
00:18:28,530 --> 00:18:30,030
Yeah, my roommate.

411
00:18:30,100 --> 00:18:31,860
She just went throh a really bad breakup

412
00:18:31,930 --> 00:18:34,500
and I thought she might like to meet somebody fun like you.

413
00:18:35,700 --> 00:18:37,960
Leonard, Stephanie, you're alive!

414
00:18:42,700 --> 00:18:44,560
So, anyway, Lisa, I just wanted to tell you again

415
00:18:44,630 --> 00:18:46,560
how much I enjoyed the other night,

416
00:18:46,630 --> 00:18:49,300
and again, I'm sorry for how it ended.

417
00:18:49,360 --> 00:18:53,030
But again, if you could let me know about Friday.

418
00:18:53,100 --> 00:18:54,730
My mother needs a head count

419
00:18:54,800 --> 00:18:57,660
so she can know how big a brisket to get.

420
00:18:57,730 --> 00:18:59,930
Howard, Howard, look at this.

421
00:19:00,000 --> 00:19:01,830
Anyway, call me.

422
00:19:01,900 --> 00:19:03,960
The possibility of life on Mars has long fascinated scientists It's Howard.

423
00:19:04,030 --> 00:19:05,400
and laypersons alike.

424
00:19:05,460 --> 00:19:07,530
It's unclear how the Mars Rover got into the crevice,

425
00:19:07,600 --> 00:19:09,230
but one thing's certain:

426
00:19:09,300 --> 00:19:11,030
The data which it has sent back contain

427
00:19:11,100 --> 00:19:13,400
the first clear indications

428
00:19:13,460 --> 00:19:16,700
that there may have been life on Mars.

429
00:19:16,730 --> 00:19:19,330
It's a scientific discovery

430
00:19:19,400 --> 00:19:22,460
that has staggering implications for all mankind.

431
00:19:22,530 --> 00:19:26,330
Unfortunately, we'll never know who's responsible.

432
00:19:31,730 --> 00:19:34,360
Son of a bitch.

433
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


434
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


਍਍㤹㤹਍〰〺㨰ⰰ〵‰ⴭ‾〰〺㨰ⰲ〰਍昼湯⁴潣潬㵲⌢晦晦〰•楳敺ㄽ㸴睷⹷癴畳瑢瑩敬⹳敮㱴是湯㹴਍