1
00:00:00,700 --> 00:00:02,990
Previously on Desperate Housewives

2
00:00:03,000 --> 00:00:05,590
Gabrielle tried to rekindle an old affair.

3
00:00:05,600 --> 00:00:06,990
Gaby, i'm getting married.

4
00:00:07,000 --> 00:00:09,090
And i was married when we got together.

5
00:00:09,100 --> 00:00:11,100
That is not how i'm gonna be married.

6
00:00:11,200 --> 00:00:15,190
Lynette got the support she needed for chemotherapy.

7
00:00:15,200 --> 00:00:18,590
Katherine, who liked everything in its place... Ooh!

8
00:00:18,600 --> 00:00:21,290
Thought that her husband was forgetting his.

9
00:00:21,300 --> 00:00:23,500
Oh, i guess you learned nothing from chicago.

10
00:00:23,500 --> 00:00:24,690
Bree's attempt to keep

11
00:00:24,700 --> 00:00:26,590
Her daughter's pregnancy a secret...

12
00:00:26,600 --> 00:00:28,890
You are keeping my grandchildren from me.

13
00:00:28,900 --> 00:00:31,600
Evoked an unexpected response.

14
00:00:32,100 --> 00:00:33,390
We're life partners.

15
00:00:33,400 --> 00:00:37,190
And Susan tried to connect with the newest neighbors.

16
00:00:37,200 --> 00:00:39,390
Yeah, i've seen a lot of cable, so i get it.

17
00:00:39,400 --> 00:00:41,400
I hope we can live up to your stereotype.

18
00:00:41,700 --> 00:00:42,800
I should go.

19
00:00:46,600 --> 00:00:48,290
The odd-looking boxes

20
00:00:48,300 --> 00:00:51,490
Were delivered to the home of Bob Hunter and Lee Mcdermott 

21
00:00:51,500 --> 00:00:53,600
Early on a tuesday morning.

22
00:00:54,300 --> 00:00:56,990
It wasn't long before workmen had opened them

23
00:00:57,000 --> 00:01:00,300
And begun assembling the various parts and pieces.

24
00:01:01,800 --> 00:01:04,090
Happily, it only took three hours

25
00:01:04,100 --> 00:01:08,400
To turn the contents into a finished work of art.

26
00:01:10,100 --> 00:01:12,890
Sadly, it only took 15 minutes

27
00:01:12,900 --> 00:01:15,090
For the residents of Wisteria Lane ...

29
00:01:16,100 --> 00:01:17,390
What the hell is it?

30
00:01:17,400 --> 00:01:20,300
To become art critics.

31
00:01:21,000 --> 00:01:23,890
I think it's a sculpture. I think it's crap.

32
00:01:23,900 --> 00:01:25,190
Of all the gay men in the world,

33
00:01:25,200 --> 00:01:29,290
We have to get the two without taste. What are we gonna do about this?

34
00:01:29,300 --> 00:01:31,590
I say we keep smiling and look for the hidden cameras.

35
00:01:31,600 --> 00:01:33,090
I think we're about to get punk'd.

36
00:01:33,100 --> 00:01:35,790
I don't think there's anything we can do. It's not our lawn.

37
00:01:35,800 --> 00:01:36,790
It's our neighborhood,

38
00:01:36,800 --> 00:01:38,900
And we have rules against this sort of thing,

39
00:01:38,900 --> 00:01:40,900
Or at least we did when i used to live here.

40
00:01:41,100 --> 00:01:43,100
Who's running the homeowners association?

41
00:01:43,100 --> 00:01:45,190
Well, it was mary alice, but as you may have heard...

42
00:01:45,200 --> 00:01:49,190
Yes, very tragic. So we haven't had a president in four years?

43
00:01:49,200 --> 00:01:51,790
No one would volunteer. It's a pain-in-the-ass job.

44
00:01:51,800 --> 00:01:53,200
I'll volunteer.

45
00:01:53,400 --> 00:01:55,290
We can hold an election in the next couple of days.

46
00:01:55,300 --> 00:01:58,190
I can get rid of this tinfoil atrocity by the weekend.

47
00:01:58,200 --> 00:01:59,790
Okay, before we become an ugly mob,

48
00:01:59,800 --> 00:02:01,790
Why doesn't one of us go talk to the guys?

49
00:02:01,800 --> 00:02:03,900
But not me. They hate me.

50
00:02:04,700 --> 00:02:07,400
Bree, you talk to them. You can relate to them.

51
00:02:07,800 --> 00:02:09,000
Why would you say that?

52
00:02:09,000 --> 00:02:10,890
You got a kid who came flying out of the closet

53
00:02:10,900 --> 00:02:13,000
And a husband who's been looking for the doorknob.

54
00:02:15,700 --> 00:02:17,000
What? You've met him.

55
00:02:17,000 --> 00:02:18,600
Ooh! They're coming.

56
00:02:22,900 --> 00:02:24,000
Good morning, ladies.

57
00:02:24,000 --> 00:02:28,000
Hi. Uh, we were just talking about your sculpture.

58
00:02:28,000 --> 00:02:28,890
That's what i love about art--

59
00:02:28,900 --> 00:02:31,590
The way it provokes discussion. Although it would've been nice

60
00:02:31,600 --> 00:02:35,300
If you had discussed it with us. What, you don't-- you don't like it?

61
00:02:36,400 --> 00:02:37,790
Well, we're not saying that.

62
00:02:37,800 --> 00:02:39,500
It's just a little, uh...

63
00:02:41,600 --> 00:02:42,800
It's an eyesore.

64
00:02:43,000 --> 00:02:44,400
Really? Mm-hmm.

65
00:02:44,500 --> 00:02:46,390
You hear that, Bob ? We flew to finland

66
00:02:46,400 --> 00:02:49,400
And paid $24,000 to commission an eyesore.

67
00:02:49,500 --> 00:02:50,500
I don't mind it.

68
00:02:51,400 --> 00:02:54,300
Not to brag, but i went to art school. Community college.

69
00:02:54,600 --> 00:02:57,000
And they taught us that art is subjective.

70
00:02:59,100 --> 00:03:00,400
Thank you, Susan .

71
00:03:00,700 --> 00:03:02,900
Susan's need for approval aside,

72
00:03:03,000 --> 00:03:05,700
This clearly is not appropriate for the street.

73
00:03:05,900 --> 00:03:09,000
Wisteria lane has a... Traditional look.

74
00:03:09,200 --> 00:03:10,190
Well, maybe you'd like it better

75
00:03:10,200 --> 00:03:11,700
If we covered it with a gingham throw.

76
00:03:14,000 --> 00:03:16,390
Ladies, uh, i'm sorry.

77
00:03:16,400 --> 00:03:19,300
We honestly thought that people would like it,

78
00:03:19,400 --> 00:03:22,890
But even if you disapprove, we hope that you will respect

79
00:03:22,900 --> 00:03:25,300
Our right to decorate as we see fit.

80
00:03:29,700 --> 00:03:31,400
Have a nice day, philistines.

81
00:03:32,100 --> 00:03:36,600
Yes, art came to Wisteria Lane on a tuesday morning,

82
00:03:36,700 --> 00:03:38,800
And by tuesday afternoon...

83
00:03:38,800 --> 00:03:42,300
I think it's time to reconvene the homeowners' association.

84
00:03:42,800 --> 00:03:44,500
All in favor?

85
00:03:44,900 --> 00:03:45,900
Aye.

86
00:03:47,000 --> 00:03:49,200
War had come as well.

87
00:03:59,200 --> 00:04:01,490
As word of the sculpture spread,

88
00:04:01,500 --> 00:04:03,690
Bob and Lee began to wonder

89
00:04:03,700 --> 00:04:06,700
If any of their neighbors would be supportive.

90
00:04:07,800 --> 00:04:10,090
But when the sculpture's true function

91
00:04:10,100 --> 00:04:12,000
Was unveiled the next day,

92
00:04:12,800 --> 00:04:15,100
Whatever support they did have...

93
00:04:18,700 --> 00:04:21,300
Was quickly washed away.

94
00:04:21,800 --> 00:04:23,100
Come on.

95
00:04:23,500 --> 00:04:25,590
It's 6:00 a.m. What is that?

96
00:04:25,600 --> 00:04:27,990
I don't know, but make it stop.

98
00:04:34,100 --> 00:04:35,600
Oh, my god.

99
00:04:43,700 --> 00:04:46,500
Wow! It's a fountain, too.

100
00:04:47,000 --> 00:04:48,690
We would have mentioned that yesterday,

101
00:04:48,700 --> 00:04:50,290
But your friends were a little uptight.

102
00:04:50,300 --> 00:04:51,690
Yeah, they can get like that.

103
00:04:51,700 --> 00:04:55,100
So do you think that you can just turn it off for a second?

104
00:05:01,400 --> 00:05:01,790
What's up?

105
00:05:01,800 --> 00:05:04,000
I was just wondering, um,

106
00:05:04,500 --> 00:05:07,700
Do you think you could move it to your backyard?

107
00:05:09,200 --> 00:05:10,700
Why? I thought you liked it.

108
00:05:10,900 --> 00:05:12,890
Remember? You said, "art is subjective."

109
00:05:12,900 --> 00:05:16,090
Yes. Quiet art is subjective

110
00:05:16,100 --> 00:05:18,590
But you see, Mike is working really long hours lately,

111
00:05:18,600 --> 00:05:20,790
And he can't s Lee p with all that noise.

112
00:05:20,800 --> 00:05:23,590
We're not gonna turn it off because we need it to drown out

113
00:05:23,600 --> 00:05:26,890
All the stuff we hear coming from your house. Like what?

114
00:05:26,900 --> 00:05:28,990
Let's see. You yakking to your mom on the phone.

115
00:05:29,000 --> 00:05:30,690
You grunting through your pilates dvds.

116
00:05:30,700 --> 00:05:33,600
You in the shower, butchering the score to "brigadoon."

117
00:05:33,600 --> 00:05:34,900
I have a lovely voice.

118
00:05:35,300 --> 00:05:37,900
Whoever told you that is not your friend.

119
00:05:39,400 --> 00:05:42,600
He's a little cranky. I think someone needs his french toast.

120
00:05:43,300 --> 00:05:44,400
Come on, Lee .

121
00:05:44,900 --> 00:05:46,590
No, no, no, no. No, no, we're not done here.

122
00:05:46,600 --> 00:05:48,490
As your neighbor, i have a right to be heard...

123
00:05:48,500 --> 00:05:50,790
And i say that simple human decency

124
00:05:50,800 --> 00:05:54,200
Dictates that you turn off that fountain right now!

126
00:06:00,100 --> 00:06:01,190
Do over, Parker .

127
00:06:01,200 --> 00:06:02,900
Hey, guys, i got your snack.

128
00:06:03,300 --> 00:06:04,390
What you playing?

129
00:06:04,400 --> 00:06:06,700
Action figures. Wanna play, mom?

130
00:06:06,800 --> 00:06:09,400
She does awesome alien voices.

131
00:06:09,800 --> 00:06:12,400
Thanks, sweetheart.

133
00:06:18,100 --> 00:06:20,500
Oh, yeah. Hi, dr. Shiller.

134
00:06:21,400 --> 00:06:23,290
Okay, that's my white blood count.

135
00:06:23,300 --> 00:06:25,290
Uh-huh, but as long as it's higher than 4.0,

136
00:06:25,300 --> 00:06:27,100
That means i don't have neutropenia, right?

137
00:06:28,500 --> 00:06:29,600
Well, that's great.

138
00:06:30,200 --> 00:06:31,900
Thanks for calling.

139
00:06:33,300 --> 00:06:35,200
Yeah, you, too. Bye.

140
00:06:38,700 --> 00:06:39,400
What?

141
00:06:39,800 --> 00:06:42,200
You can't talk about doctors up here.

142
00:06:42,200 --> 00:06:43,700
Or about being sick.

143
00:06:44,000 --> 00:06:47,200
If you do, you have to go. That's the rule.

145
00:06:49,500 --> 00:06:50,900
That's a good rule.

146
00:06:52,300 --> 00:06:54,390
Although it wasn't bad news. It was actually--

147
00:06:54,400 --> 00:06:57,800
Doesn't Matt er. We voted. It's a rule.

148
00:06:59,000 --> 00:06:59,800
Got it.

149
00:07:00,100 --> 00:07:01,900
Sick talk done, okay?

150
00:07:02,900 --> 00:07:04,000
You guys have fun.

151
00:07:06,200 --> 00:07:07,200
Freeze power.

152
00:07:07,200 --> 00:07:10,090
Do over, Parker . That guy doesn't have freezing power.

153
00:07:10,100 --> 00:07:12,700
If his guy can fly, my guy can freeze.

154
00:07:14,400 --> 00:07:17,800
Hi. It's, uh, mrs. Hodge. May i please speak with Danielle ?

155
00:07:17,800 --> 00:07:19,390
Muffins. T...

156
00:07:19,400 --> 00:07:22,790
Hands off. We're bringing these to Danielle for her birthday.

157
00:07:22,800 --> 00:07:24,100
What do you mean, she's gone?

158
00:07:25,500 --> 00:07:26,800
And you believed her?

159
00:07:27,900 --> 00:07:28,790
You idiot!

160
00:07:28,800 --> 00:07:31,990
I should sue your irresponsible ass off for this.

161
00:07:32,000 --> 00:07:34,800
Yeah, well, good day to you, too, reverend mother!

162
00:07:35,200 --> 00:07:37,490
What happened? Those stupid nuns at the convent

163
00:07:37,500 --> 00:07:38,990
Let Danielle 's grandmother kidnap her.

164
00:07:39,000 --> 00:07:42,300
She claimed i'd given her permission for a weekend visit.

165
00:07:44,400 --> 00:07:46,300
Phyllis! It's me.

166
00:07:46,500 --> 00:07:48,490
You can screen your calls all you want to,

167
00:07:48,500 --> 00:07:51,300
But trust me, old woman, you are in a world of trouble.

168
00:07:51,400 --> 00:07:53,700
I know where you live, and i am coming for you.

169
00:07:53,800 --> 00:07:54,990
Shouldn't we be worried?

170
00:07:55,000 --> 00:07:57,300
No, i think we're ready for her.

171
00:07:57,300 --> 00:08:00,000
Now show me again how you kill the zombies.

173
00:08:04,000 --> 00:08:05,900
Why can't i go? I play golf.

174
00:08:08,100 --> 00:08:11,000
And i'd love to meet your... College buddies.

175
00:08:11,300 --> 00:08:14,900
Edie, me and the guys have only two rules for these weekends--

176
00:08:15,100 --> 00:08:17,400
No plaid pants and no women.

177
00:08:17,800 --> 00:08:19,600
Fine. Be that way.

178
00:08:20,700 --> 00:08:23,700
And to think, i got you a gift.

179
00:08:28,500 --> 00:08:30,500
Hey, golf balls.

180
00:08:30,900 --> 00:08:32,100
They're monogrammed.

181
00:08:32,900 --> 00:08:34,700
Wait. These are your initials.

182
00:08:34,900 --> 00:08:37,600
Exactly. While you're out there playing,

183
00:08:38,000 --> 00:08:42,400
I want everyone to know who your balls belong to.

184
00:08:52,700 --> 00:08:54,690
Good work, boys, but i have to head out in a few minutes,

185
00:08:54,700 --> 00:08:57,300
So make sure you put all the stuff back in the garage.

186
00:08:59,000 --> 00:08:59,800
Hello?

187
00:08:59,900 --> 00:09:01,500
Hey, on my way.

188
00:09:01,600 --> 00:09:03,100
Meet you at the hotel, okay?

189
00:09:03,300 --> 00:09:05,100
I'm leaving in five minutes.

190
00:09:13,800 --> 00:09:16,300
Uh, Brett , could you come here a second?

191
00:09:18,700 --> 00:09:21,700
How long has that van been parked over there? Couple hours.

192
00:09:22,100 --> 00:09:24,400
Hours? Are you serious?

193
00:09:25,800 --> 00:09:29,000
Oh, my god. I think he's just waiting for someone to come home.

194
00:09:29,500 --> 00:09:32,100
Brett, when's the last time a cable guy waited for anyone?

195
00:09:34,800 --> 00:09:36,900
I see a lot of lawn mowing in your future.

196
00:09:37,100 --> 00:09:40,290
Hey, it's me again. You're not gonna believe this.

197
00:09:40,300 --> 00:09:42,400
Before Victor left on his business trip,

198
00:09:42,400 --> 00:09:43,900
He hired someone to tail me.

199
00:09:44,400 --> 00:09:46,400
Oh, man. Should we call this off? No way.

200
00:09:46,500 --> 00:09:48,290
It's gonna take more than a guy with mini binoculars

201
00:09:48,300 --> 00:09:51,100
And a bag of doughnuts to keep me under lock and key.

202
00:09:52,200 --> 00:09:53,600
I'll be there as soon as i can.

203
00:10:03,000 --> 00:10:04,800
Boys, time to get paid.

204
00:10:06,000 --> 00:10:07,600
Come on, Eddie !

205
00:10:17,500 --> 00:10:20,300
Bye, mrs. Lang. See you next time.

206
00:10:23,100 --> 00:10:24,700
Come back here!

207
00:10:25,200 --> 00:10:26,800
Are you taking the bus home?

209
00:10:32,700 --> 00:10:33,890
As soon as we get around the corner,

210
00:10:33,900 --> 00:10:35,600
We're gonna have to adjust this horn.

211
00:10:46,600 --> 00:10:47,400
Gabrielle.

212
00:10:48,600 --> 00:10:49,300
Hey.

213
00:10:50,400 --> 00:10:52,200
H-hi.

214
00:10:54,100 --> 00:10:56,200
Look at you. What a surprise.

215
00:10:58,000 --> 00:11:00,300
Oh, uh, this is Gaby . This is my wife Tammy .

216
00:11:00,400 --> 00:11:01,800
Tammy, this is Gabrielle .

217
00:11:02,200 --> 00:11:05,700
Wow, look at you. Congratulations.

218
00:11:05,700 --> 00:11:07,900
Thanks. It wasn't planned.

219
00:11:09,700 --> 00:11:14,100
Okay. So... Are you guys staying here?

220
00:11:14,100 --> 00:11:15,900
No, we just came for some lunch.

221
00:11:15,900 --> 00:11:17,400
Daddy owns this place.

222
00:11:17,800 --> 00:11:19,990
That's right. You're a hotel heiress.

223
00:11:20,000 --> 00:11:22,800
Yeah, but not one of the skanky ones.

224
00:11:23,300 --> 00:11:24,800
How do you two know each other?

225
00:11:26,300 --> 00:11:28,500
I used to be Gabrielle 's gardener.

226
00:11:28,800 --> 00:11:31,090
Oh! Well, as you can see,

227
00:11:31,100 --> 00:11:33,590
He's certainly married up from lawn boy.

228
00:11:33,600 --> 00:11:35,000
Tammy. What?

229
00:11:36,100 --> 00:11:37,200
Forget it.

230
00:11:38,200 --> 00:11:40,500
So i heard you married the mayor.

231
00:11:40,700 --> 00:11:42,200
You're married to Victor lang?

232
00:11:42,600 --> 00:11:44,400
He and daddy go hunting together.

233
00:11:44,500 --> 00:11:47,090
I told John if he would just be nicer to daddy,

234
00:11:47,100 --> 00:11:48,490
He could hang out with people like the mayor

235
00:11:48,500 --> 00:11:50,800
And make important contacts.

236
00:11:50,900 --> 00:11:53,090
And i keep telling you that i don't need

237
00:11:53,100 --> 00:11:55,000
To kiss your father's ass to have a career.

238
00:11:56,500 --> 00:11:58,500
Uh, yeah, so i married the mayor.

239
00:11:58,600 --> 00:11:59,590
Kooky, huh?

240
00:11:59,600 --> 00:12:02,890
So, um, is he here with you?

241
00:12:02,900 --> 00:12:06,090
Uh, no. He's away at a conference,

242
00:12:06,100 --> 00:12:09,600
So i decided to treat myself to a spa weekend.

243
00:12:09,900 --> 00:12:12,800
Ooh! You should definitely get the full body massage.

244
00:12:15,000 --> 00:12:16,500
Oh, i plan to.

245
00:12:18,000 --> 00:12:19,000
Good to see you.

246
00:12:19,000 --> 00:12:20,300
You, too, Gaby .

247
00:12:23,100 --> 00:12:25,390
Sorry about that. A complete shock.

248
00:12:25,400 --> 00:12:27,300
I mean, of all people to run into.

249
00:12:27,300 --> 00:12:28,200
Who were they?

250
00:12:32,200 --> 00:12:34,500
Just an old friend and his idiot wife.

251
00:12:34,700 --> 00:12:36,100
Come on. Let's go.

252
00:12:39,200 --> 00:12:42,200
Bree, how lovely to see you.

253
00:12:42,200 --> 00:12:45,190
Cram it, Phyllis . You got a lot of nerve

254
00:12:45,200 --> 00:12:47,800
Stealing Danielle from a convent we prepaid for.

255
00:12:48,300 --> 00:12:49,400
She didn't steal me.

256
00:12:49,900 --> 00:12:52,790
I'm a mature person capable of making my own decisions.

257
00:12:52,800 --> 00:12:54,290
Well, good. You can decide to pack,

258
00:12:54,300 --> 00:12:56,800
Because we are taking you back to the convent.

259
00:12:56,800 --> 00:12:58,590
Mnh-mnh. I'm turning 18 this weekend,

260
00:12:58,600 --> 00:13:00,600
So you can't boss me around anymore.

261
00:13:00,800 --> 00:13:01,490
I'm staying with grandma,

262
00:13:01,500 --> 00:13:03,290
And i'm gonna have my baby delivered here.

263
00:13:03,300 --> 00:13:05,590
We have an excellent medical staff.

264
00:13:05,600 --> 00:13:06,690
It's a retirement village.

265
00:13:06,700 --> 00:13:09,600
All these doctors know how to deliver is bad news.

266
00:13:09,700 --> 00:13:11,400
I don't care. I'm staying,

267
00:13:11,700 --> 00:13:14,800
And i'm gonna raise the baby here, too. What?

268
00:13:14,800 --> 00:13:16,400
Entirely her idea.

269
00:13:16,500 --> 00:13:18,890
A baby is god's most precious gift.

270
00:13:18,900 --> 00:13:20,590
I will not have mine raised

271
00:13:20,600 --> 00:13:23,300
By a cold, emotionally unavailable woman like you.

272
00:13:23,400 --> 00:13:24,390
"emotionally unavailable."

273
00:13:24,400 --> 00:13:27,100
Gosh, i wonder where she picked up that little phrase. Hmm.

274
00:13:28,700 --> 00:13:30,800
Like i'm too dumb to think of it myself?

275
00:13:31,100 --> 00:13:34,390
You're always mean to me, just like you were to dad.

276
00:13:34,400 --> 00:13:36,300
You emasculated him.

277
00:13:36,400 --> 00:13:38,300
Well, you're not gonna emasculate me.

278
00:13:38,600 --> 00:13:39,990
You don't even know what that means,

279
00:13:40,000 --> 00:13:42,390
You petulant sock puppet!

280
00:13:42,400 --> 00:13:44,000
Who cares?

281
00:13:45,300 --> 00:13:46,600
I'm going to the store.

282
00:13:49,500 --> 00:13:50,900
Buy a dictionary.

283
00:13:53,000 --> 00:13:55,300
So that's all settled.

284
00:13:56,600 --> 00:13:58,200
Would you like some iced tea?

285
00:14:08,600 --> 00:14:10,300
You aren't joining the lynch mob?

286
00:14:10,500 --> 00:14:12,790
Uh, you mean Katherine 's homeowners thing?

287
00:14:12,800 --> 00:14:14,490
Yeah, i think i'll sit this one out.

288
00:14:14,500 --> 00:14:16,900
No, no, no. You can't do that. You've got to pick a side.

289
00:14:17,600 --> 00:14:19,800
Art or mindless conformity?

290
00:14:21,200 --> 00:14:23,090
See, this is one of the upsides of having cancer.

291
00:14:23,100 --> 00:14:26,000
You get to excuse yourself from petty neighborhood squabbles.

292
00:14:26,300 --> 00:14:28,800
You won't think they're so petty when she comes after you.

293
00:14:29,400 --> 00:14:31,300
Me? Why would she do that?

294
00:14:32,000 --> 00:14:34,490
Did the homeowners' association approve everything in your yard?

295
00:14:34,500 --> 00:14:36,600
The fence? That swing?

296
00:14:37,100 --> 00:14:38,100
The tree house?

297
00:14:39,400 --> 00:14:41,190
I don't think Katherine will bother herself

298
00:14:41,200 --> 00:14:42,090
Over a tree house.

299
00:14:42,100 --> 00:14:43,700
First, they came for the fountains,

300
00:14:44,100 --> 00:14:47,700
And i did not speak out because i had no fountain. What?

301
00:14:47,900 --> 00:14:49,290
Then they came for the lawn gnomes,

302
00:14:49,300 --> 00:14:51,500
And i did not speak out because i had no gnome.

303
00:14:51,700 --> 00:14:53,490
You're comparing Katherine to a nazi?

304
00:14:53,500 --> 00:14:55,300
Then they came for my tree house,

305
00:14:55,600 --> 00:14:58,100
And there was no one left to speak out for me.

306
00:15:02,600 --> 00:15:05,390
Thank you, ladies. I so appreciate your input,

307
00:15:05,400 --> 00:15:07,500
And i think we can all agree

308
00:15:07,500 --> 00:15:10,790
That the fountain has no place on our street.

309
00:15:10,800 --> 00:15:14,900
Yeah, we gotta show those gays we mean business.

310
00:15:15,600 --> 00:15:19,890
Ida, again, the issue is not Bob and Lee being gay.

311
00:15:19,900 --> 00:15:21,200
It's the fountain.

312
00:15:21,900 --> 00:15:23,900
Well, can't it be both?

313
00:15:25,800 --> 00:15:26,500
Anyway...

314
00:15:27,100 --> 00:15:30,290
If you elect me president, my first act

315
00:15:30,300 --> 00:15:33,890
Will be to eliminate this so-called work of art.

316
00:15:33,900 --> 00:15:34,900
Hear, hear.

317
00:15:36,900 --> 00:15:37,690
Yes, Lynette .

318
00:15:37,700 --> 00:15:40,600
After you get rid of this fountain, that's it, right?

319
00:15:40,900 --> 00:15:41,600
I don't follow.

320
00:15:42,200 --> 00:15:44,590
I mean... You're not gonna start

321
00:15:44,600 --> 00:15:47,500
Checking everyone's yards for things that don't fit in?

322
00:15:47,600 --> 00:15:49,200
Oh, of course not.

323
00:15:49,900 --> 00:15:52,400
As long as those things meet the association's guidelines.

324
00:15:54,000 --> 00:15:56,100
Uh-huh. And what if they don't?

325
00:15:56,900 --> 00:15:59,000
Are you referring to something in particular?

326
00:15:59,300 --> 00:16:02,500
My kids' tree house. Can you promise you'll leave it alone?

327
00:16:02,700 --> 00:16:05,900
Well, it's not up to me. That's the whole point.

328
00:16:05,900 --> 00:16:06,700
There are rules.

329
00:16:07,400 --> 00:16:08,900
That sounds like a no.

330
00:16:09,300 --> 00:16:10,590
If i make an exception for you,

331
00:16:10,600 --> 00:16:12,500
Then i have to make one for everyone,

332
00:16:12,800 --> 00:16:15,190
And surely, you realize that the whole neighborhood

333
00:16:15,200 --> 00:16:16,900
Can't revolve around your little tree house.

334
00:16:19,000 --> 00:16:20,590
Now since i am running unopposed,

335
00:16:20,600 --> 00:16:23,000
I just need someone to second my nomination.

336
00:16:26,100 --> 00:16:28,300
Oh! Thank you, Lynette .

337
00:16:29,200 --> 00:16:31,590
No, actually, i'm nominating myself.

338
00:16:31,600 --> 00:16:33,500
I am now running for president...

339
00:16:35,000 --> 00:16:36,000
Against you.

340
00:16:45,300 --> 00:16:48,000
You know, running for president in your condition?

341
00:16:48,200 --> 00:16:49,800
I don't think it's a good idea.

342
00:16:49,900 --> 00:16:52,000
Tom, i don't want your opinion, just your vote.

343
00:16:52,400 --> 00:16:54,000
If you want to save the tree house,

344
00:16:54,100 --> 00:16:55,800
Why don't you let me run instead?

345
00:16:55,900 --> 00:16:58,390
Because you'd never win. Bossy women rule this street.

346
00:16:58,400 --> 00:17:02,200
You know that. I know one rules my life.

347
00:17:02,400 --> 00:17:03,900
I'm sorry. I didn't catch that.

348
00:17:04,500 --> 00:17:05,300
Nothing.

349
00:17:06,200 --> 00:17:09,290
Look, this is not just about a tree house or a fountain.

350
00:17:09,300 --> 00:17:10,800
This is about

351
00:17:10,800 --> 00:17:12,590
What kind of neighborhood we want to live in.

352
00:17:12,600 --> 00:17:14,190
Do we get to make our own choices,

353
00:17:14,200 --> 00:17:16,590
Or do we let the taste police make them for us?

354
00:17:16,600 --> 00:17:21,100
Ah, now i get it. This about you wanting to take on Katherine .

355
00:17:21,300 --> 00:17:24,900
No! This is about personal freedom--

356
00:17:24,900 --> 00:17:26,490
Specifically, my personal freedom

357
00:17:26,500 --> 00:17:29,290
To take down that jackbooted hausfrau.

358
00:17:29,300 --> 00:17:31,390
Honey, if you're looking for something to fight,

359
00:17:31,400 --> 00:17:32,790
How about your cancer?

360
00:17:32,800 --> 00:17:34,290
Hey, a tumor is a tumor

361
00:17:34,300 --> 00:17:36,800
Whether it's in your body or living across the street.

362
00:17:43,000 --> 00:17:44,190
I don't know why you buy those things.

363
00:17:44,200 --> 00:17:45,800
They just end up on the floor.

364
00:17:46,200 --> 00:17:49,000
Because i want to feel pretty and feminine.

365
00:17:50,900 --> 00:17:54,390
Ooh! My chili cheese fries! Just a second!

366
00:17:54,400 --> 00:17:56,800
Gabrielle? It's me-- John .

367
00:17:58,200 --> 00:18:00,000
John? John who?

368
00:18:03,200 --> 00:18:05,790
Uh, okay. You know that old friend

369
00:18:05,800 --> 00:18:07,000
I ran into in the lobby?

370
00:18:07,000 --> 00:18:08,800
It might have been John Rowland .

371
00:18:10,100 --> 00:18:12,300
Maybe. I'm not sure.

372
00:18:13,200 --> 00:18:14,100
Gabrielle?

373
00:18:14,400 --> 00:18:16,990
But just to be safe, you may wanna hide in the closet.

374
00:18:17,000 --> 00:18:19,600
What? I'm not hiding from that guy. Really?

375
00:18:19,800 --> 00:18:22,200
Because his father-in-law goes hunting with Victor --

376
00:18:22,400 --> 00:18:24,390
You know, the guy who hired someone

377
00:18:24,400 --> 00:18:26,100
To tail us and possibly kill us?

378
00:18:27,100 --> 00:18:28,200
Okay.

379
00:18:35,900 --> 00:18:37,800
John, what are you doing here?

380
00:18:38,200 --> 00:18:39,900
When i ran into you last fall,

381
00:18:39,900 --> 00:18:41,290
You wanted to start up our affair again,

382
00:18:41,300 --> 00:18:42,500
And i wasn't ready.

383
00:18:43,100 --> 00:18:45,300
Well, i'm ready.

386
00:18:57,200 --> 00:18:59,990
Listen, i promised Tom i wouldn't knock myself out

387
00:19:00,000 --> 00:19:02,800
Campaigning for this homeowners thing,

388
00:19:03,000 --> 00:19:05,090
So i was hoping you could help me--

389
00:19:05,100 --> 00:19:09,200
You know, ring some bells, talk me up, that sort of thing?

390
00:19:09,400 --> 00:19:10,900
I would love to, but...

391
00:19:12,300 --> 00:19:13,500
But what?

392
00:19:14,800 --> 00:19:15,990
This is awkward.

393
00:19:16,000 --> 00:19:18,790
Uh, i told Katherine i'd vote for her.

394
00:19:18,800 --> 00:19:20,190
You're picking her over me?

395
00:19:20,200 --> 00:19:22,090
Uh, it's not like i'm pro- Katherine .

396
00:19:22,100 --> 00:19:24,100
I'm just anti-fountain.

397
00:19:25,700 --> 00:19:28,000
Oh, don't give me that look. I made her a promise.

398
00:19:28,100 --> 00:19:30,290
Yes, but that was before your best friend

399
00:19:30,300 --> 00:19:31,900
Threw her scarf in the ring.

401
00:19:34,600 --> 00:19:36,890
Okay. If i vote for you,

402
00:19:36,900 --> 00:19:38,290
Do you promise to get rid of that fountain?

403
00:19:38,300 --> 00:19:41,990
See, that's awkward for me. This is about personal freedom.

404
00:19:42,000 --> 00:19:44,400
You know? I'm running as a libertarian.

405
00:19:44,500 --> 00:19:46,290
Well, i'm voting as a light s Lee per.

406
00:19:46,300 --> 00:19:48,190
It's right outside our bedroom window.

407
00:19:48,200 --> 00:19:51,190
Seriously, Lynette , it's like living next to splash mountain.

408
00:19:51,200 --> 00:19:53,690
But it's my kids' tree house. They really need it. Well,

409
00:19:53,700 --> 00:19:54,690
We need our s Lee p.

410
00:19:54,700 --> 00:19:56,090
Why don't you get earplugs?

411
00:19:56,100 --> 00:19:59,400
Why don't you get... Tree house plugs?

412
00:19:59,800 --> 00:20:01,890
What? That doesn't even make sense.

413
00:20:01,900 --> 00:20:02,890
Yeah, i'm sorry.

414
00:20:02,900 --> 00:20:04,700
You know, tired people aren't witty.

415
00:20:08,200 --> 00:20:10,190
Seriously, John , you have got to get out of here.

416
00:20:10,200 --> 00:20:12,990
No. Please. I need to be with you.

417
00:20:13,000 --> 00:20:15,990
What about your wife? You met her. She's dumb, demanding,

418
00:20:16,000 --> 00:20:19,290
Totally self-centered, especially in bed.

419
00:20:19,300 --> 00:20:20,590
I mean, she's awful.

420
00:20:20,600 --> 00:20:24,200
Awfully pregnant. I know. I-i'm completely trapped,

421
00:20:24,200 --> 00:20:26,090
Just like you were with mr. Solis.

423
00:20:27,400 --> 00:20:29,790
I-i wasn't "trapped."

424
00:20:29,800 --> 00:20:30,590
What do you mean?

425
00:20:30,600 --> 00:20:33,100
All you'd ever talk about was what a selfish pig he was.

426
00:20:34,400 --> 00:20:36,190
Well, i think you're paraphrasing.

427
00:20:36,200 --> 00:20:37,990
Okay, seriously, you have to go.

428
00:20:38,000 --> 00:20:42,300
Come on. You know it would be hot, just like old times.

429
00:20:42,700 --> 00:20:44,590
Remember how great our sex was? Oh,

430
00:20:44,600 --> 00:20:46,490
I don't think we need to get into that.

431
00:20:46,500 --> 00:20:48,600
What about the time we were doing it in the shower?

432
00:20:50,000 --> 00:20:53,390
Mr. Solis drove up? Uh, does not ring a bell.

433
00:20:53,400 --> 00:20:55,490
Come on. And i hid in the closet?

434
00:20:55,500 --> 00:20:58,800
And you looked so hot, mr. Solis pulled you down on the bed.

435
00:21:01,000 --> 00:21:03,700
And you had to fake an orgasm just so he wouldn't catch on.

436
00:21:05,700 --> 00:21:07,400
Yeah, good times.

437
00:21:07,800 --> 00:21:10,890
Anyways, uh, that's a negatory on the affair... What?

438
00:21:10,900 --> 00:21:12,800
And i will see you later.

439
00:21:12,900 --> 00:21:15,290
Come on, but we're so good together. Gab--

440
00:21:15,300 --> 00:21:16,900
Please!

441
00:21:21,200 --> 00:21:23,700
Boy, that was a close one, huh?

442
00:21:28,200 --> 00:21:29,290
You faked it with me

443
00:21:29,300 --> 00:21:31,600
While that wax job was hiding in the closet?

444
00:21:31,700 --> 00:21:34,600
Yes, i had an affair. Old news. Move on.

445
00:21:35,400 --> 00:21:37,890
Where's that room service? So you're not gonna apologize

446
00:21:37,900 --> 00:21:39,990
For humiliating me in my own bed?

447
00:21:40,000 --> 00:21:43,690
You deserved it. All you cared about back then was work.

448
00:21:43,700 --> 00:21:45,690
Hey, i was not that bad of a husband,

449
00:21:45,700 --> 00:21:48,090
And somebody had to support your italian shoe addiction.

450
00:21:48,100 --> 00:21:50,900
I shopped because i was bored and lonely--

451
00:21:50,900 --> 00:21:53,690
Same reason i had an affair. Yeah, with our teenage gardener!

452
00:21:53,700 --> 00:21:56,100
I should have snapped that kid's neck two years ago.

453
00:21:56,300 --> 00:21:59,390
Oh, let it go! John Rowland didn't do anything to you

454
00:21:59,400 --> 00:22:01,300
That you're not doing to Victor .

455
00:22:01,400 --> 00:22:04,500
You can't even compare the two! It's completely different!

456
00:22:04,800 --> 00:22:06,900
Is it, mr. Man in the closet?

457
00:22:08,600 --> 00:22:09,700
Yeah, you heard me.

458
00:22:10,100 --> 00:22:11,700
Who's John Rowland now?

459
00:22:21,800 --> 00:22:23,500
Katherine, what are you up to?

460
00:22:23,500 --> 00:22:24,900
Just visiting a friend.

461
00:22:25,000 --> 00:22:29,500
Liar. You're campaigning. Cookies--nice touch.

462
00:22:30,900 --> 00:22:32,200
Ditto on the scarf.

463
00:22:36,700 --> 00:22:38,800
Edie, you got a moment?

464
00:22:39,000 --> 00:22:41,390
I am running for president of the homeowners' association,

465
00:22:41,400 --> 00:22:45,000
And i want to talk to you about that horrible fountain.

466
00:22:45,000 --> 00:22:47,390
Screw the fountain. You want my support?

467
00:22:47,400 --> 00:22:50,200
Make Ida greenberg ditch that screen door.

468
00:22:50,600 --> 00:22:52,690
That rusty, old tetanus bucket...

469
00:22:52,700 --> 00:22:54,900
Looks fine to me. It's hardly ripped at all.

470
00:22:54,900 --> 00:22:56,590
In fact, if you give me your support...

471
00:22:56,600 --> 00:22:59,390
I'll make mrs. Burkette prune those roses.

472
00:22:59,400 --> 00:23:01,490
It's a garden, not a jungle,

473
00:23:01,500 --> 00:23:03,490
And you shouldn't have to...

474
00:23:03,500 --> 00:23:04,590
Pay for a fence you don't even want.

475
00:23:04,600 --> 00:23:06,590
That's not how you make good neighbors,

476
00:23:06,600 --> 00:23:09,990
And i don't care if... The Mustafas don't celebrate christmas.

477
00:23:10,000 --> 00:23:13,000
You're asking them to hang a few lights, not convert.

478
00:23:13,500 --> 00:23:15,090
When i'm president, i promise...

479
00:23:15,100 --> 00:23:16,990
You can keep that satellite dish.

480
00:23:17,000 --> 00:23:19,790
In fact, this is practically a first amendment issue.

481
00:23:19,800 --> 00:23:20,990
The way i see it...

482
00:23:21,000 --> 00:23:22,390
The entire neighborhood

483
00:23:22,400 --> 00:23:25,600
Should be a testament to symmetry and beauty.

484
00:23:25,900 --> 00:23:26,790
So...

485
00:23:26,800 --> 00:23:28,000
Have i got your vote?

486
00:23:28,400 --> 00:23:30,700
Um, i'm not sure yet.

487
00:23:31,000 --> 00:23:31,800
Keep rubbing.

488
00:23:44,300 --> 00:23:46,700
Bree, i know you're upset, but you've got to eat.

489
00:23:47,000 --> 00:23:48,800
I'm just so mad at myself.

490
00:23:49,400 --> 00:23:51,000
I should have realized

491
00:23:51,200 --> 00:23:52,790
That the maternal instinct is so strong,

492
00:23:52,800 --> 00:23:55,200
That even Danielle would develop it.

493
00:23:59,100 --> 00:24:00,100
What's so funny?

494
00:24:01,000 --> 00:24:03,100
You know those animals who eat their young?

495
00:24:03,100 --> 00:24:05,700
Even they have more maternal instinct than Danielle .

496
00:24:05,700 --> 00:24:07,500
Then why would she want the child?

497
00:24:07,600 --> 00:24:09,890
You've known her how long, and you still haven't

498
00:24:09,900 --> 00:24:11,790
Figured out how that lentil she calls a brain works?

499
00:24:11,800 --> 00:24:14,690
There's no need to insult your sister. Let him talk.

500
00:24:14,700 --> 00:24:17,500
All right, Danielle cares about three things--

501
00:24:17,900 --> 00:24:21,400
Danielle, fun, and, uh...

502
00:24:22,400 --> 00:24:24,600
Wait. I was wrong. It's just two.

503
00:24:25,600 --> 00:24:27,690
And a retirement village is fun?

504
00:24:27,700 --> 00:24:29,390
Compared to what you're offering her--

505
00:24:29,400 --> 00:24:32,190
A crappy job and community college.

506
00:24:32,200 --> 00:24:33,890
I mean, you think grandma's gonna make her do any of that?

507
00:24:33,900 --> 00:24:35,490
So Danielle 's only doing this

508
00:24:35,500 --> 00:24:37,700
Because Phyllis is offering her a cushy life?

509
00:24:37,700 --> 00:24:40,300
Yeah. If you want that baby,

510
00:24:41,100 --> 00:24:43,100
You're gonna have to outbid grandma.

511
00:24:54,700 --> 00:24:55,900
What are you doing here?

512
00:24:56,300 --> 00:24:57,500
Hi, John .

513
00:24:58,300 --> 00:24:59,400
I wanted to talk to you.

514
00:25:01,100 --> 00:25:03,700
It'll be very friendly. No hitting.

515
00:25:10,200 --> 00:25:11,600
What's up?

516
00:25:11,600 --> 00:25:13,390
This is gonna sound weird, but, uh,

517
00:25:13,400 --> 00:25:17,000
I've been doing some thinking lately, and, well,

518
00:25:18,400 --> 00:25:21,100
I've decided that it's time for me to forgive you.

519
00:25:24,100 --> 00:25:25,300
For s Lee ping with my wife.

520
00:25:28,300 --> 00:25:30,200
Yeah, well, i didn't just s Lee p with Gaby .

521
00:25:31,500 --> 00:25:32,900
I fell in love with her.

522
00:25:36,700 --> 00:25:38,100
I forgive you for that, too.

523
00:25:41,000 --> 00:25:42,300
Why are you doing this?

524
00:25:43,400 --> 00:25:45,200
You in some kind of 12-step program?

525
00:25:48,100 --> 00:25:50,590
Let's just say i've recently learned how loving someone

526
00:25:50,600 --> 00:25:52,800
Makes you forget the difference between right and wrong.

527
00:25:59,100 --> 00:26:01,400
Anyway, that's pretty much it. I should go.

529
00:26:05,500 --> 00:26:06,900
Do you still talk to Gabrielle ?

530
00:26:07,500 --> 00:26:09,400
Occasionally. Why?

531
00:26:10,700 --> 00:26:12,400
I just want to know if she was happy.

532
00:26:14,700 --> 00:26:15,700
I think she is.

533
00:26:19,200 --> 00:26:20,400
Well...

534
00:26:22,100 --> 00:26:23,000
Good for her.

535
00:26:30,900 --> 00:26:32,190
All right, before we vote,

536
00:26:32,200 --> 00:26:34,400
Are there any more questions for the cand Ida tes?

537
00:26:36,200 --> 00:26:37,900
Anybody besides Lee ?

538
00:26:38,000 --> 00:26:39,000
It's not a question.

539
00:26:39,100 --> 00:26:40,190
I just want to remind everyone

540
00:26:40,200 --> 00:26:42,800
That a vote for Katherine is a vote for fascism.

541
00:26:43,900 --> 00:26:47,300
What is it with you gay people and clothes?

542
00:26:48,300 --> 00:26:50,400
Fascism, Ida , not fashion.

543
00:26:51,000 --> 00:26:53,800
Although if you ever do want to talk fashion,

544
00:26:54,300 --> 00:26:55,600
We're here for you.

545
00:26:56,400 --> 00:26:57,690
All right, debate's over.

546
00:26:57,700 --> 00:27:01,000
Let's kick this pig. All in favor of Lynette ?

547
00:27:08,400 --> 00:27:10,900
Okay, and those for Katherine ?

548
00:27:18,500 --> 00:27:20,800
That's 14 for Lynette and 14 for Katherine .

549
00:27:20,800 --> 00:27:22,900
So what do we do? It's a tie.

551
00:27:24,400 --> 00:27:25,590
No, it's not.

552
00:27:25,600 --> 00:27:27,700
Susan voted twice.

553
00:27:31,800 --> 00:27:32,400
Did i?

554
00:27:33,400 --> 00:27:34,900
Well, that's obviously wrong.

555
00:27:36,100 --> 00:27:38,400
You only get one vote, sweet cheeks. Who's it gonna be?

556
00:27:53,300 --> 00:27:55,100
Susan, we're waiting.

557
00:27:56,200 --> 00:27:57,300
It's up to you, hon.

558
00:28:02,200 --> 00:28:03,100
Katherine.

560
00:28:05,500 --> 00:28:08,200
Okay, it's official. Katherine is our new president.

561
00:28:11,700 --> 00:28:13,490
Thank you. Thank you, everyone,

562
00:28:13,500 --> 00:28:16,790
And i promise to do my best for this neighborhood.

563
00:28:16,800 --> 00:28:19,390
And, Bob , Lee , mr. Mustafa,

564
00:28:19,400 --> 00:28:21,390
I'll be in touch regarding your various infractions.

566
00:28:22,800 --> 00:28:24,000
And you, too, Lynette .

567
00:28:27,500 --> 00:28:28,500
Meeting adjourned.

569
00:28:33,500 --> 00:28:36,700
I know. Well, i'm not surprised.

570
00:28:51,000 --> 00:28:52,190
You know, Phyllis ,

571
00:28:52,200 --> 00:28:55,300
We cannot thank you enough for accepting our apology.

572
00:28:55,700 --> 00:28:58,900
Well, i think we should try to stay on good terms

573
00:28:58,900 --> 00:29:01,100
For Danielle 's sake.

574
00:29:01,300 --> 00:29:04,590
I'm glad you suggested that we eat out here.

575
00:29:04,600 --> 00:29:06,900
I never think to do this.

576
00:29:07,100 --> 00:29:09,590
Oh, darn, i forgot the napkins.

577
00:29:09,600 --> 00:29:10,800
Oh, no problem.

578
00:29:10,800 --> 00:29:12,400
I'll go get some.

579
00:29:15,500 --> 00:29:17,590
So now that we have a moment alone,

580
00:29:17,600 --> 00:29:21,200
Your mother and i would like to say how proud we are of you.

581
00:29:21,300 --> 00:29:22,490
Yeah, right.

582
00:29:22,500 --> 00:29:25,990
Seriously, we hadn't realized you'd matured enough

583
00:29:26,000 --> 00:29:29,090
To take on the burden of motherhood all by yourself.

584
00:29:29,100 --> 00:29:30,790
Well, grandma's gonna help.

585
00:29:30,800 --> 00:29:33,390
She'll do what she can, but you mustn't overtax her.

586
00:29:33,400 --> 00:29:35,700
Her heart is not very strong.

587
00:29:36,500 --> 00:29:38,590
She seems fine to me.

588
00:29:38,600 --> 00:29:39,790
Well, knock wood.

589
00:29:39,800 --> 00:29:41,990
We'd hate to see you forced to take care of a baby

590
00:29:42,000 --> 00:29:44,100
And a sick old woman.

591
00:29:44,200 --> 00:29:48,500
Whoa! Mah-jongg. Don't see that much anymore.

593
00:29:54,700 --> 00:29:56,990
Danielle, you should introduce yourself.

594
00:29:57,000 --> 00:29:59,300
These people are your new friends. Mm.

595
00:29:59,300 --> 00:30:01,790
And you're going to learn more From their experience and wisdom

596
00:30:01,800 --> 00:30:04,990
Than you ever could have learned at that college in flor Ida .

597
00:30:05,000 --> 00:30:06,990
Wait. I thought i couldn't go there.

598
00:30:07,000 --> 00:30:08,390
You said it was just a party school.

599
00:30:08,400 --> 00:30:09,790
Well, actually, we checked into the curriculum,

600
00:30:09,800 --> 00:30:11,890
And it's very strong, but no Matt er.

601
00:30:11,900 --> 00:30:13,090
You're be happier here.

602
00:30:13,100 --> 00:30:15,490
Yes, and with a grandmother's unconditional love,

603
00:30:15,500 --> 00:30:19,100
Who needs frat boys who only like you for your convertible?

604
00:30:19,200 --> 00:30:21,290
Whoa. When did i get a convertible?

605
00:30:21,300 --> 00:30:23,790
Well, we were gonna surprise you with one for your birthday,

606
00:30:23,800 --> 00:30:27,190
But since you're keeping the baby, you'll want A more practical gift.

607
00:30:27,200 --> 00:30:29,200
We're thinking a diaper service.

608
00:30:30,000 --> 00:30:33,100
Oh, look, they have water aerobics.

609
00:30:36,900 --> 00:30:38,400
You should sign up.

610
00:30:42,300 --> 00:30:45,700
You know, maybe i should go to college.

611
00:30:46,400 --> 00:30:47,890
I mean, for the baby's sake.

612
00:30:47,900 --> 00:30:49,690
How can i support it without a degree?

613
00:30:49,700 --> 00:30:53,200
But you can't raise this child in a miami dorm room.

638
00:30:54,400 --> 00:30:57,060
You'll need to leave it with someone you can trust

639
00:30:57,100 --> 00:30:58,700
To take care of it properly.

615
00:31:02,300 --> 00:31:03,190
Sorry.

616
00:31:03,200 --> 00:31:06,000
The elevator's out. I...

617
00:31:06,100 --> 00:31:09,200
Oh. I have to catch my breath.

618
00:31:16,300 --> 00:31:17,500
Grandma?

619
00:31:17,800 --> 00:31:19,300
We need to talk.

620
00:31:30,100 --> 00:31:30,890
What's this?

621
00:31:30,900 --> 00:31:33,000
I thought we might toast my Victor y.

622
00:31:34,100 --> 00:31:36,100
I'm kind of in the middle of something here.

624
00:31:38,400 --> 00:31:42,700
So... You haven't congratulated me yet.

625
00:31:43,500 --> 00:31:44,900
I know.

626
00:31:46,700 --> 00:31:48,900
Would you like to tell me what's bothering youou?

627
00:31:48,900 --> 00:31:52,800
I just want you to think about what you've been doing for the past few days.

628
00:31:53,400 --> 00:31:56,390
You've mounted a crusade against a metal thing that shoots out water.

629
00:31:56,400 --> 00:31:58,890
I'm trying to keep the neighborhood beautiful.

630
00:31:58,900 --> 00:32:00,390
I love this street.

631
00:32:00,400 --> 00:32:01,890
Yeah, you keep saying that-- 

632
00:32:01,900 --> 00:32:03,690
how happy you used to be here,

633
00:32:03,700 --> 00:32:05,790
But ever since we've moved back,

634
00:32:05,800 --> 00:32:09,400
All i've seen is an unhappy woman Who needs to control everything.

636
00:32:11,700 --> 00:32:14,500
We've both learned what happens When you lose control.

637
00:32:15,500 --> 00:32:18,400
Oh. Chicago again.

638
00:32:19,100 --> 00:32:20,690
Tell you something else we learned there.

639
00:32:20,700 --> 00:32:24,100
When the chips are down, it helps to have friends.

640
00:32:24,500 --> 00:32:27,400
And you certainly haven't made us any lately.

641
00:32:28,900 --> 00:32:30,600
Congratulations.

642
00:32:39,500 --> 00:32:42,000
- Bye, grandma. - Good-bye, dear.

643
00:32:43,900 --> 00:32:45,800
Tell your stepfather i'll be right out.

644
00:32:51,200 --> 00:32:54,290
Oh, please, Phyllis . Even you have to agree

645
00:32:54,300 --> 00:32:56,590
That a girl who'd trade her baby for a convertible

646
00:32:56,600 --> 00:32:58,190
Isn't ready for motherhood.

647
00:32:58,200 --> 00:33:01,700
She'd have changed once the baby came.

648
00:33:02,200 --> 00:33:04,300
She's her father's daughter.

649
00:33:09,000 --> 00:33:11,290
That's a nice picture of Rex .

650
00:33:11,300 --> 00:33:13,300
Oh, i have a lot of pictures.

651
00:33:14,200 --> 00:33:16,300
All of the women here do.

652
00:33:18,300 --> 00:33:20,290
They're what we have left of the things

653
00:33:20,300 --> 00:33:23,000
Time has taken from us...

654
00:33:25,700 --> 00:33:29,700
Youth, homes and husbands...

655
00:33:30,300 --> 00:33:33,700
And for the unluckiest, children.

656
00:33:35,200 --> 00:33:38,000
I thought i was getting back a part of Rex .

657
00:33:39,100 --> 00:33:40,500
But now...

658
00:33:44,300 --> 00:33:46,190
I know you're lonely, Phyllis ,

659
00:33:46,200 --> 00:33:49,300
But i can't give up this child just to make you feel better.

660
00:33:50,000 --> 00:33:54,100
You should go. Your family's waiting for you.

661
00:34:02,700 --> 00:34:06,290
Orson and i go to our club almost every saturday night,

662
00:34:06,300 --> 00:34:09,500
If you're... Interested in babysitting.

663
00:34:10,700 --> 00:34:12,300
You mean it?

664
00:34:14,600 --> 00:34:17,200
How will you explain me to your friends?

665
00:34:17,500 --> 00:34:20,000
I'll say that you're broke and needed the money.

666
00:34:20,000 --> 00:34:24,400
Can't you just say that you like having me around?

667
00:34:25,200 --> 00:34:28,100
I need something that will fly, Phyllis .

668
00:34:39,000 --> 00:34:40,800
Hey. What's going on?

669
00:34:41,400 --> 00:34:43,200
We need toalk.

670
00:34:45,000 --> 00:34:46,500
So here's the deal.

671
00:34:47,300 --> 00:34:49,600
I think it's time for us to do the right thing.

672
00:34:50,200 --> 00:34:51,690
I don't think i like where this is going.

673
00:34:51,700 --> 00:34:53,500
We have to end this affair.

674
00:34:54,400 --> 00:34:55,290
You serious?

675
00:34:55,300 --> 00:34:56,890
All this... 

676
00:34:56,900 --> 00:34:59,590
Sneaking around, wearing disguises,

677
00:34:59,600 --> 00:35:02,200
Hiding in closets-- it's just wrong.

678
00:35:02,600 --> 00:35:03,790
We're better than this.

679
00:35:03,800 --> 00:35:06,790
So what are you suggesting, we stay with Victor and Edie ?

680
00:35:06,800 --> 00:35:09,100
No, we break up with them.

681
00:35:09,700 --> 00:35:12,490
Look, it'll hurt, but at least it's honest.

682
00:35:12,500 --> 00:35:15,190
And then when enough time has gone by and they've moved on,

683
00:35:15,200 --> 00:35:17,000
We can be together.

684
00:35:17,100 --> 00:35:19,000
How long are we talking about?

685
00:35:19,400 --> 00:35:20,890
I don't know. Six months?

686
00:35:20,900 --> 00:35:24,390
Six months? Nobody takes that long to heal anymore.

687
00:35:24,400 --> 00:35:26,490
It's a breakup, not a face-lift.

688
00:35:26,500 --> 00:35:28,890
Hey, look, i want us to be together, too,

689
00:35:28,900 --> 00:35:31,700
But i also wanna feel good about it.

690
00:35:32,100 --> 00:35:33,500
Don't you?

691
00:35:35,800 --> 00:35:38,300
Yeah. I do.

692
00:35:40,800 --> 00:35:43,100
You're such a good guy, Carlos .

693
00:35:43,300 --> 00:35:45,000
I really hate that about you.

694
00:35:46,200 --> 00:35:47,600
I know.

695
00:35:48,800 --> 00:35:52,900
So... I guess this is it.

696
00:35:55,900 --> 00:35:58,600
This kiss has to last six months.

697
00:35:58,700 --> 00:36:00,600
You better make it good.

698
00:36:17,200 --> 00:36:19,900
His guy can fly. My guy freeze.

699
00:36:24,600 --> 00:36:26,000
Hey, Lynette .

700
00:36:26,100 --> 00:36:28,100
Hey, Judas .

701
00:36:28,500 --> 00:36:29,890
Okay, fine. You're still angry,

702
00:36:29,900 --> 00:36:31,290
But i'm gonna make it up to you.

703
00:36:31,300 --> 00:36:32,790
When they come after that tree house,

704
00:36:32,800 --> 00:36:35,690
They're going to have one Susan Mayer chained to it.

705
00:36:35,700 --> 00:36:39,290
Don't do that. I wanna be sad when they knock it down.

706
00:36:39,300 --> 00:36:40,890
Lynette! What?

707
00:36:40,900 --> 00:36:42,390
You think you can just walk over here

708
00:36:42,400 --> 00:36:44,090
And cute your way out of what you did?

709
00:36:44,100 --> 00:36:45,390
We're supposed to be friends.

710
00:36:45,400 --> 00:36:49,090
Exactly, And friends don't put friends in this kind of position.

711
00:36:49,100 --> 00:36:53,400
I love you, but you can't ask me To put your kids ahead of my husband.

712
00:36:53,900 --> 00:36:56,490
No, Parker , that guy doesn't have freezing...

713
00:36:56,500 --> 00:36:58,900
You're right. I shouldn't have done that.

714
00:37:01,800 --> 00:37:04,690
But that tree house is the one place my kids can go

715
00:37:04,700 --> 00:37:09,290
And not hear about body scans and white blood cell counts.

716
00:37:09,300 --> 00:37:13,290
It is their getaway from this horrible thing

717
00:37:13,300 --> 00:37:15,100
That i've brought into the house.

718
00:37:15,700 --> 00:37:19,490
"brought"? Sweetie, it's not your fault that you're sick.

719
00:37:19,500 --> 00:37:23,800
I know that... Here. But here...

720
00:37:24,600 --> 00:37:27,100
It feels like i've ruined their childhood.

721
00:37:29,200 --> 00:37:30,390
Okay, if anybody needs me,

722
00:37:30,400 --> 00:37:33,100
I'll be at the hardware store buying chains.

723
00:37:33,100 --> 00:37:35,200
Oh, jeez. Get over here.

724
00:37:36,000 --> 00:37:37,600
Hello there!

725
00:37:39,500 --> 00:37:42,600
Oh, look, it's our new queen-- Katherine of arrogant.

726
00:37:43,000 --> 00:37:44,890
Hey, where's the wrecking ball?

727
00:37:44,900 --> 00:37:47,690
Actually, i came to tell you the tree house can stay.

728
00:37:47,700 --> 00:37:49,590
Oh, my god. That's great!

729
00:37:49,600 --> 00:37:50,490
Yes.

730
00:37:50,500 --> 00:37:52,090
If anyone complains, we'll say

731
00:37:52,100 --> 00:37:56,100
It was grandfathered in under the previous administration.

733
00:37:58,200 --> 00:38:01,300
Thanks. Why?

734
00:38:02,000 --> 00:38:03,490
Clearly, it means a lot to you,

735
00:38:03,500 --> 00:38:06,000
And i wanna be a good neighbor.

736
00:38:07,700 --> 00:38:09,100
Katherine.

737
00:38:10,100 --> 00:38:12,590
What's with you? Sometimes you act like an ice queen,

738
00:38:12,600 --> 00:38:15,100
And then you do something really nice.

739
00:38:16,200 --> 00:38:18,600
You are one complicated lady.

740
00:38:19,000 --> 00:38:22,700
Well, i've had one complicated life.

741
00:38:29,000 --> 00:38:31,400
I've had a lot of men in my life,

742
00:38:31,800 --> 00:38:34,700
But i never let myself fall in love before.

743
00:38:35,500 --> 00:38:38,700
I thought it was because i didn't wanna get hurt,But...

744
00:38:39,600 --> 00:38:42,000
Now i know the pain you feel

745
00:38:42,000 --> 00:38:43,600
Isn't the worst part.

746
00:38:45,000 --> 00:38:46,900
It's the hate.

747
00:38:48,900 --> 00:38:51,000
Could you make it out to "cash"?

748
00:39:06,200 --> 00:39:07,700
Hello, Katherine .

749
00:39:07,700 --> 00:39:09,190
You here about the fountain?

750
00:39:09,200 --> 00:39:11,690
Yes, but don't worry. There's no strict deadline.

751
00:39:11,700 --> 00:39:15,800
You can... Have it removed at your earliest convenience.

752
00:39:16,300 --> 00:39:18,800
Yeah, i don't think it's going anywhere.

753
00:39:19,200 --> 00:39:23,000
Oh, boys, boys, the war's over.

754
00:39:24,700 --> 00:39:26,100
Yes, it is.

755
00:39:26,200 --> 00:39:27,900
We know all about chicago.

756
00:39:28,900 --> 00:39:30,300
Come again?

757
00:39:30,300 --> 00:39:33,190
My ex is on the board of chicago memorial hospital.

758
00:39:33,200 --> 00:39:34,790
Seems your husband made quite a stir there--

759
00:39:34,800 --> 00:39:37,100
Whole hospital still buzzing about what he did.

760
00:39:38,100 --> 00:39:41,590
Whatever you heard is a vicious lie--

761
00:39:41,600 --> 00:39:43,300
Every word of it.

762
00:39:45,500 --> 00:39:49,600
Still, it was enough to... Make you leave town,

763
00:39:49,700 --> 00:39:53,700
Which begs the question, do you like living here?

764
00:39:57,500 --> 00:40:00,000
Oh, good. We're in agreement. The fountain stays.

765
00:40:02,500 --> 00:40:04,500
Thanks for stopping by, Katherine .

766
00:40:08,200 --> 00:40:11,400
It's the same for all of us.

767
00:40:14,500 --> 00:40:16,990
We try not to get too close

768
00:40:17,000 --> 00:40:19,600
To the people who live next door.

769
00:40:20,800 --> 00:40:23,590
It's easier to give them a polite nod

770
00:40:23,600 --> 00:40:25,500
Than to ask what's wrong.

771
00:40:27,800 --> 00:40:31,990
It's safer to keep walking by than to get involved.

772
00:40:32,000 --> 00:40:34,490
...you right now. Okay, i don't wanna work...

773
00:40:34,500 --> 00:40:37,790
True, we sometimes do get to know the people

774
00:40:37,800 --> 00:40:39,590
We share a fence with

775
00:40:39,600 --> 00:40:42,490
and end up lifelong friends.

776
00:40:42,500 --> 00:40:44,800
Thanks for everything. Thank you.

777
00:40:44,900 --> 00:40:47,890
But mostly, we keep our distance

778
00:40:47,900 --> 00:40:52,100
Because we'd rather our neighbors Know nothing about us...

779
00:40:58,200 --> 00:40:59,900
Than know too much.
