1
00:00:00,140 --> 00:00:02,510
????

2
00:00:02,510 --> 00:00:06,810
When her first husband died, 
bree thought she was rid of her mother-in-law.

3
00:00:06,810 --> 00:00:08,430
Danielle got pregnant, and bree got creative.

4
00:00:08,870 --> 00:00:10,840
Soon this whole charade will completely unravel, 
and we will be humiliated.

5
00:00:10,840 --> 00:00:14,520
?????

6
00:00:14,520 --> 00:00:17,360
Carlos and gaby's affair turned dangerous...

7
00:00:17,360 --> 00:00:20,190
If she pulled something like that on me, 
that guy wouldn't be around for long.

8
00:00:20,190 --> 00:00:22,420
And an old neighbor returned.

9
00:00:22,420 --> 00:00:25,630
I didn't want poor aunt lily to 
spend her final days in a nursing home.

10
00:00:25,630 --> 00:00:27,910
That is so kind of you.

11
00:00:33,800 --> 00:00:38,810
Mrs.Lillian sims returned to wisteria lane on a saturday.

12
00:00:39,510 --> 00:00:41,660
As she emerged from the ambulance, 

13
00:00:41,660 --> 00:00:46,600
it occurred to her the neighborhood looked exactly as she had left it.

14
00:00:48,700 --> 00:00:52,680
She then decided she should have painted her house blue.

15
00:00:55,110 --> 00:00:59,850
Moments later, she wondered if she would see her husband in heaven.

16
00:01:01,390 --> 00:01:04,120
These are just some of the thoughts that 
go through 

17
00:01:04,120 --> 00:01:08,380
an old woman's mind when she comes home to die.

18
00:01:14,280 --> 00:01:18,110
Now if you need anything, you just ring this little bell, 
and i'll come running.

19
00:01:18,110 --> 00:01:20,390
I'm sorry to be so much trouble.

20
00:01:21,040 --> 00:01:25,540
Well, the good news is, i-i won't be a burden much longer.

21
00:01:25,540 --> 00:01:27,810
Oh, don't say that.

22
00:01:27,810 --> 00:01:33,330
The doctors say there's a good chance 
that you'll be with us for a very long time.

23
00:01:33,330 --> 00:01:36,400
I know what's happening to me, katherine.

24
00:01:37,130 --> 00:01:38,900
You don't need to lie.

25
00:01:42,140 --> 00:01:43,370
Aunt lily...

26
00:01:44,260 --> 00:01:45,970
What does it feel like?

27
00:01:46,330 --> 00:01:48,920
Dying, i mean.

28
00:01:49,490 --> 00:01:51,900
It's not that bad.

29
00:01:52,440 --> 00:01:54,360
I feel lucky.

30
00:01:54,360 --> 00:02:01,560
When you know time is running out, 
you--you get a chance to reflect on your life.

31
00:02:02,960 --> 00:02:06,450
I-i really did try to live a good one.

32
00:02:06,450 --> 00:02:08,280
You did more than try.

33
00:02:08,580 --> 00:02:11,170
God is going to welcome you with open arms.

34
00:02:11,170 --> 00:02:12,750
I'm not so sure.

35
00:02:12,950 --> 00:02:14,780
Oh, why would you say that?

36
00:02:16,480 --> 00:02:19,490
I keep thinking about dylan...

37
00:02:20,000 --> 00:02:23,180
What we did, what we covered up.

38
00:02:25,550 --> 00:02:27,100
We did what we had to.

39
00:02:27,670 --> 00:02:29,920
We should have told someone.

40
00:02:29,920 --> 00:02:31,890
We couldn't.
You know that.

41
00:02:31,890 --> 00:02:36,530
It--it was a mistake, and it's not too late to rectify it.

42
00:02:37,310 --> 00:02:43,300
Your life may be over, but that does not give you 
the right to go around destroying the lives of others.

43
00:02:43,300 --> 00:02:46,960
I can't go to my grave with this on my conscience.
Please!

44
00:02:46,960 --> 00:02:50,310
We have to tell that girl what happened in this room.

45
00:02:51,250 --> 00:02:53,440
Absolutely not.

46
00:03:00,580 --> 00:03:04,100
As her guilt over the past began to mount, 

47
00:03:04,100 --> 00:03:09,110
it occurred to lillian death couldn't come quickly enough.

48
00:03:09,720 --> 00:03:13,730
This thought occurred to her niece as well.

49
00:03:14,610 --> 00:03:16,520
<font color="#4096d1">-==http://subland.5286.cn==-</font>

50
00:03:17,520 --> 00:03:19,280
<font color="#4096d1">sync:虾米 </font>

51
00:03:20,550 --> 00:03:23,460
<font color="#4096d1">Desperate.Housewives.S04E04</font>

52
00:03:26,010 --> 00:03:30,990
There were a lot of things bob hunter disliked about living in the city, 

53
00:03:31,330 --> 00:03:35,770
and the thing he hated most were the pests-- 

54
00:03:36,860 --> 00:03:39,280
the rats that lurked in the alleys...

55
00:03:40,800 --> 00:03:43,480
The flies that swarmed the garbage...

56
00:03:44,810 --> 00:03:47,620
The bugs that invaded his co-op.

57
00:03:49,610 --> 00:03:50,470
I have tried it your way...

58
00:03:50,470 --> 00:03:55,340
Finally, bob informed his significant other it was time...

59
00:03:56,150 --> 00:03:57,870
To leave the city.

60
00:03:59,020 --> 00:04:05,780
So they moved to suburbia, which they quickly discovered had a few pests...

61
00:04:05,780 --> 00:04:06,980
Hey, neighbor!

62
00:04:06,980 --> 00:04:08,190
Of its own.

63
00:04:08,190 --> 00:04:09,480
Oh, we haven't gotten a chance to meet.

64
00:04:10,360 --> 00:04:11,920
I'm susan.
I live next door.

65
00:04:12,530 --> 00:04:14,530
Hi, i'm lee.

66
00:04:14,530 --> 00:04:16,350
Uh, i-i just wanted to say hi.

67
00:04:16,350 --> 00:04:18,580
You know, i saw the movers taking in some of your furniture, 

68
00:04:18,580 --> 00:04:21,550
and i just have to say you and your wife have gorgeous taste.

69
00:04:22,440 --> 00:04:23,290
Need some help?

70
00:04:23,290 --> 00:04:24,860
Yeah, like you wouldn't believe.

71
00:04:24,860 --> 00:04:26,840
Um, i'm susan.
I live next door.

72
00:04:26,880 --> 00:04:28,850
Oh, hi.
I'm lee's partner bob.

73
00:04:28,850 --> 00:04:30,580
Oh, you're partners.

74
00:04:30,960 --> 00:04:32,280
What kind of business?

75
00:04:32,280 --> 00:04:36,060
You know, whatever it is, just don't let the neighborhood
association hear that you work out of your house.

76
00:04:36,060 --> 00:04:37,380
They're so not cool.

77
00:04:37,380 --> 00:04:39,770
Actually, we're life partners.

78
00:04:41,170 --> 00:04:46,400
Oh, that's super!

79
00:04:46,400 --> 00:04:49,310
Yeah, i've seen a lot of cable, so i get it.

80
00:04:49,780 --> 00:04:51,320
You're just great.

81
00:04:53,190 --> 00:04:54,200
Thank you.

82
00:04:54,200 --> 00:04:56,830
I-i hope we can live up to your stereotype.

83
00:04:57,690 --> 00:04:58,870
Don't mind him.

84
00:04:58,870 --> 00:05:01,890
He's just a little cranky from, uh, all the fresh air.

85
00:05:01,890 --> 00:05:03,430
Do not apologize for me.

86
00:05:03,430 --> 00:05:06,250
Lee, you're the one who said moving 
here would be better for raphael.

87
00:05:06,550 --> 00:05:07,790
So there's, uh...

88
00:05:08,290 --> 00:05:09,520
There's three of you.

89
00:05:10,260 --> 00:05:12,750
Well, that must be...

90
00:05:13,240 --> 00:05:14,080
Cozy.

91
00:05:15,880 --> 00:05:18,110
Yes.
We're gay mormons.

92
00:05:18,910 --> 00:05:19,930
Susan, uh...

93
00:05:21,160 --> 00:05:23,050
That's raphael.

94
00:05:26,970 --> 00:05:29,060
Raphael is your dog, of course.

95
00:05:29,060 --> 00:05:31,070
You know, 'cause you folks can't have kids.

96
00:05:32,550 --> 00:05:36,100
I mean, uh, i mean, of course you can have kids, 

97
00:05:36,100 --> 00:05:39,850
um, you--you know, because times have changed, 
and now you're allowed.

98
00:05:44,120 --> 00:05:46,940
What a...
Nice dog.

99
00:05:49,110 --> 00:05:50,500
I should go.

100
00:05:51,250 --> 00:05:52,750
Nice to meet you.

101
00:05:53,320 --> 00:05:55,490
- Hey, stop by any time, susan-
- ow!

102
00:05:55,490 --> 00:05:57,650
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing?

103
00:06:05,760 --> 00:06:06,350
Well...
Yes?

104
00:06:06,350 --> 00:06:09,530
I have a delivery for danielle van de kamp.

105
00:06:11,290 --> 00:06:13,910
Can i get you to sign here, please?

106
00:06:17,300 --> 00:06:18,830
Is that for us?

107
00:06:18,830 --> 00:06:20,750
No, it's for danielle.

108
00:06:21,250 --> 00:06:23,430
There you are.
Who would send her a scooter?

109
00:06:23,430 --> 00:06:25,660
I knew it!
Phyllis--rex's mother.

110
00:06:25,660 --> 00:06:29,030
Ever since he died, she's been trying to buy the children's affection.

111
00:06:29,030 --> 00:06:31,840
Wow.Well, it's a honey of a bike.

112
00:06:31,840 --> 00:06:33,600
I'm sure danielle will appreciate the thought.

113
00:06:33,600 --> 00:06:35,930
- Well,
-  i'm not giving it to her.

114
00:06:35,930 --> 00:06:39,100
Can you think of a worse present for a pregnant girl?

115
00:06:39,100 --> 00:06:41,130
Well, i'm not knocked up.
Let me have it.

116
00:06:41,130 --> 00:06:44,000
You know how i feel about 2-wheeled motorized vehicles.

117
00:06:44,000 --> 00:06:45,590
They're too dangerous.

118
00:06:46,440 --> 00:06:48,190
We'll donate it to the church.

119
00:06:49,120 --> 00:06:50,010
What?

120
00:06:50,010 --> 00:06:52,430
Reverend sikes said they're looking for items for the raffle.

121
00:06:52,430 --> 00:06:53,780
So we're just gonna give it away?

122
00:06:53,780 --> 00:06:56,310
Well, it's better than you breaking your neck on it.

123
00:06:56,310 --> 00:06:59,020
Mom, you know how much i want a scooter
Come on..

124
00:06:59,020 --> 00:07:02,160
You heard your mother.
We're donating it to the church.

125
00:07:02,160 --> 00:07:06,130
Of course, we need to make sure 
it's in good working order before we do that.

126
00:07:06,130 --> 00:07:07,970
Not without a helmet.

127
00:07:15,120 --> 00:07:16,270
This blows.

128
00:07:16,700 --> 00:07:18,980
- Are we gonna let her do this to us?
- Absolutely not.

129
00:07:18,980 --> 00:07:21,540
If we win that raffle, we're keeping it.

130
00:07:27,970 --> 00:07:28,920
Hey.

131
00:07:29,230 --> 00:07:31,790
It is nice to hear you humming again.

132
00:07:32,100 --> 00:07:34,950
Well, it's amazing what a week without chemo can do.

133
00:07:35,760 --> 00:07:37,220
When does the last round start?

134
00:07:37,220 --> 00:07:42,050
Next month, so i have some time 
before i start feeling like total crap again.

135
00:07:42,050 --> 00:07:46,040
And i was hoping we could put that time to good use.

136
00:07:46,040 --> 00:07:47,580
Are you sure?

137
00:07:47,840 --> 00:07:51,500
I mean, the doctor said it could 
be months before you get your mojo back.

138
00:07:51,500 --> 00:07:53,830
Well, it's back.

139
00:07:54,710 --> 00:07:56,990
And since when do you question the mojo?

140
00:07:56,990 --> 00:07:59,580
You're right.
You're right.Forgive me.

141
00:07:59,580 --> 00:08:02,940
Okay, so here are your options.

142
00:08:02,940 --> 00:08:08,120
"a," we could go romantic, play soft music, 
light some candles

143
00:08:08,120 --> 00:08:11,710
, or "b," go straight to the--whoa!

144
00:08:14,210 --> 00:08:16,210
- God, 
- it's so been so long.

145
00:08:16,210 --> 00:08:17,650
I hope i remember how to do this.

146
00:08:17,650 --> 00:08:19,600
Well, it's just like riding a bike.
You never forget.

147
00:08:19,600 --> 00:08:21,730
Now start pedaling.

148
00:08:35,610 --> 00:08:36,550
What are you doing?

149
00:08:36,550 --> 00:08:37,970
Ooh, sorry.
I just messed up your hair.

150
00:08:37,970 --> 00:08:39,170
I'm just trying to fix it.

151
00:08:39,880 --> 00:08:41,140
Sorry.
Al-almost got it.

152
00:08:46,840 --> 00:08:48,000
Screw it.

153
00:08:48,000 --> 00:08:49,210
What--what are you doing?

154
00:08:49,210 --> 00:08:51,400
Oh, i ripped it this morning.

155
00:08:51,400 --> 00:08:53,230
It's been itching the hell out of me...

156
00:08:53,230 --> 00:08:55,480
And this is much better.

157
00:08:55,480 --> 00:08:57,440
Are you sure you wanna take that off, honey?

158
00:08:57,840 --> 00:08:58,760
I mean, won't you be cold?

159
00:08:58,760 --> 00:09:00,430
No, i'm good.

160
00:09:13,320 --> 00:09:15,470
Hey, babe, what's going on?
You still with me?

161
00:09:16,740 --> 00:09:19,050
It's just-- it's kinda...

162
00:09:19,860 --> 00:09:20,720
What?

163
00:09:21,900 --> 00:09:23,020
Late.

164
00:09:27,390 --> 00:09:28,860
It's 9:30.

165
00:09:28,860 --> 00:09:30,770
It's just that one of our ovens broke down today, 

166
00:09:30,770 --> 00:09:32,990
and the repairman's coming first thing in the morning, 

167
00:09:32,990 --> 00:09:34,900
and maybe i could ravish you...

168
00:09:36,040 --> 00:09:37,460
Tomorrow.

169
00:09:40,330 --> 00:09:41,980
Oh, okay.

170
00:09:47,420 --> 00:09:49,590
Come on, bree.
You have to let us do this.

171
00:09:49,590 --> 00:09:53,760
Uh, it's a lovely thought, 
but i really don't want a baby shower.

172
00:09:53,760 --> 00:09:55,150
Well, i bought you an expensive gift, 

173
00:09:55,150 --> 00:09:56,650
and i'm not giving it to you unless 

174
00:09:56,650 --> 00:09:59,220
there's a party with people who can see how generous i am.

175
00:09:59,450 --> 00:10:01,460
Bree, watch this!

176
00:10:03,330 --> 00:10:05,890
Orson, i said be careful!

177
00:10:08,900 --> 00:10:12,710
I just think it's tacky to have a baby 
shower when it's not your first baby.

178
00:10:12,710 --> 00:10:15,620
Well, i don't see the problem with it...

179
00:10:15,620 --> 00:10:18,310
Yeah, and showers aren't just about presents.
They're fun.

180
00:10:18,310 --> 00:10:21,650
And we can play games, like "how big is mummy's tummy?

181
00:10:22,180 --> 00:10:23,170
" excuse me?

182
00:10:23,170 --> 00:10:24,420
Yeah, we get a ball of yarn, 

183
00:10:24,420 --> 00:10:28,380
and we each cut a piece that we think is just big enough 
to fit around your stomach, 

184
00:10:28,380 --> 00:10:30,690
and the one closest wins a prize.

185
00:10:32,350 --> 00:10:34,520
I really don't want a shower.

186
00:10:34,770 --> 00:10:36,840
Look!
Look at me!

187
00:10:37,950 --> 00:10:41,150
Orson, just five more minutes!
That's all you're getting!

188
00:10:42,160 --> 00:10:42,860
I tell you what.

189
00:10:42,860 --> 00:10:47,030
Why don't we just skip the shower, and after the baby's born, 
i'll have a christening party?

190
00:10:47,030 --> 00:10:48,130
What do you say?

191
00:10:52,830 --> 00:10:56,130
I'm okay!
I'm fine.

192
00:10:56,210 --> 00:10:57,920
Oh, dear god.

193
00:11:02,300 --> 00:11:03,530
Excuse me, ladies.

194
00:11:03,530 --> 00:11:07,680
I-i couldn't help overhearing you--
you talking about my mom's shower.

195
00:11:08,060 --> 00:11:10,430
I-i think i could be of a little assistance here.

196
00:11:19,580 --> 00:11:22,430
Why do you have to take our new neighbors cookie bars?

197
00:11:22,430 --> 00:11:24,600
Oh, look, i made a terrible first impression, 

198
00:11:24,600 --> 00:11:27,330
so i thought i'd make them some of my home-baked goodness.

199
00:11:27,330 --> 00:11:29,310
But you didn't bake any goodness.

200
00:11:29,310 --> 00:11:31,370
You just warmed up the goodness i bought at the store.

201
00:11:31,370 --> 00:11:33,590
Well, yeah.
I don't bake.Catch up.

202
00:11:34,520 --> 00:11:36,850
You know, not all neighbors have to be friends.

203
00:11:36,850 --> 00:11:38,190
Why don't you just let it go?

204
00:11:38,910 --> 00:11:41,200
Mike, they live 15 feet from us.

205
00:11:41,200 --> 00:11:43,560
If we have a fire, i wanna be sure 
that they like us enough to call 9-1-1.

206
00:11:43,560 --> 00:11:45,160
Ah, that's the real reason.

207
00:11:45,160 --> 00:11:47,130
You can't stand it when somebody doesn't like you.

208
00:11:48,360 --> 00:11:49,700
Well, maybe.

209
00:11:49,700 --> 00:11:52,490
Well, maybe bob and lee just like to keep to themselves.

210
00:11:52,490 --> 00:11:54,310
That's fine, and once they like me, 

211
00:11:54,310 --> 00:11:57,320
they can keep to themselves all they damn well please.

212
00:12:06,200 --> 00:12:08,690
I wanted to bring you a "welcome to the neighborhood" present.

213
00:12:08,690 --> 00:12:10,890
You should try one while they're still warm from the oven.

214
00:12:10,890 --> 00:12:12,540
That was really nice.
Thank you.

215
00:12:13,400 --> 00:12:14,740
Oh, are there nuts in them?

216
00:12:14,740 --> 00:12:15,650
Nuts?

217
00:12:16,940 --> 00:12:18,380
Gee, let me think.

218
00:12:19,590 --> 00:12:20,580
Nope, no nuts.

219
00:12:20,580 --> 00:12:23,430
Are you sure?'Cause i'm highly allergic.
Half a pecan could kill me.

220
00:12:31,740 --> 00:12:32,990
I'm not seeing any nuts.

221
00:12:32,990 --> 00:12:37,410
Okay, you made them, so did you or did you not put nuts in them?

222
00:12:40,320 --> 00:12:43,000
Okay, here's the thing.
I'm a really crappy baker.

223
00:12:43,000 --> 00:12:46,170
To give you something that i made myself would be like an insult, 

224
00:12:46,170 --> 00:12:47,860
so-- so--so--so you bought them, 

225
00:12:47,860 --> 00:12:49,250
and--and then you heated them up in attempt to 

226
00:12:49,250 --> 00:12:52,780
make your gesture seem more thoughtful than, in fact, it was.

227
00:12:52,780 --> 00:12:55,300
Hey, i would've made them myself if i knew how.

228
00:12:55,300 --> 00:12:56,850
Honestly, i'm a good neighbor.

229
00:12:56,850 --> 00:13:02,410
Yeah, well, neighbor, why don't you take your store-bought, warmed-up, possibly poisonous cookie bars???

230
00:13:02,410 --> 00:13:05,720
 and give them to someone more likely to survive your generosity?

231
00:13:07,800 --> 00:13:08,850
Do you like wine?

232
00:13:08,850 --> 00:13:12,010
No, no, so please don't bring me a bottle from your vineyard.

233
00:13:17,740 --> 00:13:19,600
This rip is pretty big.

234
00:13:20,040 --> 00:13:21,480
It'll take about a week.

235
00:13:21,480 --> 00:13:22,900
A week?

236
00:13:23,580 --> 00:13:24,960
All right.

237
00:13:24,960 --> 00:13:26,620
You'll hurry if you can?

238
00:13:28,890 --> 00:13:30,970
Honey, it's okay.
You look cute in a scarf.

239
00:13:30,970 --> 00:13:34,810
I'm upset 'cause that salesgirl just walked away with my sex life.

240
00:13:34,810 --> 00:13:35,330
What?

241
00:13:35,330 --> 00:13:37,820
After two months of puking my guts out, last night 

242
00:13:37,820 --> 00:13:40,400
i was finally in the mood, but tom--not so much.

243
00:13:40,400 --> 00:13:43,380
Apparently, my bald head is a big turnoff for him.

244
00:13:43,380 --> 00:13:44,710
Why'd you take your wig off?

245
00:13:44,710 --> 00:13:45,890
It was itchy.

246
00:13:45,890 --> 00:13:48,260
Okay, not smart.

247
00:13:48,260 --> 00:13:50,370
Gaby, i am his wife.

248
00:13:50,370 --> 00:13:53,510
He's supposed to love me-- not my body, me...

249
00:13:53,510 --> 00:13:54,730
My--my soul.

250
00:13:54,730 --> 00:13:56,770
Why can't he make love to my soul?

251
00:13:56,770 --> 00:13:58,050
Interesting.

252
00:13:58,470 --> 00:14:01,830
Question--when was the last time you were in the bar

253
00:14:01,830 --> 00:14:04,070
and heard a guy turn to his friend and say, 

254
00:14:04,070 --> 00:14:06,160
"hey, check out the soul on that girl"?

255
00:14:06,160 --> 00:14:07,190
What are you saying?

256
00:14:07,190 --> 00:14:09,980
I'm saying men are visual.

257
00:14:09,980 --> 00:14:12,420
Hell, i have a whole closet full of costumes.

258
00:14:12,780 --> 00:14:19,070
You need to give tom something to look at, 
something spicy, like...

259
00:14:19,070 --> 00:14:20,490
Gaby, i'm not a redhead.

260
00:14:20,490 --> 00:14:25,900
But you could be, which brings me to my second point-- men like variety.

261
00:14:25,900 --> 00:14:27,750
Tonight you're a redhead.

262
00:14:27,750 --> 00:14:32,120
Tomorrow...You are...
Helga, the sexy milkmaid.

263
00:14:32,120 --> 00:14:36,160
Or...Amber, the lonely runaway.

264
00:14:36,160 --> 00:14:42,010
Or...
Jeff, the friendly guy from work.

265
00:14:43,110 --> 00:14:45,230
What?
I don't know what tom is into.

266
00:14:49,030 --> 00:14:52,110
Claude, you know i don't like it when you "hmm.

267
00:14:53,110 --> 00:14:54,140
" edie...

268
00:14:55,020 --> 00:14:56,740
How long have you had this?

269
00:14:57,390 --> 00:14:59,840
Had what?
I don't have anything.

270
00:14:59,840 --> 00:15:02,520
I'm just here for my 5,000-mile checkup.

271
00:15:03,230 --> 00:15:07,490
Well, you know that bullet you've managed to dodge all these years?

272
00:15:09,330 --> 00:15:10,330
Which one?

273
00:15:10,330 --> 00:15:13,990
The clap?The herp?
The syph?

274
00:15:13,990 --> 00:15:15,170
Crabs?

275
00:15:15,220 --> 00:15:19,000
Relax.I'll boil all the sheets and towels, 

276
00:15:21,820 --> 00:15:25,880
and in three days, the crotch carnival packs up and leaves town.

277
00:15:25,880 --> 00:15:26,710
Oh, man.

278
00:15:27,280 --> 00:15:28,530
How did this happen?

279
00:15:28,530 --> 00:15:29,960
Don't give me that look.

280
00:15:29,960 --> 00:15:32,050
I know exactly how i got 'em.

281
00:15:32,290 --> 00:15:36,450
I used the tanning bed right after mimsy porter, that skank.

282
00:15:37,010 --> 00:15:39,510
Ew, it smells like burnt licorice.

283
00:15:39,510 --> 00:15:43,130
Well, come in the bathroom, 
and i'll show you how to use this.

284
00:15:44,180 --> 00:15:45,890
I think i can figure that out.

285
00:15:45,890 --> 00:15:48,420
You know, the good news is we're in a committed relationship.

286
00:15:48,420 --> 00:15:52,670
Otherwise, we'd have to make that 
call of shame to everyone we've been with.

287
00:15:56,460 --> 00:15:59,850
You've heard me make before, 
but something i feel very, very strongly about.

288
00:15:59,850 --> 00:16:02,370
For me, it's a very simple formula.

289
00:16:02,370 --> 00:16:05,270
More development leads to an increased tax base, 

290
00:16:05,270 --> 00:16:07,940
which helps build schools for our children.

291
00:16:08,560 --> 00:16:10,420
Around the country, the needs of children are being...

292
00:16:10,420 --> 00:16:11,690
What are you doing here?

293
00:16:11,690 --> 00:16:13,050
I need to talk to you.

294
00:16:13,050 --> 00:16:14,700
Can't you just call me?

295
00:16:15,460 --> 00:16:18,790
This is not something that you wanna hear on the phone.

296
00:16:19,420 --> 00:16:20,740
And not follow this trend.

297
00:16:21,560 --> 00:16:24,830
And we will put education where it belongs-- at the top of the list.

298
00:16:25,570 --> 00:16:26,850
How did you get those?

299
00:16:27,630 --> 00:16:29,490
How do you think?
Edie.

300
00:16:31,730 --> 00:16:33,770
You are still sleeping with edie?

301
00:16:34,590 --> 00:16:36,830
Well, you're still sleeping with victor, aren't you?

302
00:16:36,830 --> 00:16:38,950
Yeah, if i didn't, he would think something is going on.

303
00:16:38,950 --> 00:16:40,840
What is your excuse for doing it with edie?

304
00:16:40,840 --> 00:16:42,640
She wants to, and i'm a guy.

305
00:16:43,560 --> 00:16:45,480
This is serious, okay?

306
00:16:46,360 --> 00:16:50,280
If victor wakes up with a zoo in his pants, 
there's gonna be hell to pay.

307
00:16:50,280 --> 00:16:51,480
You don't have to tell me.

308
00:16:51,480 --> 00:16:54,410
If he finds out about us, 
i'm the one that's gonna wind up in a landfill.

309
00:16:54,410 --> 00:16:56,140
Okay, just don't panic, okay?

310
00:16:56,140 --> 00:16:57,970
We're gonna get the salve or the ointment or whatever 

311
00:16:57,970 --> 00:17:01,430
it is you put down there, and we're gonna be fine.

312
00:17:08,910 --> 00:17:09,850
We'r're screwed.

313
00:17:12,520 --> 00:17:13,920
Tom?

314
00:17:13,920 --> 00:17:15,510
The kids are asleep.

315
00:17:15,510 --> 00:17:17,630
Are you coming to bed anytime soon?

316
00:17:17,630 --> 00:17:22,530
Yeah, i just gotta pick a new running back for my fantasy football team.

317
00:17:25,830 --> 00:17:27,430
That's too bad.

318
00:17:27,870 --> 00:17:31,210
I had a little fantasy thing planned of my own.

319
00:17:33,440 --> 00:17:35,190
Lynette...

320
00:17:35,190 --> 00:17:36,670
Lynette's not here right now.

321
00:17:36,670 --> 00:17:40,150
I'm brandy, the slutty cheerleader.

322
00:17:52,780 --> 00:17:54,210
This is all very romantic, gaby, 

323
00:17:54,210 --> 00:17:57,840
but i still have four building proposals to read before tomorrow.

324
00:17:59,360 --> 00:18:01,620
That's nurse gaby to you.

325
00:18:03,490 --> 00:18:05,080
Nurse gaby?

326
00:18:07,810 --> 00:18:08,890
Am i sick?

327
00:18:08,890 --> 00:18:15,810
Well, the doctor says you need to relax, 
and i know just how to relax you.

328
00:18:26,250 --> 00:18:27,790
It smells like licorice.

329
00:18:27,790 --> 00:18:31,390
It's a blend of 36 essential oils, 
anise root and fennel.

330
00:18:32,290 --> 00:18:33,430
Do you like it?

331
00:18:34,830 --> 00:18:36,100
It smells a little medicine-y.

332
00:18:36,670 --> 00:18:37,850
That's the fennel.

333
00:18:50,590 --> 00:18:52,100
It's stinging a little.

334
00:18:53,510 --> 00:18:57,260
That's the tension...
Leaving your body.

335
00:18:58,990 --> 00:19:00,250
It's really stinging.

336
00:19:00,250 --> 00:19:02,410
And we can rinse it off...

337
00:19:02,410 --> 00:19:04,070
In three to five minutes.

338
00:19:04,800 --> 00:19:07,780
But before we do that...

339
00:19:08,380 --> 00:19:09,860
What the hell is that?

340
00:19:11,120 --> 00:19:14,520
You know, for a guy getting rubbed down by a hot nurse, 
you ask a lot of questions.

341
00:19:14,520 --> 00:19:15,510
Sorry.

342
00:19:22,860 --> 00:19:24,280
Oh, come on, uncle frank.

343
00:19:24,280 --> 00:19:25,540
What's the point of having a gay uncle 

344
00:19:25,540 --> 00:19:27,980
if you're not gonna help me make friends with these guys?

345
00:19:29,360 --> 00:19:33,570
Uh, mom said that the whole family knew.

346
00:19:36,350 --> 00:19:38,270
Um, okay.Gotta go.
Love you.

347
00:19:39,650 --> 00:19:40,470
What's going on?

348
00:19:40,480 --> 00:19:42,500
Oh, i found raphael
wandering in the street.

349
00:19:42,500 --> 00:19:44,100
I went to take him back,
but bob and lee aren't home,

350
00:19:44,100 --> 00:19:46,900
so i'm just gonna give him a little treat
and put him back in their yard.

351
00:19:46,900 --> 00:19:47,900
Bup, bup, bup!

352
00:19:47,900 --> 00:19:49,000
-Wait a second.
- What?

353
00:19:49,000 --> 00:19:49,900
Leave him with me.

354
00:19:49,900 --> 00:19:51,600
I need to score some points
with those guys,

355
00:19:51,600 --> 00:19:54,000
and being a dog-rescuing hero
could be just the ticket.

356
00:19:54,000 --> 00:19:56,300
So what, you're just gonna
keep him here until they come back?

357
00:19:56,300 --> 00:19:57,100
Uh-huh.

358
00:19:57,900 --> 00:19:59,200
Maybe a little longer.

359
00:19:59,900 --> 00:20:01,300
How long?

360
00:20:01,300 --> 00:20:02,700
Well, long enough for them to worry.

361
00:20:02,700 --> 00:20:05,200
You know, the more they worry,
the more i'm a hero.

362
00:20:05,200 --> 00:20:05,800
Get it?

363
00:20:05,800 --> 00:20:07,200
I get that you're insane.

364
00:20:07,200 --> 00:20:08,400
I'm not, i'm not.

365
00:20:08,400 --> 00:20:09,300
Now get some mud.

366
00:20:09,300 --> 00:20:12,300
I wanna dirty him up so he looks like
he's been through hell.

367
00:20:14,200 --> 00:20:15,600
Okay, in you go.

368
00:20:20,000 --> 00:20:21,000
Here, let me help you with those.

369
00:20:21,000 --> 00:20:21,600
Oh, that's all right.

370
00:20:21,600 --> 00:20:23,700
I've got them, mr.Knievel.

371
00:20:24,300 --> 00:20:25,400
Oh, boy.

372
00:20:25,400 --> 00:20:27,100
You're never gonna let me
live this down, are you?

373
00:20:27,100 --> 00:20:28,400
Nope.

374
00:20:29,100 --> 00:20:29,900
I thought the same thing.

375
00:20:29,900 --> 00:20:31,900
It seems to me that
you should go to the doctor again.

376
00:20:31,900 --> 00:20:32,800
Surprise!

377
00:20:36,900 --> 00:20:38,100
Uh, guys...

378
00:20:38,100 --> 00:20:39,500
What did i tell you?

379
00:20:39,500 --> 00:20:40,600
You said no shower.

380
00:20:40,600 --> 00:20:42,100
but look around--men.

381
00:20:42,100 --> 00:20:44,900
So technically, it's a party,
not a shower.

382
00:20:44,900 --> 00:20:46,900
Andrew told us that
you only said no...

383
00:20:46,900 --> 00:20:48,400
'Cause you didn't want to impose.

384
00:20:50,400 --> 00:20:51,500
Oh!

385
00:20:52,000 --> 00:20:53,400
So you're responsible?

386
00:20:53,400 --> 00:20:56,100
Yeah, well, i-i know you said
not to make a big fuss,

387
00:20:56,100 --> 00:20:58,900
but, hey, you earned it.

388
00:20:59,500 --> 00:21:00,500
Well, don't just stand there.

389
00:21:00,500 --> 00:21:01,500
Come in.

390
00:21:01,500 --> 00:21:05,600
We have lots of food
and fun and surprises.

391
00:21:06,500 --> 00:21:08,900
Yeah, all kinds of surprises.

392
00:21:08,900 --> 00:21:10,500
Where is she?

393
00:21:12,200 --> 00:21:13,400
Bree!

394
00:21:14,100 --> 00:21:15,400
Phyllis!

395
00:21:15,400 --> 00:21:17,900
I, uh, helped with the invitations, too.

396
00:21:17,900 --> 00:21:22,200
I can't tell you how touched
i was to be included,

397
00:21:22,200 --> 00:21:27,700
especially after my many conciliatory
gestures were so coldly rebuffed.

398
00:21:27,700 --> 00:21:29,300
I have been awful.

399
00:21:29,300 --> 00:21:32,700
I wouldn't blame you
if you stormed out right now.

400
00:21:32,700 --> 00:21:34,100
Nonsense.

401
00:21:34,600 --> 00:21:38,200
I'm here to celebrate
our renewed friendship...

402
00:21:38,200 --> 00:21:39,600
And your baby.

403
00:21:40,300 --> 00:21:42,500
Or should i say babies?

404
00:21:42,500 --> 00:21:44,300
You know,it's often a sign of twins

405
00:21:44,300 --> 00:21:47,800
when a mother's face
gets all plump like yours.

406
00:21:49,500 --> 00:21:50,700
Oh, um...

407
00:21:50,700 --> 00:21:54,800
I, uh, bet you wouldn't mind
if i broke my neck on that scooter now.

408
00:22:02,200 --> 00:22:03,400
I'm off to the bank.

409
00:22:03,400 --> 00:22:06,300
Aunt lily just took a pill,
so she's down for the afternoon.

410
00:22:06,300 --> 00:22:08,300
Okay.
Have fun.

411
00:22:22,400 --> 00:22:24,000
Is your mother gone?

412
00:22:24,000 --> 00:22:25,500
Yeah.
Do you need her?

413
00:22:25,500 --> 00:22:27,000
No, no.

414
00:22:28,900 --> 00:22:30,500
This is what i wanted.

415
00:22:32,000 --> 00:22:33,500
I thought you took
a sleeping pill.

416
00:22:33,500 --> 00:22:37,000
I pretended to
so she'd leave us alone.

417
00:22:38,700 --> 00:22:40,300
Aunt lily, what's going on?

418
00:22:40,900 --> 00:22:42,700
I have to tell you something.

419
00:22:44,500 --> 00:22:48,800
First, you should know
that what happened...

420
00:22:50,000 --> 00:22:52,000
It was nobody's fault.

421
00:22:53,000 --> 00:22:54,600
What do you mean, "what happened"?

422
00:22:54,600 --> 00:22:59,200
You don't remember
living on this street before, do you?

423
00:22:59,200 --> 00:23:00,100
No.

424
00:23:00,100 --> 00:23:01,100
Well...

425
00:23:01,500 --> 00:23:04,000
There's a reason for that.

426
00:23:05,000 --> 00:23:06,100
Dylan?

427
00:23:11,900 --> 00:23:13,200
Mom, i thought you left.

428
00:23:13,400 --> 00:23:14,800
I forgot my checkbook.

429
00:23:15,100 --> 00:23:16,700
Could you go down
and find it for me?

430
00:23:17,400 --> 00:23:18,000
Sure.

431
00:23:32,200 --> 00:23:34,600
You really should get your rest.

432
00:23:42,700 --> 00:23:44,800
- Hey.
- Hi.

433
00:23:44,800 --> 00:23:46,500
- Got your wig back, huh?
- Yeah.

434
00:23:46,500 --> 00:23:47,500
Good as new.

435
00:23:47,500 --> 00:23:51,200
Listen, i thought we could
put the kids to bed early tonight,

436
00:23:51,200 --> 00:23:52,500
if you know what i mean.

437
00:23:52,500 --> 00:23:55,100
I do, and i'm up for that.

438
00:23:55,800 --> 00:23:57,300
Fantastic.

439
00:23:58,680 --> 00:24:02,000
I hope brandy won't get stuck late
at cheerleading practice.

440
00:24:02,200 --> 00:24:05,900
Oh, about brandy...Bad news.

441
00:24:05,900 --> 00:24:07,100
What--what happened?

442
00:24:07,100 --> 00:24:09,900
Well, penny wanted to
play beauty school with the wig,

443
00:24:09,900 --> 00:24:13,700
and, well, let's just say
she's got no future as a stylist.

444
00:24:14,600 --> 00:24:16,000
- Bad haircut, huh?
- Oh.

445
00:24:17,100 --> 00:24:20,800
Sounds like brandy might
get awful mad about that.

446
00:24:21,500 --> 00:24:22,600
Brandy's history, tom.

447
00:24:22,600 --> 00:24:23,700
Let her go.

448
00:24:28,500 --> 00:24:29,500
Raphael!

449
00:24:31,400 --> 00:24:32,500
Raphael!

450
00:24:32,500 --> 00:24:33,600
Come home, boy!

451
00:24:35,300 --> 00:24:36,500
Raphael?

452
00:24:38,100 --> 00:24:39,300
Lee?

453
00:24:39,900 --> 00:24:41,000
Is something wrong?

454
00:24:41,000 --> 00:24:41,600
Raphael got out.

455
00:24:41,600 --> 00:24:42,400
I-i don't know what happened.

456
00:24:42,400 --> 00:24:43,900
I think he jumped the fence.

457
00:24:44,400 --> 00:24:45,300
Oh.

458
00:24:45,300 --> 00:24:47,300
Well, would you like me
to help you look for him?

459
00:24:47,300 --> 00:24:48,500
Seriously?

460
00:24:49,000 --> 00:24:50,200
What a--what about your party?

461
00:24:50,200 --> 00:24:51,300
Oh.

462
00:24:51,500 --> 00:24:53,100
It's just a baby shower...

463
00:24:53,100 --> 00:24:54,400
That i'm throwing...

464
00:24:54,400 --> 00:24:55,500
For my best friend.

465
00:24:55,500 --> 00:24:56,800
I can't--
i can't ask you to leave that.

466
00:24:56,800 --> 00:24:57,800
- That's--
- oh, please.

467
00:24:57,800 --> 00:24:59,200
What are neighbors for?

468
00:25:00,300 --> 00:25:01,900
Raphael?

469
00:25:02,300 --> 00:25:03,700
Here, puppy!

470
00:25:06,900 --> 00:25:10,500
I see you've taken down
all the pictures of rex.

471
00:25:10,500 --> 00:25:13,200
Well, i'm, uh, sorry
if that offends you, phyllis,

472
00:25:13,200 --> 00:25:16,400
but i didn't want orson to
feel uncomfortable in his new home.

473
00:25:16,400 --> 00:25:17,600
I see.

474
00:25:18,200 --> 00:25:21,000
You're trying to be considerate of
your husband's feelings.

475
00:25:22,000 --> 00:25:27,000
Well, i'm glad that you're at least
trying to get it right the second time around.

476
00:25:27,700 --> 00:25:30,400
Still, it must be
awfully hard on danielle

477
00:25:30,400 --> 00:25:35,600
and andrew to have their father's face
banished from their own home.

478
00:25:35,600 --> 00:25:37,300
He wasn't banished.

479
00:25:38,900 --> 00:25:40,000
By the way...

480
00:25:41,200 --> 00:25:43,100
Where--where's danielle?

481
00:25:45,100 --> 00:25:47,100
She's, uh, at boarding school...

482
00:25:48,200 --> 00:25:49,400
In switzerland.

483
00:25:49,700 --> 00:25:51,000
Switzerland?

484
00:25:51,000 --> 00:25:55,200
Is it asking too much to be told
what continent my granddaughter is on?

485
00:25:55,200 --> 00:25:58,600
You are keeping my grandchildren from me,
and i don't know why.

486
00:25:58,600 --> 00:25:59,600
I'm going to mingle.

487
00:26:00,200 --> 00:26:03,100
Every time i start a chat,
you walk away.

488
00:26:03,100 --> 00:26:07,700
I mean, if you don't want to talk to me,
why did you invite me?

489
00:26:07,700 --> 00:26:10,600
It's a surprise party,
you daft woman!

490
00:26:10,600 --> 00:26:13,000
What makes you think
i had a hand in the guest list?

491
00:26:13,000 --> 00:26:14,100
So...

492
00:26:15,000 --> 00:26:16,600
You don't want me here?

493
00:26:16,600 --> 00:26:17,900
Oh, for god sakes, phyllis,

494
00:26:17,900 --> 00:26:20,100
it's not as if we got along
when rex was alive.

495
00:26:20,100 --> 00:26:24,700
What did i ever do to you
but try to treat you like a daughter?

496
00:26:24,700 --> 00:26:28,200
I even gave you my mother's sable coat.

497
00:26:28,200 --> 00:26:29,500
You hated your mother.

498
00:26:29,500 --> 00:26:30,700
But i loved that coat.

499
00:26:30,700 --> 00:26:32,500
Then i'll give it back to you.

500
00:26:32,500 --> 00:26:38,400
No, you keep it as a reminder of
how hard i tried to make you like me.

501
00:26:43,600 --> 00:26:44,900
Grandma, are you leaving already?

502
00:26:45,300 --> 00:26:49,700
I'm sorry, dear, but your mother
has made it impossible for me to stay.

503
00:26:54,800 --> 00:26:57,200
Where does she keep my sable coat?

504
00:26:57,200 --> 00:26:58,900
Probably in her bedroom closet.

505
00:27:07,800 --> 00:27:09,000
Where is she going?

506
00:27:09,000 --> 00:27:10,900
She asked me
where your fur coat was.

507
00:27:12,300 --> 00:27:14,100
And--and you told her?

508
00:27:17,800 --> 00:27:18,900
Oh, crap.

509
00:27:29,100 --> 00:27:32,900
I guess you won't be needing
the breast pump i bought you.

510
00:27:38,800 --> 00:27:42,200
So...Danielle is having a baby.

511
00:27:43,100 --> 00:27:48,000
Yes, and for the sake of her reputation,
we've agreed to pretend that it's mine.

512
00:27:48,300 --> 00:27:52,000
I just hope that those swiss doctors
know what they're doing.

513
00:27:52,000 --> 00:27:54,400
She's not in switzerland.

514
00:27:54,400 --> 00:27:56,500
She's at the sisters of hope convent.

515
00:27:57,300 --> 00:27:58,600
Look, phyllis, i'm sorry.

516
00:27:58,600 --> 00:28:00,000
I know this is upsetting.

517
00:28:00,000 --> 00:28:02,000
Actually, i'm thrilled.

518
00:28:02,900 --> 00:28:05,400
I'm going to be a great-grandma.

519
00:28:07,400 --> 00:28:08,500
Well, um...

520
00:28:09,500 --> 00:28:11,400
Technically, yes.

521
00:28:14,100 --> 00:28:15,500
What do you mean, "tecically"?

522
00:28:16,500 --> 00:28:19,500
We're saying that
the baby is mine and orson's,

523
00:28:19,500 --> 00:28:24,400
and if you hover around like a grandmother,
people will be suspicious.

524
00:28:24,400 --> 00:28:27,600
You're not keeping this baby from me,

525
00:28:27,600 --> 00:28:32,900
not if you don't want me to tell those
people downstairs whose child it really is.

526
00:28:32,900 --> 00:28:34,100
You wouldn't.

527
00:28:34,100 --> 00:28:35,500
Think of danielle!

528
00:28:36,600 --> 00:28:37,900
I wish you had.

529
00:28:38,200 --> 00:28:42,600
If you'd raised her properly,
she wouldn't be pregnant without ahusband.

530
00:28:42,600 --> 00:28:45,200
You think i don't know
i'm a failure as a parent?

531
00:28:45,700 --> 00:28:47,200
That's why this child
means so much to me.

532
00:28:47,200 --> 00:28:48,800
It's my second chance.

533
00:28:50,500 --> 00:28:53,500
Well, i hope the second time around
that you take my advice.

534
00:28:53,500 --> 00:28:58,100
I always said that you were
too strict with those kids.

535
00:28:58,100 --> 00:28:59,800
Parenting tips from you?

536
00:28:59,800 --> 00:29:01,200
That's rich.

537
00:29:02,400 --> 00:29:04,500
I was a wonderful mother to rex.

538
00:29:04,500 --> 00:29:06,300
Then why did he always avoid you?

539
00:29:06,300 --> 00:29:07,700
Why were you barely ever here?

540
00:29:07,700 --> 00:29:09,700
Because of you!

541
00:29:09,700 --> 00:29:12,100
He knew you hated me.

542
00:29:12,100 --> 00:29:14,200
Oh, he was happy to
let you think that,

543
00:29:14,200 --> 00:29:17,200
but he was the one
who dreaded your visits.

544
00:29:17,700 --> 00:29:18,700
Oh.

545
00:29:22,000 --> 00:29:23,000
Phyllis, wait!

546
00:29:25,500 --> 00:29:29,200
Excuse me, everyone,
but i have something to say.

547
00:29:32,800 --> 00:29:34,000
What--what is it, grandma?

548
00:29:35,200 --> 00:29:37,800
I...

549
00:29:48,900 --> 00:29:50,700
I have to go,

550
00:29:50,700 --> 00:29:56,700
and i just wanted to say how nice
it was to see you all again after so much time.

551
00:30:00,700 --> 00:30:01,800
Good-bye.

552
00:30:10,600 --> 00:30:12,100
Thank you for the gift.

553
00:30:13,600 --> 00:30:18,200
You know, bree, you're not the only one
who would like a second chance.

554
00:30:26,500 --> 00:30:28,000
- Nothing, huh?
- No.

555
00:30:28,000 --> 00:30:29,300
No, he's lost.

556
00:30:29,300 --> 00:30:30,100
And he doesn't know
this neighborhood.

557
00:30:30,100 --> 00:30:31,700
There's no way
he's gonna find his way home.

558
00:30:31,700 --> 00:30:32,400
Oh, he will.

559
00:30:32,400 --> 00:30:34,400
Come on.
You gotta keep believing.

560
00:30:34,400 --> 00:30:36,100
Oh, crap!

561
00:30:36,100 --> 00:30:37,000
Bob's home.

562
00:30:37,000 --> 00:30:37,800
What am i gonna tell him?

563
00:30:37,800 --> 00:30:38,700
Don't.

564
00:30:38,700 --> 00:30:39,800
We'll just keep looking.

565
00:30:39,800 --> 00:30:42,800
I have a feeling we're gonna
find that cute little guy.

566
00:30:42,800 --> 00:30:45,800
You--you are so nice to do this,

567
00:30:45,800 --> 00:30:47,700
i mean,especially after the way i acted
when we first-- you know what?

568
00:30:47,700 --> 00:30:48,500
Don't worry about it.

569
00:30:48,500 --> 00:30:51,800
I'm gonna go inside and get us some water,
and then we're gonna just keep looking.

570
00:30:51,800 --> 00:30:52,500
Okay.

571
00:31:02,900 --> 00:31:03,700
Lee!

572
00:31:04,200 --> 00:31:05,000
I can't find raphael.

573
00:31:05,000 --> 00:31:06,000
You seen him anywhere?

574
00:31:06,600 --> 00:31:08,800
Oh, bob, prom--
promise you won't hate me.

575
00:31:08,800 --> 00:31:09,800
What are you talking about?

576
00:31:09,800 --> 00:31:10,800
What happened?

577
00:31:11,400 --> 00:31:12,400
Raphael got out.

578
00:31:12,400 --> 00:31:13,400
- He got out?
- Yeah.

579
00:31:13,400 --> 00:31:14,300
He doesn't know the neighborhood.

580
00:31:14,300 --> 00:31:15,700
- I know he doesn't know the neighborhood.
- What are you talking about?

581
00:31:15,700 --> 00:31:20,800
- I know--i don't--
- how are you looking for him?

582
00:31:20,800 --> 00:31:22,600
Well, susan, she--
she's getting water.

583
00:31:26,600 --> 00:31:27,900
Oh, wait, he's right there.

584
00:31:29,400 --> 00:31:30,200
Hey, hey.

585
00:31:30,200 --> 00:31:30,800
Oh!

586
00:31:30,800 --> 00:31:31,700
Hey!

587
00:31:33,700 --> 00:31:34,400
Oh!

588
00:31:34,400 --> 00:31:35,400
Oh, my god!

589
00:31:46,700 --> 00:31:48,700
What was our dog doing
in your garage?

590
00:31:48,700 --> 00:31:50,200
I have no idea.

591
00:31:57,600 --> 00:31:58,400
What?

592
00:32:03,200 --> 00:32:04,000
Here we go.

593
00:32:06,600 --> 00:32:09,400
Did you get a chance to,
uh, napalm the jungle yet?

594
00:32:10,000 --> 00:32:10,700
Yep.

595
00:32:11,800 --> 00:32:12,600
And?

596
00:32:13,400 --> 00:32:15,300
All quiet on the southern front.

597
00:32:17,700 --> 00:32:19,600
Gaby, we have got to be more careful.

598
00:32:20,200 --> 00:32:21,200
Absolutely.

599
00:32:22,500 --> 00:32:23,900
It's kind of exciting, though.

600
00:32:25,000 --> 00:32:26,100
What is?

601
00:32:26,700 --> 00:32:29,300
Playing with fire,
almost getting burned but not quite.

602
00:32:29,300 --> 00:32:30,300
Don't be thinking like that.

603
00:32:30,300 --> 00:32:32,200
If victor catches us,
he'll kill us both.

604
00:32:33,100 --> 00:32:34,300
That's what's so exciting.

605
00:32:37,700 --> 00:32:38,500
Hi.

606
00:32:40,000 --> 00:32:41,100
Oh, my--excuse me.

607
00:32:44,700 --> 00:32:46,200
Mmm, that's, um...

608
00:32:47,000 --> 00:32:49,000
An interesting cologne
you're wearing.

609
00:32:50,300 --> 00:32:51,500
My wife gave it to me.

610
00:32:51,500 --> 00:32:54,900
It's got, uh, anise root, fennel.

611
00:32:55,600 --> 00:32:56,600
What, you like it?

612
00:32:58,200 --> 00:32:59,600
Yeah, it's just, um...

613
00:33:00,500 --> 00:33:01,600
I don't know...

614
00:33:02,500 --> 00:33:04,700
Weirdly familiar.

615
00:33:14,500 --> 00:33:15,500
Crab cake?

616
00:33:15,900 --> 00:33:16,800
Uh, yeah.

617
00:33:17,600 --> 00:33:18,600
Thanks.

618
00:33:22,100 --> 00:33:23,100
Crab cake?

619
00:33:30,100 --> 00:33:31,200
Crab cake?

620
00:33:31,200 --> 00:33:32,100
Thank you.

621
00:33:37,700 --> 00:33:38,600
Crab cake?

622
00:34:01,900 --> 00:34:03,700
Kids are asleep.

623
00:34:05,200 --> 00:34:07,200
I'm not.

624
00:34:09,700 --> 00:34:10,800
Whatcha got back there?

625
00:34:10,800 --> 00:34:12,200
Just a little present.

626
00:34:14,200 --> 00:34:17,100
Say hello to brandy's
even sluttier sister...

627
00:34:17,900 --> 00:34:19,000
Candy.

628
00:34:20,700 --> 00:34:21,900
What are you doing?

629
00:34:21,900 --> 00:34:23,100
Well, i just--i just thought

630
00:34:23,100 --> 00:34:27,300
since we had so much fun last night,
maybe we can have a little more fun.

631
00:34:27,300 --> 00:34:31,400
And that's only possible
when you're pretending i'm someone else?

632
00:34:34,700 --> 00:34:36,000
Well, you have to pretend, too.

633
00:34:37,800 --> 00:34:38,800
What?

634
00:34:39,800 --> 00:34:40,700
This...

635
00:34:41,400 --> 00:34:46,300
Is me, tom,
not brandy or candy.

636
00:34:46,300 --> 00:34:48,500
It's just your wife, lynette.

637
00:34:48,500 --> 00:34:49,700
Am i not enough for you?

638
00:34:49,700 --> 00:34:51,400
What are you getting so mad for?

639
00:34:51,400 --> 00:34:53,400
The first wig was your idea.

640
00:34:53,400 --> 00:34:56,100
Yeah, because i'm bald.

641
00:34:56,100 --> 00:34:58,400
And i know that
that's a big old turnoff,

642
00:34:58,400 --> 00:35:00,400
but, you know, i can't help it.

643
00:35:00,400 --> 00:35:01,500
I have cancer.

644
00:35:01,500 --> 00:35:02,400
Yes, i know.

645
00:35:02,400 --> 00:35:03,500
I hear about it all the time.

646
00:35:04,400 --> 00:35:07,500
Can you blame me for
wanting to escape every once in a while?

647
00:35:08,000 --> 00:35:09,900
- Escape from me, you mean?
- Yes!

648
00:35:11,800 --> 00:35:13,400
You know why
last night was so much fun?

649
00:35:13,400 --> 00:35:16,600
Because i got to make love
to someone who wasn't sick.

650
00:35:17,600 --> 00:35:19,700
Look, i know, i know,
i'm not supposed to say this stuff.

651
00:35:19,700 --> 00:35:21,100
I have to be the heroic husband 

652
00:35:21,100 --> 00:35:23,800
who listens and holds you
when you cry and never cries himself.

653
00:35:23,800 --> 00:35:27,000
But this affects me, too.

654
00:35:28,500 --> 00:35:29,300
Well...

655
00:35:29,700 --> 00:35:30,900
I know that.

656
00:35:30,900 --> 00:35:32,200
- You do?
- Yeah.

657
00:35:32,200 --> 00:35:33,300
How?

658
00:35:33,800 --> 00:35:38,200
Since this whole thing began,
have you ever once asked me how i'm doing?

659
00:35:47,000 --> 00:35:48,100
Oh...

660
00:35:48,400 --> 00:35:49,300
My god.

661
00:35:49,300 --> 00:35:51,700
I haven't, have i?

662
00:35:57,900 --> 00:36:00,200
I am one of those...

663
00:36:00,800 --> 00:36:05,500
Whiny, self-involved sick people.

664
00:36:08,300 --> 00:36:08,900
I didn't say that.

665
00:36:08,900 --> 00:36:10,300
No, i am.

666
00:36:10,300 --> 00:36:14,700
It's been months, and i have barely
thought about what you're going through.

667
00:36:14,700 --> 00:36:17,600
- It's okay.You're going through something
- will you stop being so heroic?

668
00:36:18,100 --> 00:36:19,500
I'm a cancer bitch!

669
00:36:27,300 --> 00:36:28,300
What?

670
00:36:29,800 --> 00:36:31,300
I'm not gonna argue with you.

671
00:36:34,400 --> 00:36:35,400
You suck.

672
00:36:41,700 --> 00:36:42,600
Well...

673
00:36:44,000 --> 00:36:46,500
I guess i could
give candy a whirl.

674
00:36:47,600 --> 00:36:49,000
Are the kids really asleep?

675
00:36:50,500 --> 00:36:52,400
'Cause i think
she might be a screamer.

676
00:36:58,000 --> 00:37:00,300
Actually, if we're gonna pretend...

677
00:37:01,300 --> 00:37:07,300
How about tonight i'm not a hero
and you are not a cancer patient?

678
00:37:09,400 --> 00:37:15,200
We'll just be tom and lynette,
see what happens.

679
00:37:17,500 --> 00:37:18,700
Oh, i'd like that.

680
00:37:28,600 --> 00:37:32,600
- How's bob's suit?
- Ruined.

681
00:37:32,600 --> 00:37:34,400
Oh.What if
we take it to my cleaners?

682
00:37:34,400 --> 00:37:36,300
Susan, that paint's not coming out...

683
00:37:36,300 --> 00:37:38,300
So we're buying him a new suit...

684
00:37:39,100 --> 00:37:40,800
For 2,000 bucks.

685
00:37:41,400 --> 00:37:42,400
$2,000?

686
00:37:42,400 --> 00:37:44,200
Well, according to lee,
it's a dolce.

687
00:37:44,200 --> 00:37:46,500
I don't know what that means,
but he said it six times.

688
00:37:46,500 --> 00:37:47,900
That's crazy.

689
00:37:49,000 --> 00:37:52,300
No, what's crazy is i'm about to buy
the most expensive suit of my life,

690
00:37:52,300 --> 00:37:53,400
and i'll never wear it.

691
00:37:53,400 --> 00:37:54,200
Oh.

692
00:37:54,200 --> 00:37:56,600
I just wanted them to like me.

693
00:37:56,600 --> 00:37:58,000
Well, they don't.

694
00:37:58,000 --> 00:38:00,500
Lee said that six times, too.

695
00:38:00,500 --> 00:38:03,500
There must be some way
i can apologize to them.

696
00:38:03,500 --> 00:38:05,300
We can't afford
any more of your apologies.

697
00:38:05,300 --> 00:38:06,000
I know.

698
00:38:06,000 --> 00:38:08,700
- Uh, maybe if i--
- damn it, susan, let it go, okay?

699
00:38:08,700 --> 00:38:11,400
I asked you to before, and you didn't,
and look what happened.

700
00:38:11,400 --> 00:38:12,800
So i'll ask you again.

701
00:38:12,800 --> 00:38:14,000
Just let it go.

702
00:38:14,900 --> 00:38:15,600
Mike, wait.

703
00:38:15,600 --> 00:38:16,700
We should talk about this.

704
00:38:16,700 --> 00:38:17,500
I'm going to bed.

705
00:38:18,100 --> 00:38:19,400
I've gotta work tomorrow.

706
00:38:19,700 --> 00:38:20,900
I'm buying a suit.

707
00:38:36,800 --> 00:38:37,700
Grandma!

708
00:38:39,900 --> 00:38:41,100
What are you doing here?

709
00:38:41,600 --> 00:38:43,600
You needn't be embarrassed, dear.

710
00:38:44,300 --> 00:38:45,900
Your mother's told me everything.

711
00:38:47,200 --> 00:38:48,500
It's great to see you.

712
00:38:49,700 --> 00:38:50,700
I hate this place.

713
00:38:50,700 --> 00:38:52,200
It's like baby jail.

714
00:38:52,200 --> 00:38:53,500
Oh.

715
00:38:53,500 --> 00:38:55,600
Well, that's what
i've come to talk to you about.

716
00:38:56,400 --> 00:38:58,400
Perhaps it's time for you to leave.

717
00:39:04,300 --> 00:39:05,500
Dylan?

718
00:39:06,700 --> 00:39:07,900
Is that you?

719
00:39:08,100 --> 00:39:10,200
We have--have to talk.

720
00:39:21,100 --> 00:39:22,200
Hey.

721
00:39:23,200 --> 00:39:24,100
I'm glad you're home.

722
00:39:26,000 --> 00:39:27,400
I wanted to talk to you
about aunt lily.

723
00:39:28,800 --> 00:39:29,600
What about her?

724
00:39:31,900 --> 00:39:33,270
It was so weird.

725
00:39:34,000 --> 00:39:35,700
She called me
into her room this afternoon.

726
00:39:36,900 --> 00:39:40,200
She started saying she knew why i didn't
remember living on this street before.

727
00:39:40,700 --> 00:39:41,900
Oh, sweetie.

728
00:39:42,700 --> 00:39:44,900
Your aunt lily is fading fast.

729
00:39:45,700 --> 00:39:47,500
Half the time,
she doesn't know what she's saying.

730
00:39:51,100 --> 00:39:52,100
Was that her?

731
00:39:52,900 --> 00:39:54,400
No, i just checked on her.

732
00:39:54,400 --> 00:39:55,500
She's sleeping.

733
00:39:57,200 --> 00:39:59,500
You know,you have
that recital in two weeks.

734
00:39:59,500 --> 00:40:00,800
Shouldn't you be practicing?

735
00:40:07,800 --> 00:40:09,100
Dylan.

736
00:40:12,100 --> 00:40:13,900
Please!

737
00:41:23,100 --> 00:41:28,400
pests-- they come
in all shapes and sizes 

738
00:41:28,400 --> 00:41:31,900
and disrupt our lives
in a variety of ways.

739
00:41:34,300 --> 00:41:36,700
At first, they're merely annoying,

740
00:41:38,700 --> 00:41:41,200
and we do our best
to ignore them.

741
00:41:42,700 --> 00:41:43,600
Home in my own bed...

742
00:41:43,600 --> 00:41:49,600
But if we don't take them seriously,
they can become quite dangerous.

743
00:41:53,300 --> 00:41:57,900
For some, death seems to be
the easiest solution.

744
00:42:04,600 --> 00:42:10,200
But the problem with pests
is that what they leave behind...

745
00:42:10,900 --> 00:42:12,600
Is just as dangerous.

746
00:42:12,600 --> 00:42:13,600
<font color="#4096d1">-==http://subland.5286.cn==-</font>

747
00:42:13,600 --> 00:42:14,600
<font color="#4096d1">sync:虾米 蓝狼浪</font>

748
00:42:14,600 --> 00:42:15,200
<font color="#4096d1">Welcome to join 5286 team</font>

749
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


750
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


