1
00:00:04,920 --> 00:00:08,515
- Um, Agent Booth?
- Yes, Angela?

2
00:00:08,600 --> 00:00:11,956
This is the paediatric cancer floor
of the hospital.

3
00:00:12,040 --> 00:00:13,951
Mm-hm. Yeah.

4
00:00:14,040 --> 00:00:18,352
Right, well, what I'm about to show
Deputy Director Cullen is kinda gruesome.

5
00:00:18,440 --> 00:00:22,115
- Why are we meeting Cullen here?
- He's the deputy director of the FBI.

6
00:00:22,200 --> 00:00:25,397
This is where he wants us to show it to him.

7
00:00:26,680 --> 00:00:32,835
OK, listen. About a month ago his daughter
Amy was diagnosed with cancer. Meso...

8
00:00:32,920 --> 00:00:35,434
- Mesothelioma. Lung cancer.
- Exactly.

9
00:00:35,520 --> 00:00:40,833
So she's not doing so well, so it's a lot easier
for us to come to him right now.

10
00:00:40,920 --> 00:00:43,115
- Huh.
- "Huh" what?

11
00:00:43,200 --> 00:00:46,237
Nothing. It's just an extremely rare
form of lung cancer.

12
00:00:46,320 --> 00:00:49,471
- Odd for someone Amy's age to contract.
- No, no, no.

13
00:00:49,560 --> 00:00:53,030
No probing, OK?
Not to Cullen, not to his family.

14
00:00:53,120 --> 00:00:58,911
It'll take five minutes. We do the show and tell
relating to the case, then we're out. Clear?

15
00:00:59,000 --> 00:01:00,558
- It's peculiar.
- No!

16
00:01:00,640 --> 00:01:04,235
- But I... You have to admit...
- Booth.

17
00:01:04,320 --> 00:01:06,675
Dr Brennan.

18
00:01:06,760 --> 00:01:09,638
How appropriate -
bickering in an adolescent wing.

19
00:01:09,720 --> 00:01:11,870
Sir, yes. Um...

20
00:01:11,960 --> 00:01:14,520
Is it OK if we come in, sir?

21
00:01:15,720 --> 00:01:20,316
- What do you think, sweetheart?
- Booth's cool, most of the time.

22
00:01:20,400 --> 00:01:23,119
- You heard the lady. You're cool.
- Mm-hm.

23
00:01:23,200 --> 00:01:25,475
Yeah, right.

24
00:01:31,320 --> 00:01:34,118
Are you sure it's all right
for me to do this here?

25
00:01:34,200 --> 00:01:36,919
Nothing I haven't seen before.

26
00:01:37,000 --> 00:01:42,870
- Let's see what you got here, Angela.
- The estimated time of death is mid-June.

27
00:01:42,960 --> 00:01:48,910
Extreme humidity combined with insects and
precipitation accelerated the rate of decomp.

28
00:01:50,000 --> 00:01:55,916
- So the body was not mutilated after death?
- <i>(Bones)</i> The effects were environmental.

29
00:01:56,000 --> 00:02:01,199
- Murder doesn't fit the suspect's profile, sir.
- It's not nice to fool Mother Nature.

30
00:02:01,280 --> 00:02:07,071
- I'd like to see this again.
- Knock yourself out, sir. 86 times is our limit.

31
00:02:07,160 --> 00:02:09,355
Can I see your drawings?

32
00:02:09,440 --> 00:02:13,513
- Wow. These are beautiful.
- Our artist in the making.

33
00:02:13,600 --> 00:02:17,639
Right now I'm doing landscapes.
I'm really into this French dude, Rousseau.

34
00:02:17,720 --> 00:02:22,840
Yeah. There's a... there's a lot of Rousseau
in Paris. Have you ever been to the Louvre?

35
00:02:22,920 --> 00:02:29,268
No, not yet. But it's on my list -
right after "fall in love" and "learn to drive".

36
00:02:29,360 --> 00:02:31,715
Well, you've got a great eye.

37
00:02:31,800 --> 00:02:35,110
Thanks. I think what you do
is pretty awesome, too.

38
00:02:35,200 --> 00:02:38,237
I mean, computers are not for me, but I get it.

39
00:02:38,320 --> 00:02:41,073
Can I see what you're working on?

40
00:02:46,080 --> 00:02:49,117
- She's amazing.
- Mm-hm.

41
00:02:49,200 --> 00:02:51,634
Amy's been very brave this week.

42
00:02:51,720 --> 00:02:54,917
They're trying
an experimental virochemotherapy.

43
00:02:55,000 --> 00:02:56,991
And we're very optimistic.

44
00:02:57,080 --> 00:03:01,471
Since asbestos exposure is the primary way
people contract mesothelioma, how...?

45
00:03:01,560 --> 00:03:03,676
<i>(Booth clears his throat)</i>

46
00:03:03,760 --> 00:03:06,718
- How do you think Amy got it?
- We don't know, Dr Brennan.

47
00:03:06,800 --> 00:03:09,519
The first place we looked
after she was diagnosed

48
00:03:09,600 --> 00:03:13,434
was all her previous schools,
the house we lived in - nothing.

49
00:03:13,520 --> 00:03:15,875
Has there been a history of illness?

50
00:03:15,960 --> 00:03:19,589
Hardly. Apart from breaking her leg
snowboarding a year ago,

51
00:03:19,680 --> 00:03:21,989
I can't remember the last time she was sick.

52
00:03:22,080 --> 00:03:25,117
- How bad was the break?
- Compound fracture, left tibia.

53
00:03:25,200 --> 00:03:29,876
I was boarding with some friends
and I... I hit a tree. Pretty dumb, huh?

54
00:03:29,960 --> 00:03:32,269
- And that required surgery?
- A bone graft.

55
00:03:32,360 --> 00:03:36,717
I hate to drag these lovely squints
back to the lab, but we have another case.

56
00:03:36,800 --> 00:03:40,349
- No, we don't. Could I see her graft x-rays?
- Sir, I apologise.

57
00:03:40,440 --> 00:03:42,829
Of course.

58
00:03:43,640 --> 00:03:46,757
If you think they'll tell us anything.

59
00:03:49,200 --> 00:03:54,320
Whoa. Pardon the <i>fromage</i> reference, but
what's with the mouldy Gruyère in that leg?

60
00:03:54,400 --> 00:03:57,278
The lighter colour
is evidence of demineralisation.

61
00:03:57,360 --> 00:03:59,954
I'm not the bone expert here, but... yuck.

62
00:04:00,040 --> 00:04:03,555
- Osteoporosis.
- Basically, the bone has become porous.

63
00:04:03,640 --> 00:04:08,760
Something that happens with age. See if you
can isolate the grafted portion and enlarge it.

64
00:04:08,840 --> 00:04:12,594
- Amy's file states the donor was 25 years old.
- I don't buy it.

65
00:04:12,680 --> 00:04:16,753
- What about the ageing disease?
- This isn't a progerian skeleton.

66
00:04:16,840 --> 00:04:20,879
This bone is significantly less dense
than a person in their 20s, for sure.

67
00:04:20,960 --> 00:04:26,796
- How old do you think the donor really was?
- Judging from the reduction in bone mass...

68
00:04:26,880 --> 00:04:28,916
at least 60.

69
00:04:33,600 --> 00:04:38,276
- Doctor, did you perform Amy Cullers graft?
- Yes. I just do the procedure, Ms Brennan.

70
00:04:38,360 --> 00:04:40,112
- Doctor Brennan.
- MD?

71
00:04:40,200 --> 00:04:43,875
- PhD.
- Well, those who can't do, do research.

72
00:04:43,960 --> 00:04:46,030
- OK.
- Booth.

73
00:04:46,120 --> 00:04:49,635
If you're just the mechanic,
who's responsible for all the parts?

74
00:04:49,720 --> 00:04:52,917
You'll have to check with
the transplant coordinator. Why?

75
00:04:53,000 --> 00:04:58,120
There are indications the bone graft you
implanted in Amy Cullen gave her cancer.

76
00:04:58,200 --> 00:05:01,272
Every graft we get
has been tested and irradiated.

77
00:05:01,360 --> 00:05:05,319
There's one way to know for sure.
Assuming remodelling hasn't occurred,

78
00:05:05,400 --> 00:05:09,837
do a transiliac crest core biopsy on the donor
bone, then we'll have age and pathology.

79
00:05:09,920 --> 00:05:12,912
And who's going to
perform that biopsy, Doctor?

80
00:05:13,000 --> 00:05:15,798
You are.

81
00:05:24,720 --> 00:05:26,597
<i>(Booth)</i> That looks like it hurts.

82
00:05:26,680 --> 00:05:32,471
They use local anaesthetic and make
an incision before inserting the needle.

83
00:05:32,560 --> 00:05:36,758
A tiny core of bone is taken - a little more
than a sixth of an inch in diameter,

84
00:05:36,840 --> 00:05:40,196
using a ratchetlike device in the needle.

85
00:05:41,000 --> 00:05:42,672
So it hurts?

86
00:05:44,080 --> 00:05:46,275
Amy's a tough kid.

87
00:05:46,360 --> 00:05:48,430
She's doing great.

88
00:05:48,520 --> 00:05:51,318
<i>(Booth)</i> It's not Amy I'm worried about.

89
00:05:52,840 --> 00:05:55,479
Let's go talk to the coordinator
who bought the graft.

90
00:05:55,560 --> 00:05:58,677
Unlike Amy, he gets to go home tonight.

91
00:06:02,760 --> 00:06:05,354
You're a popular man, Dr Ogden.

92
00:06:05,440 --> 00:06:09,353
When you find body parts
that save lives, you have no idea.

93
00:06:09,440 --> 00:06:12,477
I had one gentleman offer me
his cattle ranch in Montana.

94
00:06:12,560 --> 00:06:16,758
Well, people, they get desperate.
Did you take him up on it?

95
00:06:16,840 --> 00:06:18,876
That would be dishonest, Agent Booth.

96
00:06:18,960 --> 00:06:22,157
If anything, this office
is built on the goodness of people.

97
00:06:22,240 --> 00:06:26,358
- Cullen, Amy A. Bone graft number 4429.
- All right.

98
00:06:26,440 --> 00:06:29,796
According to my report,

99
00:06:29,880 --> 00:06:33,589
the bone that was donated
was harvested from a 25-year-old.

100
00:06:33,680 --> 00:06:36,990
- Can you give us the name?
- I can't provide that information.

101
00:06:37,080 --> 00:06:41,278
What about other recipients? Any other
patients get a part from the same body?

102
00:06:41,360 --> 00:06:44,432
When I said I couldn't tell you,
it's because we don't know.

103
00:06:44,520 --> 00:06:46,875
You'd have to ask the tissue bank for that.

104
00:06:46,960 --> 00:06:52,796
Biotech Tissue Services. We've been using
them for a long time. Never had a problem.

105
00:06:52,880 --> 00:06:56,395
Amy Cullen has a problem. She's dying.

106
00:06:56,480 --> 00:07:01,713
Through no fault of this office. If we can be of
any further assistance, don't hesitate to call.

107
00:07:01,800 --> 00:07:05,429
Thanks for being so sympathetic.
We'll check into it.

108
00:07:10,000 --> 00:07:14,391
- New osteologic scans to input as requested.
- Hey, check this out.

109
00:07:14,480 --> 00:07:17,358
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> Monet?
- Amy Cullen.

110
00:07:17,440 --> 00:07:20,716
- You're kidding.
- No. I ran it through the digitiser.

111
00:07:20,800 --> 00:07:25,590
She's a good kid. I wanted to show her
that computers don't have to be the enemy.

112
00:07:25,680 --> 00:07:29,468
Not bad for a certified member
of the geek squad.

113
00:07:29,560 --> 00:07:33,712
- I'll take that as a compliment.
- Well, you should.

114
00:07:39,600 --> 00:07:42,717
<i>(Bones)</i> This is a cross section
from Amy's bone graft.

115
00:07:42,800 --> 00:07:45,951
Zack, what's the ratio
of primary to secondary osteons?

116
00:07:46,040 --> 00:07:50,079
I only see secondary. Exactly what
you'd expect to see in an older decedent.

117
00:07:50,160 --> 00:07:52,071
Any accompanying data?

118
00:07:52,680 --> 00:07:56,639
Well, I'm no expert,
but I think it supports as well.

119
00:07:56,720 --> 00:08:02,397
So based on this sample, it's clear that the
donor bone came from someone in their 60s.

120
00:08:02,480 --> 00:08:04,789
How do we know the bone gave Amy cancer?

121
00:08:04,880 --> 00:08:08,395
Because of this. Magnify.

122
00:08:08,480 --> 00:08:10,755
The graft is riddled with cancer.

123
00:08:10,840 --> 00:08:14,389
Cancer consistent with
morphology origin in the pleura.

124
00:08:14,480 --> 00:08:16,391
Most likely mesothelioma.

125
00:08:16,480 --> 00:08:20,837
Whoever this is had terminal cancer.
And now so does Amy.

126
00:08:20,920 --> 00:08:23,992
She went in for a broken leg
and was poisoned.

127
00:08:24,080 --> 00:08:26,036
She never even had a chance.

128
00:08:26,120 --> 00:08:29,635
Someone knew that bone was infected
and they gave it to her anyway.

129
00:08:29,720 --> 00:08:31,790
This will kill Amy Cullen.

130
00:08:31,880 --> 00:08:34,599
Well, in that case, it's murder.

131
00:09:08,440 --> 00:09:10,795
Amy's cancer originated in the bone graft.

132
00:09:10,880 --> 00:09:13,599
- The test confirms it.
- It was the operation?

133
00:09:13,680 --> 00:09:18,674
Not only was the bone contaminated by
malignancy, it was older than documented.

134
00:09:18,760 --> 00:09:22,594
- It was expired or something?
- No, sir. It came from a much older donor.

135
00:09:22,680 --> 00:09:24,796
Someone in their 60s.

136
00:09:27,360 --> 00:09:28,429
Hospital error.

137
00:09:28,520 --> 00:09:32,638
Next we find where the graft came from
and how it slipped through the system.

138
00:09:32,720 --> 00:09:35,359
This is not FBI jurisdiction.

139
00:09:36,560 --> 00:09:38,437
It's a question ofjustice.

140
00:09:38,520 --> 00:09:42,638
Does this in any way
change my daughter's prognosis?

141
00:09:45,560 --> 00:09:47,755
No.

142
00:09:47,840 --> 00:09:50,035
So she's still gonna die of this cancer?

143
00:09:50,120 --> 00:09:53,317
Barring spontaneous remission,

144
00:09:53,400 --> 00:09:56,153
the likelihood is significant.

145
00:09:57,520 --> 00:10:01,069
The FBI's not my personal police force.

146
00:10:01,160 --> 00:10:03,958
I appreciate what you've discovered.

147
00:10:04,040 --> 00:10:08,591
Call Charlie Hammond. Tell him what
happened. He'll continue the investigation.

148
00:10:08,680 --> 00:10:12,878
- My team can still...
- We'll notify CDC right away.

149
00:10:16,080 --> 00:10:19,709
So that's it? Whoever did this
to Amy Cullen just gets away.

150
00:10:19,800 --> 00:10:23,315
No. What we do now is find out a way
to make this a legitimate FBI case.

151
00:10:23,400 --> 00:10:26,119
If one graft is infected, how many others are?

152
00:10:26,200 --> 00:10:30,637
I feel like I'm on a serial-killer case
just waiting for another victim to surface.

153
00:10:30,720 --> 00:10:34,759
You're not far off. What if Biotech
makes a habit of selling diseased parts?

154
00:10:34,840 --> 00:10:38,992
It becomes FBI business
if one tainted graft is sold across state line.

155
00:10:39,080 --> 00:10:41,719
You can spit into four states
from where we are.

156
00:10:41,800 --> 00:10:44,268
- What?
- Not literally.

157
00:10:44,360 --> 00:10:48,990
- We'll find if this lab services other hospitals.
- See if they've killed anyone else.

158
00:10:49,080 --> 00:10:54,518
- Amy Cullen is not dead, Bones.
- I'm afraid there's a degree of inevitability.

159
00:10:55,720 --> 00:10:57,392
Sorry.

160
00:11:03,000 --> 00:11:04,911
It's pretty excellent, huh?

161
00:11:05,000 --> 00:11:07,912
- Is that mine?
- Uh-huh.

162
00:11:12,160 --> 00:11:14,390
How'd you do that?

163
00:11:14,480 --> 00:11:17,438
Most of the time I restore
and enance old bones.

164
00:11:17,520 --> 00:11:20,717
So this is a lot more fun.

165
00:11:33,680 --> 00:11:36,114
It's hard, you know.

166
00:11:36,200 --> 00:11:41,354
One second I'm at school
and I'm gonna be an artist...

167
00:11:41,440 --> 00:11:43,954
and the next...

168
00:11:45,040 --> 00:11:47,679
My friends don't know what to say.

169
00:11:47,760 --> 00:11:50,354
My parents are scared.

170
00:11:51,840 --> 00:11:54,957
Things change, I guess.

171
00:11:56,040 --> 00:11:58,190
Yeah.

172
00:11:58,280 --> 00:12:01,158
Yeah, sometimes they do.

173
00:12:07,360 --> 00:12:10,079
Angela?

174
00:12:10,160 --> 00:12:12,674
Is the Louvre just unbelievable?

175
00:12:14,120 --> 00:12:20,355
- It's the most beautiful place you'll ever see.
- Maybe you can tell me about it sometime.

176
00:12:20,440 --> 00:12:23,432
You'll go there yourself.

177
00:12:23,520 --> 00:12:26,273
I know you will.

178
00:12:36,120 --> 00:12:41,194
270. Here's Biotech. We get in there,
we'll sweat the head guy.

179
00:12:41,280 --> 00:12:45,034
Hello? F... BI.

180
00:12:45,120 --> 00:12:48,556
OK. So this is Biotech.

181
00:12:50,920 --> 00:12:54,959
- Sorry I couldn't be any more help.
- Thanks. I appreciate it.

182
00:12:55,040 --> 00:12:58,430
Building manager says
Biotech went belly up two years ago.

183
00:12:58,520 --> 00:13:00,795
- Couldrt pay their rent.
- Where'd they go?

184
00:13:00,880 --> 00:13:03,440
- He doesn't know.
- Two years ago?

185
00:13:03,520 --> 00:13:07,274
Exactly. Amy's graft was sold
to Washington General 12 months ago.

186
00:13:07,360 --> 00:13:11,194
If Biotech doesn't exist,
who sold a diseased bone to the hospital?

187
00:13:11,880 --> 00:13:13,871
Where is he?

188
00:13:13,960 --> 00:13:17,191
Dr Ogden had to
oversee the transport of a liver to Baltimore.

189
00:13:17,280 --> 00:13:20,795
A liver? Where'd he get this one from?
An alcoholic at a corner bar?

190
00:13:20,880 --> 00:13:23,269
We've dealt with Biotech for years.

191
00:13:23,360 --> 00:13:26,352
- There's no such company.
- That's not possible.

192
00:13:26,440 --> 00:13:28,431
I think Ogden is in on the whole thing.

193
00:13:28,520 --> 00:13:32,798
A biomedical payola. Buys third-rate parts
in exchange for a condo in St Croix.

194
00:13:32,880 --> 00:13:36,589
Dr Ogders a very good man.
I know there are problems in his past, but...

195
00:13:36,680 --> 00:13:40,878
You mean there are skeletons in his closet?
I can't wait to see this guy's record.

196
00:13:40,960 --> 00:13:45,636
Alexandra, is there any way to tell if a patient
at Washington General received a graft

197
00:13:45,720 --> 00:13:47,790
from the same donor as Amy Cullen?

198
00:13:47,880 --> 00:13:53,591
Only the tissue lab knows for sure,
but after you left, I was curious, and...

199
00:13:53,680 --> 00:13:55,432
Please.

200
00:13:55,520 --> 00:14:00,071
It's already too late for Amy,
but it might not be for someone else.

201
00:14:03,600 --> 00:14:07,673
A woman named Kelly Demarco.
It was a car accident.

202
00:14:07,760 --> 00:14:12,276
This is Booth. I need a phone and address
for a Kelly Demarco in the Potomac area.

203
00:14:12,360 --> 00:14:16,876
Two grafts, same day as Amy.
Both grafts came from Biotech.

204
00:14:17,520 --> 00:14:20,239
When? Are you sure?

205
00:14:20,320 --> 00:14:22,231
- What is it?
- Thanks.

206
00:14:22,320 --> 00:14:24,356
Kelly Demarco, she's dead.

207
00:14:24,440 --> 00:14:26,271
Oh, my God.

208
00:14:26,360 --> 00:14:32,276
We need to know for sure if she had the same
kind of cancer. We have to exhume her.

209
00:14:37,400 --> 00:14:41,473
Kelly Demarco, age 32,
dead of lung cancer two months ago.

210
00:14:41,560 --> 00:14:46,475
Take a biopsy of this ulnograph and
compare it with the sample from Amy's leg.

211
00:14:46,560 --> 00:14:51,031
I spoke to Demarco's husband. She had
the accident, she had all the operations.

212
00:14:51,120 --> 00:14:55,432
She never smoked in her life,
only to die of lung cancer eight months ago.

213
00:14:55,520 --> 00:14:57,636
When your number's up, I guess, right?

214
00:14:57,720 --> 00:15:03,113
I never understood that saying. Numbers and
equations are quantitative and predictable.

215
00:15:03,200 --> 00:15:05,998
Everyone knows when a number's up.

216
00:15:06,080 --> 00:15:09,072
- How do you listen to this?
- I find intelligence soothing.

217
00:15:09,160 --> 00:15:11,993
It's amazing how quickly this spread.

218
00:15:12,080 --> 00:15:17,598
The graft went into her body. Within weeks,
the cancer cells metastasised to her lungs.

219
00:15:17,680 --> 00:15:22,435
- By then, the disease was unstoppable.
- Same bones, same donor, same disease.

220
00:15:22,520 --> 00:15:25,114
I got three agents searching for Biotech.

221
00:15:25,200 --> 00:15:28,556
All we have is this email address
assigned to a fictitious name.

222
00:15:28,640 --> 00:15:33,509
Let's just say that Ogden
and this, uh, fake tissue lab are in cahoots.

223
00:15:33,600 --> 00:15:35,989
How many other bones
could be from this donor?

224
00:15:36,080 --> 00:15:39,152
There are 206 bones
in the human body, Agent Booth.

225
00:15:39,240 --> 00:15:41,754
Of those, any number of them are graftable.

226
00:15:41,840 --> 00:15:44,434
Hundreds of people could still be out there

227
00:15:44,520 --> 00:15:47,353
with cancer time bombs in them
and not even realise it?

228
00:15:47,440 --> 00:15:50,079
We need to call every hospital
in the DC area.

229
00:15:50,160 --> 00:15:53,789
If they acquired Biotech grafts
at the same time as Amy,

230
00:15:53,880 --> 00:15:56,917
those recipients
need to be tracked down and tested.

231
00:15:57,000 --> 00:16:02,233
Fine. If you're right, then the Bureau
can officially designate this a serial killing.

232
00:16:02,320 --> 00:16:06,518
Agent Booth,
the records you've been waiting for.

233
00:16:08,000 --> 00:16:11,470
Oh, look at this.
Alexandra Combs, she wasrt lying.

234
00:16:11,560 --> 00:16:14,154
Background check turns up
that Ogden was fired

235
00:16:14,240 --> 00:16:16,834
- from a private hospital in Denver.
- Reason?

236
00:16:16,920 --> 00:16:20,515
Accepting a bribe
for bumping someone up in the donor lists.

237
00:16:20,600 --> 00:16:22,830
This guy is dirty.

238
00:16:23,680 --> 00:16:26,990
Look, what I did in Denver was wrong,
but I did it for good reason.

239
00:16:27,080 --> 00:16:29,310
To line your pockets.

240
00:16:29,400 --> 00:16:32,073
The money went to keep
a struggling clinic afloat.

241
00:16:32,160 --> 00:16:35,152
Besides, it came from a family
that could afford it.

242
00:16:35,240 --> 00:16:38,038
So taking advantage of wealthy people is OK?

243
00:16:38,120 --> 00:16:43,797
I'm not proud of that. Taking that bribe
doesn't mean I had anything to do with this.

244
00:16:43,880 --> 00:16:46,678
Tell us about your relationship with Biotech.

245
00:16:46,760 --> 00:16:49,354
The same I have with every company,
a virtual one.

246
00:16:49,440 --> 00:16:52,318
Emails, online financial transactions.

247
00:16:52,400 --> 00:16:56,518
My assistant sends out a countrywide search
for the organ or bone that we need.

248
00:16:56,600 --> 00:16:58,318
They respond back and we bid.

249
00:16:58,400 --> 00:17:02,029
If we can reach an agreement,
then the part is transported for surgery.

250
00:17:02,120 --> 00:17:06,432
- And in Amy Cullers case?
- Same protocol. I bid, I bought, I received.

251
00:17:06,520 --> 00:17:11,036
No conversations. We're not required
to check out suppliers each time we order.

252
00:17:11,120 --> 00:17:13,509
I'll contact every bank you do business with.

253
00:17:13,600 --> 00:17:17,593
If I find one deposit that's suspicious,
you know what? You're mine.

254
00:17:17,680 --> 00:17:22,231
I swear to you I'm not involved in this.
I haven't hurt anybody.

255
00:17:24,960 --> 00:17:28,669
- <i>(Amy)</i> Your work is awesome.
- <i>(Angela)</i> Thanks.

256
00:17:28,760 --> 00:17:31,797
There's so much going on,
you know, so much to feel,

257
00:17:31,880 --> 00:17:35,156
I don't know if I'll ever
be able to do something like this.

258
00:17:35,240 --> 00:17:38,835
You will. Just give it time.

259
00:17:38,920 --> 00:17:42,071
Well, I may not have a lot of that.

260
00:17:42,160 --> 00:17:46,551
Your paintings and your sculpture,
they're alive, you know?

261
00:17:46,640 --> 00:17:50,792
It's like... you're showing me
how you felt when you painted them,

262
00:17:50,880 --> 00:17:53,189
what you've experienced.

263
00:17:53,280 --> 00:17:56,317
I can't paint what I don't know.

264
00:17:56,400 --> 00:17:58,709
You've been through more than most people.

265
00:17:58,800 --> 00:18:01,473
You mean dying?

266
00:18:01,560 --> 00:18:03,471
It's not enough.

267
00:18:03,560 --> 00:18:06,279
I really think it's best for you to stay positive.

268
00:18:06,360 --> 00:18:11,070
- Keep doing things, you mean?
- With your art? Yeah. Absolutely.

269
00:18:11,920 --> 00:18:13,956
What about guys?

270
00:18:14,040 --> 00:18:19,319
Ah, well. That totally goes without saying.
What's his name?

271
00:18:19,400 --> 00:18:22,870
Aaron. His family
just moved here from Maine.

272
00:18:22,960 --> 00:18:24,951
- Is he cute?
- He's so cute.

273
00:18:25,040 --> 00:18:29,670
- Did you ask him out?
- No. He asked me, but I don't know. I said no.

274
00:18:29,760 --> 00:18:31,955
Why?

275
00:18:38,000 --> 00:18:42,471
Look, you haven't asked my advice,
so I'm just gonna give it to you, OK?

276
00:18:42,560 --> 00:18:44,357
Just have fun.

277
00:18:44,440 --> 00:18:49,389
You know, every once in a while,
you might meet somebody who's won'th it.

278
00:18:49,480 --> 00:18:51,914
What if he's not?

279
00:18:52,000 --> 00:18:55,879
Then you've got
something else to paint about.

280
00:19:03,280 --> 00:19:07,990
Bureau's canvassed every hospital
in the area. Four have been using Biotech.

281
00:19:08,080 --> 00:19:10,674
Three recipients have lung cancer.

282
00:19:10,760 --> 00:19:14,833
This one died of lung cancer three months
ago. I'm checking on a burial site.

283
00:19:14,920 --> 00:19:18,595
That makes 13, including Amy
and the Demarco woman.

284
00:19:18,680 --> 00:19:22,992
- Probably all from the same donor.
- We're waiting on Bethesda Naval Hospital.

285
00:19:23,080 --> 00:19:26,629
- Can you ID these people?
- Got names and addresses on all of them.

286
00:19:26,720 --> 00:19:31,714
I've already contacted Washington General
to set up a biopsy testing facility.

287
00:19:31,800 --> 00:19:36,476
Man. How did one dead guy
do so much damage?

288
00:19:36,560 --> 00:19:39,233
- That's a good idea.
- What idea?

289
00:19:39,320 --> 00:19:43,677
Identify the donor and we might be able
to find out how Biotech got his bones.

290
00:19:43,760 --> 00:19:49,153
Got it. Second decedent is Ronald Lupo.
I found him at a cemetery in Lynchburg.

291
00:19:49,240 --> 00:19:50,593
- Virginia?
- Yeah. Why?

292
00:19:50,680 --> 00:19:54,992
This fraud just crossed state lines
and became a legitimate case for the FBI.

293
00:19:55,080 --> 00:19:59,039
Looks like I don't have to use
my sick days any more, huh?

294
00:20:02,080 --> 00:20:03,479
How many?

295
00:20:03,560 --> 00:20:05,232
- Sick or dead?
- Dead.

296
00:20:05,320 --> 00:20:09,996
Two... that we know of, but that
makes it a multiple-homicide case.

297
00:20:10,080 --> 00:20:13,993
Since it's not isolated
and the recipients are in multiple states...

298
00:20:14,080 --> 00:20:18,153
- This falls under FBI jurisdiction.
- Yes, sir.

299
00:20:18,240 --> 00:20:21,038
I should kick your ass.

300
00:20:21,120 --> 00:20:22,439
Yeah.

301
00:20:23,960 --> 00:20:27,873
What'd you do?
Take sick time to work on this?

302
00:20:27,960 --> 00:20:30,190
Yeah. Migraine.

303
00:20:33,720 --> 00:20:35,711
Thanks, Booth.

304
00:20:37,320 --> 00:20:40,676
Catch the son of a bitch
that did this to my daughter.

305
00:20:40,760 --> 00:20:43,354
That's absolutely my intention, sir.

306
00:20:47,800 --> 00:20:52,828
♪ <i>Where is the world</i>

307
00:20:52,920 --> 00:20:58,392
♪ <i>That we love to know?</i>

308
00:21:00,880 --> 00:21:05,590
♪ <i>And where'd the love</i>

309
00:21:05,680 --> 00:21:11,676
♪ <i>That we shared go?</i>

310
00:21:13,480 --> 00:21:17,473
♪ <i>Can you be the one?</i>

311
00:21:19,880 --> 00:21:24,032
♪ <i>Can you see the sun</i>

312
00:21:24,120 --> 00:21:27,715
♪ <i>With me, yeah?</i>

313
00:21:36,560 --> 00:21:37,629
Results?

314
00:21:37,720 --> 00:21:40,518
There are three other
early signs of cancer cells.

315
00:21:40,600 --> 00:21:46,869
Aggressive chemo and radiation treatments
should be able to slow it down.

316
00:21:46,960 --> 00:21:49,952
Admiring your handiwork, Doctor?

317
00:21:52,720 --> 00:21:54,676
I'm sorry.

318
00:21:56,000 --> 00:21:57,956
- Amy.
- Let me.

319
00:21:58,040 --> 00:21:59,871
Easy.

320
00:22:00,480 --> 00:22:02,675
Hey.

321
00:22:02,760 --> 00:22:04,716
You all right?

322
00:22:04,800 --> 00:22:07,633
Did these people get bones
from the same donor I did?

323
00:22:07,720 --> 00:22:09,358
<i>(Bones)</i> Uh-huh.

324
00:22:09,440 --> 00:22:12,398
- Do they all have cancer?
- No, not all of them.

325
00:22:12,480 --> 00:22:16,359
But the sooner the ones
who are infected know, the better.

326
00:22:16,440 --> 00:22:20,718
Who would do that? If they knew they were
sick, why make other people sick, too?

327
00:22:20,800 --> 00:22:26,318
I don't know. It's terrible.
But that's what we're trying to figure out.

328
00:22:26,400 --> 00:22:29,949
So, if you take the bad grafts out,

329
00:22:30,040 --> 00:22:32,110
will they be OK?

330
00:22:32,200 --> 00:22:37,718
- Some of them.
- But... not me.

331
00:22:40,200 --> 00:22:42,191
No.

332
00:22:43,560 --> 00:22:46,438
- I want this out of me.
- You're not strong enough.

333
00:22:46,520 --> 00:22:50,069
- Get them to take it out.
- Amy, you have to understand.

334
00:22:50,160 --> 00:22:53,311
- All of these people...
- I don't care.

335
00:22:54,960 --> 00:22:57,235
You're saving their lives.

336
00:23:10,000 --> 00:23:13,390
We've traced these grafts to the donor
and still know nothing.

337
00:23:13,480 --> 00:23:18,713
Not exactly nothing. Zack, look at the slope
of the sciatic notch in the pelvis.

338
00:23:18,800 --> 00:23:23,430
- And the nonelevated auricular surface.
- He was definitely male.

339
00:23:23,520 --> 00:23:26,956
The osteon count in the femoral joint
confirms the donor was over 60.

340
00:23:27,040 --> 00:23:30,794
It's a solid start, but we need a lot more.

341
00:23:30,880 --> 00:23:35,795
Osteophytosis with narrowing
of intervertebral spaces

342
00:23:35,880 --> 00:23:38,872
indicates consistent heavy lifting.

343
00:23:38,960 --> 00:23:43,715
- Construction worker?
- It's hard to say. Definitely a burly type.

344
00:23:43,800 --> 00:23:46,678
If we keep guessing
about what he was like on the inside,

345
00:23:46,760 --> 00:23:51,629
then Angela can hypothesise
about his appearance, size, weight.

346
00:23:51,720 --> 00:23:53,517
I'm on it.

347
00:23:55,120 --> 00:23:57,588
I scanned in the x-rays of the graft recipients

348
00:23:57,680 --> 00:24:00,240
as well as the pieces
from the exhumed bodies.

349
00:24:00,320 --> 00:24:02,629
OK. Now what? Connect the dots?

350
00:24:02,720 --> 00:24:07,840
- More like connect the body parts.
- I think of it as sculpting from the inside out.

351
00:24:07,920 --> 00:24:12,118
The more I know about our donor,
the better I can guess what he looked like.

352
00:24:12,200 --> 00:24:17,320
The fragments originated from nine sites on
the donor's body. If we connect the grafts...

353
00:24:18,360 --> 00:24:22,990
Now input all of the anatomical factors
and core anomalies.

354
00:24:24,760 --> 00:24:28,230
<i>(Angela)</i> Guys, meet donor X.

355
00:24:28,320 --> 00:24:31,357
The man who caused all this pain.

356
00:24:31,440 --> 00:24:34,079
<i>(Bones)</i> So that's our serial killer.

357
00:24:34,160 --> 00:24:37,630
He had no idea how much damage
he'd cause. Can we track him down?

358
00:24:37,720 --> 00:24:40,109
- Hodgins?
- Maybe. With LIBS.

359
00:24:40,200 --> 00:24:43,272
- Who's Libs?
- Laser-induced breakdown spectroscopy.

360
00:24:43,360 --> 00:24:47,148
- It'll give us an elemental analysis.
- Angela told us what he looked like.

361
00:24:47,240 --> 00:24:49,629
Now Hodgins can tell us where he lived.

362
00:24:49,720 --> 00:24:52,075
Well, we'll find him.

363
00:24:52,960 --> 00:24:55,918
We have to.

364
00:25:11,680 --> 00:25:15,992
Strontium isotope levels suggest donor X
lived the last 20 years on the East Coast.

365
00:25:16,080 --> 00:25:19,038
Extremely low levels of fluoride
in the cancellous bone.

366
00:25:19,120 --> 00:25:24,399
Unusual. Most tap water is fluoridated, except
for parts of the Appalachian Mountains.

367
00:25:24,480 --> 00:25:28,075
A few of the Hatfields
and McCoys still have no teeth.

368
00:25:28,160 --> 00:25:31,869
So he's from Tennessee,
West Virginia, or North Carolina.

369
00:25:31,960 --> 00:25:34,235
Oh, great. That narrows it down.

370
00:25:34,320 --> 00:25:38,598
High level of C8.
That's a key ingredient of Teflon.

371
00:25:38,680 --> 00:25:42,070
There's a Teflon
plant in Parkersburg, West Virginia.

372
00:25:42,160 --> 00:25:45,596
And minuscule traces of nuclear subparticles.

373
00:25:45,680 --> 00:25:48,956
Wasrt there a problem
at Brant's Cliff power facility?

374
00:25:49,040 --> 00:25:53,511
Just a little one. Employees were growing
a second head. Can you say cover-up?

375
00:25:53,600 --> 00:25:56,319
- OK, where's Brant's Cliff?
- West Virginia also.

376
00:25:56,400 --> 00:25:59,517
OK, fine. So we're trying to
ID a guy who's 65 years of age,

377
00:25:59,600 --> 00:26:05,232
roughly 200 pounds, lives in West Virginia,
died of lung cancer within the last year.

378
00:26:08,800 --> 00:26:12,395
There are three West Virginia donors
we could be talking about.

379
00:26:12,480 --> 00:26:15,199
- Lester Blake, Blair Simmons...
- <i>(car horn)</i>

380
00:26:15,280 --> 00:26:18,829
Hey, lady! Watch where you're driving!

381
00:26:18,920 --> 00:26:21,753
I'd rather not be a donor myself.

382
00:26:21,840 --> 00:26:26,755
Blair Simmons out of Dailey
and William Hastings out of Beards Fork.

383
00:26:26,840 --> 00:26:29,434
All three men
died of mesothelioma last August.

384
00:26:29,520 --> 00:26:31,829
We'll be in Beards Fork within about an hour.

385
00:26:31,920 --> 00:26:35,799
- Are Zack and Hodgins are on the other two?
- This is Brennan.

386
00:26:35,880 --> 00:26:39,509
I'm at Lester Blake's exhumation.
I've examined the remains.

387
00:26:40,520 --> 00:26:41,999
This is Booth.

388
00:26:42,080 --> 00:26:44,355
- Blair Simmons isn't dead.
- What?

389
00:26:44,440 --> 00:26:47,955
- He's frozen in a cryogenics lab.
- What do you mean, frozen?

390
00:26:48,040 --> 00:26:50,759
Like a supermarket turkey.
Not a scratch on him.

391
00:26:50,840 --> 00:26:53,718
And he's wedged
between Walt Disney and Ted Williams.

392
00:26:53,800 --> 00:26:57,759
No sign of tampering. His casket
hasn't been opened since his burial.

393
00:26:57,840 --> 00:27:02,118
- So if Blake isn't our donor...
- So if Simmons isn't our donor...

394
00:27:02,200 --> 00:27:05,192
Mrs Hastings,
what did your husband do for a living?

395
00:27:05,280 --> 00:27:11,230
This and that. Bill worked in construction
for a time, did the night shift at Brant's Cliff.

396
00:27:11,320 --> 00:27:14,278
- Opened a roofing business a few years back.
- Roofing?

397
00:27:14,360 --> 00:27:19,036
- Shingling and fireproofing and such.
- So he handled asbestos?

398
00:27:19,120 --> 00:27:22,829
Doctors say that's what finally got him.
But why are y'all so curious?

399
00:27:22,920 --> 00:27:28,438
He did time for petty theft and fraud. You lost
your home, cars. He left you with nothing.

400
00:27:28,520 --> 00:27:32,229
Ah, Bill Hastings was an old fool
who deserved what came to him.

401
00:27:32,320 --> 00:27:36,279
You needed money. Did anyone ask you
about selling his parts after he died?

402
00:27:36,360 --> 00:27:39,318
Pardon? I'm afraid I don't follow.

403
00:27:40,240 --> 00:27:45,189
Well, his family has a cemetery plot
in Kincaid, yet you cremated him.

404
00:27:45,280 --> 00:27:47,999
Are you hiding something?

405
00:27:51,040 --> 00:27:54,271
The guy at the funeral home
said it was cheaper.

406
00:27:54,360 --> 00:27:58,353
- We couldn't afford a proper burial.
- What funeral home?

407
00:27:58,440 --> 00:28:01,796
- It was called Martin, I think.
- Where are the ashes?

408
00:28:01,880 --> 00:28:04,474
- Out back in the yard.
- Do you mind if we take a sample?

409
00:28:04,560 --> 00:28:08,758
I sure as hell do.
I don't like what y'all are accusing me of.

410
00:28:08,840 --> 00:28:12,719
- We'll just come back with a warrant.
- You'd better bring you some dogs.

411
00:28:12,800 --> 00:28:16,395
Bring those trigger-happy agents too.
This conversation is over.

412
00:28:16,480 --> 00:28:18,994
Come on, Bones. Let's go. Have a nice day.

413
00:28:23,720 --> 00:28:27,110
She insists he wasrt the donor.
The evidence is overwhelming.

414
00:28:27,200 --> 00:28:30,670
If I had a soil sample,
there are bone fragments still intact

415
00:28:30,760 --> 00:28:32,716
that we can identify him with.

416
00:28:32,800 --> 00:28:37,430
- Was there an insurance policy in place?
- None. More reasons to sell the illegal grafts.

417
00:28:37,520 --> 00:28:40,512
But the funeral home
had to be in cahoots with her.

418
00:28:40,600 --> 00:28:43,831
So all we have to do is connect
the widow to the funeral home.

419
00:28:43,920 --> 00:28:46,992
- Then the home to Biotech.
- Mr Cullen.

420
00:28:47,080 --> 00:28:49,469
We need to speak to you and Amy's mother.

421
00:28:49,560 --> 00:28:52,950
We'll go. Come on, Bones.

422
00:28:53,040 --> 00:28:56,510
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"The Dumbing Down of Love"</i>
<i>by Frou Frou)</i>

423
00:28:59,120 --> 00:29:02,795
♪ <i>Well-painted passion</i>

424
00:29:03,680 --> 00:29:06,114
♪ <i>You rightly suspect</i>

425
00:29:06,200 --> 00:29:10,239
She's telling them the treatment didn't work.

426
00:29:10,320 --> 00:29:12,629
There's nothing else they can do.

427
00:29:12,720 --> 00:29:15,473
♪ <i>Whichever way you fall</i>

428
00:29:16,480 --> 00:29:18,675
I hate seeing them so sad.

429
00:29:18,760 --> 00:29:22,753
♪ <i>And if I tell you</i>

430
00:29:22,840 --> 00:29:27,550
♪ <i>Lover alone without love</i>

431
00:29:27,640 --> 00:29:31,633
♪ <i>And what will happen?</i>

432
00:29:31,720 --> 00:29:36,396
♪ <i>Lover alone without love</i>

433
00:29:36,480 --> 00:29:40,519
♪ <i>Will you listen?</i>

434
00:29:40,600 --> 00:29:45,799
♪ <i>Lover alone without love</i>

435
00:29:48,920 --> 00:29:52,356
Bones. Bones, I know
that you find dead people intriguing,

436
00:29:52,440 --> 00:29:55,557
butjust try to put on your sad face.

437
00:29:56,480 --> 00:29:58,391
<i>(Booth clears his throat)</i>

438
00:30:04,360 --> 00:30:07,432
- I'm in the middle of a service.
- This'll only take a minute.

439
00:30:07,520 --> 00:30:10,159
Mr... Jessup, he ain't going nowhere.

440
00:30:10,240 --> 00:30:13,118
- What is this about, exactly?
- William Hastings.

441
00:30:13,200 --> 00:30:17,034
- Is he someone you've lost?
- More like somebody we found.

442
00:30:17,120 --> 00:30:19,350
He passed away a year ago -
you cremated him,

443
00:30:19,440 --> 00:30:23,353
but somehow his bones were illegally
harvested prior to the procedure.

444
00:30:23,440 --> 00:30:25,271
- Not here.
- What do you mean?

445
00:30:25,360 --> 00:30:28,193
This is my mortuary.
I've been in business a decade.

446
00:30:28,280 --> 00:30:32,671
I have no recollection
whatsoever of Mr Hastings.

447
00:30:32,760 --> 00:30:35,399
His wife mentioned this place specifically.

448
00:30:35,480 --> 00:30:39,234
- The bereaved are often confused.
- In this case, I don't think so.

449
00:30:39,320 --> 00:30:44,872
- <i>We</i> don't think so.
- Excuse me. I have mourners waiting.

450
00:30:44,960 --> 00:30:48,236
Maybe you can double-check
your records and get back to me.

451
00:30:48,320 --> 00:30:54,634
I would, but my records are impeccable.
There's nothing to double-check.

452
00:30:54,720 --> 00:30:57,996
- That was quick.
- I need to get those ashes from her yard.

453
00:30:58,080 --> 00:30:59,798
I'll get the warrant.

454
00:30:59,880 --> 00:31:02,633
Don't forget the dogs
and the gun-toting agents.

455
00:31:02,720 --> 00:31:04,870
Trust me, I won't forget that.

456
00:31:09,480 --> 00:31:11,152
I looked it up on the internet.

457
00:31:11,240 --> 00:31:14,949
You can get $10,000 for grafts
on the black market these days.

458
00:31:15,040 --> 00:31:19,238
- Ten grand? Mine are won'th more than that.
- What makes you so special?

459
00:31:19,320 --> 00:31:21,788
Three glasses of milk a day,
I work out, I eat right.

460
00:31:21,880 --> 00:31:25,668
X-ray shows a high concentration
of calcium carbonate.

461
00:31:25,760 --> 00:31:31,835
That's a revelation. Is there anything we can
link to William Hastings' medical records?

462
00:31:31,920 --> 00:31:35,629
The cremains are consistent
to those of William Hastings.

463
00:31:35,720 --> 00:31:39,633
I keep asking, if the widow is guilty,
why keep the remains so close to home?

464
00:31:39,720 --> 00:31:42,757
- What if she didn't know about it?
- She hated the guy.

465
00:31:42,840 --> 00:31:46,549
My guess is she has 10 G's
stuffed in her mattress back in trailerville.

466
00:31:46,640 --> 00:31:50,474
No. I mean it. There are no
unusual bank records, no deposits.

467
00:31:50,560 --> 00:31:53,791
What if they took the grafts
and she was none the wiser?

468
00:31:53,880 --> 00:31:55,757
Man, is she gonna be pissed.

469
00:31:55,840 --> 00:32:00,914
If it's not the widow Hastings, I'm doubling
down on the mortician. Everyone in? You in?

470
00:32:11,440 --> 00:32:13,715
Thank you. Oh, jeez.

471
00:32:13,800 --> 00:32:16,473
This body's being prepped.
What do you want?

472
00:32:16,560 --> 00:32:19,711
We want to know
where you harvested Mr Hastings' body.

473
00:32:19,800 --> 00:32:23,998
- I told you I don't know who Hastings is.
- Well, we think you're lying.

474
00:32:24,080 --> 00:32:27,072
We think you're selling bone grafts illegally.

475
00:32:27,160 --> 00:32:30,038
Your accusations are outlandish.
Call my lawyer.

476
00:32:30,120 --> 00:32:34,511
Yeah? Well, we have a warrant here
to look around a little.

477
00:32:37,880 --> 00:32:40,348
What's this place?

478
00:32:40,440 --> 00:32:45,468
- Casket showroom. They're having a sale.
- It looks like a sick department store.

479
00:32:45,560 --> 00:32:48,632
Nobody would be cutting anybody up
in this place. Let's go.

480
00:32:48,720 --> 00:32:50,995
Whoa. Wait.

481
00:32:51,080 --> 00:32:55,119
- Over there.
- What? It's a water line. What's the big deal?

482
00:32:55,200 --> 00:32:58,158
<i>(Bones)</i> The floor slopes
toward the centre of the room.

483
00:32:58,240 --> 00:33:04,475
This wasrt always used for a showroom.
I wonder what's under the carpet.

484
00:33:04,560 --> 00:33:07,233
If body work was done in here,

485
00:33:07,320 --> 00:33:10,437
they'd need a drain.

486
00:33:10,520 --> 00:33:13,910
- You're kidding me. It's a drain?
- This is our sales office.

487
00:33:14,000 --> 00:33:18,755
There is nothing in here you need to see.
The only thing in this room is caskets.

488
00:33:18,840 --> 00:33:22,594
- I'm not so sure about that.
- No... You are making a mistake.

489
00:33:22,680 --> 00:33:24,671
Am I?

490
00:33:25,560 --> 00:33:28,393
- She's ruining my merchandise.
- How much is that one?

491
00:33:28,480 --> 00:33:30,994
- $7,000.
- Bones, watch the scuff marks.

492
00:33:31,080 --> 00:33:33,958
Mr Martin, this room
is designed to be washed clean.

493
00:33:34,040 --> 00:33:38,318
You've got drains in the floor. I think
this is where you did the bone harvesting.

494
00:33:38,400 --> 00:33:41,073
You thought we'd come back
so you moved everything.

495
00:33:41,160 --> 00:33:43,594
That's absurd. I did no such thing.

496
00:33:43,680 --> 00:33:46,353
You're an excellent house cleaner,

497
00:33:46,440 --> 00:33:51,594
but in the carpeting and tidying up,
you forgot about one thing.

498
00:33:55,360 --> 00:33:59,911
Bone dust.
You forgot about airborne particles.

499
00:34:02,800 --> 00:34:04,836
Today, Zack. I need something today.

500
00:34:04,920 --> 00:34:09,391
- Hey, don't harass my assistant.
- That's right. That's ourjob.

501
00:34:09,480 --> 00:34:14,759
I sifted dust particles then separated
the largest pieces to compare the osteons.

502
00:34:14,840 --> 00:34:19,914
- The particles came from human remains.
- William Hastings' remains?

503
00:34:20,000 --> 00:34:24,152
I am comparing particles to the biopsy
we excised from Kelly Demarco.

504
00:34:24,240 --> 00:34:26,037
Compare.

505
00:34:31,440 --> 00:34:33,590
So? Is it him?

506
00:34:34,120 --> 00:34:37,157
It's him. But... here's the kickster.

507
00:34:37,240 --> 00:34:39,595
"Kicker", Bones. "Here's the kicker."

508
00:34:39,680 --> 00:34:43,912
- There's bone dust from seven other bodies.
- Seven?

509
00:34:44,000 --> 00:34:47,595
Cutting periosteum for grafting purposes
takes medical training.

510
00:34:47,680 --> 00:34:53,198
- These bone grafts are expertly harvested.
- So we're looking for someone with training.

511
00:34:53,280 --> 00:34:56,955
Martin is a mortician, not a doctor.
Let's say he's running a chop shop.

512
00:34:57,040 --> 00:35:00,396
Let's say he was selling
illegal parts to tissue labs.

513
00:35:00,480 --> 00:35:05,998
- Who was actually doing the cutting?
- Who was selling to hospitals as Biotech?

514
00:35:09,840 --> 00:35:13,913
How much money have you made
over the years doing this, Nick? Hm?

515
00:35:14,000 --> 00:35:18,232
- Tens? Hundreds of thousands of dollars.
- I don't know what you're talking about.

516
00:35:18,320 --> 00:35:21,437
William Hastings
had an aggressive form of cancer.

517
00:35:21,520 --> 00:35:24,478
You made some pocket change off his grafts.

518
00:35:24,560 --> 00:35:28,519
Now people are sick. Two died.
You're looking at multiple counts of murder.

519
00:35:28,600 --> 00:35:31,512
- I didn't kill anybody.
- No, you didn't kill anybody.

520
00:35:31,600 --> 00:35:35,229
- They were dead. You were recycling.
- I didn't do anything wrong.

521
00:35:35,320 --> 00:35:37,276
- Do you have doctor training?
- No.

522
00:35:37,360 --> 00:35:40,158
- Spend any time in the service as a medic?
- No.

523
00:35:40,240 --> 00:35:44,392
Then who did the cutting of the grafts, huh?
Somebody knew what they were doing.

524
00:35:44,480 --> 00:35:46,869
Records show that around Hastings' death,

525
00:35:46,960 --> 00:35:49,952
you received dozens of calls
from disposable cells.

526
00:35:50,040 --> 00:35:54,511
Four different ones, huh?
What do you make of that?

527
00:35:54,600 --> 00:35:56,511
- I don't recall this.
- You know what?

528
00:35:56,600 --> 00:36:02,675
The dust we got from your showroom
matched Hastings and seven other bodies.

529
00:36:02,760 --> 00:36:05,558
- Who do you work with?
- I don't know what you mean.

530
00:36:05,640 --> 00:36:11,749
You do. You and your partners knew that
the bones were cancerous and you didn't...

531
00:36:11,840 --> 00:36:14,718
Who was it, huh?
Who the hell did this to my daughter?

532
00:36:14,800 --> 00:36:18,315
Sir! Sir! I got him. I got him, sir. Please.

533
00:36:19,440 --> 00:36:23,672
Bones, how long
is it gonna take you to...? Bones!

534
00:36:31,960 --> 00:36:34,918
Oh, Dr Brennan. You startled me.

535
00:36:35,000 --> 00:36:37,195
- Mind if I come in?
- Not at all.

536
00:36:37,280 --> 00:36:39,430
I was trying to keep things organised.

537
00:36:39,520 --> 00:36:42,910
What we do is so important,
we can't risk making any mistakes.

538
00:36:43,000 --> 00:36:46,197
Miss Combs, tell me,
what do you use these phones for?

539
00:36:46,280 --> 00:36:49,431
Recipients. We never know
when a donor organ will come in,

540
00:36:49,520 --> 00:36:52,717
so it's imperative
that they can be reached at all times.

541
00:36:52,800 --> 00:36:55,792
Ever use one yourself?

542
00:36:55,880 --> 00:36:59,190
- What can I do for you?
- Did you always want to work in a hospital?

543
00:36:59,280 --> 00:37:03,831
I mean, it's incredibly rewarding, I know,
but you ever want to study medicine?

544
00:37:03,920 --> 00:37:05,876
I did at one time, yes.

545
00:37:05,960 --> 00:37:08,872
How do you feel?
Have you been coughing at all?

546
00:37:08,960 --> 00:37:13,112
- Do you feel a tightness in your chest?
- I feel fine, actually.

547
00:37:13,200 --> 00:37:15,668
How often does Dr Ogden
write prescriptions?

548
00:37:15,760 --> 00:37:18,194
Rarely. As coordinator, he doesn't practise.

549
00:37:18,280 --> 00:37:23,274
Yet the pharmacy told the FBI he wrote you
a script for an expectorant for a cough.

550
00:37:23,360 --> 00:37:29,390
- There must be some mistake. He'd never...
- You wrote that yourself, didn't you?

551
00:37:29,480 --> 00:37:33,234
I know what you've been doing with Martin -
to Hastings and the others.

552
00:37:33,320 --> 00:37:38,917
If you'd finished medical school, you'd know.
Bone dust is very dangerous if inaled.

553
00:37:39,000 --> 00:37:42,037
When you were taking those grafts,
I doubt you wore a mask.

554
00:37:42,120 --> 00:37:44,998
You're sick, Miss Combs, and I...

555
00:37:45,080 --> 00:37:49,198
I don'tjust mean in a mentally disturbed way.

556
00:37:50,200 --> 00:37:52,919
- You can't prove anything.
- We're in a hospital.

557
00:37:53,000 --> 00:37:56,629
Why don't we
go get a chest x-ray and find out?

558
00:37:56,720 --> 00:38:01,999
- I'd like to read you your rights.
- Alexandra, what's going on?

559
00:38:03,200 --> 00:38:05,589
So the assistant fancied herself a doctor?

560
00:38:05,680 --> 00:38:10,879
Not a doctor exactly, but qualified enough
to extricate bone grafts from a cadaver.

561
00:38:10,960 --> 00:38:15,476
- And what about Biotech Tissue Labs?
- Once it was a legitimate company.

562
00:38:15,560 --> 00:38:21,908
Combs kept it alive on the web and funnelled
the money into her own bank account.

563
00:38:22,000 --> 00:38:25,117
- So where does that leave Amy?
- Same as where she started.

564
00:38:25,200 --> 00:38:28,909
Just with answers, that's all.

565
00:38:29,000 --> 00:38:31,878
Well, that is perfect.

566
00:38:31,960 --> 00:38:34,758
- Angela.
- That's OK. I got it.

567
00:38:40,760 --> 00:38:42,716
Hey.

568
00:38:42,920 --> 00:38:44,035
Hey.

569
00:38:44,120 --> 00:38:47,874
- You all right?
- Yeah.

570
00:38:48,880 --> 00:38:51,713
No. No, I'm not.

571
00:38:52,800 --> 00:38:55,712
Look, we can solve 100-year-old crimes.

572
00:38:55,800 --> 00:38:58,997
We can... we can track down serial killers

573
00:38:59,080 --> 00:39:03,995
and identify people
when nothing is left of them but sludge.

574
00:39:04,080 --> 00:39:08,232
So, why can't we help a 15-year-old girl?

575
00:39:09,640 --> 00:39:12,950
All she wants to do is fall in love...

576
00:39:14,040 --> 00:39:16,395
and visit the Louvre.

577
00:39:18,120 --> 00:39:19,997
You can do that.

578
00:39:20,080 --> 00:39:21,798
What do you mean?

579
00:39:21,880 --> 00:39:26,271
You made a whole guy
out of bone chips and lights.

580
00:39:26,360 --> 00:39:29,079
You can create the Louvre.

581
00:39:33,000 --> 00:39:37,516
What about love?
What do you have to say about love?

582
00:39:37,600 --> 00:39:40,592
It's overrated.

583
00:39:41,160 --> 00:39:43,116
Most of the time.

584
00:39:57,120 --> 00:39:59,315
OK.

585
00:39:59,400 --> 00:40:01,755
Now, tell me what you see.

586
00:40:01,840 --> 00:40:05,196
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Born" by Over the Rhine)</i>

587
00:40:08,040 --> 00:40:10,190
<i>(Amy)</i> Oh, wow! No way.

588
00:40:10,280 --> 00:40:13,989
Angela, this is unbelievable.

589
00:40:17,480 --> 00:40:20,870
- Welcome to the Louvre.
- I'm really there.

590
00:40:20,960 --> 00:40:24,191
- That's amazing.
- Is this your doing, Dr Brennan?

591
00:40:24,280 --> 00:40:27,397
No, sir. It's all Ms Montenegro.

592
00:40:27,480 --> 00:40:29,835
Thank you, Angela.

593
00:40:29,920 --> 00:40:31,956
You're welcome.

594
00:40:32,040 --> 00:40:34,554
So what do you think?

595
00:40:37,160 --> 00:40:41,278
I think it's like heaven.
I don't know what to say.

596
00:40:41,720 --> 00:40:44,598
Don't say anything. You don't have to.

597
00:40:44,680 --> 00:40:50,198
♪ <i>I was born to love</i>

598
00:40:50,280 --> 00:40:54,319
♪ <i>I'm gonna learn to love</i>

599
00:40:54,400 --> 00:41:01,397
♪ <i>Without fear</i>

600
00:41:28,520 --> 00:41:30,875
Visiontext Subtitles: Sarah Johnston

601
00:41:37,680 --> 00:41:39,033
What's that mean?

602
00:41:39,720 --> 00:41:41,711
ENGLISH SDH

