1
00:00:02,120 --> 00:00:04,953
♪ <i>Telling silly lies</i>

2
00:00:07,520 --> 00:00:13,516
♪ <i>Once in your life, you've got to come clean</i>

3
00:00:18,440 --> 00:00:24,834
♪ <i>Cos I've seen them all,</i>
<i>from beggars to queens</i>

4
00:00:29,880 --> 00:00:35,193
♪ <i>Once in your life, you find out about others</i>

5
00:00:35,280 --> 00:00:40,877
♪ <i>There's nothing you do</i>
<i>that can make me retreat</i>

6
00:00:40,960 --> 00:00:45,431
♪ <i>And victims of love</i>
<i>put locks on your soul</i>

7
00:00:45,520 --> 00:00:48,512
- <i>(Goodman)</i> Temperance.
- Ohh!

8
00:00:48,600 --> 00:00:51,990
- I startled you?
- I was chatting with a friend online.

9
00:00:52,080 --> 00:00:56,358
I'm sorry. But we have
a new delivery, top priority.

10
00:01:03,800 --> 00:01:05,995
- Sounds like a good friend.
- Yes.

11
00:01:06,080 --> 00:01:11,518
It's fascinating how interest
and intimacy can be cultivated online.

12
00:01:11,600 --> 00:01:13,477
So you've never met this friend?

13
00:01:13,560 --> 00:01:16,154
I've done enough Googling
to schedule dinner.

14
00:01:16,240 --> 00:01:18,276
You said there was a delivery?

15
00:01:18,360 --> 00:01:22,797
- The bones washed up on Chesapeake Bay.
- He's been fish food for quite a while.

16
00:01:22,880 --> 00:01:26,316
- They ate through both tibiae.
- Evidence of bullet wounds.

17
00:01:26,400 --> 00:01:28,675
Which explains why he has all those holes.

18
00:01:28,760 --> 00:01:32,469
Looks as though
they werert made by a.32. Maybe a.38.

19
00:01:32,560 --> 00:01:36,473
- Heard you need a face.
- The FBI's pretty certain this is James Cugini.

20
00:01:36,560 --> 00:01:39,233
They're looking for evidence
to lead to the killer.

21
00:01:39,320 --> 00:01:41,595
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> Jimmy Cugini.
- <i>(Bones)</i> Who?

22
00:01:41,680 --> 00:01:45,832
A mob boss who disappeared six years ago
after his daughter's dance recital.

23
00:01:45,920 --> 00:01:48,036
Cement shoes. Pretty trite.

24
00:01:48,120 --> 00:01:51,430
Why mess with the classics?

25
00:01:52,080 --> 00:01:54,435
- They find any of the bullets?
- No.

26
00:01:54,520 --> 00:01:56,556
They really are quite good at this.

27
00:01:56,640 --> 00:01:59,871
Should we be involved in mob stuff?
They're really into killing.

28
00:01:59,960 --> 00:02:04,158
I can provide ajob description if you've
forgotten what we do here, Dr Hodgins.

29
00:02:04,240 --> 00:02:08,313
After you clean him up, Zack,
x-ray the bones for any bullet fragments.

30
00:02:08,400 --> 00:02:13,599
Be careful with the exit and entrance wounds.
I want to recover any markings the bullet left.

31
00:02:13,680 --> 00:02:16,353
I could have 'em ready about eight tonight.

32
00:02:16,440 --> 00:02:20,115
Can't work tonight. Tomorrow morning's fine.

33
00:02:20,200 --> 00:02:23,795
- You have a date tonight.
- It's not a date. It's a meal.

34
00:02:23,880 --> 00:02:26,474
- With a man?
- Did you meet him on that website?

35
00:02:26,560 --> 00:02:29,950
- You're dating online?
- It's a practical way

36
00:02:30,040 --> 00:02:34,158
of objectively examining a potential partner
without all the game playing.

37
00:02:34,240 --> 00:02:37,357
That comes later, if it works out.
Hi, I'm Angela.

38
00:02:37,440 --> 00:02:40,989
Special Agent Jamie Kenton. Hi.
Dr Brennan.

39
00:02:41,080 --> 00:02:43,230
Hey.

40
00:02:44,480 --> 00:02:46,118
You two know each other?

41
00:02:46,200 --> 00:02:49,272
I was at the Bureau
when Booth took his coffee cup.

42
00:02:49,360 --> 00:02:52,158
Apparently they're
the world's best FBI agents.

43
00:02:52,240 --> 00:02:57,155
He's on the Cugini case - one of the original
investigators. This is Brennars brain trust.

44
00:02:57,240 --> 00:03:00,949
- Your victim is over here.
- What if your date's a psycho?

45
00:03:01,040 --> 00:03:03,838
- Only about a billion people date online.
- I have.

46
00:03:03,920 --> 00:03:08,550
Whatever happened to seeing someone
across a crowded room, eyes meeting,

47
00:03:08,640 --> 00:03:11,074
that old black magic gets you in its spell?

48
00:03:11,160 --> 00:03:13,799
- There's no such thing as magic.
- There's magic.

49
00:03:13,880 --> 00:03:18,510
- Why are you here? Kentors handling this.
- We have some remains to look at.

50
00:03:18,600 --> 00:03:21,433
- <i>(Bones)</i> I'm looking at them.
- Not the Cugini case.

51
00:03:21,520 --> 00:03:24,114
Kenton will baby-sit him. These are fresh.

52
00:03:24,200 --> 00:03:26,668
<i>(Bones)</i> I was told that this took precedence.

53
00:03:26,760 --> 00:03:29,797
That was before we found
someone ripped apart by dogs.

54
00:03:30,120 --> 00:03:31,439
<i>(dogs barking)</i>

55
00:03:31,520 --> 00:03:35,399
90% of flesh is missing because of mutilation.

56
00:03:35,480 --> 00:03:39,712
And postmortem anthropophagi
caused by canine scavenging.

57
00:03:39,800 --> 00:03:41,358
Do they have to stay here?

58
00:03:41,440 --> 00:03:44,716
- We're waiting to see if you need them.
- No. Not now.

59
00:03:44,800 --> 00:03:48,998
- Ask him to save the excrement for Hodgins.
- Lucky Hodgins.

60
00:03:54,240 --> 00:03:56,595
- What about the eyes?
- Gone.

61
00:03:56,680 --> 00:03:58,796
- Gouged out?
- Yes.

62
00:03:58,880 --> 00:04:03,590
The scrapings in the orbital cavity
is much rougher than the knife scarring.

63
00:04:03,680 --> 00:04:07,798
- It was done with a different weapon.
- Son of a bitch.

64
00:04:07,880 --> 00:04:10,030
- You've seen this before?
- Yeah.

65
00:04:10,120 --> 00:04:13,237
Two years ago we found
a 17-year-old girl in a tool shed,

66
00:04:13,320 --> 00:04:15,959
bound, slashed, eyes gouged out.

67
00:04:16,040 --> 00:04:18,315
Nothing for her parents to identify.

68
00:04:18,400 --> 00:04:21,995
Suspect was Kevin Hollings,
but we couldn't get the hard evidence,

69
00:04:22,080 --> 00:04:24,310
so the DA refused to prosecute.

70
00:04:24,400 --> 00:04:27,312
He's twisted, Bones.

71
00:04:27,400 --> 00:04:30,756
- It's like a game to him.
- He used dogs before?

72
00:04:30,840 --> 00:04:34,230
No. He's making the killings more elaborate.
He's testing us.

73
00:04:34,320 --> 00:04:37,710
Until he gets caught.
Isn't that the expected pathology?

74
00:04:37,800 --> 00:04:39,028
Yeah.

75
00:04:39,120 --> 00:04:43,113
I can determine the kinds of weapons,
time of death. Hodgins might find...

76
00:04:43,200 --> 00:04:45,589
<i>(phone rings)</i>

77
00:04:47,680 --> 00:04:48,908
Brennan.

78
00:04:49,000 --> 00:04:51,560
Just working.

79
00:04:52,360 --> 00:04:54,476
Bag that.

80
00:04:55,560 --> 00:04:57,869
Yeah. Of course, I'm starving.

81
00:04:57,960 --> 00:05:00,474
7:30. OK. Yes.

82
00:05:00,560 --> 00:05:02,949
I'll meet you there. OK. Bye.

83
00:05:03,040 --> 00:05:06,510
My reservation just got pushed
so I have a few extra minutes.

84
00:05:06,600 --> 00:05:08,397
- Few extra minutes. Great.
- What?

85
00:05:08,480 --> 00:05:10,198
- Nothing.
- You disapprove?

86
00:05:10,280 --> 00:05:12,191
- I said "great".
- With attitude.

87
00:05:12,280 --> 00:05:14,794
Don't go overboard with the psychology.

88
00:05:14,880 --> 00:05:19,795
I am an adult, Booth. I see men. I go out
with them. On occasion, I sleep with them.

89
00:05:19,880 --> 00:05:22,553
You don't know
who this guy is that you're meeting.

90
00:05:22,640 --> 00:05:27,077
I trekked through Tibet avoiding the Chinese
army. I can handle meeting for dinner.

91
00:05:27,160 --> 00:05:30,948
Fine. You know what? You have fun
with Dick431 or whatever his handle is.

92
00:05:31,040 --> 00:05:33,679
- Yeah, I will. Thanks.
- Fine.

93
00:05:33,760 --> 00:05:35,716
Good.

94
00:05:39,520 --> 00:05:43,069
Victim is female, late teens to mid-20s.

95
00:05:43,160 --> 00:05:46,072
Knife marks on the bone.
Evidence of deep cuts.

96
00:05:46,160 --> 00:05:50,153
Probably to open up the flesh, make it...

97
00:05:50,800 --> 00:05:52,950
more appetising for the dogs.

98
00:05:55,320 --> 00:05:57,311
<i>(phone rings)</i>

99
00:05:58,640 --> 00:06:01,234
David. Hi.

100
00:06:02,560 --> 00:06:07,395
Yeah, I'm here.
Well, I guess I'm two doors down.

101
00:06:08,760 --> 00:06:13,311
No. I know.
The traffic on the beltway can be brutal. OK.

102
00:06:13,400 --> 00:06:15,436
Bye.

103
00:06:15,520 --> 00:06:17,750
<i>(gunshots)</i>

104
00:06:19,000 --> 00:06:22,356
<i>(man)</i> Get down! Are you all right?

105
00:06:58,640 --> 00:07:02,269
We need enlargements.
Did you examine the excrement?

106
00:07:02,360 --> 00:07:05,272
I'm doing the faecal flotation.
I don't say that a lot.

107
00:07:05,360 --> 00:07:10,115
- Check for fibres the FBI might've missed...
- You've already told him... twice.

108
00:07:10,200 --> 00:07:12,156
Are you sure you don't want a drink?

109
00:07:12,240 --> 00:07:15,437
It wouldn't be difficult
for someone to encode a data strip,

110
00:07:15,520 --> 00:07:19,957
implant it in an ID card with the correct
authentication data, and sneak in here.

111
00:07:20,040 --> 00:07:22,998
- It is possible.
- Are you two going to help or not?

112
00:07:23,080 --> 00:07:27,119
Booth's pissed that you came here.
He had more questions for you at the scene.

113
00:07:27,200 --> 00:07:31,910
He doesn't want to come here because he
has to park in the structure. I need her face.

114
00:07:32,000 --> 00:07:35,959
- These bullet wounds haven't been cleaned.
- I worked on them for hours.

115
00:07:36,040 --> 00:07:39,157
Then that wasrt long enough, was it?

116
00:07:40,240 --> 00:07:42,754
I'm sorry. But...

117
00:07:44,360 --> 00:07:48,194
You take a sinus probe, you put
a little cotton swab on the end of it.

118
00:07:48,280 --> 00:07:52,910
You dip it in water and you dab it
inside the wound until it's clean.

119
00:07:53,000 --> 00:07:57,152
- The Sistine Chapel took 13 years to clean.
- I didn't think we had that much time.

120
00:07:57,240 --> 00:08:01,199
- <i>(Booth)</i> What are you doing?
- Working. Why does everyone find that odd?

121
00:08:01,280 --> 00:08:04,397
Because maybe an hour ago
someone tried to kill you.

122
00:08:04,480 --> 00:08:07,119
It's not a good idea
for you to work these cases.

123
00:08:07,200 --> 00:08:08,713
This is what I do.

124
00:08:08,800 --> 00:08:12,349
Whoever did this wants to make sure
you don't finish your investigation.

125
00:08:12,440 --> 00:08:16,911
Hundreds of criminals want me to stop what
I do. Are you suggesting I give up my career?

126
00:08:17,000 --> 00:08:19,833
- Just be reasonable.
- Fine.

127
00:08:19,920 --> 00:08:23,151
Logic suggests the shooter
is involved in one of these cases,

128
00:08:23,240 --> 00:08:25,595
so I should find out who killed them.

129
00:08:25,680 --> 00:08:29,753
- Did Forensics recover the bullets?
- Ballistics is running tests on them.

130
00:08:29,840 --> 00:08:32,434
Did you pick up the suspect
in the womars murder?

131
00:08:32,520 --> 00:08:35,478
I don't want to spook him
until we have enough evidence.

132
00:08:35,560 --> 00:08:40,429
- Did you get a list of women missing age 18...
- 18 to 25, yes. They're on your server.

133
00:08:40,520 --> 00:08:44,433
- Everyone is doing theirjob.
- I'll see if any of them match the victim.

134
00:08:44,520 --> 00:08:48,593
What about the Romanos? Hodgins says
they were feuding with the Cuginis.

135
00:08:48,680 --> 00:08:52,673
Kenton is pulling the files on the case
and all mob activity six years ago.

136
00:08:52,760 --> 00:08:55,957
Bones, there is one other person
we have to look at. Your date.

137
00:08:56,040 --> 00:08:59,316
Well, I spoke with him, Booth.
He was in his car in traffic.

138
00:08:59,400 --> 00:09:01,595
And why would he want to kill me?

139
00:09:01,680 --> 00:09:04,752
Why would somebody
want to kill your victim over there?

140
00:09:04,840 --> 00:09:09,470
I know it's hard to admit that you might be
wrong, but I don't care about your feelings.

141
00:09:09,560 --> 00:09:12,632
I'm concerned with your life.
They're bringing your date in.

142
00:09:12,720 --> 00:09:14,392
- Grab your coat.
- I'm working.

143
00:09:14,480 --> 00:09:21,033
Bones, I'm not letting you out of my sight
until I find out who is trying to kill you.

144
00:09:24,240 --> 00:09:26,117
- Temperance.
- David.

145
00:09:26,200 --> 00:09:28,350
- Someone shot at you.
- Yeah.

146
00:09:28,440 --> 00:09:30,431
Oh, my God. What can I do?

147
00:09:30,520 --> 00:09:34,638
I'm Special Agent Seeley Booth.
I'll be asking the questions. Sit down.

148
00:09:34,720 --> 00:09:39,430
Sure. I didn't see anything. I saw all the cops,
but I had no idea it had to do with you.

149
00:09:39,520 --> 00:09:43,229
You're an investment banker,
good-Iooking, but you find women online.

150
00:09:43,320 --> 00:09:45,595
- Excuse me?
- Don't you find women at work?

151
00:09:45,680 --> 00:09:48,194
She was online. She's a great-Iooking doctor.

152
00:09:48,280 --> 00:09:53,308
- Your picture doesn't do you justice.
- Well, thank you. Yours either. I...

153
00:09:53,400 --> 00:09:57,029
- The resolution mustrt be very good online.
- Bones.

154
00:09:57,120 --> 00:09:58,997
- Oh, he's a Luddite.
- Hey.

155
00:09:59,080 --> 00:10:02,675
- Someone who's afraid of technology.
- I know what a Luddite is.

156
00:10:02,760 --> 00:10:05,399
So, you're saying
that you were stuck in traffic?

157
00:10:05,480 --> 00:10:08,074
What, you think I shot at her?

158
00:10:08,160 --> 00:10:11,994
I'm a fundraiser for the Brady Campaign
against gun violence.

159
00:10:12,080 --> 00:10:14,992
- Do you think I tried to kill you?
- He has to do this.

160
00:10:15,080 --> 00:10:18,197
- Yeah. So what time did you leave work?
- About 6:45.

161
00:10:18,280 --> 00:10:22,273
- Any witnesses?
- My assistant, the client that I was with.

162
00:10:22,360 --> 00:10:25,477
The valet at the parking garage.
Unless they're suspects.

163
00:10:25,560 --> 00:10:28,552
- We'll talk to everyone.
- Did you see the traffic report?

164
00:10:28,640 --> 00:10:30,710
He did.

165
00:10:32,520 --> 00:10:34,511
You did.

166
00:10:36,240 --> 00:10:41,314
- Do I have to get an attorney?
- Just stay close in case we need you.

167
00:10:41,400 --> 00:10:45,552
Yeah, sure. I mean, anything I can do to help.

168
00:10:46,240 --> 00:10:49,198
So, this whole online thing,
how long does it last?

169
00:10:49,280 --> 00:10:53,353
Because if it's just a way to... <i>(whistles)</i>
Hook up, I think it's pretty low.

170
00:10:53,440 --> 00:10:56,398
- My partner met his wife online.
- You're kidding.

171
00:10:56,480 --> 00:11:00,109
- No. They've been married five years.
- Doesrt mean it's not creepy.

172
00:11:00,200 --> 00:11:03,909
Did I miss something?
I don't want to get in the way between you...

173
00:11:04,000 --> 00:11:07,390
- Oh, no.
- No. God.

174
00:11:07,480 --> 00:11:09,516
- Maybe we could reschedule dinner.
- No.

175
00:11:09,600 --> 00:11:11,989
- Sure.
- Great.

176
00:11:12,080 --> 00:11:14,674
- Someone needs this room. Let's go.
- Yeah, sure.

177
00:11:14,760 --> 00:11:18,389
- Well, I'll email you. Stay safe.
- She will stay safe.

178
00:11:20,320 --> 00:11:23,357
- He's nice, don't you think?
- Yeah, he's nice...

179
00:11:23,440 --> 00:11:25,078
as a suspect. What?

180
00:11:25,160 --> 00:11:27,196
Hello?

181
00:11:32,920 --> 00:11:34,751
The victim is Penny Hamilton,

182
00:11:34,840 --> 00:11:39,277
19, a student at American who disappeared
walking back to her dorm.

183
00:11:39,360 --> 00:11:41,635
She was going to Haiti to work in a clinic.

184
00:11:41,720 --> 00:11:44,359
- Booth will think this is his fault.
- He knew her?

185
00:11:44,440 --> 00:11:48,672
The killer has done this before.
Booth couldn't get the evidence he needed.

186
00:11:48,760 --> 00:11:51,672
The guy promised Booth he never would.

187
00:11:51,760 --> 00:11:56,151
Where is Booth, anyway? I thought
he wasrt gonna let you out of his sight.

188
00:11:56,240 --> 00:12:02,190
I gave him the positive ID on Cugini.
He's calling it in to Kenton.

189
00:12:02,280 --> 00:12:06,751
So how do you like David? It's not often
you can interrogate a guy on a first date.

190
00:12:06,840 --> 00:12:12,073
I like him. Booth still doesn't approve,
but I told him to mind his own business.

191
00:12:12,160 --> 00:12:16,438
Booth is a big, strong, hot guy
who wants to save your life.

192
00:12:16,520 --> 00:12:21,958
You actually have a knight in shining
FBI body armour. So cut him some slack.

193
00:12:22,040 --> 00:12:25,749
Kenton heard the Romanos are pissed.
When they get pissed, they shoot.

194
00:12:25,840 --> 00:12:29,833
I have cleaned the bones, Dr Brennan.
You could eat off them.

195
00:12:29,920 --> 00:12:32,992
Is this her?

196
00:12:33,080 --> 00:12:35,514
Yeah.

197
00:12:44,920 --> 00:12:50,711
Nice work. You can see the markings left
on the bone where the bullet passed through.

198
00:12:50,800 --> 00:12:53,268
- I can?
- Yes.

199
00:12:53,360 --> 00:12:55,510
Here and here on the outer compact bone.

200
00:12:55,600 --> 00:13:00,754
- Could you recreate the complete imprint?
- I don't know if I have enough to work with.

201
00:13:00,840 --> 00:13:03,115
- What are you getting at?
- After discharge,

202
00:13:03,200 --> 00:13:06,954
every bullet has a distinct pattern
etched into it from the barrel.

203
00:13:07,040 --> 00:13:11,113
That same pattern would be etched
into the bone as it passes through.

204
00:13:11,200 --> 00:13:14,431
If we get the pattern,
we can reverse-engineer the bullet.

205
00:13:14,520 --> 00:13:17,239
Then you'd be able to tell
which weapon was used.

206
00:13:17,320 --> 00:13:20,312
- I have never heard of that.
- It's a theory I'm working on.

207
00:13:20,400 --> 00:13:24,632
- This would be a good time to test it.
- Great. Anything more about the girl?

208
00:13:24,720 --> 00:13:30,158
The knife marks were made by a nonserrated
blade consistent with a pocketknife like this.

209
00:13:30,240 --> 00:13:35,872
I found additional knife marks on C5,
indicating that the throat was slashed.

210
00:13:35,960 --> 00:13:39,555
- What about her eyes?
- The grooving doesn't match the knife.

211
00:13:39,640 --> 00:13:42,154
And Hodgins is playing with dog poop.

212
00:13:42,240 --> 00:13:46,472
Let's go. Kenton is putting together
everything on Cugini's disappearance.

213
00:13:46,560 --> 00:13:48,710
I'm probably more valuable here.

214
00:13:48,800 --> 00:13:52,679
No. You're more valuable alive.
I'm not leaving you alone. Come on.

215
00:13:52,760 --> 00:13:55,115
If it's so dangerous,
why are you leaving us?

216
00:13:55,200 --> 00:14:00,320
Big strong guy like you, huh?
You'd be able to take care of yourself.

217
00:14:01,960 --> 00:14:04,155
<i>(Kenton)</i> I worked with the Romanos.

218
00:14:04,240 --> 00:14:08,119
I never got very high in the organisation.
I left when my cover was blown.

219
00:14:08,200 --> 00:14:11,237
- You think one of the Romanos did this?
- It had to be.

220
00:14:11,320 --> 00:14:15,233
Hard to tell who. They use
a lot of different guys for ajob like this.

221
00:14:15,320 --> 00:14:18,551
That's Frank Lombardi.
He's been seen in the area.

222
00:14:18,640 --> 00:14:24,476
Suspected of killing over 25 people. Shooting
mostly, but he likes the occasional garrotting.

223
00:14:24,560 --> 00:14:26,915
Think they'd try to do away with the doctor?

224
00:14:27,000 --> 00:14:31,073
They're trying to look legit.
They don't want ancient history resurfacing.

225
00:14:31,160 --> 00:14:34,755
- Bad for business.
- But you don't know it's them.

226
00:14:34,840 --> 00:14:38,549
I have sources. They tell me
the Romanos know you're working this case.

227
00:14:38,640 --> 00:14:42,997
And they know you're the best.
I recommend you walk away.

228
00:14:43,080 --> 00:14:46,356
Is that why you brought me here?
To scare me into giving up?

229
00:14:46,440 --> 00:14:49,000
I want you to get real. These people...

230
00:14:49,080 --> 00:14:51,640
We don't know who it is.
It could be them or Hollings.

231
00:14:51,720 --> 00:14:57,590
No. Serial killers, they follow a pattern. They
don't torture, then pick people off with a rifle.

232
00:14:57,680 --> 00:15:02,117
Hollings promised no one would find enough
to get him. Maybe he knows I can.

233
00:15:02,200 --> 00:15:05,078
- Too dangerous.
- You almost got a bullet in the skull.

234
00:15:05,160 --> 00:15:09,551
I can give you answers, Booth.
I can help you get Hollings.

235
00:15:09,640 --> 00:15:13,838
You really want me to walk away
because it's dangerous?

236
00:15:13,920 --> 00:15:16,718
Sorry, man. I tried.

237
00:15:18,600 --> 00:15:21,433
Any word from Ballistics
on the bullets meant for me?

238
00:15:21,520 --> 00:15:24,830
- It was a military issue. Colt AR-15.
- <i>(phone rings)</i>

239
00:15:24,920 --> 00:15:25,909
Brennan.

240
00:15:26,000 --> 00:15:29,197
<i>Fasciola hepatica</i>.
It's a parasite found in beef liver.

241
00:15:29,280 --> 00:15:32,909
Their eggs are in the excrement.
The dogs were strays and starving.

242
00:15:33,000 --> 00:15:37,755
Someone lured them with liver scraps. There
was no evidence of liver found at the scene.

243
00:15:37,840 --> 00:15:42,630
So if we find any traces of liver
at Hollings' place that contains the parasite,

244
00:15:42,720 --> 00:15:45,109
- we can tie him to the dogs.
- It's possible.

245
00:15:45,200 --> 00:15:49,398
I found that the cut marks on her bone
showed that there was a nick in the blade.

246
00:15:49,480 --> 00:15:51,869
OK. Thanks.

247
00:15:59,840 --> 00:16:01,592
Agent Booth?

248
00:16:01,680 --> 00:16:03,910
- Long time no see.
- Hollings.

249
00:16:04,000 --> 00:16:07,151
- Could we take a look around?
- Do you have a warrant?

250
00:16:07,240 --> 00:16:10,915
No. But you enjoy
being cooperative, if I remember.

251
00:16:11,000 --> 00:16:14,231
Come in, please.

252
00:16:14,320 --> 00:16:16,788
You must be Dr Brennan.

253
00:16:16,880 --> 00:16:19,599
I read about the incident the other night.

254
00:16:19,680 --> 00:16:22,353
- You must've had a fright.
- Don't play with her.

255
00:16:22,440 --> 00:16:25,750
I hope you don't think I was being insensitive.

256
00:16:26,840 --> 00:16:29,593
Tell me what you're looking for
and I could help.

257
00:16:29,680 --> 00:16:32,114
We just want to look around, that's all.

258
00:16:32,200 --> 00:16:34,316
Be my guest.

259
00:16:35,720 --> 00:16:38,518
- Could I open this?
- Of course.

260
00:16:44,440 --> 00:16:47,796
Is this about the girl
they found the other night?

261
00:16:47,880 --> 00:16:50,314
Terrible thing.

262
00:16:50,400 --> 00:16:53,437
You don't think
I'm involved in this one too, do you?

263
00:16:53,520 --> 00:16:56,353
Blades are clean. No nicks.

264
00:16:56,440 --> 00:17:01,594
I guarantee that whatever you're looking for,
you're not gonna find here.

265
00:17:02,600 --> 00:17:05,398
What we need might be locked up someplace.

266
00:17:05,480 --> 00:17:07,914
Wow. There are thousands of keys here.

267
00:17:08,000 --> 00:17:10,230
Tens of thousands.

268
00:17:10,320 --> 00:17:12,754
Maybe we'll just
take them down to the Bureau.

269
00:17:12,840 --> 00:17:16,515
That's a private collection.
Without cause or a warrant...

270
00:17:16,600 --> 00:17:21,754
I do have cause. This key here is from
a federal building. It says "do not duplicate".

271
00:17:21,840 --> 00:17:25,196
And this one looks like it was used
in a burglary around the corner.

272
00:17:25,280 --> 00:17:29,512
- Oh, since you did allow us in your home...
- This is very rude, Agent Booth.

273
00:17:29,600 --> 00:17:33,275
- I open my home to you, then...
- We should photograph everything.

274
00:17:33,360 --> 00:17:36,796
How he's arranged the items in the room
could be very important.

275
00:17:36,880 --> 00:17:43,069
- I'd like to call my attorney.
- The game's not so fun now, is it, Hollings?

276
00:17:48,360 --> 00:17:51,909
I have a court date tomorrow.
You had no right to take his keys.

277
00:17:52,000 --> 00:17:54,878
There were burglaries.
Those keys could give answers.

278
00:17:54,960 --> 00:17:59,829
- My client can't be tied to those burglaries.
- You're probably right, but I have ajob to do.

279
00:17:59,920 --> 00:18:03,435
Mr Hollings has always been
so understanding of that in the past.

280
00:18:03,520 --> 00:18:08,594
Oh, I... I do understand. I've given you
a statement, explained where I got the keys.

281
00:18:08,680 --> 00:18:11,399
- And since you haven't charged him...
- Yet.

282
00:18:11,480 --> 00:18:17,669
But I'm really looking forward
to charging him with this. Look at that. Wow.

283
00:18:17,760 --> 00:18:20,274
<i>(whistles)</i>

284
00:18:24,680 --> 00:18:29,549
I imagine it must be very frustrating
when you... when you can't solve a crime.

285
00:18:29,640 --> 00:18:32,916
My client is a respected researcher
with Whitley Chemical.

286
00:18:33,000 --> 00:18:37,596
He hasn't missed a day of work in the
past two weeks. Unless you have evidence...

287
00:18:37,680 --> 00:18:40,752
Can't stop looking at it, can you, Hollings?

288
00:18:40,840 --> 00:18:42,956
What does it do to you?

289
00:18:43,040 --> 00:18:45,395
Does it make you hot?

290
00:18:48,960 --> 00:18:52,396
- Is that the psycho?
- He's brilliant.

291
00:18:52,480 --> 00:18:58,112
He knew we were looking for a pocketknife
so he left one in plain sight. The wrong one.

292
00:18:58,200 --> 00:19:00,998
If you don't find anything concrete,
he walks again?

293
00:19:01,080 --> 00:19:05,631
I don't know if Booth could live with that.
Those keys have to lead somewhere.

294
00:19:05,720 --> 00:19:10,350
The files we had on the suspects. People we
knew worked for the Romanos six years ago.

295
00:19:10,440 --> 00:19:13,432
Physical descriptions,
blood types, everything we had.

296
00:19:13,520 --> 00:19:15,875
Might help if you find any more evidence.

297
00:19:15,960 --> 00:19:20,750
Thanks. After we recreate the bullet, we can
track the angle of entry based on height...

298
00:19:20,840 --> 00:19:24,276
I don't get it. You don't have
the physical round that was shot.

299
00:19:24,360 --> 00:19:28,911
I'm trying to make one based on the wounds.
Could give us the murder weapon.

300
00:19:29,000 --> 00:19:31,309
- Sweet.
- If it works.

301
00:19:32,600 --> 00:19:35,068
Let me know if there's anything else I can do.

302
00:19:35,160 --> 00:19:37,879
- Sure.
- <i>(Booth)</i> I can and I will.

303
00:19:37,960 --> 00:19:39,678
<i>(lawyer)</i> You're fishing.

304
00:19:39,760 --> 00:19:44,470
No judge will let you keep that collection,
Agent Booth. You have to know that.

305
00:19:44,560 --> 00:19:46,994
We'll have it back by tomorrow.

306
00:19:49,240 --> 00:19:51,435
<i>(Hollings)</i> Nice try.

307
00:19:54,160 --> 00:19:59,029
I got the keys, but the judge will release them
in 18 hours unless we find something.

308
00:19:59,120 --> 00:20:02,317
- Bones thought maybe you could help.
- I'm an archaeologist.

309
00:20:02,400 --> 00:20:06,632
She thought you could look at it
as though it were some kind of historical site.

310
00:20:06,720 --> 00:20:11,316
That's a reasonable assumption. A persors
environment is a reflection of who he is.

311
00:20:11,400 --> 00:20:15,996
He's a predator, very smart, enjoys the game.
You know, he feels like he's untouchable.

312
00:20:16,080 --> 00:20:18,116
The room is centred around this chair.

313
00:20:18,200 --> 00:20:21,909
You can see how he's surrounded
back and sides by the bulk of the keys.

314
00:20:22,000 --> 00:20:26,949
If this were an innocent collection,
he'd be facing it, but he's displaying it.

315
00:20:27,040 --> 00:20:29,508
A guy like this, you know, his kills are prizes.

316
00:20:29,600 --> 00:20:35,550
The Bureau's searching to match one to
a locker or apartment, but there's too many.

317
00:20:35,640 --> 00:20:39,599
Mayan rulers kept souvenirs of kills.
They called it a "tzompantli".

318
00:20:39,680 --> 00:20:43,559
It was believed that it would
strike fear into anyone who saw it.

319
00:20:43,640 --> 00:20:45,073
- He's a Ioner.
- Yes.

320
00:20:45,160 --> 00:20:49,312
But this gave him enough power and security
that he let you into his home.

321
00:20:49,400 --> 00:20:51,755
- He's right-handed, correct?
- Yeah.

322
00:20:51,840 --> 00:20:54,798
Well, the bulk of the keys are on his right side.

323
00:20:54,880 --> 00:20:58,509
Those of the greatest value to him
would be in reach.

324
00:20:58,600 --> 00:21:00,989
They hold his power.

325
00:21:01,080 --> 00:21:04,959
I would look at any of the keys
in the containers on his right side over here.

326
00:21:07,080 --> 00:21:11,232
I thought it could be a saw blade of some
kind. I compared the damage with these.

327
00:21:11,320 --> 00:21:17,077
The crenulations form a pattern. They don't
match what we see in the orbital cavities.

328
00:21:17,160 --> 00:21:19,310
What if she were struggling?

329
00:21:19,400 --> 00:21:23,712
Lack of haemorrhage in the tissue suggests
she was dead before the eyes were removed.

330
00:21:23,800 --> 00:21:26,872
We need to find something smaller,
a surgical instrument.

331
00:21:26,960 --> 00:21:31,476
The concrete used to sink Cugini
contains fly ash instead of Portland cement.

332
00:21:31,560 --> 00:21:33,710
- It's very exciting.
- Not yet.

333
00:21:33,800 --> 00:21:37,429
Each company has its own mixture.
Building codes have to be met.

334
00:21:37,520 --> 00:21:43,117
After that, it's up to each company. These
people used fly ash, which is much cheaper.

335
00:21:43,200 --> 00:21:47,637
Tapford Construction.
Six years ago it was owned by Carlo Romano.

336
00:21:47,720 --> 00:21:49,870
<i>(Bones)</i> Romano doesn't seem worried.

337
00:21:49,960 --> 00:21:51,951
- <i>(Booth)</i> Hubris.
- <i>(Bones)</i> Good word.

338
00:21:52,040 --> 00:21:54,998
<i>(Booth)</i> Thanks.
He won't be smug after we talk to him.

339
00:21:55,080 --> 00:21:58,959
I'm running the names of employees
from his company six years ago,

340
00:21:59,040 --> 00:22:01,918
pulling sales invoices.
Gonna be a lot to sort through.

341
00:22:02,000 --> 00:22:06,391
Hodgins is seeing if there's any skin
or fingernail in the concrete to pull DNA from.

342
00:22:06,480 --> 00:22:10,678
- That's another remote possibility.
- <i>(phone rings)</i>

343
00:22:11,760 --> 00:22:14,274
Booth.

344
00:22:14,360 --> 00:22:18,876
Yeah. Judge ordered the release of Hollings'
possessions. We can't hold him.

345
00:22:18,960 --> 00:22:24,034
- How many have they been through?
- The lab had to match serial numbers,

346
00:22:24,120 --> 00:22:26,475
compare the crenulations.

347
00:22:26,560 --> 00:22:29,996
- The crenulations.
- They haven't been through the first 500...

348
00:22:30,080 --> 00:22:31,354
There is no lock.

349
00:22:31,440 --> 00:22:34,159
- Those keys don't open anything.
- What?

350
00:22:34,240 --> 00:22:38,711
The crenulations, the grooves carved
into the bone around the victim's eyes,

351
00:22:38,800 --> 00:22:43,112
they were irregular, like...
like the grooves of a key.

352
00:22:43,200 --> 00:22:47,318
- Bones, how many keys do you need?
- Well, car, house, lab, morgue.

353
00:22:47,400 --> 00:22:50,437
- I need a lot of keys.
- <i>(clears throat)</i> Grooves?

354
00:22:50,520 --> 00:22:54,832
He must've used a key to gouge out the eyes.
And he kept it near him in his apartment.

355
00:22:54,920 --> 00:22:58,629
That was his souvenir.
How much longer can you keep the keys?

356
00:22:58,720 --> 00:23:02,508
- He's on his way to reclaim them now.
- So you have at least a half an hour?

357
00:23:02,600 --> 00:23:03,919
At least.

358
00:23:04,000 --> 00:23:08,471
Tell Forensics to forget about matching them
to any locks. Have them image each key.

359
00:23:08,560 --> 00:23:12,599
Send them to Zack so he can find a key
that matches the grooves on the bone.

360
00:23:12,680 --> 00:23:15,797
- That shouldn't take long.
- Image key, send to Zack.

361
00:23:15,880 --> 00:23:19,236
- She's good, huh?
- Told you.

362
00:23:19,920 --> 00:23:23,230
Romano didn't give us anything,
so I should be back at the lab.

363
00:23:23,320 --> 00:23:28,440
Your squints can handle it. You haven't slept.
Get some rest. I'll sleep on the couch.

364
00:23:28,520 --> 00:23:32,593
- You think you're staying here with me?
- Yeah. Nice place, by the way, Bones.

365
00:23:32,680 --> 00:23:35,399
No. I'm... I'm locked in here, Booth.
I'll be fine.

366
00:23:35,480 --> 00:23:40,315
Stay away from your windows. A sniper
has a clear shot from any of these buildings.

367
00:23:40,400 --> 00:23:43,358
I could've stayed at the lab.
Security's tight there.

368
00:23:43,440 --> 00:23:47,274
Then you would've worked,
gotten tired, and been more vulnerable.

369
00:23:47,360 --> 00:23:49,590
Trust me, this is the best, all right?

370
00:23:49,680 --> 00:23:51,955
So...

371
00:23:52,040 --> 00:23:56,556
- Where's the TV?
- I had one, but it broke. I...

372
00:23:56,640 --> 00:24:00,997
I mostly just read and listen to music.

373
00:24:01,640 --> 00:24:03,915
So let's listen to some music, huh?

374
00:24:06,040 --> 00:24:08,600
Music. What have we got? Bones.

375
00:24:08,680 --> 00:24:12,150
Wow, world music. There's a shock.

376
00:24:13,240 --> 00:24:17,756
- "Tibetan Throat Singers." Rock on, Bones.
- That's mostly for work...

377
00:24:17,840 --> 00:24:21,594
Kanye West, Cat Power... Oh, oh. All right.

378
00:24:21,680 --> 00:24:27,312
Look at this. There's lots ofjazz. I think that
free-form stuff would be too unpredictable.

379
00:24:27,400 --> 00:24:32,838
No. I love it. The artist has to live within a set
tonal structure and trust his own instincts

380
00:24:32,920 --> 00:24:36,799
to find his way out of an infinite maze
of musical possibilities,

381
00:24:36,880 --> 00:24:39,030
and the great ones do.

382
00:24:41,360 --> 00:24:43,590
- What?
- Oh, nothing. I just...

383
00:24:43,680 --> 00:24:47,070
I just never expected
that you would, you know...

384
00:24:47,160 --> 00:24:48,991
That I would love music?

385
00:24:49,080 --> 00:24:53,039
Well, I don't usually get to talk about it,
but since you brought it up...

386
00:24:53,120 --> 00:24:57,591
No, hey. No, I didn't mean to make you
self-conscious. Whoa, what's this?

387
00:24:57,680 --> 00:24:58,749
- What is it?
- Nice.

388
00:24:58,840 --> 00:25:00,398
Booth...

389
00:25:01,080 --> 00:25:03,958
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Hot Blooded" by Foreigner)</i>

390
00:25:04,800 --> 00:25:07,678
- How did that get there?
- Everybody loves Foreigner.

391
00:25:07,760 --> 00:25:11,150
"Hot Blooded." Talk about a guilty pleasure.

392
00:25:15,720 --> 00:25:19,474
♪ <i>Well, I'm hot blooded, check it and see</i>

393
00:25:19,560 --> 00:25:24,475
- <i>(Booth)</i> Kick it, baby.
- ♪ <i>I got a fever of 103</i>

394
00:25:24,560 --> 00:25:28,269
♪ <i>Come on, baby,</i>
<i>you can do more than dance</i>

395
00:25:28,360 --> 00:25:32,911
♪ <i>I'm hot blooded, I'm hot blooded</i>

396
00:25:33,800 --> 00:25:36,268
<i>(phone rings)</i>

397
00:25:38,240 --> 00:25:40,231
Brennan.

398
00:25:40,320 --> 00:25:44,154
David, hi. I'm fine, thanks.

399
00:25:44,240 --> 00:25:49,598
Booth, yeah. I'm still under lockdown
until we solve these crimes.

400
00:25:49,680 --> 00:25:53,070
Yes. Foreigner.

401
00:25:53,160 --> 00:25:56,357
OK, I'II... OK, sure. I'll talk to you tomorrow.

402
00:25:56,440 --> 00:25:59,318
OK, thanks for calling. Bye.

403
00:26:01,960 --> 00:26:04,155
- I hope he didn't think...
- No.

404
00:26:04,240 --> 00:26:08,552
Because I wouldn't want to,
you know, ruin things for you or...

405
00:26:08,640 --> 00:26:11,029
Not a problem.

406
00:26:13,800 --> 00:26:17,429
Hey, you got a soda? Some juice?

407
00:26:17,520 --> 00:26:20,193
- Yeah. In my fridge. I'll get it.
- No, no, no, no.

408
00:26:20,280 --> 00:26:24,273
You know what? I'm not your guest.
You don't have to wait on me. I'll get it.

409
00:26:24,360 --> 00:26:28,876
- Do you want anything?
- That's OK.

410
00:26:28,960 --> 00:26:33,431
Oh, there's glasses
in the cupboard to the right of the fridge.

411
00:26:55,040 --> 00:26:58,555
- Kentors on his way. Stay with him.
- <i>(Bones)</i> I will.

412
00:26:58,640 --> 00:27:01,473
- Did they gather all the evidence?
- Yes.

413
00:27:01,560 --> 00:27:04,711
- You're sure?
- Yes. Booth, I was there.

414
00:27:04,800 --> 00:27:08,190
They were very thorough
and I was very annoying.

415
00:27:10,000 --> 00:27:13,037
I'm sorry, Booth.
It should be me lying in that bed.

416
00:27:13,120 --> 00:27:17,910
I'm fine, you know. I don't even know
if I have to stay here, you know?

417
00:27:18,000 --> 00:27:20,309
- You got blown up.
- I've been worse.

418
00:27:20,400 --> 00:27:26,077
You have burns, lacerations, two broken
ribs, greenstick fracture of the clavicle.

419
00:27:26,160 --> 00:27:29,072
OK, I got blown up.

420
00:27:32,280 --> 00:27:34,953
Can you hand me one of the puddings?

421
00:27:40,760 --> 00:27:42,716
Oh, man.

422
00:27:43,800 --> 00:27:46,633
Thanks, Bones. Look at that.

423
00:27:46,720 --> 00:27:48,517
Oh.

424
00:27:50,280 --> 00:27:53,829
You know, on your x-rays,

425
00:27:53,920 --> 00:27:59,278
there's a history of multiple fractures
on your feet consistent with beating.

426
00:27:59,360 --> 00:28:03,399
It's a common method of torture
in the Middle East,

427
00:28:03,480 --> 00:28:08,474
beating the soles of the feet
with pipes or... hoses.

428
00:28:08,560 --> 00:28:10,551
Yeah, I know.

429
00:28:10,640 --> 00:28:16,317
And there are indications of injuries
sustained while you were shielding someone.

430
00:28:16,400 --> 00:28:18,072
How the hell can you tell that?

431
00:28:18,160 --> 00:28:22,517
The scarring shows
that the ribcage spread in such a way that...

432
00:28:22,600 --> 00:28:24,477
Yeah.

433
00:28:24,560 --> 00:28:27,279
OK.

434
00:28:27,360 --> 00:28:29,954
A buddy of mine...

435
00:28:31,240 --> 00:28:33,595
he lost his weapon and I...

436
00:28:36,320 --> 00:28:38,311
I tried.

437
00:28:43,040 --> 00:28:45,110
He didn't make it.

438
00:28:48,440 --> 00:28:52,149
You know, you shouldn't
be looking at my x-rays.

439
00:28:53,200 --> 00:28:55,395
- I'm sorry.
- <i>(knock at door)</i>

440
00:28:55,480 --> 00:28:56,754
- Hey.
- Yeah.

441
00:28:56,840 --> 00:28:58,910
You look like crap.

442
00:28:59,000 --> 00:29:02,595
A little bit more pudding
and I'll be just fine. Stick with her.

443
00:29:02,680 --> 00:29:06,116
- If you want me to.
- Don't you think I should be consulted?

444
00:29:06,200 --> 00:29:10,273
- No. Keep her close.
- <i>(Kenton)</i> Don't worry.

445
00:29:10,360 --> 00:29:13,079
- <i>(Zack) Could've been you.</i>
- <i>(Bones) Yes, I know.</i>

446
00:29:13,160 --> 00:29:18,154
- He survived cos he reached for the glass.
- I know. Can we change the subject?

447
00:29:18,240 --> 00:29:20,515
Let's talk revenge... blood lust.

448
00:29:20,600 --> 00:29:24,957
The release we want can only be achieved
when we gather enough evidence

449
00:29:25,040 --> 00:29:29,192
to neutralise the person responsible
for putting Booth in hospital.

450
00:29:29,280 --> 00:29:33,319
- Neutralise can mean either "kill" or "arrest".
- Yes. It can mean either.

451
00:29:33,400 --> 00:29:35,630
What exactly are you doing?

452
00:29:35,720 --> 00:29:39,395
I'm using a program to fill in
the missing markings made by the bullet

453
00:29:39,480 --> 00:29:41,436
when it passed through the bone.

454
00:29:41,520 --> 00:29:44,796
Impressed? I have so many more tricks.

455
00:29:44,880 --> 00:29:48,429
There's no ring. Single or gay?

456
00:29:48,520 --> 00:29:51,080
Gay... Why would you say gay?

457
00:29:51,160 --> 00:29:53,469
<i>Brokeback,</i> baby. Gotta ask.

458
00:29:53,560 --> 00:29:55,391
- Not gay.
- Angela.

459
00:29:55,480 --> 00:29:57,391
We'll talk later.

460
00:29:57,480 --> 00:30:02,679
So you'd match a digital replica of the bullet
with any recovered bullets the FBI has?

461
00:30:02,760 --> 00:30:08,232
- Yes. To cross-reference crimes, suspects...
- Amazing.

462
00:30:08,320 --> 00:30:12,598
I just finished with Forensics
analysing the composition of the explosives.

463
00:30:12,680 --> 00:30:14,830
The isotopes and sulphur match.

464
00:30:14,920 --> 00:30:19,630
It is a perfect match to the sulphur
made by the company Hollings works for.

465
00:30:20,360 --> 00:30:22,396
- FBI!
- Go! Go!

466
00:30:22,480 --> 00:30:25,074
Show yourself!

467
00:30:25,160 --> 00:30:26,957
Clear!

468
00:30:40,080 --> 00:30:42,275
He took off.

469
00:30:43,840 --> 00:30:47,549
He marked the same part of town
where we found the other victim.

470
00:30:47,640 --> 00:30:50,598
He's going after someone else.
I want all this bagged.

471
00:30:50,680 --> 00:30:53,990
- <i>(agent)</i> Let's go. Don't disturb anything.
- <i>(phone rings)</i>

472
00:30:54,080 --> 00:30:55,832
- Brennan.
- We found the key.

473
00:30:55,920 --> 00:30:58,673
FBI said Hollings
never returned to claim them.

474
00:30:58,760 --> 00:31:00,830
It matches the bone damage exactly.

475
00:31:00,920 --> 00:31:02,990
- And it's one of Hollings' keys?
- <i>Yes.</i>

476
00:31:03,080 --> 00:31:08,074
Hodgins tried to retrieve DNA, but he says
it was dipped in some kind of chemical bath.

477
00:31:08,160 --> 00:31:11,470
- Good work.
- Maybe you should come in now.

478
00:31:11,560 --> 00:31:14,950
<i>I'll be fine, Zack. Any luck with the bullet?</i>

479
00:31:15,040 --> 00:31:18,828
You want to go back to the lab
until we get any news? It'll be safer.

480
00:31:18,920 --> 00:31:21,036
<i>(Bones) I'll see you in a few minutes.</i>

481
00:31:21,360 --> 00:31:23,271
<i>(commentator) He's got the ball again...</i>

482
00:31:27,840 --> 00:31:28,875
Hey.

483
00:31:28,960 --> 00:31:32,032
- Is Brennan all right?
- Sure. She's with your compadre.

484
00:31:32,120 --> 00:31:34,873
I just came by to see how you are.

485
00:31:34,960 --> 00:31:36,678
Oh.

486
00:31:36,760 --> 00:31:40,912
Pudding. I still remember this stuff
from when I got my appendix out.

487
00:31:41,000 --> 00:31:44,595
Yeah. And it's as good as you remember.

488
00:31:44,680 --> 00:31:46,511
- Key fit?
- Yeah.

489
00:31:46,600 --> 00:31:50,070
They found a map of where the other body
was found, and more keys.

490
00:31:50,160 --> 00:31:54,278
On a map? We didn't...
we didn't catch that before?

491
00:31:54,360 --> 00:31:58,069
- I guess not. Or your killer's getting sloppy.
- That's not like him.

492
00:31:58,160 --> 00:32:03,234
It wasrt like him to use explosives. People
change. That's the wonderful thing about life.

493
00:32:03,320 --> 00:32:08,872
Now we can get him before
he gets Brennan. Can I have this one?

494
00:32:08,960 --> 00:32:10,951
- You OK?
- Huh?

495
00:32:11,040 --> 00:32:12,439
Yeah. Yeah.

496
00:32:12,520 --> 00:32:16,957
I'm just thinking. People don't change.
We like to believe they do, but they don't.

497
00:32:17,040 --> 00:32:18,996
You thinking it's the mob guys?

498
00:32:19,080 --> 00:32:23,153
I'm just thinking that things...
they don't make sense.

499
00:32:23,240 --> 00:32:27,597
You're feeling something a little more
devious. More like a frame-up? I like it.

500
00:32:27,680 --> 00:32:30,399
- Very conspiratorial.
- Things are just too neat.

501
00:32:30,480 --> 00:32:33,711
- Hollings would never leave a map there.
- Go with me on this.

502
00:32:33,800 --> 00:32:37,349
Mob guys know you're closing in
and want to make it look like the psycho.

503
00:32:37,440 --> 00:32:40,557
They've been involved in
more complicated conspiracies.

504
00:32:40,640 --> 00:32:44,713
They set up Lee Harvey Oswald,
worked with the CIA to kill Castro.

505
00:32:44,800 --> 00:32:48,918
Someone planted that evidence.
Someone who knew what we were up to.

506
00:32:49,000 --> 00:32:51,514
Someone at the lab works for the Mob.

507
00:32:51,600 --> 00:32:56,674
I can see it. No difference between a corrupt
corporate government and organised crime.

508
00:32:56,760 --> 00:32:59,479
- You're right.
- Excuse me?

509
00:32:59,560 --> 00:33:05,351
The only way this could unfold is if someone
on the inside was orchestrating things.

510
00:33:05,440 --> 00:33:10,309
People never tell me I'm right.
They only say I'm crazy. Love you, man.

511
00:33:10,400 --> 00:33:12,834
- What the hell are you doing?
- You're driving.

512
00:33:12,920 --> 00:33:14,592
- Cool.
- OK.

513
00:33:14,680 --> 00:33:18,798
Yeah. OK. Make sure there's backup.

514
00:33:18,880 --> 00:33:23,032
Someone took a woman into those
abandoned buildings off Hunter Boulevard.

515
00:33:23,120 --> 00:33:26,476
- I'll drop you off at the lab.
- No. I'm coming.

516
00:33:27,560 --> 00:33:31,917
- Booth said it was pointless to argue.
- He's a smart man, Booth. I'll call Zack.

517
00:33:32,000 --> 00:33:34,150
I know how to complete the bullet.

518
00:33:34,240 --> 00:33:39,268
Even if we only have one side, if we can
approximate the spin as it was fired...

519
00:33:44,400 --> 00:33:47,517
You really are the best.

520
00:33:47,600 --> 00:33:49,591
It's too bad.

521
00:33:54,960 --> 00:33:59,192
<i>(Booth)</i> You work for the FBI and they
put you on hold when you want information.

522
00:33:59,280 --> 00:34:04,479
Kenton was working Organised Crime at
the same time that Cugini was killed. Right?

523
00:34:04,560 --> 00:34:08,269
He was the only one
who knew the details on both investigations.

524
00:34:08,360 --> 00:34:12,194
He takes what he knows about Hollings
to throw suspicions off himself.

525
00:34:12,280 --> 00:34:13,679
<i>(groans)</i>

526
00:34:13,760 --> 00:34:17,196
Maybe that nurse was right
to be pissed that you were leaving.

527
00:34:17,280 --> 00:34:20,511
If we werert in a toy car... Yeah?

528
00:34:20,600 --> 00:34:24,195
Listen to me, Bobby.
Just get some units out there now. OK?

529
00:34:24,280 --> 00:34:28,876
I want to know about any activity
in the abandoned buildings on that map.

530
00:34:28,960 --> 00:34:35,433
- Brennars not picking up her cell.
- Kenton never called for backup or anything.

531
00:34:35,520 --> 00:34:39,354
Jeez. How could I be so stupid?
I mean, everything pointed to him.

532
00:34:39,440 --> 00:34:42,193
- It is not your fault.
- How could it not be my fault?

533
00:34:42,280 --> 00:34:48,116
It was my job to protect her.
Instead, I hand her over to him.

534
00:34:49,760 --> 00:34:52,035
Certain crimes you just gotta let slide.

535
00:34:52,120 --> 00:34:56,272
A death like Cugini's is an internal issue.
It doesn't affect anyone else.

536
00:34:56,360 --> 00:35:00,035
- You killed Cugini?
- You don't get rich working for the FBI.

537
00:35:00,120 --> 00:35:02,759
When I was undercover,
the Romanos were good to me.

538
00:35:02,840 --> 00:35:06,549
When you accept their generosity,
you have to do what they ask.

539
00:35:06,640 --> 00:35:09,234
Is that how you live with yourself?

540
00:35:09,320 --> 00:35:13,359
It's no different to Booth taking out
someone from the other side in the Gulf.

541
00:35:13,440 --> 00:35:16,193
That was a war. His actions saved lives.

542
00:35:16,280 --> 00:35:21,115
You don't think getting rid of Cugini
ended a street war?

543
00:35:21,200 --> 00:35:24,033
So my death will be justified now?

544
00:35:24,120 --> 00:35:26,509
Bureau keeps a shell from every weapon.

545
00:35:26,600 --> 00:35:31,720
You match it, it points to my weapon and I go
down. The Romanos make sure I don't talk.

546
00:35:31,800 --> 00:35:34,917
Well, at least I'm dying for a good reason.

547
00:36:04,480 --> 00:36:06,948
<i>(Hodgins)</i> Maybe you're wrong.
Hollings is missing.

548
00:36:07,040 --> 00:36:12,797
Convenient. Kenton planted the lead so
we'd go after Hollings, who we'd never find.

549
00:36:12,880 --> 00:36:15,314
- Because he's dead?
- Because he's dead.

550
00:36:15,400 --> 00:36:20,520
This whole conspiracy thing is a lot more
intense when you're in the middle of it.

551
00:36:20,600 --> 00:36:22,989
Yeah. OK.

552
00:36:23,080 --> 00:36:27,710
Look, an agent talked to a witness who saw
a couple go into a building off of North 23rd.

553
00:36:27,800 --> 00:36:29,711
"A building"? That's specific.

554
00:36:29,800 --> 00:36:33,315
Crackheads aren't that detail-oriented.
Step on it. Come on.

555
00:36:36,680 --> 00:36:38,875
<i>(muffled screams)</i>

556
00:36:38,960 --> 00:36:41,599
They're not gonna find Hollings. Uh-uh.

557
00:36:41,680 --> 00:36:43,671
<i>(dogs bark)</i>

558
00:36:46,360 --> 00:36:50,751
You know, he used to
slit their throat like they were cattle.

559
00:36:50,840 --> 00:36:54,355
Told me he used the key
to unlock the soul behind their eyes.

560
00:36:54,440 --> 00:36:58,911
That is one sick bastard
the world ain't gonna miss.

561
00:37:03,960 --> 00:37:06,713
We used thermal imagery
to see inside the buildings.

562
00:37:06,800 --> 00:37:09,519
Found a crackhouse.
Just about to move in here next.

563
00:37:09,600 --> 00:37:12,876
He hears, he could freak out and kill her.
We gotta be careful.

564
00:37:12,960 --> 00:37:14,632
- There's no "we".
- I'm going in.

565
00:37:14,720 --> 00:37:19,510
- You can barely stand.
- I said I'm going in. Give me my gun.

566
00:37:21,960 --> 00:37:24,349
Bring me that vest for Booth.

567
00:37:24,440 --> 00:37:26,317
- Wear this.
- Yeah.

568
00:37:28,440 --> 00:37:29,759
<i>(groans)</i>

569
00:37:29,840 --> 00:37:32,559
You know what?
You can come too. Put that on.

570
00:37:32,640 --> 00:37:35,154
- You stay back.
- I can do that.

571
00:37:45,600 --> 00:37:48,319
<i>(dogs bark)</i>

572
00:37:48,400 --> 00:37:50,118
I'm sorry.

573
00:37:50,200 --> 00:37:52,714
I really am.

574
00:37:53,880 --> 00:37:55,598
<i>(muffled scream)</i>

575
00:38:19,040 --> 00:38:21,235
<i>(groans)</i>

576
00:38:21,320 --> 00:38:24,790
Maybe you shouldn't
have had all that pudding.

577
00:38:37,800 --> 00:38:40,155
<i>(whistles)</i>

578
00:38:47,120 --> 00:38:52,752
I'm not like him, though. The things
I have to do to you, you'll be gone first.

579
00:38:53,600 --> 00:38:55,477
You'll never know a thing.

580
00:38:55,560 --> 00:38:58,393
I never expected anyone to find out.

581
00:38:58,480 --> 00:39:00,277
<i>(Bones gasps)</i>

582
00:39:07,080 --> 00:39:10,038
All right. OK. All right.

583
00:39:19,200 --> 00:39:22,636
Oh, it's OK. I'm right here. It's all over.

584
00:39:23,720 --> 00:39:25,312
All right. OK.

585
00:39:25,400 --> 00:39:27,994
Shh. I'm right here. All right.

586
00:39:28,080 --> 00:39:30,753
It's all over. Shh. All right.

587
00:39:30,840 --> 00:39:33,957
- How did you get out of the hospital?
- I...

588
00:39:34,040 --> 00:39:39,672
Hodgins gave me a ride. Maybe you can
give me a ride back, huh? Can you?

589
00:39:41,760 --> 00:39:43,557
<i>(groans)</i> OK.

590
00:39:44,680 --> 00:39:49,708
Kenton is telling us everything. I guess
there's nothing to hide. He's finished anyway.

591
00:39:49,800 --> 00:39:54,078
- Better late than never, huh?
- Yeah, I guess.

592
00:39:54,160 --> 00:39:56,799
You know, I... I let you down, Bones.

593
00:39:56,880 --> 00:39:59,599
I'm... sorry.

594
00:39:59,680 --> 00:40:02,911
- You saved my life.
- Yeah. But, you know, it shouldn't...

595
00:40:03,000 --> 00:40:05,878
it shouldn't have gone down like that.

596
00:40:08,880 --> 00:40:11,997
- What a pair.
- <i>(phone rings)</i>

597
00:40:12,840 --> 00:40:14,512
Brennan.

598
00:40:15,600 --> 00:40:18,068
I'm leaving right now.

599
00:40:20,600 --> 00:40:22,272
David.

600
00:40:22,360 --> 00:40:28,879
- We're finally having our dinner.
- I figured you didn't dress up for me.

601
00:40:28,960 --> 00:40:31,758
- You sure you don't want anything?
- I'll be fine.

602
00:40:31,840 --> 00:40:35,594
I'm just gonna, you know,
flip around the TV here.

603
00:40:39,560 --> 00:40:41,630
OK.

604
00:40:41,720 --> 00:40:44,518
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah. Have a good night.

605
00:40:44,600 --> 00:40:47,114
Thanks.

606
00:40:48,800 --> 00:40:51,758
- <i>(woman on TV) Dow averages...</i>
- <i>(man) Pancakes...</i>

607
00:40:51,840 --> 00:40:54,752
<i>(woman #2)... marched on Washington early...</i>

608
00:41:03,600 --> 00:41:07,957
<i>(man on TV) We'll finish a delightful</i>
<i>evening with reintegrated champagne.</i>

609
00:41:08,040 --> 00:41:10,713
I rescheduled.

610
00:41:10,800 --> 00:41:13,473
My... my head still hurts.

611
00:41:17,760 --> 00:41:21,548
- You can watch TV if you like.
- Sure.

612
00:41:27,880 --> 00:41:30,235
Bones. Arm.

613
00:41:30,320 --> 00:41:31,753
Thanks.

614
00:41:31,840 --> 00:41:37,995
<i>(man #2 on TV) Wherever there's a fight</i>
<i>so hungry people can eat... I'll be there.</i>

615
00:41:38,080 --> 00:41:42,631
<i>Wherever there's a cop</i>
<i>beating up a guy, I'll be there.</i>

616
00:42:08,040 --> 00:42:10,873
Visiontext Subtitles: Sarah Johnston

617
00:42:15,280 --> 00:42:16,633
What's that mean?

618
00:42:17,320 --> 00:42:19,311
ENGLISH SDH

