1
00:00:01,080 --> 00:00:05,596
<i>(officer)</i> If you had any kind of weapon,
you'd let me know, right, buddy?

2
00:00:05,680 --> 00:00:08,478
<i>(officer #2)</i> Make it easy on yourself.

3
00:00:08,560 --> 00:00:10,551
<i>(sirens approaching)</i>

4
00:00:16,080 --> 00:00:18,640
Why did they call in the FBI
to Little Salvador?

5
00:00:18,720 --> 00:00:21,154
A car's got Virginia plates across state line.

6
00:00:21,240 --> 00:00:25,313
There's a suspected gang member and RICO
to deal with. Do you really want to know?

7
00:00:25,400 --> 00:00:29,552
No. I was using it as an excuse to make
conversation and re-establish our connection.

8
00:00:29,640 --> 00:00:33,599
- What?
- I read about improving work relationships.

9
00:00:33,680 --> 00:00:38,879
- I don't expect you to tell me everything.
- I appreciate the effort, Bones.

10
00:00:40,080 --> 00:00:44,073
It's like they recreated their country,
down to being terrified of the police.

11
00:00:44,160 --> 00:00:48,153
A lot of them are undocumented and get
nervous around the law. What have we got?

12
00:00:48,240 --> 00:00:50,708
Ran a stop sign.
I pulled him over, he tried to run.

13
00:00:50,800 --> 00:00:55,078
Oh, look at this - a Mara Muerte tattoo.
It's one of the most feared gangs in the area.

14
00:00:55,160 --> 00:00:57,594
No wonder he was chauffeuring
a dead body around.

15
00:00:57,680 --> 00:01:00,478
- Couldrtjoin the Boys Club?
- I'm here because...?

16
00:01:00,560 --> 00:01:04,838
On routine inspection of the vehicle,
I found this.

17
00:01:07,560 --> 00:01:11,917
Vertical brow ridge suggests female.
Recently dug up, looks like.

18
00:01:12,000 --> 00:01:14,560
Could you hold his hands up, please?

19
00:01:14,640 --> 00:01:19,430
We should analyse the dirt on his hands
and compare it to the dirt on the remains.

20
00:01:19,520 --> 00:01:21,476
Where was she buried?

21
00:01:21,880 --> 00:01:24,075
<i>(in Spanish)</i>

22
00:01:26,800 --> 00:01:29,792
- He's ignoring us in two languages.
- Where's the cemetery?

23
00:01:29,880 --> 00:01:35,750
The closest one I know about is Holy Rood,
but that's a good ten miles from here.

24
00:01:46,400 --> 00:01:50,598
- Maybe your Spanish is a little rusty.
- They think getting involved gets you killed.

25
00:01:50,680 --> 00:01:52,272
<i>(gunshots)</i>

26
00:01:54,280 --> 00:01:56,748
<i>(officer)</i> Get down! Get down!

27
00:02:02,920 --> 00:02:05,434
Shots fired! Shots fired!

28
00:02:06,880 --> 00:02:08,916
Hey!

29
00:02:11,960 --> 00:02:13,996
Hey!

30
00:02:20,000 --> 00:02:22,355
Don't make me shoot you!

31
00:03:15,400 --> 00:03:21,589
Decomp, insect activity, volatile fatty-acid
levels in the soil due to putrefaction

32
00:03:21,680 --> 00:03:23,989
suggest she was buried for six months.

33
00:03:24,080 --> 00:03:27,675
Typically, gravediggers
are necrophiliacs looking for action.

34
00:03:27,760 --> 00:03:29,159
Um... Eww.

35
00:03:29,240 --> 00:03:32,915
- Dental exam shows striated enamel.
- Indicating?

36
00:03:33,000 --> 00:03:37,915
Malnutrition - which, with anthropometrics,
suggests the victim is from Central America.

37
00:03:38,000 --> 00:03:40,116
We found her
in a Salvadorian neighbourhood.

38
00:03:40,200 --> 00:03:43,510
In Pikeville, Tennessee, a guy dug up
the graves of all these people

39
00:03:43,600 --> 00:03:46,239
to make sure their bodies were still there.

40
00:03:46,320 --> 00:03:47,355
They werert.

41
00:03:47,440 --> 00:03:51,991
Sketch the face. I'm not sure if we'll find a
match. She might have been undocumented.

42
00:03:52,080 --> 00:03:56,995
Goodman is an expert in iconography. Maybe
he'll determine where this rosary was made.

43
00:03:57,080 --> 00:04:01,471
Depression fracture on her occipital bone
straddling the left lambdoidal suture.

44
00:04:01,560 --> 00:04:03,994
One hard hit congruent with,
say, a baseball bat.

45
00:04:04,080 --> 00:04:06,878
She was religious.
She should have had a casket,

46
00:04:06,960 --> 00:04:10,077
a proper burial with her name on a headstone.

47
00:04:10,160 --> 00:04:13,789
We are going to find out who she is
and we are going to give her that.

48
00:04:14,880 --> 00:04:16,711
<i>(Booth)</i> Miguel Villeda.

49
00:04:16,800 --> 00:04:20,349
Warlord of the Venganza Roja street gang.

50
00:04:20,440 --> 00:04:24,797
According to this,
you are one fierce, fierce guy.

51
00:04:24,880 --> 00:04:27,792
- It didn't stop your guys from picking me up.
- They say why?

52
00:04:27,880 --> 00:04:30,553
Someone took a shot at some Mara Muerte.

53
00:04:30,640 --> 00:04:32,790
Not a shot.

54
00:04:32,880 --> 00:04:35,678
A couple of dozen shots. A drive-by.

55
00:04:35,760 --> 00:04:40,072
Hardly anyone is stupid enough to shoot
at those guys any more. Your name came up.

56
00:04:40,160 --> 00:04:44,915
It wasrt my people. So, are you gonna
charge me with something or let me go?

57
00:04:45,000 --> 00:04:49,437
Extortion, drugs,
assault, attempted murder.

58
00:04:49,520 --> 00:04:51,750
I could hold you for a while.

59
00:04:51,840 --> 00:04:55,435
- What's your problem, man?
- My problem is that somebody shot at me.

60
00:04:55,520 --> 00:04:58,239
Shot at me and my partner.
Plus a bad guy got away.

61
00:04:58,320 --> 00:05:01,073
So I'm a little cranky about the whole thing.

62
00:05:01,160 --> 00:05:03,435
<i>Mira, gabacho.</i>

63
00:05:03,520 --> 00:05:07,274
I don't really scare that way -
the whole in-your-face staring thing.

64
00:05:07,360 --> 00:05:10,989
No? Give me a chance, man.
I'm just getting started.

65
00:05:11,080 --> 00:05:13,799
- So someone shot at you, huh?
- That's right.

66
00:05:13,880 --> 00:05:16,917
When was the last time you heard
of a drive-by where no one got hit?

67
00:05:17,000 --> 00:05:22,199
Innocent bystanders mostly.
It's not like you always hit what you aim at.

68
00:05:22,280 --> 00:05:27,638
Think, just for a couple of seconds,
about why the guy never got hit.

69
00:05:30,640 --> 00:05:33,234
Ah, yeah, you see? You got it now?

70
00:05:33,320 --> 00:05:35,515
Mara Muerte did a drive-by on their own guy?

71
00:05:35,600 --> 00:05:39,832
A drive-by happens, yeah.
And you all hit the deck.

72
00:05:39,920 --> 00:05:43,310
And the gangbanger makes a run for it.

73
00:05:54,960 --> 00:05:57,838
I have it on good authority
the guys who shot at our killer

74
00:05:57,920 --> 00:06:00,275
were doing it so he'd have a chance to escape.

75
00:06:00,360 --> 00:06:03,432
The victim was pregnant
when she was hit over the head.

76
00:06:03,520 --> 00:06:06,239
- Pregnant?
- Five weeks along. Get your hands off.

77
00:06:06,320 --> 00:06:09,756
I ran samples from the body, shovel
and burlap through the chromatograph

78
00:06:09,840 --> 00:06:13,992
and it came back full of organic compounds -
plant detritus, root remnants, fertiliser.

79
00:06:14,080 --> 00:06:17,072
- Stuff you'd find in a cemetery.
- I also found this.

80
00:06:17,160 --> 00:06:19,913
<i>Fernaldia pandurata,</i>
otherwise known as loroco buds.

81
00:06:20,000 --> 00:06:23,515
Loroco is an edible flowering plant.
It's native to El Salvador.

82
00:06:23,600 --> 00:06:26,114
It's grown in vegetable gardens,
not cemeteries.

83
00:06:26,200 --> 00:06:30,239
She was buried in a vegetable garden?
OK. Can you recognise this loco plant?

84
00:06:30,320 --> 00:06:33,198
Loroco. I've eaten it,
but I wouldn't recognise it.

85
00:06:33,280 --> 00:06:37,512
It's quite distinctive. I'm also analysing
the dirt on the suspect's shoe.

86
00:06:37,600 --> 00:06:41,593
First glance, it matches the vegetation
we found, but with a couple of extras.

87
00:06:41,680 --> 00:06:45,992
OK. Hodgins, suit up. You're coming with us.
We're going to the barrio.

88
00:06:46,080 --> 00:06:49,390
Fieldwork! Cool! Do I get a gun?

89
00:06:49,480 --> 00:06:53,473
- You can't arm Hodgins and not me.
- What is it with you people and the guns?

90
00:06:58,800 --> 00:07:02,429
Look at this. The government
goes bankrupt giving tax breaks to the rich,

91
00:07:02,520 --> 00:07:06,399
so there's no money left to help these people
with job training, health care...

92
00:07:06,480 --> 00:07:08,516
Just look for a garden with the plant.

93
00:07:08,600 --> 00:07:12,275
Those who do land ajob work for
a minimum wage that hasn't risen in years.

94
00:07:12,360 --> 00:07:15,511
That's for those here legally.
The undocumented do a lot worse.

95
00:07:15,600 --> 00:07:19,309
What is this? NPR Radio?
Are you two running for office?

96
00:07:19,400 --> 00:07:21,834
<i>(Hodgins)</i> Look. Over there.

97
00:07:24,000 --> 00:07:25,991
Loroco plant.

98
00:07:27,960 --> 00:07:34,354
That's the same approximate maturity
that would have yielded the buds we found.

99
00:07:36,120 --> 00:07:40,272
Adipocere. Forms on the body
in response to moisture on the ground.

100
00:07:40,360 --> 00:07:43,989
Trogid beetles.
They got a thing for decomposing flesh.

101
00:07:44,080 --> 00:07:47,629
- Found a couple on the burlap.
- The rest of the rosary.

102
00:07:47,720 --> 00:07:52,316
There's another freshly overturned
pile of dirt over here.

103
00:08:00,000 --> 00:08:03,151
- More adipocere.
- Not from the same body?

104
00:08:03,240 --> 00:08:06,835
Another body was buried here,
but it's gone now.

105
00:08:07,600 --> 00:08:09,352
Double homicide.

106
00:08:15,920 --> 00:08:17,717
<i>(drill whirs)</i>

107
00:08:21,480 --> 00:08:25,951
I spoke to the City Development Office.
The garden is being excavated next week.

108
00:08:26,040 --> 00:08:29,828
My guess is we interrupted a gangbanger
moving two murder victims.

109
00:08:29,920 --> 00:08:32,673
A gangbanger who buries his victim
with a rosary?

110
00:08:32,760 --> 00:08:37,629
- Did you find any gunshot wounds?
- No. Just head trauma.

111
00:08:37,720 --> 00:08:39,790
You really like this part, don't you?

112
00:08:39,880 --> 00:08:42,110
I like answers, yes.

113
00:08:44,600 --> 00:08:49,594
Localised staining
on the endocranial surface indicating...

114
00:08:49,680 --> 00:08:53,036
Subdural haematoma.
The head wound caused internal bleeding,

115
00:08:53,120 --> 00:08:55,634
but death was not instantaneous.

116
00:08:55,720 --> 00:08:58,553
<i>(Bones)</i> She may have been conscious
long after the assault.

117
00:08:58,640 --> 00:09:04,158
But there's no sign of bone remodelling.
She died soon after the assault.

118
00:09:05,240 --> 00:09:10,394
There's patterning on the ectocranial surface.
Whatever weapon was used, it left a mark.

119
00:09:10,480 --> 00:09:12,755
We're gonna bring in
the leader of Mara Muerte.

120
00:09:12,840 --> 00:09:15,832
See if we can identify
the gangbanger that got away.

121
00:09:15,920 --> 00:09:20,516
- Why would a gang leader cooperate?
- I'm gonna ask him very, very nicely, Bones.

122
00:09:20,600 --> 00:09:23,034
You know that book I'm reading?

123
00:09:23,120 --> 00:09:26,635
It says sarcasm is never helpful.
I could lend it to you if you want.

124
00:09:26,720 --> 00:09:31,510
I found <i>Spodoptera ornithogalli</i> and
<i>tetranychus urticae</i> on the shoe and victim.

125
00:09:31,600 --> 00:09:33,830
I also found <i>Notonectidae</i> and <i>Corixidae.</i>

126
00:09:33,920 --> 00:09:37,196
It's an aquatic fauna
typically found around ponds and streams.

127
00:09:37,280 --> 00:09:39,589
There are no ponds or streams
at the burial site.

128
00:09:39,680 --> 00:09:45,550
Here's the kicker. There was also evidence of
genetic material from a <i>franklinia alatamaha.</i>

129
00:09:45,640 --> 00:09:49,838
- You're kidding! Frankie Alabama?
- Did you hear what I said about sarcasm?

130
00:09:49,920 --> 00:09:53,879
It's a rare flowering plant
that hasn't been seen in the wild since 1800.

131
00:09:53,960 --> 00:09:57,270
The only known specimen in this area
outside a specialised garden

132
00:09:57,360 --> 00:10:00,397
was given to Senator Alan Corman as a gift.

133
00:10:00,480 --> 00:10:03,278
- I love going after senators.
- Whoa. Simmer down.

134
00:10:03,360 --> 00:10:05,351
We'll check the botanical garden first.

135
00:10:05,440 --> 00:10:07,829
Fine. It's at the White House.

136
00:10:07,920 --> 00:10:09,512
<i>(laughs)</i>

137
00:10:09,600 --> 00:10:12,114
You should do that
even less than normal people.

138
00:10:12,200 --> 00:10:15,317
Keep your eyes open
for backswimmers and water boatmen.

139
00:10:15,400 --> 00:10:17,550
The <i>Notonectidae</i> can be different colours.

140
00:10:17,640 --> 00:10:21,076
- That's a nice try. You're coming with us.
- I call shotgun.

141
00:10:22,840 --> 00:10:24,398
I called shotgun.

142
00:10:24,480 --> 00:10:27,552
What does it mean to a society
when niceties aren't observed?

143
00:10:27,640 --> 00:10:30,950
We got two bodies, one unaccounted for.
We've been shot at.

144
00:10:31,040 --> 00:10:36,194
And now we know that there's a gang member
walking around a US senator's place.

145
00:10:36,280 --> 00:10:38,191
Any theories?

146
00:10:38,280 --> 00:10:41,955
Come on, guys. Let's think of it
as a puzzle and there's a missing piece.

147
00:10:42,040 --> 00:10:46,830
I like puzzles. I find them relaxing. I just
finished <i>The Anatomy Lesson</i>, Rembrandt.

148
00:10:46,920 --> 00:10:50,230
- You're kidding, right?
- What do you find relaxing?

149
00:10:50,320 --> 00:10:54,632
- I... I restore vintage cars.
- I know what I find relaxing.

150
00:10:54,720 --> 00:10:57,109
Everybody finds
what you find relaxing relaxing.

151
00:10:57,200 --> 00:11:00,590
Corman is a big supporter
of business leaders in Central America.

152
00:11:00,680 --> 00:11:03,638
That means supporting regimes
that use death squads

153
00:11:03,720 --> 00:11:08,555
to silence any opposition from working
people, the same people who flee to the US.

154
00:11:08,640 --> 00:11:10,710
That's great. OK, let's focus.

155
00:11:10,800 --> 00:11:13,394
Now we have a link
between Corman and the Salvadorians.

156
00:11:13,480 --> 00:11:17,917
- You think the senator murdered two people?
- I think we got another piece of the puzzle.

157
00:11:25,840 --> 00:11:28,354
<i>(man) No sé qué vas a hacer,</i>
<i>pero tengo que podar el árbol.</i>

158
00:11:28,440 --> 00:11:32,149
Because of my husband's official work
in El Salvador,

159
00:11:32,240 --> 00:11:34,800
we formed a bond
with the country and the people.

160
00:11:34,880 --> 00:11:39,954
We have several Salvadorians working here.
I've sponsored quite a few for citizenship.

161
00:11:40,040 --> 00:11:42,759
Screening would keep out
members of death squads.

162
00:11:42,840 --> 00:11:44,193
Hodgins.

163
00:11:44,280 --> 00:11:47,795
Just because I'm anti-socialist
doesn't make me pro death squad.

164
00:11:47,880 --> 00:11:51,190
Dr Brennan has evidence that a gang member
has been on your property.

165
00:11:51,280 --> 00:11:53,840
We employ 20 staff members, give or take.

166
00:11:53,920 --> 00:11:57,196
All of our staff members
are either legal aliens or citizens.

167
00:11:57,280 --> 00:12:00,272
Our house manager's in charge
of hiring and managing them.

168
00:12:00,360 --> 00:12:03,352
Do you recognise this man?

169
00:12:03,440 --> 00:12:07,274
No. I assume he did something worse
than trespass on my property?

170
00:12:07,360 --> 00:12:09,715
- House manager, is he from El Salvador?
- Yes.

171
00:12:09,800 --> 00:12:13,509
- Agent, you didn't answer my question.
- We're investigating a death.

172
00:12:13,600 --> 00:12:18,310
- You understand why I can't talk about it.
- Could we show this to your house manager?

173
00:12:18,400 --> 00:12:20,516
Of course.

174
00:12:20,600 --> 00:12:23,160
<i>Franklinia alatamaha.</i> It's beautiful.

175
00:12:23,240 --> 00:12:25,834
We're the only people cultivating it privately.

176
00:12:25,920 --> 00:12:27,956
Do you have a pond on the property?

177
00:12:28,040 --> 00:12:30,474
Yes. On the other side of the shrubs.
It's small.

178
00:12:30,560 --> 00:12:35,031
- Could Dr Hodgins take a look at it?
- Of course. Be my guest.

179
00:12:35,120 --> 00:12:38,556
Logan, come say hello. We have guests.

180
00:12:38,640 --> 00:12:43,555
Our son. He's studying landscape architecture
at Georgetown. Likes to supervise the men.

181
00:12:43,640 --> 00:12:48,714
Logan, this is Special Agent Booth
from the FBI. His associate, Dr Brennan.

182
00:12:48,800 --> 00:12:52,952
- What's the FBI doing here?
- They'd like to ask Hector some questions.

183
00:12:53,040 --> 00:12:55,315
Yeah. Hey, Hector.

184
00:12:55,400 --> 00:12:58,039
<i>Ven. Hablamos para tú.</i>

185
00:13:02,160 --> 00:13:06,551
- Yes, sir?
- I'm Agent Booth. You recognise this guy?

186
00:13:07,360 --> 00:13:09,351
No, I don't think so.

187
00:13:09,440 --> 00:13:13,513
It could be José.
He works here sometimes as a gardener.

188
00:13:13,600 --> 00:13:15,955
Really? I don't think so.

189
00:13:16,040 --> 00:13:18,554
- José who?
- José Vargas.

190
00:13:18,640 --> 00:13:23,634
- Logan, Agent Booth said he was in a gang.
- A gang? No. No way.

191
00:13:23,720 --> 00:13:27,190
José's a nice guy. You know, wife and kid.

192
00:13:28,280 --> 00:13:31,636
I found both backswimmers
and water boatmen.

193
00:13:42,360 --> 00:13:43,349
What is it?

194
00:13:45,680 --> 00:13:47,671
Gladly.

195
00:13:49,160 --> 00:13:51,037
<i>Gracias.</i>

196
00:14:00,600 --> 00:14:04,149
Looks like we found the second body.

197
00:14:11,440 --> 00:14:16,116
Casings of tineid moths puts the time of
death about a year, six months before the girl.

198
00:14:16,200 --> 00:14:20,830
Heart-shaped pelvic inlet, long projections of
bone into the ribs suggest it's a male over 60.

199
00:14:20,920 --> 00:14:23,798
Anthropometrics suggests Hispanic origins.

200
00:14:23,880 --> 00:14:26,269
We reassembled the rosary
found on the woman.

201
00:14:26,360 --> 00:14:29,477
The carving of fire in the centrepiece
is an archetypal symbol

202
00:14:29,560 --> 00:14:34,031
found at an area of El Salvador since
the Chaparrastique volcano erupted in 1787.

203
00:14:34,120 --> 00:14:36,315
This indicates where the female is from?

204
00:14:36,400 --> 00:14:39,949
A village called Milagro de la Paz
in the southeast of the country.

205
00:14:40,040 --> 00:14:42,952
I was there three years ago
identifying death-squad victims.

206
00:14:43,040 --> 00:14:46,032
I finished the sketch of the woman.

207
00:14:46,120 --> 00:14:51,592
She was pregnant, starting over
in a new country, so I gave her a smile.

208
00:14:51,680 --> 00:14:54,353
- Made her look hopeful.
- Thanks, Angela.

209
00:14:54,440 --> 00:14:57,273
Let's clean the bones
so we can find a cause of death.

210
00:14:57,360 --> 00:14:59,351
I think I just found it.

211
00:15:04,880 --> 00:15:09,192
It's a bullet.
Looks like steel core, copperjacket.

212
00:15:09,280 --> 00:15:13,432
Military issue.
Those are kinds of weapons gangs like.

213
00:15:13,520 --> 00:15:20,392
They escape from death squads and get killed
by the same weapon they were running from.

214
00:15:22,240 --> 00:15:26,870
<i>(Booth)</i> I got José's address from Logan.
Let's check it out.

215
00:15:30,800 --> 00:15:31,835
Thanks.

216
00:15:31,920 --> 00:15:34,514
FBI. Make your presence known.

217
00:15:38,080 --> 00:15:40,640
Look. He has a family, a baby.

218
00:15:40,720 --> 00:15:43,951
Is anybody here?
You don't have to be afraid.

219
00:15:45,080 --> 00:15:48,436
<i>¿Hay alguien aquí? No tiene que tener miedo.</i>

220
00:15:48,520 --> 00:15:52,308
Of course they're gonna be afraid, Bones.
I have a gun.

221
00:15:53,240 --> 00:15:57,074
Milagro de la Paz.
That's where the victims are from.

222
00:15:57,160 --> 00:15:59,310
They were here. The bottle's still warm.

223
00:15:59,400 --> 00:16:01,834
- They're still here.
- How do you know?

224
00:16:01,920 --> 00:16:05,310
They're prepared for this kind of thing.

225
00:16:07,720 --> 00:16:12,748
Hiding from death squads,
people learn to build false walls.

226
00:16:12,840 --> 00:16:19,439
Closet. OK, hold on, Bones. Let's just pretend
that I'm the cop for a second, OK?

227
00:16:32,880 --> 00:16:35,997
<i>Yo no sé nada. Por favor, yo no hice nada.</i>

228
00:16:36,080 --> 00:16:39,868
<i>Solamente queremos saber dónde está José.</i>

229
00:16:39,960 --> 00:16:42,315
<i>ÉI estará bien si no ha hecho nada malo.</i>

230
00:16:42,400 --> 00:16:43,913
What did you say?

231
00:16:44,000 --> 00:16:47,470
That we want to talk to José,
that they have nothing to worry about.

232
00:16:47,560 --> 00:16:49,869
Wanna be deported?
Wanna see your baby again?

233
00:16:49,960 --> 00:16:53,157
Because if he was born here,
we can keep him.

234
00:16:53,240 --> 00:16:55,390
Booth, stop! She's frightened enough.

235
00:16:55,480 --> 00:16:57,710
- We have a double murder.
- She didn't do it.

236
00:16:57,800 --> 00:17:02,112
Just tell her what I said. Tell her we're
calling Immigration and we'll get to José.

237
00:17:02,200 --> 00:17:05,556
No. She's lived with intimidation
her whole life. I won't add to it.

238
00:17:05,640 --> 00:17:08,791
You're acting like I'm gonna hurt her.
I just want information.

239
00:17:08,880 --> 00:17:13,032
I am asking you as a favour
not to make me do this.

240
00:17:13,120 --> 00:17:15,634
To scare her.

241
00:17:15,720 --> 00:17:17,073
Please.

242
00:17:20,280 --> 00:17:21,713
This is interesting.

243
00:17:21,800 --> 00:17:24,917
Interesting or horrible?
Sometimes it's the same thing with you.

244
00:17:25,000 --> 00:17:27,992
This hole in the sternum,
it's not a gunshot wound.

245
00:17:28,080 --> 00:17:30,275
It's a sternal foramen.

246
00:17:31,520 --> 00:17:36,071
I found the same thing on the female victim.
It seemed like a meaningless anomaly.

247
00:17:36,160 --> 00:17:40,153
It's a hereditary condition.
The two victims were related.

248
00:17:40,240 --> 00:17:42,390
Based on their ages, father and daughter.

249
00:17:42,480 --> 00:17:45,677
So father and daughter
buried next to each other, right?

250
00:17:45,760 --> 00:17:50,231
Then dug up.
But then the father was re-buried. Why?

251
00:17:50,320 --> 00:17:54,313
The gangbanger was taking the daughter
to be re-buried when the cops got him.

252
00:17:54,400 --> 00:17:59,155
This is the stuff that Booth is good at,
the murky ways of the human heart, all that.

253
00:17:59,240 --> 00:18:02,198
- We work the hard evidence.
- We've used up all the evidence.

254
00:18:02,280 --> 00:18:06,671
OK. OK, let's just... You know what?
Let's just pretend we're Booth, OK?

255
00:18:06,760 --> 00:18:08,751
Ooh! Let me try!

256
00:18:10,920 --> 00:18:13,718
The daughter got pregnant from the killer
and came here.

257
00:18:13,800 --> 00:18:18,828
- He catches up to him. They fight.
- He joins a gang and then kills her.

258
00:18:18,920 --> 00:18:23,152
The father comes after him seeking revenge
and the killer kills him.

259
00:18:23,240 --> 00:18:27,711
No, no. The father's death preceded
the daughter's by at least six months.

260
00:18:27,800 --> 00:18:31,952
I've found something.
I can't get this bullet out of the pelvic bone.

261
00:18:32,040 --> 00:18:33,234
Oh, wow.

262
00:18:33,320 --> 00:18:37,632
The bone started healing around the bullet.
See the remodelling?

263
00:18:37,720 --> 00:18:40,359
This wound healed years ago.

264
00:18:40,440 --> 00:18:43,591
- He didn't die by being shot.
- Tough old bastard.

265
00:18:44,320 --> 00:18:47,437
- How was he murdered?
- He wasrt murdered.

266
00:18:47,520 --> 00:18:51,877
- Metastatic carcinoma.
- Probably originating in the prostate.

267
00:18:51,960 --> 00:18:55,635
So he survives being shot,
then he dies of cancer?

268
00:18:55,720 --> 00:18:58,553
- Mega tough old bastard.
- Yeah.

269
00:19:05,360 --> 00:19:08,079
- Anything?
- Yeah.

270
00:19:08,160 --> 00:19:13,996
Immigration has the wife. She got a lawyer
from the Salvadorian League of... something.

271
00:19:14,080 --> 00:19:16,833
She's not giving us anything about José.

272
00:19:16,920 --> 00:19:19,514
- Are you mad at me?
- No.

273
00:19:20,800 --> 00:19:24,395
But I could have gotten something
if you hadrt got all mushy on me.

274
00:19:24,480 --> 00:19:26,994
I was uncomfortable with...

275
00:19:27,080 --> 00:19:29,355
You always say I'm not a cop.

276
00:19:30,280 --> 00:19:34,239
You're right. Especially in a situation like that.

277
00:19:34,320 --> 00:19:37,710
- It's OK. We're not gonna need her anyway.
- Really? Why?

278
00:19:37,800 --> 00:19:41,475
Cos I had the Gang Unit put a lean
on Roberto Ortez, the head of Mara Muerte.

279
00:19:41,560 --> 00:19:43,915
- The gang that José belongs to?
- Yeah.

280
00:19:44,000 --> 00:19:46,912
They convinced Ortez
to bring José in for questioning.

281
00:19:47,000 --> 00:19:51,437
- But why would he do that?
- Ortez's sister is in the can for possession.

282
00:19:51,520 --> 00:19:54,910
- I promised him I could make that go away.
- Can you?

283
00:19:55,000 --> 00:19:57,070
It's a local beef, I'm a federal...

284
00:19:57,160 --> 00:20:01,551
But hey, you know, I'm a cop,
and thank God for bad sisters, huh?

285
00:20:24,040 --> 00:20:28,318
He has a collapsed lung, broken ribs,
one arm is broken, shoulder's dislocated.

286
00:20:28,400 --> 00:20:30,436
- But we can talk to him?
- You can try.

287
00:20:30,520 --> 00:20:32,590
Hey, thanks.

288
00:20:37,080 --> 00:20:40,868
Your own guys? They'd do this to you?
Jeez, I wish I had my own gang.

289
00:20:40,960 --> 00:20:43,997
I don't belong to no gang. I'm a gardener.

290
00:20:44,080 --> 00:20:47,072
Oh, a gardener
with a Mara Muerte tattoo on his neck

291
00:20:47,160 --> 00:20:50,197
who can now understand English
and plants dead bodies.

292
00:20:50,280 --> 00:20:54,558
- Maybe that stuff's private.
- You're an illegal immigrant, a gang member.

293
00:20:54,640 --> 00:20:59,589
You're under arrest for transporting a dead
body and you're under suspicion for murder.

294
00:20:59,680 --> 00:21:04,993
I'm gonna call ICE and have you
and your wife deported back to El Salvador.

295
00:21:05,080 --> 00:21:08,789
- I got a son.
- Forget it. We keep the son.

296
00:21:08,880 --> 00:21:11,474
That's my son. It's my only son.

297
00:21:12,320 --> 00:21:13,719
- You got kids?
- No.

298
00:21:13,800 --> 00:21:16,678
- Yes, you do.
- Difference is I'm a fit father.

299
00:21:16,760 --> 00:21:20,799
I'm not murdering guys and little girls,
burying them, digging them up.

300
00:21:20,880 --> 00:21:25,112
Booth, I don't think
he murdered those people.

301
00:21:25,200 --> 00:21:27,350
You can tell by looking at his x-rays?

302
00:21:27,440 --> 00:21:32,833
He has the same genetic condition
the two victims had. A sternal foramen.

303
00:21:33,720 --> 00:21:38,191
- They were probably his sister and his father.
- That true?

304
00:21:38,280 --> 00:21:44,833
Hey, buddy, you want to be on my good side,
cos I wasrtjoking about keeping your kid.

305
00:21:44,920 --> 00:21:46,911
Yes.

306
00:21:47,000 --> 00:21:49,958
It was my sister. It was my father.

307
00:21:50,040 --> 00:21:55,239
Your father died of natural causes, fine.
But your sister was murdered.

308
00:21:56,840 --> 00:22:02,551
You know what? Forget it. Gang is the only
family he cares about. Enjoy your trip home.

309
00:22:02,640 --> 00:22:08,397
And have fun explaining to your wife
why she doesn't have a baby in her arms.

310
00:22:09,760 --> 00:22:12,194
Give us something.

311
00:22:12,280 --> 00:22:15,955
Help us to do the right thing for your sister.

312
00:22:17,040 --> 00:22:19,838
- I cannot.
- Just anything.

313
00:22:22,240 --> 00:22:24,913
At least you could tell us their names.

314
00:22:27,480 --> 00:22:29,675
You want their names, huh?

315
00:22:30,920 --> 00:22:34,310
Duarte was our family name.

316
00:22:35,280 --> 00:22:38,795
María was my sister.
Our father was named Agustín.

317
00:22:40,880 --> 00:22:43,314
That's all I can tell you.

318
00:22:48,600 --> 00:22:51,319
- José's sister hated him.
- Why?

319
00:22:51,400 --> 00:22:53,789
She didn't approve of his associations.

320
00:22:53,880 --> 00:22:59,352
You mean associations like the leader
of one of the most murderous street gangs?

321
00:22:59,440 --> 00:23:01,431
If she hated José so much,
why did he move her?

322
00:23:01,520 --> 00:23:06,310
Their burial site was threatened. He wanted to
move her to a better place, and his father.

323
00:23:06,400 --> 00:23:08,595
Real family guy, you know?

324
00:23:09,720 --> 00:23:13,998
I'm not the leader of the whole gang,
just the DC chapter.

325
00:23:14,080 --> 00:23:17,038
You shot at us
so José could have a chance to get away?

326
00:23:17,120 --> 00:23:21,079
Mara Muerte takes care of its own,
even a throwaway like José.

327
00:23:21,160 --> 00:23:23,594
- Can I ask you something?
- Go ahead.

328
00:23:23,680 --> 00:23:26,433
José's all beaten up
so he won't tell us anything.

329
00:23:26,520 --> 00:23:29,478
You don't even ask for a lawyer,
but you hardly stop talking.

330
00:23:29,560 --> 00:23:32,279
- Bones.
- Hey, I'm the boss, lady, OK?

331
00:23:32,360 --> 00:23:36,353
José's a <i>sobrinado.</i>
He's not as smart as me.

332
00:23:36,440 --> 00:23:38,510
You intimidate him into silence,

333
00:23:38,600 --> 00:23:43,674
but you can walk in to the FBI, say what you
want and walk away like you own the place?

334
00:23:43,760 --> 00:23:47,719
- That's right.
- Who would have the guts to kill his sister?

335
00:23:47,800 --> 00:23:49,392
Who cares, man?

336
00:23:49,480 --> 00:23:54,235
- It's the most feared gang in the city.
- She wasrt <i>my</i> sister, man.

337
00:23:54,320 --> 00:23:58,632
There had to be somebody else in the gang,
somebody more important than José.

338
00:23:58,720 --> 00:24:01,917
You know what, lady? You think too much.

339
00:24:02,000 --> 00:24:06,232
Maybe you need a man like me to get your
mind off things. You know what I'm saying?

340
00:24:06,320 --> 00:24:09,551
I can be your adorir Salvadorian.

341
00:24:16,400 --> 00:24:18,550
I don't know who killed José's sister.

342
00:24:18,640 --> 00:24:24,909
But I'll tell you what. Because I like you
so much, if I find out who did it, I'll kill him.

343
00:24:37,240 --> 00:24:42,109
You been waiting for me? Push that button
again and we can go down together, <i>chulas.</i>

344
00:24:42,200 --> 00:24:45,795
You think you can intimidate people
into doing what you want?

345
00:24:45,880 --> 00:24:47,871
OK, I'll push it myself.

346
00:24:50,560 --> 00:24:52,676
How do you handle
someone who isn't afraid?

347
00:24:52,760 --> 00:24:55,149
Just get out of my way.

348
00:24:55,240 --> 00:24:57,959
I said move your ass, ma'am.

349
00:24:58,040 --> 00:24:59,473
I wouldn't...

350
00:25:01,920 --> 00:25:04,229
That's gonna hurt in the morning.

351
00:25:19,960 --> 00:25:22,030
Feel better?

352
00:25:22,120 --> 00:25:24,839
Yeah. I really do.

353
00:25:31,680 --> 00:25:34,433
- You beat up a gang leader?
- Booth told you that?

354
00:25:34,520 --> 00:25:39,036
You did.
You got into a fight with a gangbanger.

355
00:25:40,400 --> 00:25:42,595
- You're mad at me?
- The guy's a killer.

356
00:25:42,680 --> 00:25:45,752
Angela, relax. We were in the FBI building.

357
00:25:45,840 --> 00:25:50,675
I know you're all about self-reliance
and standing up for yourself,

358
00:25:50,760 --> 00:25:55,834
but now, as your friend, and knowing
how much you hate psychology here,

359
00:25:55,920 --> 00:25:57,911
you need therapy.

360
00:25:58,000 --> 00:26:02,232
I'm sorry I upset you.
It's just that I've dealt with him before.

361
00:26:02,320 --> 00:26:06,029
- With who?
- People who get what they want through fear.

362
00:26:06,120 --> 00:26:08,588
Gangbangers, members of death squads.

363
00:26:08,680 --> 00:26:11,990
I know it's psychology again,
but you said "him" - one guy.

364
00:26:12,080 --> 00:26:17,473
I didn't mean Ortez specifically.
I meant people like him.

365
00:26:18,760 --> 00:26:22,116
- On my last trip to El Salvador...
- I remember.

366
00:26:22,200 --> 00:26:25,397
I tried to get you to go to Italy with me.

367
00:26:26,800 --> 00:26:30,998
I was in a tent
set up by one of the grave sites.

368
00:26:32,160 --> 00:26:35,550
I was working
with the remains of a young girl.

369
00:26:35,640 --> 00:26:37,631
Maybe 13.

370
00:26:38,880 --> 00:26:42,919
She'd been shot in the head
and dumped into a well.

371
00:26:44,080 --> 00:26:49,234
This cop shows up and he might
have been a soldier, it's not easy to tell.

372
00:26:49,320 --> 00:26:53,108
I thought he was there to guard me,
but he told me to stop.

373
00:26:53,200 --> 00:26:55,839
When I refused, he called in two others.

374
00:26:55,920 --> 00:26:58,434
They put a bag over my head

375
00:26:58,520 --> 00:27:03,640
and tossed me into a cell
with a dirt floor and no windows.

376
00:27:03,720 --> 00:27:07,838
- For how long?
- Later I found out it was three days.

377
00:27:07,920 --> 00:27:11,390
But I thought it was a week, maybe more.

378
00:27:12,600 --> 00:27:17,355
He came in every day
and made me believe I was going to die.

379
00:27:17,440 --> 00:27:20,716
He said that he'd shoot me
and toss me into a well

380
00:27:20,800 --> 00:27:25,669
and that no one would ever know
who I was or what became of me.

381
00:27:27,440 --> 00:27:32,036
I promised myself,
if I ever had the chance, I'd get even.

382
00:27:36,560 --> 00:27:39,154
That doesn't mean I need therapy.

383
00:27:41,360 --> 00:27:45,319
I identified the type of wood
in the weapon that killed María.

384
00:27:46,320 --> 00:27:48,834
Am I interrupting a female moment?

385
00:27:48,920 --> 00:27:50,911
No. What was the wood?

386
00:27:51,000 --> 00:27:53,878
Quarter-sawn Cumaru.
Definitely not from a shovel handle.

387
00:27:53,960 --> 00:27:56,633
What is made out of quarter-sawn Cumaru?

388
00:27:56,720 --> 00:28:00,349
- Very expensive furniture.
- Senatorially expensive?

389
00:28:00,440 --> 00:28:02,590
Most definitely.

390
00:28:05,360 --> 00:28:08,397
- I don't recognise her, no.
- Neither do I, I'm afraid.

391
00:28:08,480 --> 00:28:10,835
- How about you, Hector?
- Her name was María.

392
00:28:10,920 --> 00:28:15,198
She used to work as a maid here.
She had papers.

393
00:28:15,280 --> 00:28:18,352
Fake ones. Probably supplied
by our neighbourhood gang.

394
00:28:18,440 --> 00:28:21,477
Hector couldn't be expected
to identify forged papers.

395
00:28:21,560 --> 00:28:23,630
What happened to María?

396
00:28:23,720 --> 00:28:26,678
One day she didn't show up for work.
That's all.

397
00:28:26,760 --> 00:28:29,320
Did she interact
with anyone here besides José?

398
00:28:29,400 --> 00:28:32,233
I don't know about that kind of thing.

399
00:28:32,320 --> 00:28:34,436
What kind of thing, Hector?

400
00:28:36,040 --> 00:28:38,235
I don't know anything.

401
00:28:38,320 --> 00:28:40,788
What do you mean, Hector?

402
00:28:43,680 --> 00:28:47,992
- Was María involved with the senator?
- What? Of course not!

403
00:28:48,080 --> 00:28:50,469
No.

404
00:28:50,560 --> 00:28:55,918
- No, not the senator.
- Well, tell the truth, Hector. This is the FBI.

405
00:28:56,920 --> 00:28:59,150
Logan.

406
00:28:59,240 --> 00:29:01,800
She was involved with Logan.

407
00:29:03,720 --> 00:29:05,756
What kind of involved?

408
00:29:05,840 --> 00:29:07,831
I'd rather not say.

409
00:29:09,880 --> 00:29:11,677
María's dead, Logan.

410
00:29:12,640 --> 00:29:14,631
María's dead?

411
00:29:18,240 --> 00:29:19,958
Yes.

412
00:29:20,040 --> 00:29:22,634
Of course that changes things.

413
00:29:25,000 --> 00:29:26,991
María and I were...

414
00:29:28,040 --> 00:29:31,476
What? Were lovers?
Bones, what the hell are you doing?

415
00:29:31,560 --> 00:29:34,028
How long have you had this bed?

416
00:29:35,200 --> 00:29:38,192
Since I was, like, 15. Why?

417
00:29:38,280 --> 00:29:40,396
Do you know what kind of wood it is?

418
00:29:40,480 --> 00:29:44,473
Curu... Cumaru, something like that. Why?

419
00:29:44,560 --> 00:29:50,271
Because María's skull was banged in
by something made out of Cumaru wood.

420
00:29:50,360 --> 00:29:53,875
There's dried blood and skin on this post.

421
00:30:00,880 --> 00:30:04,873
I caught María dancing once in the hallway.

422
00:30:06,880 --> 00:30:11,476
She thought no one was watching,
but I was watching.

423
00:30:13,600 --> 00:30:15,636
I'd noticed her before.

424
00:30:16,760 --> 00:30:19,718
She was very pretty.

425
00:30:20,640 --> 00:30:23,154
More than what these pictures tell you.

426
00:30:23,240 --> 00:30:28,109
Logan, I will say again that I do not advise
answering questions. You're not under arrest.

427
00:30:28,200 --> 00:30:33,877
Perhaps you'd like to check with the senator
and see if he'd rather I arrested Logan.

428
00:30:33,960 --> 00:30:37,191
Because, you know,
I'm sure the press would love that.

429
00:30:38,920 --> 00:30:41,388
When did you start
having a sexual relationship?

430
00:30:41,480 --> 00:30:44,950
- Perhaps six months ago.
- You kept it a secret?

431
00:30:45,040 --> 00:30:49,352
María was certain that
if my parents found out, she'd be fired.

432
00:30:49,440 --> 00:30:51,635
Were you aware she was here illegally?

433
00:30:51,720 --> 00:30:53,995
I advise you: Do not answer that question.

434
00:30:54,080 --> 00:30:57,152
Were you aware that she was pregnant?

435
00:30:58,240 --> 00:31:00,549
María was pregnant?

436
00:31:02,680 --> 00:31:07,151
- There's no proof that you were the father.
- No. Shut up.

437
00:31:08,440 --> 00:31:10,431
Of course I'm the father.

438
00:31:20,280 --> 00:31:22,919
- And the father?
- A powerful man with a lot to lose.

439
00:31:23,000 --> 00:31:25,673
But why kill her?
Why not have her deported?

440
00:31:25,760 --> 00:31:28,399
- That leaves Hector.
- He hires the servants.

441
00:31:28,480 --> 00:31:32,439
I mean, one of them gets pregnant,
he feels like it's his mess to clean up.

442
00:31:32,520 --> 00:31:36,035
We still can't figure out how María's skull
was fractured by the bedpost.

443
00:31:36,120 --> 00:31:39,715
That's sort of your line of work, Bones.
So go have fun.

444
00:31:40,600 --> 00:31:44,115
<i>(Angela)</i> Your top three suspects
are Senator Corman, 6'1",

445
00:31:44,200 --> 00:31:47,715
Logan Corman, 5'10",
and Hector Santiago, 5'6".

446
00:31:47,800 --> 00:31:49,711
María was 5'1".

447
00:31:49,800 --> 00:31:53,270
The bed is a California King
with seven-foot posts.

448
00:31:53,360 --> 00:31:57,831
<i>(Bones)</i> And assuming that they argued
near the foot of the bed...

449
00:31:57,920 --> 00:32:01,037
Given their heights,
the angle of impact doesn't match.

450
00:32:01,120 --> 00:32:04,556
Her skull connects well below
where you found the traces of blood.

451
00:32:04,640 --> 00:32:06,835
What if they were standing on the bed?

452
00:32:06,920 --> 00:32:10,037
It's high enough,
but her head struck the outside of the post.

453
00:32:10,120 --> 00:32:14,671
How tall would her assailant have to be
to fit the evidence?

454
00:32:18,160 --> 00:32:21,118
- That... That's tall.
- 7'8".

455
00:32:21,200 --> 00:32:23,953
Somebody you'd notice around the house.

456
00:32:24,040 --> 00:32:27,237
- Let's think outside the box.
- What do you mean, go non-human?

457
00:32:27,320 --> 00:32:31,108
No. What else explains
striking the bedpost in that manner?

458
00:32:31,200 --> 00:32:33,430
I guess falling.

459
00:32:33,520 --> 00:32:36,592
Falling? María was a maid.

460
00:32:36,680 --> 00:32:40,275
Do you have
a schematic version of the room?

461
00:32:43,600 --> 00:32:46,114
If she fell backwards...

462
00:32:46,200 --> 00:32:49,078
But it doesn't explain
the damage done to her skull.

463
00:32:49,160 --> 00:32:52,197
What force does explain the damage?

464
00:32:52,280 --> 00:32:58,674
206 pounds per square inch, which means she
would've had to have fallen from a height of...

465
00:32:59,600 --> 00:33:02,512
- It's no good.
- I know what happened.

466
00:33:02,600 --> 00:33:04,875
She was yanked off the ladder.

467
00:33:04,960 --> 00:33:08,157
- You mean somebody pulled her off?
- Yes.

468
00:33:08,240 --> 00:33:10,390
The missing 84 pounds per square inch

469
00:33:10,480 --> 00:33:14,871
can be explained by a hard yank
from a full-grown man.

470
00:33:19,880 --> 00:33:25,034
I don't know if it's murder, but someone
is definitely responsible for María's death.

471
00:33:25,840 --> 00:33:28,308
This is not about the gang.

472
00:33:28,400 --> 00:33:31,631
The gang had nothing to do with her death.

473
00:33:31,720 --> 00:33:34,598
María was pulled off that ladder.

474
00:33:34,680 --> 00:33:37,114
Who are you protecting?

475
00:33:37,200 --> 00:33:41,113
- I got nothing to say.
- What did the senator offer you?

476
00:33:41,200 --> 00:33:43,794
Asylum for the whole family?

477
00:33:44,800 --> 00:33:46,756
I know what happened.

478
00:33:46,840 --> 00:33:52,915
Your father died of cancer around
the same time your wife was pregnant.

479
00:33:53,000 --> 00:33:55,958
You wanted your child
to be born an American citizen.

480
00:33:56,040 --> 00:34:00,079
So you couldn't report your father's death
for fear of being deported.

481
00:34:00,160 --> 00:34:03,709
You buried him yourself, in the garden.

482
00:34:05,200 --> 00:34:10,069
And when your sister died,
you buried her in the same place.

483
00:34:11,040 --> 00:34:17,229
As my father died, he said to me,
"You take care of your sister."

484
00:34:21,000 --> 00:34:26,757
You joined Mara Muerte so you could get fake
papers, so she could work for the senator.

485
00:34:26,840 --> 00:34:28,558
María...

486
00:34:28,640 --> 00:34:31,200
María, man, she was so angry. She would...

487
00:34:31,280 --> 00:34:35,193
She'd get so angry,
sometimes she just didn't speak to me.

488
00:34:35,280 --> 00:34:38,590
She didn't understand what you had to do
for her and your family?

489
00:34:38,680 --> 00:34:43,276
It was the only way for me
to keep my promise to my father.

490
00:34:45,680 --> 00:34:47,671
Look at me now, huh?

491
00:34:48,760 --> 00:34:55,154
All because I wanted to give my sister
and my father a beautiful place to rest.

492
00:34:56,120 --> 00:34:58,873
It's near... It's near a pond.

493
00:34:59,760 --> 00:35:01,751
It's beautiful, huh?

494
00:35:06,160 --> 00:35:08,151
It's all for nothing.

495
00:35:09,840 --> 00:35:12,400
My family's ruined.

496
00:35:15,080 --> 00:35:17,275
- She didn't fall.
- No, she was pushed.

497
00:35:17,360 --> 00:35:21,638
No, Senator. Actually, she was pulled.
Probably off that ladder.

498
00:35:21,720 --> 00:35:24,871
- Pulled? Pulled by who?
- Perhaps by your son or the senator.

499
00:35:24,960 --> 00:35:28,669
Oh, my God!
I do not pull maids off of ladders.

500
00:35:28,760 --> 00:35:31,877
- Will you please open that up?
- Why would they do that?

501
00:35:31,960 --> 00:35:35,077
- Because María was pregnant by your son.
- What?!

502
00:35:35,160 --> 00:35:39,073
Even if that were true,
that is not how we would handle the situation.

503
00:35:39,160 --> 00:35:41,754
- You'd have her deported.
- It would be handled.

504
00:35:41,840 --> 00:35:45,230
And not by pulling her off a ladder.

505
00:35:45,320 --> 00:35:48,118
Senator, would you mind reaching up?

506
00:35:48,200 --> 00:35:51,078
- What is that gonna prove?
- Are you refusing, sir?

507
00:35:51,160 --> 00:35:53,833
I'm trained in kinesiology,
the study of human movement.

508
00:35:53,920 --> 00:35:56,673
And you're gonna be able to tell
who pulled her off?

509
00:35:56,760 --> 00:36:00,958
- Absolutely, yes.
- Oh, for God sake, Alan. Just do it. Just do it.

510
00:36:01,040 --> 00:36:03,031
Fine.

511
00:36:06,960 --> 00:36:09,918
Well? Was it me?

512
00:36:10,000 --> 00:36:12,958
- Hector?
<i>- Si?</i>

513
00:36:13,040 --> 00:36:16,191
Would you please
pull me down off this ladder?

514
00:36:16,280 --> 00:36:18,919
No. No, I won't.

515
00:36:19,000 --> 00:36:21,230
Hector, just do as she asks.

516
00:36:22,040 --> 00:36:23,758
Hector.

517
00:36:25,440 --> 00:36:27,590
How did it happen, Hector?

518
00:36:27,680 --> 00:36:29,830
You told her to stay out of Logars room.

519
00:36:29,920 --> 00:36:32,718
You didn't approve.
You knew what was going on.

520
00:36:32,800 --> 00:36:36,588
- Hector?
- If it wasrt you, just pull me down.

521
00:36:37,480 --> 00:36:41,712
María defied you. She went to Logars room.
You got angry. You pulled her off the ladder.

522
00:36:41,800 --> 00:36:44,360
It was an accident.

523
00:36:48,920 --> 00:36:52,469
Yeah... It was an accident.

524
00:36:54,760 --> 00:36:58,639
- I can't believe that worked.
- Psychology. It's a very powerful force.

525
00:36:58,720 --> 00:37:03,191
I gave her 500 dollars and I drove her home.

526
00:37:03,280 --> 00:37:05,510
I thought she was gonna go to a doctor.

527
00:37:05,600 --> 00:37:07,909
She was afraid she'd get deported.

528
00:37:08,000 --> 00:37:11,436
- You should have told us.
- You don't want to know.

529
00:37:11,520 --> 00:37:14,637
You don't want to know about any of this.

530
00:37:14,720 --> 00:37:18,190
I know my job. I know what you want.

531
00:37:20,640 --> 00:37:26,829
Hector Alvarado, I'm placing you under arrest
on suspicion of manslaughter.

532
00:37:35,360 --> 00:37:38,238
Booth? A message
from the Gang Task Force Unit.

533
00:37:38,320 --> 00:37:42,598
Mara Muerte has put a hit out
on your lady scientist.

534
00:37:43,400 --> 00:37:45,311
- Oh, man.
- Any response?

535
00:37:45,400 --> 00:37:48,915
Yeah. Just tell 'em...
tell 'em I got the message.

536
00:37:49,000 --> 00:37:51,389
- And tell 'em thanks.
- Sure.

537
00:38:01,000 --> 00:38:04,993
<i>Señor, acepta en tus brazos</i>
<i>las almas de tus hijos devotos,</i>

538
00:38:05,080 --> 00:38:08,072
<i>María Duarte y Agustín Duarte.</i>

539
00:38:08,160 --> 00:38:13,792
<i>Que tu Espíritu Santo los ilumine,</i>
<i>dándoles bienvenida en tu amor.</i>

540
00:38:13,880 --> 00:38:18,192
<i>Padre Nuestro que estás en los Cielos,</i>
<i>santificado sea tu nombre.</i>

541
00:38:18,280 --> 00:38:23,559
<i>Véngase tu reino. Hágase tu voluntad</i>
<i>en la Tierra como en el Cielo.</i>

542
00:38:23,640 --> 00:38:28,236
<i>Danos hoy nuestro pan de cada día,</i>
<i>y perdona nuestras ofensas, así como...</i>

543
00:38:28,320 --> 00:38:33,792
This is nice of you. Not many people
would pay for a funeral like this.

544
00:38:33,880 --> 00:38:36,678
Where's Booth? He said he'd come.

545
00:38:58,560 --> 00:39:01,233
- Are you crazy?
- You put a hit out on my partner?

546
00:39:01,320 --> 00:39:05,757
She's not FBI.
I never said anything about FBI.

547
00:39:05,840 --> 00:39:08,752
She's my partner, <i>esé</i>!
And if anything happens to her,

548
00:39:08,840 --> 00:39:12,196
I will find you and I will kill you.
I won't think twice.

549
00:39:12,280 --> 00:39:15,317
Come here. Look in my eyes. Look at my face.

550
00:39:15,400 --> 00:39:20,474
If anything happens to her, I will kill you.
This is between you and me.

551
00:39:20,560 --> 00:39:25,429
And nobody sees, nobody knows.
You got nothing to prove. Understand?

552
00:39:25,520 --> 00:39:27,511
You understand?

553
00:39:28,920 --> 00:39:35,109
I thought so. Now, if you don't mind, I'll leave
first because I have somewhere I have to be.

554
00:39:46,160 --> 00:39:50,233
- I will pay you back for this funeral.
- Don't worry about it.

555
00:39:50,320 --> 00:39:54,950
- It's my family. It's my duty.
- Arert you leaving for El Salvador tonight?

556
00:39:55,040 --> 00:39:57,508
Well, my child is an American.

557
00:39:59,680 --> 00:40:01,318
He's...

558
00:40:01,400 --> 00:40:03,994
He's not gonna grow up
the way that Rosa and I did.

559
00:40:04,080 --> 00:40:07,709
<i>Lo regresamos, de alguna manera.</i>

560
00:40:07,800 --> 00:40:12,078
- She says that we're gonna bring him back.
- I understand.

561
00:40:12,160 --> 00:40:16,631
One way or another,
your son will have a better life than you did.

562
00:40:16,720 --> 00:40:18,915
<i>- Gracias.</i>
<i>- Gracias.</i>

563
00:40:30,080 --> 00:40:35,234
- Am I in trouble?
- You're late for a funeral. Of course you are.

564
00:40:35,880 --> 00:40:37,279
Sorry.

565
00:40:37,360 --> 00:40:39,510
I apologise.

566
00:40:39,600 --> 00:40:42,558
- Everything OK here?
- Where were you?

567
00:40:43,080 --> 00:40:47,471
- I had something to do.
- More important than a funeral?

568
00:40:48,480 --> 00:40:50,675
I thought so at the time.

569
00:40:51,680 --> 00:40:55,389
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Nada Es Para Siempre" by Elefante)</i>

570
00:41:31,760 --> 00:41:36,993
Visiontext Subtitles: Simon Campbell

571
00:41:40,440 --> 00:41:41,759
What's that mean?

572
00:41:42,520 --> 00:41:44,511
ENGLISH SDH

