1
00:00:01,080 --> 00:00:04,390
The victim was stabbed upward of 30 times.
Every rib is marked.

2
00:00:04,480 --> 00:00:07,711
- Vertebrae sternal, vertebrae costal.
- What kind of weapon?

3
00:00:07,800 --> 00:00:11,839
Vacations in the desert.
It's like lunching at the dump.

4
00:00:11,920 --> 00:00:14,070
Pointed, with no cutting edge.

5
00:00:14,160 --> 00:00:16,720
Like a giant ice pick.

6
00:00:16,800 --> 00:00:18,358
Whoa, Angela.

7
00:00:18,440 --> 00:00:20,795
Or a sharpened screwdriver.

8
00:00:20,880 --> 00:00:25,795
- We told her, "Cover up, avoid melanoma"?
- Who's the guy?

9
00:00:25,880 --> 00:00:28,952
- Her boyfriend Kirk.
- Angela has a boyfriend?

10
00:00:29,040 --> 00:00:33,033
Every year for three weeks,
Angela has a boyfriend and a vacation.

11
00:00:33,120 --> 00:00:37,875
Whoa. Playing house in a postboho
rustic artist's cabin in the desert

12
00:00:37,960 --> 00:00:42,351
with her pseudo-celebrity photographer
boyfriend. That is not a vacation.

13
00:00:42,440 --> 00:00:44,590
Eight months to a year dead, correct?

14
00:00:44,680 --> 00:00:49,117
Yeah, yeah. Pupal casings, maggots,
blah blah blah. Eight months to a year.

15
00:00:49,200 --> 00:00:53,159
Angela, we're betting.
Are you using Crisco or butter for sunscreen?

16
00:00:53,600 --> 00:00:57,229
Hey, Brennan,
could I talk to you in private, please?

17
00:01:01,160 --> 00:01:03,879
- <i>You'll think I'm crazy.</i>
- Boyfriend trouble?

18
00:01:03,960 --> 00:01:07,475
No, I'd... I'd just send it to you,
but the sheriff won't let me.

19
00:01:07,560 --> 00:01:09,232
Send what?

20
00:01:09,320 --> 00:01:13,074
Somebody left a human skull in a box
on the sheriff's porch.

21
00:01:13,160 --> 00:01:16,072
He says it was probably a Navaho
who respects the dead,

22
00:01:16,160 --> 00:01:19,675
but doesn't wanna get pulled in
to the whole white justice system.

23
00:01:19,760 --> 00:01:23,912
The thing is is that Kirk went out
into the desert five days ago on a photo shoot

24
00:01:24,000 --> 00:01:27,356
and he hasn't come back.
Nobody can find him or his guide.

25
00:01:27,440 --> 00:01:30,671
- You think the skull is Kirk's?
- <i>No. No.</i>

26
00:01:30,760 --> 00:01:33,320
Kirk's always going into the desert for days.

27
00:01:33,400 --> 00:01:36,119
You're really sending me
mixed messages, Ange.

28
00:01:36,200 --> 00:01:38,998
Yeah, well, I'm freaking out, I guess.

29
00:01:39,080 --> 00:01:42,436
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have called.
Pretend I didn't call.

30
00:01:42,520 --> 00:01:46,559
I'll just...
I'll talk to you when Kirk gets back. Sorry.

31
00:01:49,040 --> 00:01:53,079
- You're taking a vacation in the desert?
- I don't get the attraction.

32
00:01:53,160 --> 00:01:55,310
- Snakes, scorpions.
- Only for a few days.

33
00:01:55,400 --> 00:01:57,630
- Buzzards.
- What about the stabbing?

34
00:01:57,720 --> 00:02:00,996
Zack identified the weapon and the victim.
Ourjob is done.

35
00:02:08,040 --> 00:02:10,918
It's not like I actually think
that the skull is Kirk's,

36
00:02:11,000 --> 00:02:14,515
but, I mean, if you could just look at it
and just tell me it isn't

37
00:02:14,600 --> 00:02:17,398
then I could stop worrying
about him being dead

38
00:02:17,480 --> 00:02:21,268
and just be mad at him for being a flaky artist.

39
00:02:22,120 --> 00:02:26,272
You won't get anything here. We're 100 miles
past where Jesus lost his sandals.

40
00:02:26,360 --> 00:02:28,999
I assume that's a way of saying
we're isolated.

41
00:02:29,080 --> 00:02:31,116
Yeah. That's why we come out here.

42
00:02:31,200 --> 00:02:35,113
It's like you stand still
and the whole universe just comes at you.

43
00:02:35,200 --> 00:02:36,838
At 110 degrees.

44
00:02:36,920 --> 00:02:40,037
You know, Kirk was out with a good guide -
our friend Dhani.

45
00:02:40,120 --> 00:02:44,432
I mean, he said he'd be back.
He said we'd go out for nachos and beer.

46
00:02:44,520 --> 00:02:48,911
And this is a man
who's serious about his beer.

47
00:02:52,200 --> 00:02:56,239
I got the Navaho police looking between
Dano Ona Canyon and the Otero Bluffs.

48
00:02:56,320 --> 00:03:00,313
Dr Brennan is a forensic anthropologist
with the Jeffersonian Institution.

49
00:03:00,400 --> 00:03:03,676
I spend my time helping the FBI
conduct murder investigations.

50
00:03:03,760 --> 00:03:07,753
Angie, I got my hands full getting
searchers out to look for Dhani and Kirk.

51
00:03:07,840 --> 00:03:13,551
State police said they'd lend us a chopper,
but only if we narrow down the search area.

52
00:03:13,640 --> 00:03:16,916
They gotta be running low on water.
I give them a couple of days.

53
00:03:17,000 --> 00:03:22,632
- Ben, if you could show Dr Brennan the skull.
- Or point me toward the morgue.

54
00:03:32,240 --> 00:03:34,834
Welcome to the Merville County morgue.

55
00:03:45,080 --> 00:03:48,993
Prominent brow ridge
indicates the victim is male. Do you mind?

56
00:03:49,440 --> 00:03:54,036
- Be my guest.
- She wants the plate, Ben, not the muffin.

57
00:03:57,640 --> 00:04:00,757
Cranial shape and nasal features
suggest Caucasian.

58
00:04:00,840 --> 00:04:04,037
- Died in the last several days.
- Critters been at it good.

59
00:04:04,120 --> 00:04:07,999
Pattern of basilar suture fusion
puts age 30 to 35.

60
00:04:08,080 --> 00:04:12,358
- Well, it doesn't look like Kirk.
- It doesn't look like anyone, Angie.

61
00:04:16,720 --> 00:04:18,199
Putrescine.

62
00:04:18,280 --> 00:04:21,875
- Early stages of decomp.
- Cause of death?

63
00:04:21,960 --> 00:04:26,078
A man gets caught unawares out
in the desert, he could be dead in a few hours.

64
00:04:26,160 --> 00:04:27,559
- Uh-oh.
- What?

65
00:04:27,640 --> 00:04:31,189
Base of the skull here,
detached from the spinal cord.

66
00:04:31,280 --> 00:04:35,159
See these little bevel marks?
Perimortem contact with gunshot.

67
00:04:35,240 --> 00:04:38,550
It wasrt the desert
who caught this man unawares.

68
00:04:38,640 --> 00:04:41,313
It was someone with a gun.

69
00:05:18,000 --> 00:05:21,993
- You can't say that it's Kirk.
- I know.

70
00:05:23,640 --> 00:05:25,915
You want some tea?

71
00:05:26,920 --> 00:05:29,115
I'd rather have a beer.

72
00:05:38,800 --> 00:05:42,190
This woman modelling in these pictures,
is this Dhani?

73
00:05:42,280 --> 00:05:46,159
Yeah. Dhani Webber.
It's Kirk's guide in the desert.

74
00:05:46,240 --> 00:05:50,119
- She's beautiful.
- Dhani's lived here her whole life.

75
00:05:50,200 --> 00:05:53,397
Ben says that she knows the desert
better than anybody.

76
00:05:53,480 --> 00:05:58,713
There's no way that she gets lost
or she runs out of water. There's just no way.

77
00:05:58,800 --> 00:06:01,712
- No.
- What?

78
00:06:01,800 --> 00:06:05,793
If you hug me and you be all caring,
it's because you think Kirk is dead.

79
00:06:05,880 --> 00:06:10,715
- Or because he was sleeping with Dhani.
- No. It's because...

80
00:06:11,840 --> 00:06:17,392
I'm sorry that my friend is upset
because someone she loves is missing.

81
00:06:17,480 --> 00:06:19,198
All right.

82
00:06:19,280 --> 00:06:21,191
I can buy that.

83
00:06:25,400 --> 00:06:29,393
You know, if you don't mind,
I'm just gonna head to bed.

84
00:06:29,480 --> 00:06:31,471
Good night.

85
00:06:32,880 --> 00:06:34,438
<i>(phone rings)</i>

86
00:06:34,520 --> 00:06:36,795
OK. Booth.

87
00:06:36,880 --> 00:06:40,236
- How far are you from Dulles?
- As far as your office is.

88
00:06:40,320 --> 00:06:43,118
- What?
- I need your findings on the Richmond case.

89
00:06:43,200 --> 00:06:46,033
Zack won't tell me
unless you give him permission.

90
00:06:46,120 --> 00:06:48,111
There's a 9:15 flight to Denver,

91
00:06:48,200 --> 00:06:52,193
then an 11:35 flight to Santa Fe.
You'll have to run to make the connection.

92
00:06:52,280 --> 00:06:55,431
- Forget it.
- Booth. Please.

93
00:06:55,960 --> 00:06:59,839
Angela's boyfriend is missing, maybe dead.

94
00:06:59,920 --> 00:07:02,354
- It took all of my charm...
- Oh, boy.

95
00:07:02,440 --> 00:07:04,874
...to get the sheriff to let me look at the skull.

96
00:07:04,960 --> 00:07:07,349
When I asked to send it to the Jeffersonian,

97
00:07:07,440 --> 00:07:10,591
he told me I am not a cop
and I don't have any jurisdiction.

98
00:07:10,680 --> 00:07:13,717
Which is true. OK, look.
What do you want me to do?

99
00:07:13,800 --> 00:07:16,189
I want you to get federal on his ass.

100
00:07:30,360 --> 00:07:35,559
Hey. There you go. People in the desert don't
have actual addresses. What's up with that?

101
00:07:35,640 --> 00:07:39,189
- <i>(Bones)</i> You made it.
- Yeah. I'm touring the hottest places.

102
00:07:39,280 --> 00:07:42,317
Next stop - there you go - hell.

103
00:07:42,400 --> 00:07:44,755
I'm not really awake yet.

104
00:07:44,840 --> 00:07:47,354
Last night before I left I used my FBI powers

105
00:07:47,440 --> 00:07:50,671
to force the sheriff
to send the skull to the Jeffersonian.

106
00:07:50,760 --> 00:07:53,638
I talked to him this morning.
He seems resentful.

107
00:07:53,720 --> 00:07:56,314
- What time is it?
- Let's go. Drink that on the way.

108
00:07:56,400 --> 00:08:01,269
- On the way where?
- To the model, guide, whatever's place.

109
00:08:01,360 --> 00:08:03,351
Dhani. Can I come with you?

110
00:08:03,440 --> 00:08:08,150
- We can ask tougher questions without you.
- Wait outside while I get dressed.

111
00:08:08,240 --> 00:08:11,755
No. The surs been up for an hour.
It's the surface of Mercury.

112
00:08:11,840 --> 00:08:17,631
I can stand here and close my eyes,
eat my doughnuts. It's the best I can do, OK?

113
00:08:23,920 --> 00:08:27,356
What tougher questions can we ask
without Angela being here?

114
00:08:27,440 --> 00:08:30,512
Things like did her boyfriend
run off with the model guide?

115
00:08:30,600 --> 00:08:33,194
We discussed this.
She said it couldn't happen.

116
00:08:33,280 --> 00:08:37,319
No offence, but she doesn't know this guy.
She's with him three weeks a year.

117
00:08:37,400 --> 00:08:41,791
No offence, but you are a stodgy traditionalist
when it comes to relationships.

118
00:08:41,880 --> 00:08:43,950
Stodgy? Stodgy.

119
00:08:44,040 --> 00:08:46,190
- OK, here's the deal.
- Yeah, stodgy.

120
00:08:46,280 --> 00:08:49,590
We find out the skull isn't Kirk,
we let the locals handle it, OK?

121
00:08:49,680 --> 00:08:52,319
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah, you say, "Of course".

122
00:08:52,400 --> 00:08:55,949
But then you get all caught up in it,
and then... What?

123
00:08:56,040 --> 00:08:57,268
Oh.

124
00:08:57,360 --> 00:09:00,636
- What do you want?
- FBI. We're looking for Dhani Webber.

125
00:09:00,720 --> 00:09:03,188
- Who are you?
- I'm the guy holding the big gun.

126
00:09:03,280 --> 00:09:06,078
On a federal agent,
which I've been nice about so far.

127
00:09:06,160 --> 00:09:11,996
- Let's rush him. He can't shoot us both.
- How about I just show him my badge?

128
00:09:12,080 --> 00:09:13,672
OK?

129
00:09:13,760 --> 00:09:17,958
- Alex Joseph. This is me and Dhani's place.
- Where's Dhani Webber?

130
00:09:18,040 --> 00:09:21,715
Missing. In the desert for almost a week.
I've been looking for her.

131
00:09:21,800 --> 00:09:25,031
- You point your gun at everybody?
- Maybe I'm nervous.

132
00:09:25,120 --> 00:09:28,954
Anything you might be nervous about?
Something Dhani got caught up in?

133
00:09:29,040 --> 00:09:31,634
- Nothing I can think of.
- Can we look inside?

134
00:09:31,720 --> 00:09:35,315
- Not without a warrant.
- You have a problem with law enforcement?

135
00:09:35,760 --> 00:09:37,830
You could say that, I guess.

136
00:09:42,920 --> 00:09:47,948
Model runs off with handsome photographer,
boyfriend with a gun finds them in the desert.

137
00:09:48,040 --> 00:09:51,077
- He's twitchy.
- What if he's escaping out the back door?

138
00:09:51,160 --> 00:09:54,630
You don't spend a lot of time in trailers,
do you?

139
00:09:59,080 --> 00:10:00,991
Hah. Whoa.

140
00:10:01,080 --> 00:10:02,911
What? That's Sheriff Dawes.

141
00:10:03,000 --> 00:10:07,039
Yeah, he definitely has a problem
with law enforcement.

142
00:10:07,120 --> 00:10:08,189
Huh.

143
00:10:11,560 --> 00:10:14,791
Dr Brennan doesn't like us
to listen to music while working.

144
00:10:14,880 --> 00:10:16,916
Dr Brennan is not here.

145
00:10:17,000 --> 00:10:20,754
She thinks the work deserves
our full concentration. I need the skull.

146
00:10:20,840 --> 00:10:24,594
I'm still finding particulates.
Since you're Dr Brennars assistant,

147
00:10:24,680 --> 00:10:27,478
without her,
you don't carry that much weight here.

148
00:10:27,560 --> 00:10:30,279
I'm telling Dr Goodman.

149
00:10:34,200 --> 00:10:36,668
Why didn't you mention
your relationship to Dhani?

150
00:10:36,760 --> 00:10:41,072
Dhani Webber drop you for the photographer,
the Indian guy, or both?

151
00:10:41,160 --> 00:10:43,913
Moron. Dhani's my sister.

152
00:10:44,000 --> 00:10:47,470
Half-sister. Mostly I raised her.
You can check with Angie.

153
00:10:47,560 --> 00:10:53,908
OK, we got that wrong. I pretty much don't
like the look of your sister's boyfriend Alex.

154
00:10:54,000 --> 00:10:59,358
Assault, narcotics, bootlegs for
the reservation. Yeah, Dhani could do better.

155
00:10:59,440 --> 00:11:02,113
Any chance Dhani
got caught up with something ugly?

156
00:11:02,200 --> 00:11:05,476
Till I find otherwise,
I'm assuming Dhani and Kirk are lost.

157
00:11:05,560 --> 00:11:09,109
Alex Joseph - is he bad enough
to hurt them if he finds them together?

158
00:11:09,200 --> 00:11:12,237
- It's on my list of nightmares, yeah.
- <i>(phone rings)</i>

159
00:11:13,400 --> 00:11:16,437
- Brennan.
- DNA results are in.

160
00:11:16,520 --> 00:11:19,398
The skull is definitely Kirk Persinger.

161
00:11:21,360 --> 00:11:23,032
Poor Angela.

162
00:11:23,120 --> 00:11:27,238
The hair tests off the charts for
<i>Lophophora williamsii</i>- derived mescaline.

163
00:11:27,320 --> 00:11:29,117
- What's that?
- Peyote.

164
00:11:29,560 --> 00:11:32,791
- Anything on the scoring?
- <i>(Zack) I haven't had a crack at it.</i>

165
00:11:32,880 --> 00:11:38,034
Hodgins hogged it. The markings trace
to several desert-dwelling species.

166
00:11:38,120 --> 00:11:42,671
It seems a full-grown male coyote did
the most work, but one with a malformed jaw.

167
00:11:42,760 --> 00:11:48,551
- Very unusual bite formations.
- Ask Dr Goodman to find a naturalist.

168
00:11:48,640 --> 00:11:50,756
Kirk Persinger?

169
00:11:50,840 --> 00:11:53,673
Yes. They found traces of peyote.

170
00:11:54,760 --> 00:11:58,389
Drug related. Shot to the spine,
execution style. So, Sheriff,

171
00:11:58,480 --> 00:12:02,268
do you still think
this is a simple missing persons case?

172
00:12:04,360 --> 00:12:06,794
I have to tell Angela.

173
00:12:08,080 --> 00:12:14,030
Listen, Sheriff, I'm sorry for the concern
you must be feeling for your sister.

174
00:12:15,040 --> 00:12:16,155
Yeah.

175
00:12:21,960 --> 00:12:25,839
I will call the FBI office in Albuquerque
and take over the investigation.

176
00:12:25,920 --> 00:12:27,399
- I wouldn't.
- Why?

177
00:12:27,480 --> 00:12:31,871
Desert dwellers are very insular.
Mongolians, Bedouins of the Sahara,

178
00:12:31,960 --> 00:12:36,750
the Himba of Kanana. Good hosts,
but extremely distrustful of outsiders.

179
00:12:36,840 --> 00:12:39,877
This is the United States of America,
not Outer Mongolia.

180
00:12:39,960 --> 00:12:44,112
The only reason Sheriff Dawes
talks to us at all is because we know Angela.

181
00:12:44,200 --> 00:12:47,875
- Alex Joseph held a gun on us.
- I admit, I've met friendlier people.

182
00:12:47,960 --> 00:12:52,397
If a bunch of outsiders come in from
Albuquerque, led by an outsider from DC,

183
00:12:52,480 --> 00:12:57,190
I promise you, the people here
will close ranks and shut up until we go away.

184
00:12:57,280 --> 00:13:01,478
- Then they'll take care of it in their own way.
- OK. Who are you? Dr Phil?

185
00:13:01,560 --> 00:13:04,597
- Who's Dr Phil? Some kind of expert?
- He likes to think so.

186
00:13:04,680 --> 00:13:10,516
OK, I'll take what you say under advisement.
We need to find out who gave Kirk his peyote.

187
00:13:10,600 --> 00:13:13,239
How are we gonna do that?

188
00:13:13,320 --> 00:13:15,914
Talk to his girlfriend.

189
00:13:17,160 --> 00:13:20,357
I'm so sorry, Angela. We both are.

190
00:13:21,040 --> 00:13:23,429
I knew it was Kirk.

191
00:13:23,520 --> 00:13:28,150
That's why I called you.
We have to find out what happened to Dhani.

192
00:13:28,240 --> 00:13:33,951
Angela, I'm gonna have to ask you
a couple of difficult questions, OK?

193
00:13:34,040 --> 00:13:37,271
What can you tell me about Kirk's drug use?

194
00:13:37,360 --> 00:13:39,749
Kirk didn't do drugs.

195
00:13:39,840 --> 00:13:42,752
Hodgins found peyote in his hair.

196
00:13:44,080 --> 00:13:46,674
I thought that you meant <i>drug</i> drugs.

197
00:13:46,760 --> 00:13:51,470
The peyote wasrt recreational.
Kirk took part in some native Indian rites.

198
00:13:51,560 --> 00:13:54,233
While high on drugs.

199
00:13:54,680 --> 00:13:58,639
- Did you do peyote with Kirk?
- The peyote has nothing to do with anything.

200
00:13:58,720 --> 00:14:04,352
Angela, you may have come in contact
with Kirk's killer without even realising it.

201
00:14:05,080 --> 00:14:07,469
Who was his connection?

202
00:14:09,520 --> 00:14:12,114
He's Kirk's friend.

203
00:14:13,160 --> 00:14:16,869
- I need the name.
- Wayne.

204
00:14:16,960 --> 00:14:19,520
Wayne Kellogg.

205
00:14:19,600 --> 00:14:22,319
He's an important local artist.

206
00:14:34,720 --> 00:14:40,397
I don't deny having participated in the peyote
ritual on several occasions. Utterly spiritual.

207
00:14:40,480 --> 00:14:42,835
- You're not Indian.
- Not by birth, no.

208
00:14:42,920 --> 00:14:47,232
But as you can see from my artwork, I have
a deep spiritual connection to the Navaho.

209
00:14:47,320 --> 00:14:50,039
- Do you sell a lot of work?
- I sell well overseas.

210
00:14:50,120 --> 00:14:53,192
Enough to keep this place
and a beach house in LA. Why?

211
00:14:53,280 --> 00:14:56,272
Why not buy Navaho art
created by actual Navahos?

212
00:14:56,360 --> 00:14:59,716
Peyote is only legal
if you belong to the Native American Church.

213
00:14:59,800 --> 00:15:03,634
You and Kirk bought it illegally,
which involves drug dealers.

214
00:15:03,720 --> 00:15:06,188
You can follow my train of thought,
can't you?

215
00:15:06,280 --> 00:15:08,953
Look, I realise Kirk's missing.

216
00:15:09,040 --> 00:15:13,397
- Kirk's not missing.
- He's dead.

217
00:15:13,480 --> 00:15:17,598
- What about Dhani?
- Dhani Webber remains unaccounted for.

218
00:15:18,800 --> 00:15:23,351
- God, this is terrible.
- I need the name of your drug connection.

219
00:15:23,440 --> 00:15:26,193
No. I'm sorry.

220
00:15:26,280 --> 00:15:31,832
They trust me. I understand the difficulty in
finding peyote plants miles out in the desert,

221
00:15:31,920 --> 00:15:35,390
secret places passed on
from generation to generation.

222
00:15:35,480 --> 00:15:38,040
Mr Kellogg, is that your vehicle?

223
00:15:38,120 --> 00:15:40,236
Yes. Why?

224
00:15:40,320 --> 00:15:43,232
Alex Joseph borrowed that Humvee.

225
00:15:44,720 --> 00:15:49,714
Alex Joseph didn't go to the desert to look
for Dhani, he went out to look for peyote.

226
00:15:49,800 --> 00:15:52,439
I never said that.

227
00:15:57,040 --> 00:15:59,998
Mr Joseph, it's FBI again.

228
00:16:00,080 --> 00:16:03,675
- I'd like to ask you a few more questions.
- <i>(coughing)</i>

229
00:16:03,760 --> 00:16:05,751
Booth?

230
00:16:12,520 --> 00:16:14,511
Booth.

231
00:16:21,880 --> 00:16:26,476
Oh, come on, Sheriff. Come on. Even out
here, you know how the drug world works.

232
00:16:26,560 --> 00:16:30,997
Kirk is found dead,
Joseph is beaten to a pulp. It's all connected.

233
00:16:31,080 --> 00:16:35,278
- My priority is to find Dhani.
- Find Kirk's murderer, we probably find her.

234
00:16:35,360 --> 00:16:39,035
Maybe Dhani is the murderer.
What? I gotta ask.

235
00:16:39,120 --> 00:16:43,352
Dhani never hurt anybody in her life,
except maybe herself.

236
00:16:43,440 --> 00:16:49,072
You know, another thing I have to consider,
maybe Dhani calls up her brother the sheriff

237
00:16:49,160 --> 00:16:52,789
and says, "This photographer raped me.
What do I do now?"

238
00:16:52,880 --> 00:16:57,237
What you're proving now is you don't know
anything about the people that live here.

239
00:16:57,320 --> 00:17:02,678
Joseph met us with a rifle. Maybe he was
afraid it was you coming around the corner.

240
00:17:02,760 --> 00:17:05,320
Alex Joseph is unconscious.

241
00:17:05,400 --> 00:17:07,960
You maybe can talk to him when he wakes up.

242
00:17:08,040 --> 00:17:13,239
Me, I'm going to help
the search parties find my sister.

243
00:17:16,120 --> 00:17:19,590
Thanks to Fish and Wildlife,
most coyote packs in this region

244
00:17:19,680 --> 00:17:22,513
have at least one member
wearing a GPS collar.

245
00:17:22,600 --> 00:17:26,149
You can find one coyote
with a wonky jaw in the desert?

246
00:17:26,240 --> 00:17:30,836
What we do here is process information
from rangers, amateur naturalists,

247
00:17:30,920 --> 00:17:33,434
conservationists, even school groups.

248
00:17:33,520 --> 00:17:38,435
The desert coyote pack's range is not huge,
perhaps ten square miles.

249
00:17:38,520 --> 00:17:43,435
The pack is typically three to eight animals,
led by the alpha mating pair.

250
00:17:43,520 --> 00:17:46,273
- Wow.
- What wow?

251
00:17:46,360 --> 00:17:51,115
Professor Inez has found your coyote,
but he's way out in the desert.

252
00:17:51,200 --> 00:17:55,716
Three pups, three females, two males,
including the leader with the wonky jaw.

253
00:17:55,800 --> 00:17:57,870
With eight coyotes going at a cadaver,

254
00:17:57,960 --> 00:18:01,396
we're talking needle in a haystack
finding the remains.

255
00:18:01,480 --> 00:18:03,630
The mamas and the pups feed together

256
00:18:03,720 --> 00:18:07,599
so I'd expect ribcage and smaller bones
to be in a concentrated area,

257
00:18:07,680 --> 00:18:13,437
but the males move away from each other
with larger pieces. No more than a half a mile.

258
00:18:15,000 --> 00:18:17,912
Three weeks a year, 15 weeks in total.

259
00:18:18,600 --> 00:18:21,717
- You think that's crazy?
- Well...

260
00:18:22,720 --> 00:18:25,359
It's not typical, that's for sure.

261
00:18:25,440 --> 00:18:30,753
And if he was yours, 100% yours,
for three weeks a year,

262
00:18:30,840 --> 00:18:32,796
that's...

263
00:18:35,840 --> 00:18:38,957
that's more than I've ever had.

264
00:18:40,840 --> 00:18:46,278
Kirk's photographs show the world as a more
beautiful place than it is. A better place.

265
00:18:46,720 --> 00:18:50,508
He made me feel like that was my real home,

266
00:18:50,960 --> 00:18:54,350
that I belonged there with him.

267
00:18:55,800 --> 00:19:00,157
He's the guy I compare all other guys to.

268
00:19:02,920 --> 00:19:09,155
Now he's gone and I feel like I can't even
breathe, sweetie. I can't even take a breath.

269
00:19:12,080 --> 00:19:16,232
You think it's possible that Dhani's
still out there? Could she still be alive?

270
00:19:16,320 --> 00:19:18,629
I don't know. There's no crime scene

271
00:19:18,720 --> 00:19:23,191
and we're not even sure
where the rest of Kirk's remains are.

272
00:19:23,280 --> 00:19:26,556
- I want to help you look for her tomorrow.
- Are you sure?

273
00:19:26,640 --> 00:19:29,598
Yeah. Dhani was our friend.

274
00:19:29,680 --> 00:19:33,229
I have to help find her. Please.

275
00:19:47,240 --> 00:19:49,310
I love the desert.

276
00:19:49,400 --> 00:19:52,597
- Or I used to.
- Nothing looks the way it should.

277
00:19:52,680 --> 00:19:56,150
Stuff that's far away looks near,
stuff that's near looks far.

278
00:19:56,240 --> 00:20:00,518
Yeah, well, you can't trust your eyes out here.
Not your eyes alone.

279
00:20:00,600 --> 00:20:04,752
You know,
Kirk said that if you stood still long enough,

280
00:20:04,840 --> 00:20:08,719
that the desert would actually speak to you.

281
00:20:09,160 --> 00:20:12,994
- Show you some kind of truth.
- That ever happen to you?

282
00:20:13,080 --> 00:20:16,038
No, but he really believed that.

283
00:20:23,640 --> 00:20:26,200
- Alex Joseph woke up.
- Good.

284
00:20:26,640 --> 00:20:30,235
You think whoever beat him up
had something to do with Kirk's murder?

285
00:20:30,320 --> 00:20:32,117
- Yeah.
- No.

286
00:20:33,440 --> 00:20:35,908
How can you be so sure?

287
00:20:36,000 --> 00:20:38,275
- You were the one that beat him up?
- No.

288
00:20:38,360 --> 00:20:40,635
OK, well,

289
00:20:40,720 --> 00:20:42,711
do you know who did?

290
00:20:42,800 --> 00:20:45,792
These guys. Or guys just like them.

291
00:20:45,880 --> 00:20:48,678
- Why?
- Peyote ritual.

292
00:20:48,760 --> 00:20:51,672
These people take it seriously.
It's their religion.

293
00:20:51,760 --> 00:20:57,039
Alex Joseph starts selling it to white guys
like Kellogg and Kirk, they don't like it.

294
00:20:57,120 --> 00:21:01,591
- Arert you gonna arrest any of them?
- No, but I might deputise a couple.

295
00:21:01,680 --> 00:21:05,309
Sheriff, I get how you handle things out here,
but I gotta ask you,

296
00:21:05,400 --> 00:21:11,157
if they beat up an Indian for selling peyote,
what are they gonna do to Kirk for taking it?

297
00:21:11,240 --> 00:21:14,391
Nothing. Kirk's a white man.

298
00:21:14,480 --> 00:21:17,278
The way they see it, he's my responsibility.

299
00:21:17,360 --> 00:21:20,113
<i>(man)</i> Hey! We've got something over here!

300
00:21:20,200 --> 00:21:21,997
Sheriff Dawes!

301
00:21:23,040 --> 00:21:25,031
<i>(man #2)</i> Bring your team over here.

302
00:21:28,600 --> 00:21:30,716
<i>(man #1)</i> Watch where you step.

303
00:21:39,960 --> 00:21:44,272
Ange, they found some bones over here.
It might be Kirk.

304
00:21:44,360 --> 00:21:47,875
- It is Kirk. This is his camera.
- Are you sure?

305
00:21:49,280 --> 00:21:54,354
No, no, no. Don't. Don't.
There could be exposed film in there.

306
00:21:54,440 --> 00:21:56,431
It's cracked.

307
00:21:56,520 --> 00:22:00,308
We can't let any more light in.
It'll damage the film.

308
00:22:00,400 --> 00:22:02,436
Maybe Kirk was right.

309
00:22:02,520 --> 00:22:06,559
This could be a good way for the desert
to tell us what happened to him -

310
00:22:06,640 --> 00:22:09,677
a photograph of his murderer.

311
00:22:16,040 --> 00:22:18,873
This camera's going
to the state police crime lab.

312
00:22:18,960 --> 00:22:22,669
Angela is better at developing film
than anyone in Santa Fe.

313
00:22:22,760 --> 00:22:25,558
I can use Kirk's equipment.
It's top of the line.

314
00:22:25,640 --> 00:22:28,108
And we won't have to wait for results, Sheriff.

315
00:22:28,200 --> 00:22:33,991
With your sister maybe still alive
out in the desert, every hour counts.

316
00:22:35,000 --> 00:22:38,515
- I can't do it.
- <i>(Angela)</i> Booth.

317
00:22:38,600 --> 00:22:45,119
According to Homeland Security, Kellogg
sold exactly $120,000 won'th of art overseas.

318
00:22:45,200 --> 00:22:49,716
- What's that got to do with anything?
- It doesn't buy him a beach house in LA.

319
00:22:49,800 --> 00:22:51,836
He lied. Let's go check him out.

320
00:22:51,920 --> 00:22:54,434
- What will we look for?
- What we always look for.

321
00:22:54,520 --> 00:22:59,753
Something that doesn't fit,
something, you know... something.

322
00:23:02,480 --> 00:23:05,756
I can't believe that you think
that I'm a suspect.

323
00:23:05,840 --> 00:23:08,434
Angie, not to speak ill of the dead,

324
00:23:08,520 --> 00:23:13,799
but a woman like you, you're won'th more
than three weeks a year, you understand?

325
00:23:13,880 --> 00:23:19,716
- I murdered Kirk cos he didn't give me time?
- I'm just a law man. People are people.

326
00:23:19,800 --> 00:23:23,554
Ben, Kirk wasrt the one
who put limits on our time together.

327
00:23:23,640 --> 00:23:27,918
He wanted me to marry him.
And he deserved more. And better.

328
00:23:28,000 --> 00:23:30,798
Please, Ben, I wanna help find Dhani,

329
00:23:30,880 --> 00:23:33,394
and there could be evidence on this film.

330
00:23:33,480 --> 00:23:37,439
Just let me do
what I do better than anybody else.

331
00:23:47,200 --> 00:23:49,191
Thank you.

332
00:23:51,240 --> 00:23:52,878
Angie.

333
00:23:52,960 --> 00:23:56,919
Maybe he deserved more.
It's not my place to say.

334
00:23:57,920 --> 00:24:01,151
But he couldn't have done better.
No man could.

335
00:24:06,200 --> 00:24:12,116
I haven't attained anything like the success
Kirk has, but I do all right. Why?

336
00:24:12,200 --> 00:24:16,273
- You have a beach house.
- I applied for a warrant to check your assets.

337
00:24:16,360 --> 00:24:21,992
I told you, I do well in Europe. Germany
especially appreciates native-themed work.

338
00:24:22,080 --> 00:24:26,471
- Kirk's remains were way out in the desert.
- What's that got to do with me?

339
00:24:26,560 --> 00:24:29,677
Because you have a vehicle
capable of going out that far.

340
00:24:29,760 --> 00:24:32,035
A vehicle I often loan out.

341
00:24:32,120 --> 00:24:35,749
- What are these?
- Engraving plates. Please don't touch them.

342
00:24:35,840 --> 00:24:40,755
The oils on your skin will compromise
the integrity. Why would I kill Kirk?

343
00:24:40,840 --> 00:24:44,116
Maybe because, you know,
you had a little thing for Dhani.

344
00:24:44,200 --> 00:24:47,829
Or maybe because you were jealous
of Kirk's artistic success.

345
00:24:47,920 --> 00:24:51,469
- These aren't native designs.
- I'm working a line of inquiry here.

346
00:24:51,560 --> 00:24:56,554
All of your work is stolen from native
designs. These are floral. It doesn't fit.

347
00:24:56,640 --> 00:25:01,430
Not stolen, inspired by.
And that piece is commissioned.

348
00:25:01,520 --> 00:25:04,159
- Another way I make money.
- <i>(phone rings)</i>

349
00:25:04,240 --> 00:25:05,229
Hi, Angela.

350
00:25:05,320 --> 00:25:08,915
Most of the film was wrecked,
but I developed a few usable images.

351
00:25:09,000 --> 00:25:12,470
- That's great.
- No, because Ben got me to make prints,

352
00:25:12,560 --> 00:25:15,074
and then he bolted with them
and the negatives.

353
00:25:15,160 --> 00:25:18,277
- Dawes took off with the negatives.
- What did she find?

354
00:25:18,360 --> 00:25:22,319
- Did you recognise anything?
- Dhani in the desert.

355
00:25:22,400 --> 00:25:25,597
That's all.
I have no idea what he got so excited about.

356
00:25:25,680 --> 00:25:29,514
- Nothing that meant anything to Angela.
- We'll go take a look ourselves.

357
00:25:29,600 --> 00:25:31,431
Talk to you again.

358
00:25:33,040 --> 00:25:37,591
- I wanted to show these photos to Joseph.
- Why Joseph?

359
00:25:37,680 --> 00:25:40,911
Angela says they're only photos
of your sister in the desert.

360
00:25:41,000 --> 00:25:44,959
Right. The only person that knows the desert
as good as Dhani is Joseph.

361
00:25:45,040 --> 00:25:47,508
This formation here, I'm not familiar with it.

362
00:25:47,600 --> 00:25:50,956
There's nothing like this
near Kirk's remains or the camera.

363
00:25:51,040 --> 00:25:53,679
He was killed somewhere else and moved.

364
00:25:53,760 --> 00:25:58,072
If we find that outcropping, maybe
we find where Kirk was killed and my sister.

365
00:25:58,160 --> 00:26:00,151
- Did Joseph recognise it?
- Yeah.

366
00:26:00,240 --> 00:26:03,232
- Where?
- It's easier I take you than explain.

367
00:26:03,320 --> 00:26:07,677
Whoa. OK. If Joseph is the murderer,
he'd just send you on a wild-goose chase.

368
00:26:07,760 --> 00:26:11,799
Then we know he's the murderer and
all we've wasted is gas and a goose chase.

369
00:26:11,880 --> 00:26:14,314
How far out are we going?

370
00:26:14,400 --> 00:26:16,470
A ways.

371
00:26:22,040 --> 00:26:24,759
One week in the desert
and there's nothing but bone.

372
00:26:24,840 --> 00:26:27,479
- Same guy?
- Looks like it.

373
00:26:27,560 --> 00:26:31,075
I think it would be better
if I went over the bones before you start.

374
00:26:31,160 --> 00:26:34,197
I disagree, and you can't have them
unless I release them.

375
00:26:34,280 --> 00:26:36,635
You're gonna have to do the boss thing, boss.

376
00:26:36,720 --> 00:26:40,872
Sir, Dr Brennan needs to know
how this man died, which is my territory,

377
00:26:40,960 --> 00:26:43,394
- more than when and where he died.
- Dr Hodgins.

378
00:26:43,480 --> 00:26:47,359
Even I can see he got shot in the head.
Dr Brennan needs the murder scene.

379
00:26:47,440 --> 00:26:51,718
It's the desert. Particulates aren't going to
narrow it down any more than that.

380
00:26:51,800 --> 00:26:55,315
We won't know that
until I look at the particulates.

381
00:26:57,520 --> 00:27:01,274
Dr Hodgins will have access
to the bones first, Mr Addy.

382
00:27:02,640 --> 00:27:04,835
That's the wrong decision.

383
00:27:12,840 --> 00:27:15,070
My lungs are gonna come out my throat.

384
00:27:15,160 --> 00:27:19,358
Where I come from, when you say
you're driving a ways, it means 45 minutes.

385
00:27:19,440 --> 00:27:23,115
- Out here it means four hours.
- We've been driving five.

386
00:27:23,200 --> 00:27:26,431
I maybe should've said quite a ways.

387
00:27:26,520 --> 00:27:27,669
There it is.

388
00:27:40,160 --> 00:27:41,991
Well...

389
00:27:42,080 --> 00:27:45,789
- That it?
- Yeah, I think so. Different time of day.

390
00:27:45,880 --> 00:27:48,872
You look for the exact spot
the pictures were taken.

391
00:27:48,960 --> 00:27:51,349
I'm gonna take another circle in the truck.

392
00:27:51,440 --> 00:27:53,431
- Looking for your sister?
- Yeah.

393
00:27:53,520 --> 00:27:57,399
I think we want to go south slightly,
maybe southwest.

394
00:27:57,480 --> 00:28:03,476
- You can tell from the shadows?
- Yeah, and the angle on the outcropping.

395
00:28:04,920 --> 00:28:08,356
- Where's he going?
- He's looking for his sister.

396
00:28:10,480 --> 00:28:13,278
Either of you two bring any water?

397
00:28:15,320 --> 00:28:17,629
- Why? Are you worried?
- Yeah.

398
00:28:17,720 --> 00:28:19,039
About what?

399
00:28:19,120 --> 00:28:22,590
Because we're way past
where Jesus lost his sandals.

400
00:28:22,680 --> 00:28:25,592
And I don't hear the truck any more.

401
00:28:27,440 --> 00:28:28,919
Great.

402
00:28:35,200 --> 00:28:38,749
No cellphone service, no water.

403
00:28:38,840 --> 00:28:42,549
How long do you think we'll survive
if the sheriff doesn't come back?

404
00:28:42,640 --> 00:28:45,234
- Three days.
- How far are we from the highway?

405
00:28:45,320 --> 00:28:49,199
- Five days, minimum.
- I don't like that math.

406
00:28:50,600 --> 00:28:52,670
Wait a second.

407
00:28:54,440 --> 00:28:57,637
- <i>(Booth)</i> Kirk's?
- It looks like it, yeah.

408
00:29:01,040 --> 00:29:06,068
Yeah. The distributor's smashed.
All the wires are pulled out.

409
00:29:06,160 --> 00:29:11,154
It doesn't make sense that he brings us
to the scene of the crime and leaves us to die.

410
00:29:11,240 --> 00:29:15,153
One godforsaken part of desert
is as good as another godforsaken part.

411
00:29:15,240 --> 00:29:19,438
We don't even know
if Sheriff Dawes actually called Alex Joseph.

412
00:29:19,520 --> 00:29:23,911
- I mean, he could've done all this himself.
- Could Dawes do that, Ange?

413
00:29:24,360 --> 00:29:29,195
Well, I always thought Ben Dawes was a good
man. It would take a lot to change my mind.

414
00:29:29,280 --> 00:29:31,396
Like being left to die in the desert?

415
00:29:31,480 --> 00:29:35,473
These tracks, they don't match
the sheriff's vehicle. They're too wide.

416
00:29:35,560 --> 00:29:37,630
Humvee maybe?

417
00:29:38,080 --> 00:29:40,674
This is blood, I think.

418
00:29:41,480 --> 00:29:43,755
The victim was kneeling here.

419
00:29:43,840 --> 00:29:45,831
Bones.

420
00:29:45,920 --> 00:29:48,229
Sorry.

421
00:29:49,160 --> 00:29:53,199
He was dragged this way,
then the blood trail ends.

422
00:29:53,280 --> 00:29:55,555
He was thrown into the Humvee.

423
00:29:55,640 --> 00:29:58,438
We're 200 miles
from where we found Kirk's bones.

424
00:29:58,520 --> 00:30:03,310
You think the murderer drove that far
to drop the body? Where are you going?

425
00:30:03,400 --> 00:30:05,197
Booth.

426
00:30:05,920 --> 00:30:08,593
The tracks, they stop right here.

427
00:30:08,680 --> 00:30:12,150
- What here? There's no here here.
- Landing strip, huh?

428
00:30:12,240 --> 00:30:14,629
I knew this was about drugs.

429
00:30:15,640 --> 00:30:17,949
Mexico's about 80 miles that way.

430
00:30:18,400 --> 00:30:19,799
<i>(car horn)</i>

431
00:30:21,520 --> 00:30:23,238
Oh, yes!

432
00:30:23,320 --> 00:30:28,189
Only Angela could get a ride
in the middle of nowhere.

433
00:30:31,040 --> 00:30:33,952
- Any signs of your sister?
- She's been out there a week.

434
00:30:34,040 --> 00:30:36,998
She could be alive
if she had a few canteens of water.

435
00:30:37,080 --> 00:30:39,833
- Humvee tracks, Sheriff.
- Alex Joseph?

436
00:30:40,280 --> 00:30:42,669
Catches Kirk and Dhani out here...

437
00:30:42,760 --> 00:30:46,878
- Sandy, this is Dawes. Do you receive me?
- <i>Loud and clear. Where are you?</i>

438
00:30:46,960 --> 00:30:52,557
Hell and gone. I need a deputy down at
the clinic to slap some cuffs on Alex Joseph.

439
00:30:52,640 --> 00:30:55,996
<i>Alex Joseph took off, Sheriff.</i>
<i>We've got no idea where he went.</i>

440
00:30:56,080 --> 00:30:57,433
Kellogg's Humvee.

441
00:30:57,520 --> 00:31:01,195
Sandy, go collect Wayne Kellogg's Humvee.
We'll see you in a few hours.

442
00:31:03,680 --> 00:31:10,074
Any blood stains should flare bluish green
when the Luminol hits them.

443
00:31:11,400 --> 00:31:16,349
- Nothing.
- Kirk was put into the Humvee. Treads match.

444
00:31:16,440 --> 00:31:19,955
It's clean. Give Kellogg his truck back.

445
00:31:20,040 --> 00:31:23,157
- Tell him sorry for the inconvenience.
- Try the hood.

446
00:31:23,240 --> 00:31:26,835
You think they tied Kirk's bloody dead body
to the hood like an elk,

447
00:31:26,920 --> 00:31:30,629
then drove him 200 miles
before dumping him for coyotes?

448
00:31:30,720 --> 00:31:33,109
Even out here, people might notice.

449
00:31:33,200 --> 00:31:35,191
Right there.

450
00:31:42,440 --> 00:31:43,555
Hm.

451
00:31:43,640 --> 00:31:46,598
I'll be damned.

452
00:31:46,680 --> 00:31:48,477
Yeah.

453
00:31:55,160 --> 00:31:57,230
- Zack.
- Yes, Dr Brennan.

454
00:31:57,320 --> 00:32:01,108
Do the bones show more damage
than can be explained by animal activity?

455
00:32:01,200 --> 00:32:04,237
Analysis indicates
the pubic rami are fractured

456
00:32:04,320 --> 00:32:07,357
and the left hemipelvis is severely displaced.

457
00:32:07,440 --> 00:32:11,558
- Congruent with a fall?
- Yes. Were they found at the base of a cliff?

458
00:32:11,640 --> 00:32:15,155
He wasrt driven 200 miles,
he was driven a couple hundred yards.

459
00:32:15,240 --> 00:32:18,232
Loaded his body in the airplane,
then tossed it.

460
00:32:18,320 --> 00:32:21,392
I'm not happy with how long
it took you to get back to me.

461
00:32:21,480 --> 00:32:25,155
- We'll talk about it when I get back.
- Sorry, Dr Brennan.

462
00:32:27,160 --> 00:32:30,516
You could've told her it wasrt your fault.

463
00:32:32,480 --> 00:32:35,119
I still have some work to do here.

464
00:32:39,480 --> 00:32:42,790
They dumped Kirk's body.
They could've done the same to Dhani.

465
00:32:42,880 --> 00:32:45,599
- Kirk was dead when they tossed him.
- Absolutely.

466
00:32:45,680 --> 00:32:48,399
And I saw no evidence
of a second murder at the site.

467
00:32:48,480 --> 00:32:53,190
Which leaves me hoping either my sister
was kidnapped or is dying in the desert.

468
00:32:53,280 --> 00:32:57,910
Kidnap is a federal offence.
It's an FBI matter. I can help you if you want.

469
00:32:58,000 --> 00:32:59,513
Brennan.

470
00:32:59,600 --> 00:33:04,037
- Those photos you sent me of engravings.
- Kellogg said it was a commissioned work.

471
00:33:04,120 --> 00:33:06,714
- I think these are engravers' plates.
- <i>For what?</i>

472
00:33:06,800 --> 00:33:11,828
Currency. To be exact, I believe these are
dyes for the Venezuelan 500 bolívar bill.

473
00:33:11,920 --> 00:33:15,708
- Dyes? Counterfeiters' dyes?
- Yes.

474
00:33:16,560 --> 00:33:18,630
Did you say counterfeiters?

475
00:33:19,640 --> 00:33:23,155
I've got a warrant here
to search your studio for engraving plates.

476
00:33:23,240 --> 00:33:27,711
Well, as Mr Kellogg's attorney,
I can advise you you're certain to find some.

477
00:33:27,800 --> 00:33:29,233
I'm an engraver.

478
00:33:29,320 --> 00:33:33,711
Larry, did you tell Wayne how when someone
dies during the commission of a felony,

479
00:33:33,800 --> 00:33:36,792
everyone involved in that felony
is charged with murder?

480
00:33:36,880 --> 00:33:38,950
Counterfeiting is a felony.

481
00:33:41,360 --> 00:33:46,388
My client will confess to counterfeiting in
return for immunity from the murder charge.

482
00:33:46,480 --> 00:33:51,270
- Not good enough.
- He will provide the time of the next pick-up.

483
00:33:51,360 --> 00:33:53,749
You can arrest the actual murderers.

484
00:33:53,840 --> 00:33:58,550
When Sheriff Dawes says not good enough,
he means his sister, Larry.

485
00:33:58,640 --> 00:34:02,679
- He doesn't know anything about Dhani.
- What does he know?

486
00:34:06,920 --> 00:34:09,639
One week ago,
I arranged to meet some associates

487
00:34:09,720 --> 00:34:12,871
at an airstrip in the desert
to pass on commissioned art.

488
00:34:12,960 --> 00:34:14,871
He means counterfeit plates.

489
00:34:14,960 --> 00:34:19,556
As the plane landed, my associates
noticed two people spying on them

490
00:34:19,640 --> 00:34:24,156
from a vantage point above the airstrip.
They became very agitated.

491
00:34:24,240 --> 00:34:27,676
They commandeered my vehicle
and they drove up the hill.

492
00:34:27,760 --> 00:34:32,470
I got my Humvee, then I drove up there,
but I didn't see anything.

493
00:34:32,560 --> 00:34:35,233
Like blood on the hood of your vehicle?

494
00:34:36,720 --> 00:34:41,919
Well, the fact remains
that agreeing to this deal is the only way

495
00:34:42,000 --> 00:34:47,199
that you're going to catch the actual
murderers. You know where to find me.

496
00:34:47,280 --> 00:34:51,512
Wayne, I need to know
if they loaded Dhani on that plane.

497
00:34:51,600 --> 00:34:54,319
I never saw Dhani.

498
00:34:54,400 --> 00:34:57,358
- <i>(Booth)</i> Sheriff.
- That's my sister. My sister!

499
00:34:57,440 --> 00:35:00,591
I am truly sorry about Dhani, Ben. Truly sorry.

500
00:35:00,680 --> 00:35:03,911
But I don't think Wayne knows anything.

501
00:35:05,000 --> 00:35:07,230
Come on, Dawes. Easy.

502
00:35:07,320 --> 00:35:08,719
Come on.

503
00:35:15,120 --> 00:35:18,510
I guess we're gonna have to
take that deal, right?

504
00:35:19,680 --> 00:35:21,955
I was trained as an army ranger.

505
00:35:22,040 --> 00:35:25,316
- That mean anything to you, Sheriff Dawes?
- Yeah.

506
00:35:25,400 --> 00:35:30,679
I'd be happy to go back out to that crime
scene to see if there's anything we missed.

507
00:35:30,760 --> 00:35:33,399
Appreciate it.

508
00:35:34,240 --> 00:35:37,596
To win arguments here,
you'll need at least one doctorate.

509
00:35:37,680 --> 00:35:41,389
- I'm Dr Brennars grad student.
- I'm aware.

510
00:35:41,480 --> 00:35:46,395
Once I get my doctorate, she'll take another
student. My job here will go to that person.

511
00:35:46,480 --> 00:35:52,476
You have a first-rate mind, Mr Addy.
You can't assist Dr Brennan forever.

512
00:35:55,360 --> 00:35:57,590
I really hope this is necessary.

513
00:35:57,680 --> 00:36:02,708
He's comfortable here. He's enamoured with
Dr Brennan and he's stopped his thesis.

514
00:36:02,800 --> 00:36:06,076
It's just... I like the guy.

515
00:36:06,160 --> 00:36:10,472
So do I, which is why
we must think of what's best for him.

516
00:36:10,560 --> 00:36:13,199
It's time for Mr Addy to grow up.

517
00:36:17,320 --> 00:36:20,039
- So you say Dhani knows the desert.
- That's right.

518
00:36:20,120 --> 00:36:23,396
If it were you here stranded,
which way would you go?

519
00:36:23,480 --> 00:36:26,438
Highway's about a five-day walk that way.

520
00:36:26,520 --> 00:36:30,195
Mexico's three days that way,
and that way's two days to a ranch.

521
00:36:30,280 --> 00:36:33,716
You might find some stock water,
but the terrain is rougher.

522
00:36:33,800 --> 00:36:37,634
- So it all depends how much water she had.
- Is there any way to know?

523
00:36:37,720 --> 00:36:41,759
All right, look. We'll all take a point
off this compass, all right?

524
00:36:41,840 --> 00:36:45,958
Walk out in a straight line for 15 minutes
and we look for tracks.

525
00:36:46,040 --> 00:36:47,837
OK?

526
00:36:51,560 --> 00:36:54,472
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Rain" by Patti Griffin)</i>

527
00:37:13,680 --> 00:37:18,515
♪ <i>It's hard to listen to a hard, hard heart</i>

528
00:37:18,600 --> 00:37:23,549
♪ <i>Beating close to mine</i>

529
00:37:23,640 --> 00:37:28,555
♪ <i>Pounding up against the stone and steel</i>

530
00:37:28,640 --> 00:37:32,155
♪ <i>Walls that I won't climb</i>

531
00:37:33,160 --> 00:37:38,109
♪ <i>Sometimes a hurt is so deep, deep, deep</i>

532
00:37:38,200 --> 00:37:42,830
♪ <i>You think that you're gonna drown</i>

533
00:37:42,920 --> 00:37:47,152
♪ <i>Sometimes all I can do is weep, weep, weep</i>

534
00:37:47,240 --> 00:37:50,357
♪ <i>With all this rain</i>

535
00:37:50,440 --> 00:37:52,317
♪ <i>Falling down</i>

536
00:37:52,400 --> 00:37:57,110
♪ <i>Strange how hard it rains now</i>

537
00:37:57,560 --> 00:38:01,189
♪ <i>Rows and rows of big dark clouds</i>

538
00:38:01,280 --> 00:38:03,430
Are you all right?

539
00:38:07,560 --> 00:38:10,313
Dhani went that way.

540
00:38:13,720 --> 00:38:15,517
OK.

541
00:38:17,160 --> 00:38:21,790
♪ <i>Rain</i>

542
00:38:21,880 --> 00:38:26,715
♪ <i>Strange how hard it rains now</i>

543
00:38:26,800 --> 00:38:31,112
♪ <i>Rows and rows of big dark clouds</i>

544
00:38:31,200 --> 00:38:36,672
♪ <i>But I'm still alive underneath this shroud</i>

545
00:38:36,760 --> 00:38:40,958
♪ <i>Rain</i>

546
00:38:41,040 --> 00:38:45,636
♪ <i>Oh, rain</i>

547
00:38:45,840 --> 00:38:48,434
♪ <i>Oh, rain</i>

548
00:38:50,720 --> 00:38:57,717
♪ <i>Oh, rain</i>

549
00:39:00,960 --> 00:39:03,793
Ready to go home?

550
00:39:03,880 --> 00:39:05,950
Yeah.

551
00:39:09,800 --> 00:39:12,997
You aren't coming back again, are you?

552
00:39:14,120 --> 00:39:15,872
No.

553
00:39:15,960 --> 00:39:17,439
Never.

554
00:39:19,200 --> 00:39:21,760
He loved me.

555
00:39:22,280 --> 00:39:24,316
For three weeks a year.

556
00:39:24,400 --> 00:39:25,879
No.

557
00:39:25,960 --> 00:39:28,633
He loved me all the time.

558
00:39:28,720 --> 00:39:33,077
I was the one who could only manage
three weeks a year.

559
00:39:34,880 --> 00:39:37,314
I'm afraid that I...

560
00:39:37,400 --> 00:39:40,676
I'm just afraid
that I don't have a generous heart.

561
00:39:40,760 --> 00:39:46,630
I'm afraid that I won't have the chance
that I had with Kirk ever again.

562
00:39:48,160 --> 00:39:50,310
You will.

563
00:39:50,400 --> 00:39:52,436
How can you be so sure?

564
00:39:52,520 --> 00:39:57,548
Because nothing in this universe
happens just once, Angela.

565
00:39:58,000 --> 00:40:01,436
Nothing. Infinity goes in both directions.

566
00:40:01,520 --> 00:40:04,478
There is no unique event,

567
00:40:04,560 --> 00:40:07,836
no singular moment.

568
00:40:07,920 --> 00:40:10,388
I don't know what that means.

569
00:40:10,480 --> 00:40:14,268
It means you will get another chance.

570
00:40:14,360 --> 00:40:16,999
You promise?

571
00:40:17,640 --> 00:40:19,949
From your heart?

572
00:40:20,040 --> 00:40:22,952
Better. From my head.

573
00:40:23,520 --> 00:40:26,717
And, yes, Ange, I promise,

574
00:40:27,720 --> 00:40:29,915
from my heart,

575
00:40:30,000 --> 00:40:32,719
you will get another chance.

576
00:40:35,280 --> 00:40:39,319
Well, Dawes and his deputies,
they caught the counterfeiters.

577
00:40:39,400 --> 00:40:43,439
Dhani gave a statement saying
it was Kellogg who pulled the trigger on Kirk.

578
00:40:43,520 --> 00:40:47,354
Dhani knows that you pointed that helicopter
in the right direction.

579
00:40:47,440 --> 00:40:50,876
Obviously you subconsciously
sifted through rational facts

580
00:40:50,960 --> 00:40:53,838
and processed the most likely scenario.

581
00:40:53,920 --> 00:40:57,276
- I'm sure that's it.
- Yeah. What else could it be?

582
00:40:57,360 --> 00:40:59,555
It's the only rational explanation.

583
00:40:59,640 --> 00:41:02,757
Are you guys making fun of me?

584
00:41:02,840 --> 00:41:07,391
You know, let's go back home,
where there's water, shelter and living things.

585
00:41:07,480 --> 00:41:09,471
Come on.

586
00:41:11,960 --> 00:41:15,111
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Too Easy" by OneRepublic)</i>

587
00:41:17,960 --> 00:41:21,839
♪ <i>It's too easy</i>

588
00:41:21,920 --> 00:41:25,913
♪ <i>It's too easy for you</i>

589
00:41:28,800 --> 00:41:32,475
♪ <i>Autumn wind turns again</i>

590
00:41:32,560 --> 00:41:39,193
♪ <i>Days are warm, start to fade</i>

591
00:42:01,920 --> 00:42:04,275
Visiontext Subtitles: Jo Clarke

592
00:42:14,400 --> 00:42:15,719
What's that mean?

593
00:42:16,480 --> 00:42:18,471
ENGLISH SDH

