1
00:00:02,040 --> 00:00:06,636
As far back as 1938
the director of the FBI, J Edgar Hoover,

2
00:00:06,720 --> 00:00:11,840
wrote to the then curator of the Jeffersonian
Institution, Professor Daniel Payne,

3
00:00:11,920 --> 00:00:16,550
to aid in the evaluation of specimens
who were thought to be irrefutably human.

4
00:00:16,640 --> 00:00:18,756
This was the result.

5
00:00:18,840 --> 00:00:20,478
<i>(laughter)</i>

6
00:00:21,280 --> 00:00:24,477
Despite this disagreement,
the FBI and the Jeffersonian

7
00:00:24,560 --> 00:00:29,236
have forged a mutually beneficial
if somewhat tense relationship

8
00:00:29,320 --> 00:00:31,754
which survives to this day.

9
00:00:31,840 --> 00:00:33,831
Thank you.

10
00:00:36,800 --> 00:00:40,759
Thank you, Dr Brennan.
Are there any questions? Yes?

11
00:00:40,840 --> 00:00:46,358
- How much have you made from your book?
- I don't really know. I have an agent...

12
00:00:46,440 --> 00:00:50,991
That's not the kind of question we're looking
for from an anthropology student. Yes?

13
00:00:51,080 --> 00:00:53,548
Did you get your agent
before you wrote the book?

14
00:00:53,640 --> 00:00:57,474
People, Dr Brennan is
an accomplished forensic anthropologist

15
00:00:57,560 --> 00:00:59,437
who writes books on the side.

16
00:00:59,520 --> 00:01:02,557
I have a question regarding
the FBI's role in your book.

17
00:01:02,640 --> 00:01:06,519
Who do you base brilliant and insightful
Special Agent Andy Lister on?

18
00:01:06,600 --> 00:01:08,830
Oh, for God's sake.

19
00:01:08,920 --> 00:01:11,878
- I'm pretty sure it was me.
- What are you doing here, Booth?

20
00:01:11,960 --> 00:01:16,272
Local police got an anonymous call
saying there were human remains

21
00:01:16,360 --> 00:01:19,193
in a field behind a mall out in the suburbs.

22
00:01:19,280 --> 00:01:24,149
I did a profile of the suburb as a grad student.
The whole notion of a created community,

23
00:01:24,240 --> 00:01:27,835
a modern utopia
with its own mores and rules is fascinating.

24
00:01:27,920 --> 00:01:29,751
Fascinating to who?

25
00:01:29,840 --> 00:01:33,196
- To whom.
- Whom. <i>(laughs)</i> You gotta be kidding.

26
00:01:33,280 --> 00:01:36,352
- What? My publishers gave it to me.
- Gave it to you?

27
00:01:36,440 --> 00:01:39,557
Book sales are pretty good.
It's supposed to be a nice car.

28
00:01:39,640 --> 00:01:44,589
- Gave it to you? Why did you park crooked?
- Well, the guy said to always park it like that.

29
00:01:44,680 --> 00:01:48,229
- He's wrong. Makes you look like an idiot.
- How about I drive?

30
00:01:48,320 --> 00:01:52,279
- I cannot show up at a crime scene in that.
- Why?

31
00:01:52,360 --> 00:01:55,989
Because it would detract from the gravity
of my FBI presence,

32
00:01:56,080 --> 00:01:58,150
especially if you parked crooked.

33
00:01:58,240 --> 00:02:02,313
Why is the FBI involved in the search
for human remains behind a suburban mall?

34
00:02:02,400 --> 00:02:05,073
Because this boy is missing.

35
00:02:05,160 --> 00:02:06,912
<i>(Bones)</i> Oh.

36
00:02:07,000 --> 00:02:09,275
- A child.
- Yeah.

37
00:02:11,520 --> 00:02:13,988
Anonymous call came in a couple hours ago.

38
00:02:14,080 --> 00:02:16,878
- No sign of him yet.
- How do you know it wasrt a prank?

39
00:02:16,960 --> 00:02:21,670
<i>(upset girl) You have to come right away.</i>
<i>There's, like, a dead kid here all rotted away.</i>

40
00:02:21,760 --> 00:02:25,150
<i>He's in the field behind Clayton Hills Mall.</i>
<i>You better come!</i>

41
00:02:25,240 --> 00:02:27,037
- That rings true.
- Why anonymous?

42
00:02:27,120 --> 00:02:29,429
Kids come here to party, misbehave.

43
00:02:29,520 --> 00:02:32,876
Adolescents and preadolescents
tend to seek their own space,

44
00:02:32,960 --> 00:02:37,033
to establish their own society,
to counter parental influence.

45
00:02:37,120 --> 00:02:40,476
- You mind if I make an observation?
- No, of course not.

46
00:02:40,560 --> 00:02:45,031
In your book the cops come off
as very one-dimensional. Why is that?

47
00:02:45,120 --> 00:02:50,752
- You mean two-dimensional.
- One-dimensionality exists only in theory.

48
00:02:50,840 --> 00:02:52,637
OK.

49
00:02:52,720 --> 00:02:58,716
- Really looking forward to your next book.
- Did you bring the thermal imager?

50
00:02:58,800 --> 00:03:02,759
I don't think we need it.
It makes me look like the Great Gazoo.

51
00:03:02,840 --> 00:03:07,834
I don't know what that means
but we definitely need it, Zack.

52
00:03:10,840 --> 00:03:14,549
How's it going there, Darth?
See anything on Saturn?

53
00:03:15,360 --> 00:03:18,033
Oh, please tell me you've seen
one <i>Star Wars</i> movie.

54
00:03:18,120 --> 00:03:22,671
- When I was seven. And leave Zack alone.
- Can we please hurry up? It's stuffy in here.

55
00:03:22,760 --> 00:03:27,959
I should be able to see any heat residue
released from decomposing bodies.

56
00:03:28,040 --> 00:03:31,396
- <i>(Booth)</i> Party central.
- Because suburbs are so homogeneous,

57
00:03:31,480 --> 00:03:34,950
adolescents tend to rebel
in predictable and uniform ways.

58
00:03:35,040 --> 00:03:38,430
Fire, illicit substances, wayward behaviour.

59
00:03:38,520 --> 00:03:41,592
Do you think that would include
abducting a six-year-old?

60
00:03:41,680 --> 00:03:45,070
It's extreme.
Adolescents are more likely to drink alcohol

61
00:03:45,160 --> 00:03:49,073
and listen to culturally inappropriate music
at high volume.

62
00:03:49,160 --> 00:03:52,277
<i>(Zack)</i> I'm picking something up.

63
00:03:52,360 --> 00:03:54,749
- Oh, my God.
- <i>(Booth)</i> What?

64
00:03:56,640 --> 00:03:58,596
Why'd you stop?

65
00:03:58,680 --> 00:04:01,274
You can turn on your flashlight,

66
00:04:01,360 --> 00:04:04,557
aim it over here.

67
00:04:45,640 --> 00:04:50,919
<i>(Bones)</i> Before proceeding with maceration,
any general observations? Zack?

68
00:04:51,000 --> 00:04:54,549
Epiphyseal fusion puts the age
at approximately 6 to 10 years,

69
00:04:54,640 --> 00:04:59,794
- though the stature suggests younger.
- Good. I concur. Cause of death?

70
00:04:59,880 --> 00:05:02,269
Blunt trauma to the chest.

71
00:05:03,960 --> 00:05:05,916
Are you all right?

72
00:05:06,000 --> 00:05:09,356
He's so small. That's all.

73
00:05:09,440 --> 00:05:11,954
Go on with your work. I'm OK.

74
00:05:12,040 --> 00:05:16,875
The remains were significantly degraded
by animal activity, mostly dog and rodent.

75
00:05:16,960 --> 00:05:20,669
Despite the condition of the body
he's been dead only 36 to 48 hours.

76
00:05:20,760 --> 00:05:23,194
These were found a few yards from the body.

77
00:05:23,280 --> 00:05:25,999
In perfect condition. What does that tell you?

78
00:05:26,080 --> 00:05:32,076
- He wasrt wearing them when he was killed.
- Which suggests he was sexually assaulted.

79
00:05:32,160 --> 00:05:34,151
I'm done.

80
00:05:37,920 --> 00:05:40,514
<i>(Bones)</i> I think we have a match.

81
00:05:41,920 --> 00:05:43,990
The clothing matches.

82
00:05:44,080 --> 00:05:46,640
It's Charles Gregory Sanders.

83
00:05:47,080 --> 00:05:51,631
<i>(Booth)</i> On behalf of the FBI,
we're extremely sorry for the loss of your son.

84
00:05:51,720 --> 00:05:55,952
I have a few questions.
I mean, only if you're up to it.

85
00:05:57,040 --> 00:05:58,996
You have two other sons?

86
00:05:59,080 --> 00:06:01,958
Foster sons.
Though I try not to make the distinction.

87
00:06:02,040 --> 00:06:06,352
Shawn and David Cook. They are brothers.
I live right next door.

88
00:06:06,440 --> 00:06:09,034
Charlie was your own?

89
00:06:09,120 --> 00:06:10,553
Yes.

90
00:06:10,640 --> 00:06:14,952
- Charlie was mine.
- What about Mr Sanders?

91
00:06:15,040 --> 00:06:18,191
We divorced shortly before
Charlie was even born.

92
00:06:18,280 --> 00:06:21,511
- He works overseas.
- He doesn't even send child support.

93
00:06:21,600 --> 00:06:25,354
You mind if I ask
how you afford this nice neighbourhood?

94
00:06:25,440 --> 00:06:26,998
Mm.

95
00:06:27,080 --> 00:06:31,756
Child Services wouldn't allow
a single mother to foster if she worked.

96
00:06:31,840 --> 00:06:35,913
I live off the proceeds of a generous
trust fund my parents set up long ago.

97
00:06:36,000 --> 00:06:40,949
On the day that Charlie disappeared,
all three boys went to the park?

98
00:06:41,040 --> 00:06:44,589
It's a very safe neighbourhood.
They walk farther to school.

99
00:06:44,680 --> 00:06:47,638
We all keep an eye out
for each other around here.

100
00:06:47,720 --> 00:06:50,188
People are good neighbours, take an interest.

101
00:06:50,280 --> 00:06:53,590
- <i>(man)</i> Mom?
- In here, Skyler. This is my son, Skyler.

102
00:06:53,680 --> 00:06:56,399
Dad told me to bring them back.
We gotta go on ajob.

103
00:06:56,480 --> 00:07:01,349
- <i>(boy)</i> There's nothing to do here.
- <i>(sighs)</i> Our video game's broke.

104
00:07:01,440 --> 00:07:06,468
Shawn, David, this is Agent Booth. He's
gonna find out what happened to Charlie.

105
00:07:06,560 --> 00:07:12,032
- How are you gonna figure it out?
- Oh, I'm in the FBI. We always figure it out.

106
00:07:12,120 --> 00:07:18,070
Boys, if it's all right with your mother, maybe
I could help you out with your video game.

107
00:07:26,040 --> 00:07:28,554
These are invitations to a banquet.

108
00:07:28,640 --> 00:07:31,200
You called a meeting to invite us to a party?

109
00:07:31,280 --> 00:07:35,990
Don't think of it as an invitation.
Consider it a summons. It's for donors.

110
00:07:36,080 --> 00:07:38,958
Meet and greet, press the flesh, butt-kiss.

111
00:07:39,040 --> 00:07:42,510
I don't like it any more than you do.
These people fund our research

112
00:07:42,600 --> 00:07:46,559
and all they want in return is to rub elbows
with a scientist once in a while.

113
00:07:46,640 --> 00:07:48,756
- Can't make it.
- Yeah, me neither.

114
00:07:48,840 --> 00:07:53,038
- I have a date that night.
- You don't even know when it is.

115
00:07:53,560 --> 00:07:56,996
- Yes, Mr Addy.
- What kind of food will there be?

116
00:07:57,080 --> 00:08:01,073
When I said, "Think of this as a summons,"
I understated. It's a subpoena.

117
00:08:01,160 --> 00:08:04,152
A grand jury subpoena.
Ignore it at your own peril.

118
00:08:04,240 --> 00:08:07,596
- You're not gonna fire us if we don't go.
- No, not fire you.

119
00:08:07,680 --> 00:08:11,275
But I can move your parking spot
to lot M. Enjoy the shuttle ride.

120
00:08:11,360 --> 00:08:15,239
- The shuttle smells like feet.
- I know when I'm beat. I'm in.

121
00:08:15,320 --> 00:08:18,471
- What the hell? It's a party.
- Do I have to wear a tie?

122
00:08:18,560 --> 00:08:21,199
Formal wear.
I've arranged for a limo to pick us up.

123
00:08:21,280 --> 00:08:24,397
Not me. I'm not afraid of parking or feet.

124
00:08:24,480 --> 00:08:27,153
You drive me to work.
Don'tjust think of yourself.

125
00:08:27,240 --> 00:08:30,596
Repercussions and consequences,
Dr Hodgins. I'm your boss.

126
00:08:30,680 --> 00:08:33,478
And you will go to this banquet.

127
00:08:40,120 --> 00:08:45,035
- Do you know what you're doing?
- Yeah. I can fix anything. Cool.

128
00:08:45,120 --> 00:08:47,998
You guys, uh... you have girlfriends?

129
00:08:48,080 --> 00:08:50,150
- I do.
- Her name's Leila.

130
00:08:50,240 --> 00:08:54,313
- Leila. Leila.
- I thought you were gonna ask about Charlie.

131
00:08:54,400 --> 00:08:58,154
Yeah, so which one of you puny mortals
wants to challenge me first?

132
00:08:58,240 --> 00:09:00,470
- Oh, me!
- <i>(video game noises)</i>

133
00:09:08,000 --> 00:09:12,676
- You about to clean the bones?
- Yes. I'm warming up the boiler now.

134
00:09:13,280 --> 00:09:16,033
Something wrong?

135
00:09:16,120 --> 00:09:19,112
These are the smallest remains
I've ever worked on.

136
00:09:19,200 --> 00:09:24,069
That's a valid observation, Zack,
but it's not helpful to the investigation.

137
00:09:24,160 --> 00:09:27,152
Sorry, Dr Brennan.

138
00:09:28,360 --> 00:09:31,830
I was at Waco. Branch Davidian compound.

139
00:09:32,360 --> 00:09:37,514
I helped identify children
who had been killed in the fire.

140
00:09:37,600 --> 00:09:39,591
17 of them.

141
00:09:39,680 --> 00:09:41,989
So you're saying I'll get used to it?

142
00:09:42,080 --> 00:09:47,074
No. I'm saying you'll never get used to it.
We're primates, social creatures.

143
00:09:47,160 --> 00:09:51,472
It's coded into our DNA to protect our young,
even from each other.

144
00:09:51,560 --> 00:09:53,835
So I'm always going to feel terrible?

145
00:09:53,920 --> 00:09:57,595
What helps me is to pull back emotionally.

146
00:09:57,680 --> 00:10:00,877
Just put your heart in a box.

147
00:10:02,600 --> 00:10:06,309
I am not good with metaphor, Dr Brennan.

148
00:10:07,320 --> 00:10:12,075
- Focus on the details.
- Details, yeah. I can do that.

149
00:10:12,160 --> 00:10:14,037
No trauma to the skull.

150
00:10:14,120 --> 00:10:18,830
No compound fractures. Charlie was not
beaten to death or dismembered.

151
00:10:18,920 --> 00:10:22,799
It helps not to refer to the victim by name.

152
00:10:22,880 --> 00:10:28,113
Greenstick fractures
on ribs four, five, six and seven,

153
00:10:28,200 --> 00:10:31,988
and the sternum is snapped transversely
from the tip to the xiphoid.

154
00:10:32,080 --> 00:10:33,672
What does that indicate?

155
00:10:33,760 --> 00:10:36,752
The victim's chest was struck
by a heavy, blunt object.

156
00:10:36,840 --> 00:10:41,197
Are you certain we've learned everything
we can from the body at this stage?

157
00:10:41,280 --> 00:10:44,397
I've been over everything at least three times.

158
00:10:44,480 --> 00:10:46,596
Smell the mouth.

159
00:10:50,080 --> 00:10:54,232
Anything behind the typical smells
of decomposition?

160
00:10:54,320 --> 00:10:58,836
Some kind of chemical? Something used
to render the boy unconscious.

161
00:10:58,920 --> 00:11:05,234
Take samples from the mouth, jaw, sinuses,
and what's left of the oesophagus.

162
00:11:07,320 --> 00:11:09,959
Kids make it harder, Zack.

163
00:11:15,200 --> 00:11:19,273
- <i>(Booth)</i> All right, you beat me bad.
- <i>(boy)</i> No wonder you don't have a girlfriend.

164
00:11:19,360 --> 00:11:21,999
- David!
- It's OK, Mrs Sanders. It's all right.

165
00:11:22,080 --> 00:11:24,992
- No, I do have a girlfriend.
- Is she pretty?

166
00:11:25,080 --> 00:11:27,275
Nah. She's butt ugly.

167
00:11:27,360 --> 00:11:30,636
- Got a glass eye, snaggly back teeth.
- <i>(laughter)</i>

168
00:11:30,720 --> 00:11:33,792
So, was Leila with you
the day that Charlie disappeared?

169
00:11:33,880 --> 00:11:37,839
Uh, yeah, actually. We stopped and played
some video games at the arcade.

170
00:11:37,920 --> 00:11:43,233
- Before you and Charlie went to the park.
- You didn't go to the mall that day, David.

171
00:11:45,240 --> 00:11:46,832
Shawn?

172
00:11:48,120 --> 00:11:51,749
- Don't ask Shawn, Mom.
- You met Leila at the mall, didn't you?

173
00:11:52,720 --> 00:11:55,712
You left Charlie with Shawn at the park.

174
00:11:56,840 --> 00:11:59,832
Just for a few minutes
and then they came back to the mall.

175
00:11:59,920 --> 00:12:02,480
- David!
- Shawn let go of his hand for a second.

176
00:12:02,560 --> 00:12:04,596
Charlie was gone like that.

177
00:12:04,680 --> 00:12:07,831
And then we came straight home.

178
00:12:07,920 --> 00:12:11,595
Charlie wasrt taken from the park,
he was snatched from the mall.

179
00:12:11,680 --> 00:12:13,955
We've been looking in the wrong place.

180
00:12:14,040 --> 00:12:16,952
<i>(Skyler's dad)</i> Come on, son. Let's go.

181
00:12:29,400 --> 00:12:31,914
What's with the rubber band?

182
00:12:32,000 --> 00:12:37,996
Methyl oxide vapour will bind to whatever
Charlie breathed in before he was killed.

183
00:12:39,240 --> 00:12:42,038
- Ouch!
- It's an anger management technique, right?

184
00:12:42,120 --> 00:12:47,319
The key there is management,
which is what I'm doing. Managing my anger.

185
00:12:47,400 --> 00:12:51,154
There'll be a colour change.
Red for chalcogens and blue for halogens.

186
00:12:51,240 --> 00:12:53,231
I get that you're a little off kilter.

187
00:12:53,320 --> 00:12:56,835
Mad at the government,
conspiracy of dunces, all that.

188
00:12:56,920 --> 00:13:01,869
Furious you've had to mount a boy's jawbone
inside a box to find out what killed him.

189
00:13:01,960 --> 00:13:07,318
What I don't get is why going to a banquet
makes you angry.

190
00:13:07,400 --> 00:13:10,597
Halogens it is.
I'm gonna scrape off the particles

191
00:13:10,680 --> 00:13:14,195
and see if the mass spectrometer
can identify what type of halogen.

192
00:13:14,280 --> 00:13:17,158
Anger is only fear turned inwards.

193
00:13:26,000 --> 00:13:32,394
There are 20 surveillance cameras taking stills
every two seconds throughout the mall.

194
00:13:32,480 --> 00:13:35,517
I concentrated on the ones
aimed at the public concourse.

195
00:13:35,600 --> 00:13:39,070
10,000 people a day go through that mall.
How will we find one kid?

196
00:13:39,160 --> 00:13:43,836
Angela designed a mass recognition program
to apply body types to skeletal remains.

197
00:13:43,920 --> 00:13:46,275
Endomorph, ectomorph, that sort of thing.

198
00:13:46,360 --> 00:13:49,079
I modified it
to scan two-dimensional images.

199
00:13:49,160 --> 00:13:54,598
We're looking for body masses roughly
congruent with Charlie, Shawn and David.

200
00:13:54,680 --> 00:13:58,673
- There's David.
- You're actually one of them, aren't you?

201
00:13:58,760 --> 00:14:01,354
- One of who?
- A squint. I mean, you look normal

202
00:14:01,440 --> 00:14:04,273
and you act normal
but you're actually one of them.

203
00:14:04,360 --> 00:14:07,989
This whole mass recognition program
was Brennars idea.

204
00:14:08,080 --> 00:14:10,355
I'm completely normal, really.

205
00:14:10,440 --> 00:14:13,876
Yeah, maybe before you got this job,
but now...

206
00:14:14,680 --> 00:14:16,910
I see Charlie.

207
00:14:18,120 --> 00:14:20,475
Oh. That's him, all right.

208
00:14:20,560 --> 00:14:22,755
<i>(Angela)</i> Oh, God.

209
00:14:22,840 --> 00:14:25,400
Ange? Are you OK?

210
00:14:25,480 --> 00:14:30,634
These are probably the last pictures
of this little guy alive.

211
00:14:32,920 --> 00:14:36,708
Why is he alone?
Why isn't anybody with him?

212
00:14:36,800 --> 00:14:37,789
<i>(sighs)</i>

213
00:14:37,880 --> 00:14:41,919
Sorry. Max resolution is
640 by 480 pixels per square inch.

214
00:14:42,000 --> 00:14:45,675
He's not alone. Someone's calling him
over. Can't you just zoom in?

215
00:14:45,760 --> 00:14:50,993
The fewer pixels that make up an image, the
more the picture degrades once we zoom in.

216
00:14:51,080 --> 00:14:53,469
Did that sound too squinty?

217
00:14:53,560 --> 00:14:57,348
- Any way to enance it?
- I wouldn't bet a date with Colin Farrell on it.

218
00:14:57,440 --> 00:15:00,750
- I know him. He's funny.
- Funny is Will Ferrell, sweetie.

219
00:15:00,840 --> 00:15:02,751
Hot is Colin Farrell.

220
00:15:02,840 --> 00:15:07,516
The kid was definitely moving toward
someone. He wasrt trying to get away.

221
00:15:07,600 --> 00:15:11,991
I want to add the neighbourhood kid, Skyler,
to the list of possible suspects.

222
00:15:12,080 --> 00:15:16,949
I have one other angle
but our bad guy's still obstructed in it.

223
00:15:21,040 --> 00:15:24,157
Who the hell are you?

224
00:15:34,320 --> 00:15:37,790
Are you thinking of leaving the Jeffersonian?

225
00:15:38,800 --> 00:15:40,836
I'm not really this person.

226
00:15:41,560 --> 00:15:44,597
- What person?
- I'm not like you.

227
00:15:45,040 --> 00:15:49,750
I'm not driven by the need
forjustice and all that.

228
00:15:49,840 --> 00:15:52,354
I'm a good-time girl.

229
00:15:52,440 --> 00:15:54,351
We have good times.

230
00:15:54,440 --> 00:15:59,116
Cracking jokes over murdered skeletons
is not good times.

231
00:15:59,200 --> 00:16:04,274
- It's harder on you than it is for the rest of us.
- No, it's not.

232
00:16:05,640 --> 00:16:07,949
Why?

233
00:16:08,040 --> 00:16:10,031
Because you look at their faces.

234
00:16:10,120 --> 00:16:13,192
We look at everything else.
It's more clinical for us.

235
00:16:13,280 --> 00:16:16,670
For you... it's personal.

236
00:16:16,760 --> 00:16:21,880
- When we see a murdered child...
- Honey, I... I'm... No offence.

237
00:16:21,960 --> 00:16:27,114
I'm really not up for one of your
"it takes a village" anthropology lessons.

238
00:16:27,560 --> 00:16:30,677
This is the longest I've ever had ajob.

239
00:16:30,760 --> 00:16:32,955
That's because of you.

240
00:16:34,400 --> 00:16:37,710
If this is about hours
or time to do your own art, then...

241
00:16:37,800 --> 00:16:40,360
Just let me work on it, OK?

242
00:16:41,320 --> 00:16:45,233
I'm an artist. I used to draw naked guys.

243
00:16:46,040 --> 00:16:48,110
Now I draw dead guys.

244
00:16:50,720 --> 00:16:53,473
Just don't decide anything
without talking to me.

245
00:16:53,560 --> 00:16:55,710
Of course I won't.

246
00:16:58,720 --> 00:17:00,711
<i>(sighs)</i>

247
00:17:11,120 --> 00:17:14,669
- Angela might quit.
- I'm amazed she's stuck it out this long.

248
00:17:14,760 --> 00:17:17,672
- Why?
- Oh, because she's human.

249
00:17:17,760 --> 00:17:22,197
I'm sorry, Bones. It's just that, you know,
uh, Angela didn't get the same training

250
00:17:22,280 --> 00:17:25,317
that the rest of you got on Planet Vulcan.

251
00:17:25,400 --> 00:17:27,709
- I don't know what that means.
- She's sensitive.

252
00:17:27,800 --> 00:17:29,631
- Who's sensitive?
- Angela.

253
00:17:29,720 --> 00:17:33,952
She likes puppies, and kitties,
and ducklings, and Jell-O shots,

254
00:17:34,040 --> 00:17:36,952
and, you know, dancing on bars. <i>(hums)</i>

255
00:17:37,400 --> 00:17:41,996
I know that. She's my best friend. Angela's
not the only person who likes baby animals.

256
00:17:42,080 --> 00:17:46,676
- I never got the big attraction.
- I rest my case. She's more sensitive.

257
00:17:46,760 --> 00:17:51,231
We cross-referenced the length and density
of Charlie's legs with children his age.

258
00:17:51,320 --> 00:17:53,914
The victim, I mean.

259
00:17:56,440 --> 00:18:00,479
The thing to do is concentrate on the details.

260
00:18:01,920 --> 00:18:04,992
- Let's do that.
- We found some abnormalities.

261
00:18:05,080 --> 00:18:07,310
They're bowed and abnormally short.

262
00:18:07,400 --> 00:18:11,712
- The bones show freezing of the joints.
- Are you saying Charlie was crippled?

263
00:18:11,800 --> 00:18:15,952
- The victim was disabled, yes.
- His mother never mentioned that.

264
00:18:16,040 --> 00:18:19,749
The ribs are broken in two places,
not typical of blunt-force trauma.

265
00:18:19,840 --> 00:18:24,868
- How do you explain that?
- I attribute it to his medical condition.

266
00:18:24,960 --> 00:18:31,149
- I agree. What is that condition?
- It looks like scoliosis, a bend in the spine.

267
00:18:34,360 --> 00:18:36,191
I think it's more than that, Zack.

268
00:18:36,280 --> 00:18:40,319
There are multiple calcified lesions
on the posterior thoracic vertebrae.

269
00:18:40,400 --> 00:18:46,111
That, plus Charlie's short stature,
and the asymmetric length of his legs...

270
00:18:46,200 --> 00:18:49,715
Margaret Sanders may not be
Charlie's biological mother.

271
00:18:49,800 --> 00:18:50,949
What?

272
00:18:51,040 --> 00:18:53,998
Test the bones
for X-linked hypophosphataemia

273
00:18:54,080 --> 00:18:55,911
and Coffin-Lowry Syndrome.

274
00:18:56,000 --> 00:18:57,911
Whoa, whoa. OK, hold on.

275
00:18:58,000 --> 00:19:01,231
Simmer down. Back up to the part
where she's not his mother.

276
00:19:01,320 --> 00:19:04,551
Dr Brennan is having me check
for hereditary genetic defects

277
00:19:04,640 --> 00:19:06,676
which are passed from mother to child.

278
00:19:06,760 --> 00:19:11,709
If Charlie had one, then Margaret
Sanders is not his mother.

279
00:19:17,320 --> 00:19:22,872
- How can you say that?
- Charlie suffered from hypophosphataemia.

280
00:19:22,960 --> 00:19:25,838
- Charlie's real mother would have it.
- You do not.

281
00:19:25,920 --> 00:19:28,434
Never say I wasrt Charlie's real mother.
I was.

282
00:19:28,520 --> 00:19:34,231
Biological mother, then. Mrs Sanders,
you are not Charlie's biological mother.

283
00:19:34,320 --> 00:19:36,550
You want to explain that to us?

284
00:19:38,320 --> 00:19:42,757
I can't have children.
That's why my husband left me.

285
00:19:42,840 --> 00:19:46,310
- So I took in foster kids.
- Like Shawn and David Cook.

286
00:19:46,400 --> 00:19:48,391
And Charlie.

287
00:19:49,320 --> 00:19:51,550
Though his name was Nathan.

288
00:19:51,640 --> 00:19:53,870
I got him as a baby down in Pittsburgh.

289
00:19:53,960 --> 00:19:55,951
Ten days old.

290
00:19:57,240 --> 00:20:02,951
His mother was arrested on drug charges
and Child Services brought him to me.

291
00:20:03,040 --> 00:20:07,477
Three weeks I had him.
Then the charges were dropped.

292
00:20:07,560 --> 00:20:10,074
- You kept him?
- No.

293
00:20:10,160 --> 00:20:13,994
I gave him back, but it nearly killed me.

294
00:20:15,320 --> 00:20:17,515
I stayed in touch.

295
00:20:18,520 --> 00:20:21,432
I bought him things. Formula, stroller.

296
00:20:22,240 --> 00:20:25,232
I wanted to make sure he was all right.

297
00:20:25,320 --> 00:20:28,118
Nathan what, Mrs Sanders?

298
00:20:29,360 --> 00:20:31,396
Nathan Downey.

299
00:20:31,480 --> 00:20:34,677
His mother was a drug addict named Jeanine.

300
00:20:35,680 --> 00:20:40,037
On Christmas Day, I found her dead on
the kitchen floor, a needle stuck in her arm,

301
00:20:40,120 --> 00:20:43,430
and I could hear Charlie crying upstairs.

302
00:20:43,520 --> 00:20:46,318
- So I went up.
- And you took him home.

303
00:20:46,400 --> 00:20:49,437
I looked him in the eyes and I promised him

304
00:20:49,520 --> 00:20:53,115
I would never leave him alone again.

305
00:20:53,200 --> 00:20:55,475
And he stopped crying.

306
00:20:55,560 --> 00:20:59,314
I expected every day
for Child Services to come looking.

307
00:20:59,400 --> 00:21:03,678
He would have ended up
back in the system anyway.

308
00:21:04,600 --> 00:21:07,910
I meant to keep him safe... <i>(sobs)</i>

309
00:21:08,000 --> 00:21:10,719
And love him.

310
00:21:10,800 --> 00:21:13,439
And now he's dead.

311
00:21:18,480 --> 00:21:21,392
- I had to arrest her.
- The story checked out.

312
00:21:21,480 --> 00:21:23,072
She confessed to kidnapping.

313
00:21:23,160 --> 00:21:28,439
Margaret responded to the anthropological
imperative. She saw an orphan and reacted.

314
00:21:28,520 --> 00:21:32,354
This is not a <i>National Geographic</i> study, OK?
This is the suburbs.

315
00:21:32,440 --> 00:21:38,151
- Why would she kill the boy? She loved him.
- The kid gets sick, he's not what you wanted.

316
00:21:38,240 --> 00:21:43,951
I bet you could give me a dozen examples
of societies that have killed their own young.

317
00:21:44,040 --> 00:21:46,076
What about Shawn and David Cook?

318
00:21:46,160 --> 00:21:48,515
- Where do they go now?
- Back into the system.

319
00:21:48,600 --> 00:21:51,398
Do you have any idea how bad
the foster-care system is?

320
00:21:51,480 --> 00:21:53,516
Do you? What do you want to do, hm?

321
00:21:53,600 --> 00:21:56,353
Do you want to kidnap them
like she kidnapped Charlie?

322
00:21:56,440 --> 00:22:00,149
I want you to let them go home
to Margaret Sanders.

323
00:22:00,240 --> 00:22:02,435
It's not gonna happen.

324
00:22:07,760 --> 00:22:10,149
- Try redigitising and resizing.
- I did.

325
00:22:10,240 --> 00:22:13,357
The extrapolation protocol
got confused by the spread.

326
00:22:13,440 --> 00:22:15,749
You know Hodgins better than anybody else.

327
00:22:15,840 --> 00:22:18,752
So, why is he so bent out of shape
about this banquet?

328
00:22:18,840 --> 00:22:21,638
- What makes you say that?
- When someone mentions it

329
00:22:21,720 --> 00:22:24,359
he snaps that rubber band around his wrist.

330
00:22:24,440 --> 00:22:27,591
What makes you think
I know Hodgins better than anyone else?

331
00:22:27,680 --> 00:22:30,240
- You're roommates.
- I live above his garage.

332
00:22:30,320 --> 00:22:32,276
- But you see a lot of each other.
- No.

333
00:22:32,360 --> 00:22:36,035
- He drives you to work.
- I've never been up to the main house.

334
00:22:36,120 --> 00:22:38,793
- The main house?
- It's at the end of the driveway

335
00:22:38,880 --> 00:22:41,394
on the other side of the tennis courts.

336
00:22:41,480 --> 00:22:44,517
OK. Anything on the identity
of Charlie's abductor?

337
00:22:44,600 --> 00:22:49,720
I can't clear up this image. Tell Booth what
you told me about living in Hodgins' garage.

338
00:22:49,800 --> 00:22:53,634
There's a bedroom, living room, kitchen,
another bedroom, a den...

339
00:22:53,720 --> 00:22:57,633
- Quite a garage. Can we focus on the case?
- How many cars does he have?

340
00:22:57,720 --> 00:23:01,508
Including the antique ones, about 12.
And a boat.

341
00:23:01,600 --> 00:23:05,479
Zack has never seen the main house.
The tennis courts block the view.

342
00:23:05,560 --> 00:23:09,348
- Well, he must be one of <i>those</i> Hodgins.
- Who are those Hodgins?

343
00:23:09,440 --> 00:23:13,479
- You know, the Cantilever Group Hodgins.
- Oh, my God.

344
00:23:13,560 --> 00:23:16,472
The Cantilever Group
generates more GNP than Europe.

345
00:23:16,560 --> 00:23:20,712
Get this. They are the single biggest donors
to the Jeffersonian Institution.

346
00:23:20,800 --> 00:23:24,395
Ha! That makes Hodgins your boss. <i>(laughs)</i>

347
00:23:26,560 --> 00:23:29,313
What do you talk about
when he drives you to work?

348
00:23:29,400 --> 00:23:32,915
I mostly sleep.
Hodgins mostly yells at the radio.

349
00:23:33,000 --> 00:23:36,151
If you can't see the face,
maybe you can grab a reflection.

350
00:23:36,240 --> 00:23:39,038
- That's a workable idea.
- Well, I'd say thanks,

351
00:23:39,120 --> 00:23:43,238
you know, if you didn't say it
like it was some kind of a miracle.

352
00:23:47,600 --> 00:23:53,311
Chem lab mass spectrometer identifies the
particulates in Charlie's mouth as fluoride.

353
00:23:53,400 --> 00:23:55,755
- I recognise that look.
- What?

354
00:23:55,840 --> 00:24:00,789
You're writing another book. When you write
you look like you stuck a fork in a toaster.

355
00:24:00,880 --> 00:24:04,429
- Am I in this one, too?
- Fluoride? At what concentration?

356
00:24:04,520 --> 00:24:07,557
- It's too high for toothpaste.
- Put together a list of...

357
00:24:07,640 --> 00:24:11,599
Put together a list of anything
that contains fluoride at those levels.

358
00:24:11,680 --> 00:24:13,716
All right. Do you have time for this?

359
00:24:13,800 --> 00:24:16,360
- They gave me a car.
- Nice. Who?

360
00:24:16,440 --> 00:24:19,910
My publisher. I feel like I have to earn it
by writing another book.

361
00:24:20,000 --> 00:24:26,348
Fight coercion in all its forms. You don't write
the book. I don't go to the banquet. Solidarity.

362
00:24:29,880 --> 00:24:32,235
Angela has a face for the abductor.

363
00:24:37,200 --> 00:24:41,591
I looked on both cameras.
This one offered up more reflective surfaces.

364
00:24:41,680 --> 00:24:43,113
Right at the door.

365
00:24:43,200 --> 00:24:47,034
- <i>(Angela)</i> Check this out.
- <i>(Booth)</i> The abductor's face.

366
00:24:47,120 --> 00:24:51,511
The computer can interpret the spaces
between the white and the dark gaps

367
00:24:51,600 --> 00:24:53,875
and fill in the missing pieces.

368
00:24:53,960 --> 00:24:59,830
- Wait. That doesn't look like an adult.
- I already polarised the image.

369
00:25:02,560 --> 00:25:06,235
- Shawn Cook.
- The victim's foster brother.

370
00:25:11,680 --> 00:25:15,514
- <i>(Booth)</i> Where were you taking Charlie?
- I brought him to the mall.

371
00:25:15,600 --> 00:25:20,549
I know you brought him to the mall,
but we got a picture of you...

372
00:25:20,640 --> 00:25:23,234
leading him out of the mall.

373
00:25:25,840 --> 00:25:29,435
- Have you seen much of this?
- I'm ajuvenile prosecutor.

374
00:25:29,520 --> 00:25:32,398
I wish I could say kids killing kids was rare.

375
00:25:32,800 --> 00:25:35,633
<i>(Booth)</i> Where were you taking him, Shawn?

376
00:25:35,720 --> 00:25:39,554
- When can I talk to Margaret?
- After you answer my questions.

377
00:25:39,640 --> 00:25:42,279
Can he do that? Lie to a kid?

378
00:25:42,360 --> 00:25:44,590
We're after a child killer, Dr Brennan.

379
00:25:44,680 --> 00:25:48,275
If the child advocate in there
doesn't complain, I sure won't.

380
00:25:48,360 --> 00:25:51,670
Well, what's the point
if he doesn't advocate for the child?

381
00:25:51,760 --> 00:25:55,673
I get the impression you're a little confused
as to what side you're on.

382
00:25:56,520 --> 00:25:57,873
Shawn.

383
00:25:58,680 --> 00:26:01,148
- You know what that is?
- A scar?

384
00:26:01,240 --> 00:26:02,389
Yeah.

385
00:26:02,480 --> 00:26:06,473
Got it when I was playing soldier
with my brother Jared.

386
00:26:06,560 --> 00:26:09,597
- Did it hurt?
- Yeah, it hurt.

387
00:26:09,680 --> 00:26:11,591
But it was an accident.

388
00:26:11,680 --> 00:26:13,875
You got any scars?

389
00:26:18,080 --> 00:26:20,150
My dad did it with a cigarette.

390
00:26:21,120 --> 00:26:23,793
He shouldn't have done that.

391
00:26:24,760 --> 00:26:29,709
Margaret didn't do anything like that.
I love Margaret.

392
00:26:29,800 --> 00:26:34,828
What I need to know is
if Charlie had some kind of an accident.

393
00:26:36,760 --> 00:26:38,079
Shawn?

394
00:26:38,160 --> 00:26:40,390
Maybe we can just take a break.

395
00:26:40,480 --> 00:26:41,629
Shawn.

396
00:26:41,720 --> 00:26:44,917
- He's not aggressive enough.
- Foster kids are powerless.

397
00:26:45,000 --> 00:26:50,597
They're treated like garbage, and all you have
to say is, "He's not aggressive enough"?

398
00:26:50,680 --> 00:26:56,869
Dr Brennan, you know this boy may very well
have beaten a child to death with a rock?

399
00:27:10,920 --> 00:27:15,994
- How long have we known each other?
- Do people really ever know each other?

400
00:27:16,080 --> 00:27:18,719
How come you never invited me
over to your house?

401
00:27:18,800 --> 00:27:23,510
- Oh, I didn't pick up that kind of vibe off you.
- I thought we were close, all of us.

402
00:27:23,600 --> 00:27:26,353
What else don't I know?
Is Zack from another planet?

403
00:27:26,440 --> 00:27:28,715
Oh, come on. That one's obvious.

404
00:27:30,040 --> 00:27:31,917
You're rich.

405
00:27:32,000 --> 00:27:35,117
You single-handedly own
the Cantilever Group.

406
00:27:35,200 --> 00:27:37,589
Don't deny it. I know.

407
00:27:38,240 --> 00:27:40,356
- Who else knows?
- Zack.

408
00:27:40,440 --> 00:27:41,793
Booth.

409
00:27:41,880 --> 00:27:44,155
Don't tell Brennan.

410
00:27:44,240 --> 00:27:46,879
Why don't you want us to know
that you're our boss?

411
00:27:46,960 --> 00:27:52,557
I don't want to be anybody's boss.
I never did. Please respect that.

412
00:27:57,840 --> 00:28:01,549
- What's up with Angela?
- It's job pressure.

413
00:28:02,080 --> 00:28:05,516
Fluoride at lower concentrations
is used in toothpaste, tea,

414
00:28:05,600 --> 00:28:09,912
and is added to our water, which can cause
a range of conditions. Brain damage...

415
00:28:10,000 --> 00:28:14,152
Which has nothing to do
with the case at hand.

416
00:28:14,840 --> 00:28:18,992
The concentrations found in our victim
might come from paint thinners, car wax,

417
00:28:19,080 --> 00:28:21,833
- or various other industrial products.
- OK.

418
00:28:21,920 --> 00:28:24,480
Did Angela say anything
about quitting herjob?

419
00:28:24,560 --> 00:28:26,551
No.

420
00:28:26,640 --> 00:28:29,916
But we hardly know anything
about each other.

421
00:28:39,120 --> 00:28:40,314
Bones.

422
00:28:40,400 --> 00:28:46,032
I thought you'd like to know
that Shawn and David are in emergency care.

423
00:28:46,120 --> 00:28:51,240
Pulled some strings, you know,
to make sure they get to stay together.

424
00:28:51,320 --> 00:28:54,312
- That's good. Thanks.
- It's the best I could do.

425
00:28:54,400 --> 00:28:58,029
- Yeah, I understand.
- No, you say you understand but you don't.

426
00:28:58,120 --> 00:29:03,877
Not really. I mean, if you don't like the rule
you ignore it, right? I can't have that.

427
00:29:03,960 --> 00:29:06,269
- And if you want to do this...
- Do what?

428
00:29:06,360 --> 00:29:09,477
Work on cases, you know, with me,
outside the lab.

429
00:29:09,560 --> 00:29:13,269
If you want to do that,
I need to know that you will respect the law.

430
00:29:13,360 --> 00:29:17,717
Tell you what. If I can't respect the law,
I can at least respect you.

431
00:29:17,800 --> 00:29:20,758
Oh. <i>(stammers, laughs)</i>

432
00:29:20,840 --> 00:29:23,912
Yeah, that'll work.
It kinda comes outta nowhere, but...

433
00:29:24,000 --> 00:29:26,798
<i>(Bones)</i> Look what you did.

434
00:29:26,880 --> 00:29:29,189
It's a pencil. I'll get you a new one.

435
00:29:29,280 --> 00:29:32,033
The victim was killed by trauma to the chest

436
00:29:32,120 --> 00:29:35,157
but the ribs are broken in two places,
notjust one.

437
00:29:35,240 --> 00:29:38,676
Because of the, uh... the brittle bones,
because of his disease.

438
00:29:38,760 --> 00:29:40,796
But there's another explanation.

439
00:29:40,880 --> 00:29:43,917
- Whoa. What's the other explanation?
- Compression.

440
00:29:44,000 --> 00:29:45,956
- Charlie was crushed to death?
- Yes.

441
00:29:46,040 --> 00:29:49,032
Greenstick fractures,
vertebral and sternal. See?

442
00:29:49,120 --> 00:29:53,113
Shawn outweighed Charlie by 30Ibs.
How could he have crushed him to death?

443
00:29:53,200 --> 00:29:56,158
We need to run some scenarios
through the Angelator.

444
00:29:56,240 --> 00:29:58,231
- Angela.
- Booth.

445
00:29:59,480 --> 00:30:04,429
Zack has been informed that if he tells anyone
who I am, I will kick him out on the street.

446
00:30:04,520 --> 00:30:08,115
- There's nothing I can threaten you two with.
- Yeah, that's a shame.

447
00:30:08,200 --> 00:30:12,591
What I want out of my life is to come in here
and sift through slime and bugs.

448
00:30:12,680 --> 00:30:15,513
My family is one of those
who secretly run the world.

449
00:30:15,600 --> 00:30:19,798
Paranoia and delusions of grandeur
all in one package.

450
00:30:19,880 --> 00:30:25,876
You call it paranoia, I call it the family
business. Please, could you just stop?

451
00:30:26,720 --> 00:30:29,029
The reason I do not want to go
to that banquet

452
00:30:29,120 --> 00:30:33,636
is because the other members of the ruling
elite will make a big fuss about seeing me.

453
00:30:33,720 --> 00:30:39,272
My secret will be out and my life,
this life that I love, will be ruined.

454
00:30:39,720 --> 00:30:45,875
I'm asking you, please, please just let me be
Jack Hodgins who works in the lab.

455
00:30:53,000 --> 00:30:56,788
Charlie was 3'4" tall and weighed 58Ibs.

456
00:30:56,880 --> 00:31:01,476
- And Shawn?
- Shawn Cook is 1.4m tall and weighs 31kg.

457
00:31:01,560 --> 00:31:04,518
His brother David was 5'8, 150Ibs.

458
00:31:04,600 --> 00:31:07,512
1.75m, 68kg.

459
00:31:07,600 --> 00:31:11,229
I thought the break to Charlie's sternum
was caused by blunt trauma

460
00:31:11,320 --> 00:31:15,029
because it only ran along one fault line.
When Booth broke my pencil,

461
00:31:15,120 --> 00:31:19,079
I realised there's another way
to cause the same injury. Compression.

462
00:31:19,160 --> 00:31:22,232
Hodgins found no particulates
that suggested crushing.

463
00:31:22,320 --> 00:31:27,758
Body weight. There has to be enough weight
on the victim so no air can get into the lungs.

464
00:31:27,840 --> 00:31:32,960
Prolonged pressure caused the sternum
to snap in half and the ribs to break.

465
00:31:33,040 --> 00:31:35,508
Oh, my God.

466
00:31:38,760 --> 00:31:41,149
Sorry. Sorry.

467
00:31:42,600 --> 00:31:46,149
I entered real-world variables
taking into account Charlie's size

468
00:31:46,240 --> 00:31:51,758
and the pressure that was required to break
Charlie's sternum in the way it was broken.

469
00:31:51,840 --> 00:31:55,230
- What did you end up with?
- 86.2kg.

470
00:31:56,320 --> 00:31:58,834
- What's that in American?
- 190Ibs.

471
00:32:00,720 --> 00:32:04,030
Way too much for either of the Cook kids
or Margaret Sanders.

472
00:32:04,120 --> 00:32:07,874
I'd put the neighbourhood kid, Skyler,
at about 160Ibs.

473
00:32:07,960 --> 00:32:12,829
- It can't be him, either.
- We should be looking for a full-grown man.

474
00:32:12,920 --> 00:32:16,799
Get Shawn to tell you where he took Charlie
when they left the mall.

475
00:32:16,880 --> 00:32:19,235
He won't talk to me.

476
00:32:19,320 --> 00:32:21,038
- Let me do it.
- Oh, no.

477
00:32:21,120 --> 00:32:24,112
You know, people are not
your strong point, Bones,

478
00:32:24,200 --> 00:32:27,875
and, besides, he's not gonna care
how many facts you put in front of him.

479
00:32:27,960 --> 00:32:31,873
Could you just go with me on this one,
Booth? We're trying to catch a killer.

480
00:32:31,960 --> 00:32:35,839
- Let me help.
- Whers the last time you talked to a kid?

481
00:32:35,920 --> 00:32:38,115
I know what to say.

482
00:32:39,680 --> 00:32:45,277
- <i>Do you remember me, Shawn?</i>
- <i>The museum lady. The one who's so smart.</i>

483
00:32:45,360 --> 00:32:47,191
<i>Yeah, I'm pretty smart.</i>

484
00:32:47,280 --> 00:32:51,273
- And very modest.
- Oh, believe me, she is being modest.

485
00:32:51,360 --> 00:32:55,239
Smart enough to know
that you didn't kill Charlie.

486
00:32:55,320 --> 00:32:58,118
You don't have to say anything, Shawn.

487
00:32:58,200 --> 00:33:00,191
Just listen.

488
00:33:01,640 --> 00:33:06,430
They give you a garbage bag
to carry all your stuff,

489
00:33:06,520 --> 00:33:09,717
like they're telling you
everything you own is garbage.

490
00:33:09,800 --> 00:33:15,352
And then you have to go to a new school
in clothes that smell like garbage bags.

491
00:33:15,440 --> 00:33:19,228
All the regular kids know you're a foster kid.

492
00:33:22,120 --> 00:33:24,680
How do you know what it's like?

493
00:33:24,760 --> 00:33:27,832
They bounce you from place to place

494
00:33:27,920 --> 00:33:30,434
and it's never home.

495
00:33:31,320 --> 00:33:34,596
Sometimes the foster parents are nice.

496
00:33:35,720 --> 00:33:37,870
- Like Margaret?
- Yeah.

497
00:33:37,960 --> 00:33:42,511
And sometimes they separate you
from your brother.

498
00:33:42,600 --> 00:33:45,114
It must have been nice with Margaret,

499
00:33:45,200 --> 00:33:47,191
staying with David.

500
00:33:48,280 --> 00:33:50,475
<i>(sniffs)</i>

501
00:33:50,560 --> 00:33:52,835
We got bunk beds.

502
00:33:52,920 --> 00:33:56,196
At night, I knew David was there,

503
00:33:56,280 --> 00:33:59,352
like he was guarding me.

504
00:33:59,440 --> 00:34:01,635
Margaret's nice.

505
00:34:02,920 --> 00:34:07,277
You'd do almost anything
to stay with Margaret, right?

506
00:34:08,280 --> 00:34:12,432
The man you took Charlie to,
the man who hurt him,

507
00:34:12,520 --> 00:34:14,511
he knows that.

508
00:34:14,600 --> 00:34:17,239
You didn't know that he'd hurt Charlie,
but he did,

509
00:34:17,320 --> 00:34:21,359
and then he told you that Margaret
would blame you, that she'd hate you.

510
00:34:21,440 --> 00:34:25,718
But this man is lying to you, Shawn.
I can make sure that you go back to Margaret.

511
00:34:25,800 --> 00:34:29,349
How? You work at a museum.

512
00:34:29,440 --> 00:34:32,318
I have a friend at the FBI.

513
00:34:32,400 --> 00:34:36,313
He will make sure that you and David
get to live with Margaret again.

514
00:34:36,400 --> 00:34:39,631
- You can't make promises like that.
- Yes, I can.

515
00:34:39,720 --> 00:34:43,315
- He will do it. My friend will make it happen.
- Oh, man.

516
00:34:43,400 --> 00:34:47,393
But you have to tell me who hurt Charlie.

517
00:34:47,480 --> 00:34:50,631
I'll need your help to keep the promises
she made to that boy.

518
00:34:50,720 --> 00:34:52,950
- Hey, l-I can't promise...
- Mrs Johnson.

519
00:34:53,040 --> 00:34:56,874
My people and your people
are gonna have to make this happen.

520
00:34:56,960 --> 00:35:00,794
What if Margaret doesn't want me any more?

521
00:35:00,880 --> 00:35:03,030
Charlie was her real son.

522
00:35:03,120 --> 00:35:05,918
Charlie wasrt her biological son either.

523
00:35:06,000 --> 00:35:11,279
Charlie was just like you,
someone that Margaret chose to love.

524
00:35:13,880 --> 00:35:18,635
I don't think we should let that man take you
and David and Charlie away from Margaret,

525
00:35:18,720 --> 00:35:21,280
do you?

526
00:35:21,360 --> 00:35:24,796
We should stop him.
You and I should stop him.

527
00:35:40,440 --> 00:35:42,192
<i>(whispers)</i>

528
00:35:44,280 --> 00:35:47,033
She did it. She got his name.

529
00:35:51,400 --> 00:35:54,073
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Some of Us" by Starsailor)</i>

530
00:36:04,040 --> 00:36:09,637
Edward Nelson, you are under arrest for the
sexual assault and murder of Charlie Sanders.

531
00:36:09,720 --> 00:36:15,113
You have the right to an attorney. If you
cannot afford one, one will be appointed.

532
00:36:15,200 --> 00:36:17,794
♪ <i>Forget what he did</i>

533
00:36:17,880 --> 00:36:22,476
♪ <i>Can I be the kid for your soul to keep</i>

534
00:36:24,960 --> 00:36:27,428
♪ <i>Some of us laugh</i>

535
00:36:27,520 --> 00:36:29,795
♪ <i>Some of us cry</i>

536
00:36:29,880 --> 00:36:32,269
♪ <i>Some of us smoke</i>

537
00:36:32,360 --> 00:36:34,112
♪ <i>Some of us lie</i>

538
00:36:34,200 --> 00:36:38,876
♪ <i>But it's all just the way</i>

539
00:36:38,960 --> 00:36:42,635
♪ <i>That we cope with our lives</i>

540
00:36:44,880 --> 00:36:46,757
♪ <i>I've grown to see</i>

541
00:36:46,840 --> 00:36:51,311
♪ <i>The philosophy of my own mistrust</i>

542
00:36:54,440 --> 00:36:56,874
♪ <i>We all have our faults</i>

543
00:36:56,960 --> 00:37:01,829
♪ <i>Mine come in waves that you turn to rust</i>

544
00:37:12,160 --> 00:37:15,948
♪ <i>My wandering soul</i>

545
00:37:16,840 --> 00:37:19,559
♪ <i>Found solace at last</i>

546
00:37:19,640 --> 00:37:21,073
- Boys!
- Mom!

547
00:37:21,160 --> 00:37:23,515
Mom!

548
00:37:23,600 --> 00:37:27,798
- Are we gonna be a family again?
- <i>(Margaret)</i> Oh, you betcha.

549
00:37:38,280 --> 00:37:39,793
<i>(Booth)</i> We have him cold.

550
00:37:39,880 --> 00:37:44,431
The insecticide he was using on the termites
matches the fluoride concentration.

551
00:37:44,520 --> 00:37:46,590
Skyler's dad admitted everything.

552
00:37:46,680 --> 00:37:49,797
He said crushing Charlie to death
was a mistake?

553
00:37:49,880 --> 00:37:54,556
He never abused Shawn. He just used him
to get near Charlie. It played out like you said.

554
00:37:54,640 --> 00:37:58,349
He had Charlie out in that field.
Some teenage kids, they come by.

555
00:37:58,440 --> 00:38:02,956
So he knelt on Charlie to keep him from
crying out. Shawn ran back to his brother.

556
00:38:03,040 --> 00:38:06,191
Charlie was small and weak,
his sternum collapsed.

557
00:38:06,280 --> 00:38:09,352
- You think he abused any other kids?
- Yeah.

558
00:38:09,440 --> 00:38:11,590
Probably his own son.

559
00:38:11,680 --> 00:38:17,869
- You report that to Child Services?
- Mm-hm. Try to get the kid some help.

560
00:38:19,200 --> 00:38:21,714
- And I'm sorry.
- For what?

561
00:38:22,160 --> 00:38:25,596
You have personal experience in the system.

562
00:38:30,640 --> 00:38:34,838
I was a foster child
until my grandfather got me out.

563
00:38:34,920 --> 00:38:37,878
When you said,
"They'd take you away from your brother,"

564
00:38:37,960 --> 00:38:42,272
I kinda had the feeling
you werert talking about David Cook.

565
00:38:42,360 --> 00:38:44,078
Booth,

566
00:38:44,160 --> 00:38:48,073
I'll tell you about it one day,
but tonight I have to get dressed for a party.

567
00:38:48,160 --> 00:38:50,390
Oh.

568
00:38:50,480 --> 00:38:51,469
OK, Bones.

569
00:38:51,560 --> 00:38:53,994
There's a huge ding
on my passenger side door

570
00:38:54,080 --> 00:38:56,992
because you told me
not to park it at an angle.

571
00:38:57,080 --> 00:38:58,513
<i>(laughs)</i>

572
00:38:58,600 --> 00:39:01,319
OK, that's just mean.

573
00:39:02,200 --> 00:39:03,599
You're mean.

574
00:39:05,160 --> 00:39:07,151
Sorry.

575
00:39:13,720 --> 00:39:17,269
- That is not a tuxedo, Dr Hodgins.
- I am not going, Dr Goodman.

576
00:39:17,360 --> 00:39:19,590
You are going.

577
00:39:19,680 --> 00:39:22,513
When we arrive,
the donors will be wearing name tags.

578
00:39:22,600 --> 00:39:26,036
- What do we talk about?
- Your work, of course.

579
00:39:26,120 --> 00:39:29,476
Zack's work consists
of removing flesh from corpses.

580
00:39:29,560 --> 00:39:32,757
Hodgins dissects bugs
that have been eating eyeballs.

581
00:39:32,840 --> 00:39:38,119
- Leave me out of it. I am not going.
- And how do you see yourjob?

582
00:39:38,200 --> 00:39:40,191
I draw death masks.

583
00:39:40,280 --> 00:39:43,989
- Is that really how you see it?
- Don't you?

584
00:39:44,080 --> 00:39:46,958
You are the best of us, Miss Montenegro.

585
00:39:47,040 --> 00:39:50,237
You discern humanity
in the wreck of a ruined human body.

586
00:39:50,320 --> 00:39:54,029
You give victims back their faces,
their identities.

587
00:39:54,120 --> 00:39:57,999
You remind us all
of why we're here in the first place.

588
00:39:58,920 --> 00:40:01,639
Because we treasure human life.

589
00:40:06,000 --> 00:40:08,275
- Oh, for God's sake.
- What happened?

590
00:40:08,360 --> 00:40:13,309
All Angela needed was to hear herjob
description in a deep African-American tone.

591
00:40:13,400 --> 00:40:16,153
- Mr Addy.
- We need Hodgins in the lab tonight.

592
00:40:16,240 --> 00:40:19,550
The FBI needs this analysed by morning.

593
00:40:20,240 --> 00:40:24,153
- Uh, I'm gonna get right on it.
- Wait a minute. What case file is this?

594
00:40:24,240 --> 00:40:28,916
- Am I supposed to know about it?
- Booth mentioned it to me earlier today.

595
00:40:29,360 --> 00:40:31,510
That's good enough for me.

596
00:40:31,600 --> 00:40:34,717
Fine. You're off the hook, Dr Hodgins.

597
00:40:35,760 --> 00:40:38,558
Let's not keep the limo waiting.

598
00:40:38,640 --> 00:40:40,631
Thanks.

599
00:40:46,000 --> 00:40:48,150
You look nice.

600
00:40:49,720 --> 00:40:52,234
Better than nice. You look...

601
00:40:54,000 --> 00:40:56,116
very...

602
00:40:57,320 --> 00:40:59,550
Thanks.

603
00:40:59,640 --> 00:41:02,712
- How did you know I'd keep your promise?
- What promise?

604
00:41:02,800 --> 00:41:05,792
To get Shawn and David
back with Margaret Sanders.

605
00:41:05,880 --> 00:41:08,269
Maybe I was lying.

606
00:41:08,360 --> 00:41:10,271
To catch the bad guy.

607
00:41:10,360 --> 00:41:12,999
I learned that trick from you.

608
00:41:13,080 --> 00:41:15,116
The end justifies the means.

609
00:41:16,160 --> 00:41:18,071
Hm.

610
00:41:18,520 --> 00:41:20,556
Booth.

611
00:41:21,200 --> 00:41:23,839
I knew you'd back me up.

612
00:41:24,280 --> 00:41:27,829
- I knew you wouldn't make me a liar.
- How'd you know?

613
00:41:28,840 --> 00:41:31,149
Because you want to go to heaven.

614
00:41:31,240 --> 00:41:34,710
- But you don't believe in heaven.
- But you do.

615
00:41:34,800 --> 00:41:37,519
♪ <i>Some of us laugh</i>

616
00:41:37,600 --> 00:41:39,795
♪ <i>Some of us cry</i>

617
00:41:39,880 --> 00:41:41,233
♪ <i>Some of us lie</i>

618
00:41:41,320 --> 00:41:45,871
♪ <i>But it's all just the way</i>

619
00:41:45,960 --> 00:41:50,317
♪ <i>That we cope with our lives</i>

620
00:42:06,200 --> 00:42:09,829
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke

621
00:42:21,440 --> 00:42:22,759
What's that mean?

622
00:42:23,800 --> 00:42:25,791
ENGLISH SDH

