1
00:00:09,240 --> 00:00:11,879
<i>(Booth)</i> Bones, where's the kid?

2
00:00:14,000 --> 00:00:17,549
- Who's that with Zack?
- Naomi from Palaeontology.

3
00:00:17,640 --> 00:00:23,954
Naomi and Zack slept together a month ago.
Since then, she hasn't returned a single call.

4
00:00:25,120 --> 00:00:28,032
- You working on anything interesting?
- Me?

5
00:00:28,120 --> 00:00:32,432
Yeah, yeah. A three-dimensional model
of an Etruscan burial crypt.

6
00:00:32,520 --> 00:00:34,795
- You?
- Yeah. Oh, God, yeah. Very exciting.

7
00:00:34,880 --> 00:00:37,678
- Some silt profiles.
- Mm, mm.

8
00:00:38,800 --> 00:00:41,075
God, Etruscan burial crypts are so boring.

9
00:00:41,160 --> 00:00:43,594
Oh, man, I know.
I mean, silt profiles?

10
00:00:43,680 --> 00:00:46,478
- You know what we need?
- A murder investigation.

11
00:00:46,560 --> 00:00:49,313
Brennan and Booth
are out front now waiting for Zack.

12
00:00:49,400 --> 00:00:51,789
There's a case? Why didn't you say so?

13
00:00:51,880 --> 00:00:53,677
Zack, you gotta go!

14
00:00:53,760 --> 00:00:56,558
Oh, she really bolted.
Doesrt look good for Zack.

15
00:00:56,640 --> 00:00:59,438
- Come on, Zack. Shake it off. Be a man.
- You OK, honey?

16
00:00:59,520 --> 00:01:01,988
She said, "Take a hint."
I asked, "What hint?"

17
00:01:02,080 --> 00:01:05,789
Naomi said if she told me,
it wouldn't be a hint, it would be a statement.

18
00:01:05,880 --> 00:01:07,836
Throw yourself into your work.

19
00:01:07,920 --> 00:01:11,151
You really do hate slime profiles.
Have a little compassion.

20
00:01:11,240 --> 00:01:14,198
I understood the words.
I do not comprehend her meaning.

21
00:01:14,280 --> 00:01:16,157
- Did you tell Naomi that?
- Yes.

22
00:01:16,240 --> 00:01:20,199
She said, "Ask your friends", if I have any.

23
00:01:22,680 --> 00:01:25,194
Hodgins is right.
Let's not keep Booth waiting.

24
00:01:25,280 --> 00:01:30,877
- Somebody is decomposing as we speak.
- Get out there and bring us home a case.

25
00:01:39,160 --> 00:01:43,472
- We've got a dead body in a prep school.
- Good morning to you, too.

26
00:01:43,560 --> 00:01:46,552
You're successful with women, right?
They like you.

27
00:01:46,640 --> 00:01:50,872
- It's prestigious, a lot of rich kids.
- I thought it was good to say good morning.

28
00:01:50,960 --> 00:01:54,396
If a woman said to you,
"Take a hint", what would it mean?

29
00:01:54,480 --> 00:01:57,472
Can we just concentrate on the job?

30
00:02:00,000 --> 00:02:04,596
Thank you. Now, I know the sheriff out there.
She's mostly OK.

31
00:02:04,680 --> 00:02:07,114
But the school's got a lot of pull in the county

32
00:02:07,200 --> 00:02:10,237
and she's probably
trying to scrape the case off on us.

33
00:02:10,320 --> 00:02:14,313
What I'm saying is it's notjust a crime scene,
it's a political situation.

34
00:02:14,400 --> 00:02:17,631
So when we get there,
you follow my lead and you pay attention.

35
00:02:17,720 --> 00:02:21,315
You'd call after every sexual encounter?
That's the good thing...

36
00:02:21,400 --> 00:02:25,473
Look, this is a work mode. This is
a work zone. You do not talk sex at work.

37
00:02:25,560 --> 00:02:27,391
First I'm too task-oriented,

38
00:02:27,480 --> 00:02:31,314
then when I say good morning,
you say I should concentrate on the job.

39
00:02:31,400 --> 00:02:34,790
Look, we got about a 45-minute drive, hm?

40
00:02:34,880 --> 00:02:38,350
What do you say
we pass it in quiet meditation?

41
00:02:52,320 --> 00:02:55,039
- <i>(Zack)</i> Can I talk now?
- <i>(Booth)</i> No.

42
00:02:55,120 --> 00:02:59,113
- <i>(Bones)</i> OK, we're here now.
- <i>(Booth)</i> My car, my rules, period.

43
00:03:01,800 --> 00:03:04,473
FBI. Seeley Booth
and a forensic anthropologist.

44
00:03:04,560 --> 00:03:07,279
Dr Temperance Brennan,
Jeffersonian Institute.

45
00:03:07,360 --> 00:03:09,157
Plus one crack assistant.

46
00:03:09,240 --> 00:03:14,394
- I'll need to see some ID, please.
- This reminds me of where I went to school.

47
00:03:14,480 --> 00:03:20,157
You don't get much farther from the real
world. Whose kids go here is classified.

48
00:03:20,240 --> 00:03:23,949
Agent Booth, Dr Brennan,
I'll lead you to Mr Sanders, head of security.

49
00:03:24,040 --> 00:03:30,229
- Aim us in the right direction. We'll find it.
- All outsiders are to be escorted, sir.

50
00:03:31,440 --> 00:03:37,037
Huh. "<i>Omnia mea mecum porto</i>." What does
that mean, huh? "Regular people stay out"?

51
00:03:37,120 --> 00:03:39,395
<i>(both)</i> "I carry with me all my things."

52
00:03:45,840 --> 00:03:47,751
I knew that.

53
00:03:52,720 --> 00:03:57,316
- Hey, Seeley. How's it going?
- Congratulations on being elected full sheriff.

54
00:03:57,400 --> 00:03:59,356
Very impressive.

55
00:03:59,440 --> 00:04:03,672
I'm Leo Sanders, head of security.
This is Headmaster Peter Ronson.

56
00:04:03,760 --> 00:04:07,799
- Where are the human remains?
- Dr Brennan and her assistant Jack, uh...

57
00:04:07,880 --> 00:04:11,236
- Zack Addy.
- Could you show me to the remains?

58
00:04:11,320 --> 00:04:15,313
<i>(Leo)</i> Even though the school was mostly
empty during the two-week break...

59
00:04:15,400 --> 00:04:18,472
I don't know if you remember me,
but we worked together.

60
00:04:18,560 --> 00:04:22,519
- Bones found in a culvert a year ago?
- I remember the bones and the culvert.

61
00:04:22,600 --> 00:04:27,310
Bones, being nice to the locals and
remembering their names, it wouldn't hurt.

62
00:04:27,400 --> 00:04:32,269
Our term break ends tomorrow. I'd like to
get this tidied up so the students never know.

63
00:04:32,360 --> 00:04:35,477
But we don't know what happened.
Did anyone touch the body?

64
00:04:35,560 --> 00:04:38,870
- I doubt it. It's grisly.
- <i>(Leo)</i> Not big on small talk, is she?

65
00:04:38,960 --> 00:04:41,554
<i>(Booth)</i> Dr Brennars very focused.

66
00:04:43,800 --> 00:04:46,837
Where are the remains?

67
00:04:46,920 --> 00:04:48,273
Bones.

68
00:04:59,440 --> 00:05:00,998
Is that a student?

69
00:05:01,080 --> 00:05:04,072
It's a secure campus.
Must be student, staff or faculty.

70
00:05:04,160 --> 00:05:06,196
Video first. Don't disturb the crows.

71
00:05:06,280 --> 00:05:08,874
That'd be a shame -
disturb the flesh-eating birds.

72
00:05:08,960 --> 00:05:13,909
Want to increase the perimeter? Gentlemen,
give my forensic anthropologist some room.

73
00:05:14,000 --> 00:05:16,116
<i>Your</i> forensic anthropologist?

74
00:05:16,200 --> 00:05:19,078
Agent Booth,
if you decide it's suicide, it's my problem.

75
00:05:19,160 --> 00:05:23,438
Actually, the person who decides
if this was a suicide is me.

76
00:05:23,520 --> 00:05:28,389
- Give the bone lady some room.
- I'm glad we had that chat about being nice.

77
00:05:28,480 --> 00:05:33,270
I don't like sheriffs. They're elected.
Their goal is being re-elected, not the truth.

78
00:05:33,360 --> 00:05:34,952
- I got video.
- Go to stills.

79
00:05:35,040 --> 00:05:39,272
- Can we just get him down from there?
- There's a lot of work to do before that.

80
00:05:39,360 --> 00:05:41,271
- Step back.
- I'm the headmaster.

81
00:05:41,360 --> 00:05:43,510
And this is a crime scene. Step back.

82
00:05:58,400 --> 00:06:01,517
- I'm gonna need an evidence bag.
- Heads up.

83
00:06:02,560 --> 00:06:06,030
<i>(Bones)</i> I'm gonna need a bigger bag.

84
00:06:42,120 --> 00:06:45,351
I make this a male.
Approximately five foot six, 130 pounds.

85
00:06:45,440 --> 00:06:51,072
From the looks of his sternum and skull,
I'd say mid-adolescence, say 14 to 17.

86
00:06:51,160 --> 00:06:54,755
- High cheekbones. You think Asian?
- I'm getting a Hispanic vibe.

87
00:06:54,840 --> 00:06:59,152
There is a significant <i>Crematogaster</i>
ant colony in the tree that fed on the body,

88
00:06:59,240 --> 00:07:03,597
as well as tabanid maggots. I'll give you
a time of death when I find out who ate what.

89
00:07:03,680 --> 00:07:07,719
Check for insect pupa and larva. See
what drugs might have been in his system.

90
00:07:07,800 --> 00:07:09,836
He was wearing this.

91
00:07:09,920 --> 00:07:11,717
<i>(Angela)</i> Catholic boy.

92
00:07:13,160 --> 00:07:15,720
One-by-two forceps.

93
00:07:20,960 --> 00:07:23,758
- What is that?
- Cochlear implant.

94
00:07:23,840 --> 00:07:25,512
The birds were trying to get it.

95
00:07:25,600 --> 00:07:28,319
That would set a boy apart from others,
being deaf.

96
00:07:28,400 --> 00:07:30,118
Get a serial number.

97
00:07:30,200 --> 00:07:33,556
I'll get X-rays and 3-D imaging
of the entire skeleton.

98
00:07:33,640 --> 00:07:36,154
I didn't talk at school. I didn't kill myself.

99
00:07:36,240 --> 00:07:40,950
That wasrt a high school.
It was an experimental eugenics programme.

100
00:07:47,280 --> 00:07:50,272
<i>(Booth) How hard is it</i>
<i>to find which student is missing?</i>

101
00:07:50,360 --> 00:07:54,114
We can't call parents and say,
"We found a body. Where is your child?"

102
00:07:54,200 --> 00:07:57,670
- We can do a roll call.
- Our high-risk students are accounted for.

103
00:07:57,760 --> 00:07:59,990
- High risk?
- The ones with bodyguards.

104
00:08:00,080 --> 00:08:04,392
- What are our options vis-à-vis publicity?
- Not my concern.

105
00:08:04,480 --> 00:08:07,756
There are students we don't want
the whole world to know about.

106
00:08:07,840 --> 00:08:12,356
It's a suicide. We're not asking you
to forego the glory of catching a murderer.

107
00:08:12,440 --> 00:08:14,635
<i>(phone rings)</i>

108
00:08:14,720 --> 00:08:16,711
Excuse me. Sorry.

109
00:08:16,800 --> 00:08:18,916
Booth.

110
00:08:19,000 --> 00:08:21,560
We'll have the identity within the hour.

111
00:08:21,640 --> 00:08:24,154
- That's fast.
- <i>Know what a cochlear implant is?</i>

112
00:08:24,240 --> 00:08:26,356
- Hearing aid?
- Not exactly.

113
00:08:26,440 --> 00:08:29,193
It's a more sophisticated piece of equipment...

114
00:08:29,280 --> 00:08:32,556
- Can you get the serial number?
- Yes. What's interesting...

115
00:08:32,640 --> 00:08:34,517
Oh, you can fill me in later.

116
00:08:34,600 --> 00:08:37,797
- But the interesting thing is that his...
- <i>That's correct.</i>

117
00:08:37,880 --> 00:08:41,236
- What?
- That is interesting.

118
00:08:41,320 --> 00:08:44,756
- Are you drunk or something?
- We'll catch up later and...

119
00:08:44,840 --> 00:08:47,035
I'm not certain his death is a suicide.

120
00:08:47,120 --> 00:08:51,910
You know, we'll grab some Chinese food and
you can fill me in later on the boring details.

121
00:08:52,000 --> 00:08:53,831
Sorry.

122
00:08:53,920 --> 00:08:56,753
Death is upsetting
to a community as tight as ours.

123
00:08:56,840 --> 00:09:00,196
Well, you're famous
for keeping your students safe.

124
00:09:00,280 --> 00:09:03,272
You can't be held responsible
if a student kills himself.

125
00:09:03,360 --> 00:09:06,432
We all agree that suicide
is the only feasible conclusion.

126
00:09:06,520 --> 00:09:10,718
- We understand each other.
- Hm. Sure as hell do.

127
00:09:13,160 --> 00:09:18,029
I'll need a complete enrolment list
including teachers, staff, students.

128
00:09:18,120 --> 00:09:19,997
That's extremely confidential.

129
00:09:20,080 --> 00:09:24,278
Well, you know,
luckily I'm good at keeping secrets.

130
00:09:33,960 --> 00:09:36,633
What? It's not suicide? What the hell is that?

131
00:09:36,720 --> 00:09:40,235
<i>(Bones)</i> We can't have just anyone
contaminate the boring details.

132
00:09:40,320 --> 00:09:45,519
The boring details... Do not push me. "Boring
details" was my signal for you to stop talking.

133
00:09:45,600 --> 00:09:47,556
- I want a card.
- I want a gun.

134
00:09:47,640 --> 00:09:49,551
- You shot someone.
- He was a bad guy.

135
00:09:49,640 --> 00:09:52,074
- Who's our victim?
- All the boring details?

136
00:09:52,160 --> 00:09:56,039
- Let it go, Bones. Move on.
- Don't call me Bones.

137
00:09:56,120 --> 00:09:59,510
We traced the implant
to Dr Maurice Ledbetter at Cedars-Sinai,

138
00:09:59,600 --> 00:10:02,956
who placed it in a boy named Nestor Olivos.

139
00:10:03,040 --> 00:10:08,034
Nestor Olivos, student visa,
son of a Venezuelan ambassador. What else?

140
00:10:08,120 --> 00:10:11,112
- You want all the boring details?
- Let it go, Bones.

141
00:10:11,200 --> 00:10:13,270
Don't call me Bones!

142
00:10:14,200 --> 00:10:18,239
- The boy's hyoid bone is broken.
- Strangulation, it's always broken.

143
00:10:18,320 --> 00:10:23,713
- In adults. This was a boy.
- His hyoid is flexible, unbreakable.

144
00:10:23,800 --> 00:10:28,715
Well, maybe the kid's got some kind of
Venezuelan brittle-bone syndrome.

145
00:10:29,440 --> 00:10:31,908
I'm just trying to help. So he was murdered?

146
00:10:32,000 --> 00:10:35,356
I don't know what happened to the boy.
I don't have all the facts.

147
00:10:35,800 --> 00:10:38,951
<i>(two phones ring)</i>

148
00:10:44,560 --> 00:10:47,677
How hard can it be?
A kid hanging from a tree. It's a suicide.

149
00:10:47,760 --> 00:10:49,910
Is Hanover Prep stirring the pudding?

150
00:10:50,000 --> 00:10:53,356
Of course. Every mover and shaker's
connected to that school.

151
00:10:53,440 --> 00:10:57,672
- "The future of the country's at stake."
- I want to declare it a murder to shake...

152
00:10:57,760 --> 00:11:02,470
I'm not gonna declare it a murder
just so you can "shake things up".

153
00:11:03,280 --> 00:11:08,832
- The evidence is ambiguous at best.
- Well, unambiguise it, please, Dr Goodman.

154
00:11:08,920 --> 00:11:13,869
Look, you're experienced within your field of
bones, right? Doesrt your gut say suicide?

155
00:11:13,960 --> 00:11:16,713
- I don't use my gut for that, sir.
- She doesn't.

156
00:11:16,800 --> 00:11:21,874
Like all of us at the Jeffersonian, Dr Brennan
prefers science to the digestive tract.

157
00:11:21,960 --> 00:11:24,269
- What about your gut?
- My gut says it stinks.

158
00:11:24,360 --> 00:11:28,239
- Smells with his gut, what's his nose for?
- <i>(Santana)</i> All right, all right.

159
00:11:28,320 --> 00:11:32,916
In order for an investigation to occur,
you, Dr Brennan, have to declare it a murder.

160
00:11:33,000 --> 00:11:35,309
Without an investigation, we can't,

161
00:11:35,400 --> 00:11:39,109
but there's no investigation
unless Dr Brennan declares it a murder.

162
00:11:39,200 --> 00:11:42,033
Shall I send for a philosopher?

163
00:11:42,120 --> 00:11:44,076
They're saying it's my call.

164
00:11:44,160 --> 00:11:48,039
<i>(Santana)</i> You see?
It's how you talk to these people.

165
00:11:50,640 --> 00:11:54,235
My official finding is that Nestor Olivos...

166
00:11:59,320 --> 00:12:02,198
is a victim of a homicide.

167
00:12:16,720 --> 00:12:18,631
- Thank you.
- For what?

168
00:12:18,720 --> 00:12:21,518
- For going with my instincts in there.
- I did not.

169
00:12:21,600 --> 00:12:26,993
I bought time to find the facts I need
to tell me what happened to Nestor Olivos.

170
00:12:27,080 --> 00:12:30,834
- What's with you and the school?
- They thought we understood each other.

171
00:12:30,920 --> 00:12:34,151
I don't like people
who think they're better than others.

172
00:12:34,240 --> 00:12:38,597
- Some people are better than others.
- What you just said there is so un-American.

173
00:12:38,680 --> 00:12:41,717
All men are equal.
Either you believe that or you don't.

174
00:12:41,800 --> 00:12:48,433
Some people are smarter than others.
There's no use being offended by the fact.

175
00:12:48,520 --> 00:12:52,752
- What are we gonna tell Nestor's parents?
- We tell them their son was found dead.

176
00:12:52,840 --> 00:12:56,276
"We're looking into it. Sorry for your loss."

177
00:12:56,360 --> 00:12:59,477
- And we are.
- What?

178
00:12:59,560 --> 00:13:02,074
Sorry for their loss. It's sad.

179
00:13:02,160 --> 00:13:04,594
- Try to remember that.
- I'm not a sociopath.

180
00:13:04,680 --> 00:13:09,754
You're bad with people, OK?
No use being offended by the fact.

181
00:13:13,600 --> 00:13:18,435
- Hanging from a tree at the school?
- <i>(Booth)</i> I'm afraid so, Ambassador Olivos.

182
00:13:18,520 --> 00:13:23,355
We will provide you with full details
when Dr Brennan finishes her investigation.

183
00:13:23,440 --> 00:13:29,117
- Will you need us to identify his remains?
- That won't be necessary.

184
00:13:36,000 --> 00:13:38,070
When did you last hear from Nestor?

185
00:13:38,160 --> 00:13:41,994
A few days after his holiday began.
He went with a friend to Nova Scotia.

186
00:13:42,080 --> 00:13:44,833
- We received an email.
- Can we have a copy?

187
00:13:44,920 --> 00:13:49,038
It'll help us determine
exactly when the victim died.

188
00:13:49,120 --> 00:13:52,795
Your son. We're very sorry for your loss.

189
00:13:52,880 --> 00:13:57,237
There was nothing to suggest in the email
that Nestor was unappy, not enough to...

190
00:13:57,320 --> 00:13:59,470
We would like to take him home.

191
00:14:01,000 --> 00:14:04,629
We must petition the church
to bury him in consecrated ground.

192
00:14:04,720 --> 00:14:09,157
Nestor was an altar boy.
They will bury him properly.

193
00:14:10,080 --> 00:14:11,991
When will you release him to us?

194
00:14:12,080 --> 00:14:15,277
That's up to Dr Brennan.

195
00:14:21,320 --> 00:14:24,676
- What did Naomi mean by, "Take a hint"?
- Ooh.

196
00:14:25,600 --> 00:14:28,478
- What did I do wrong?
- It's not what you did wrong.

197
00:14:28,560 --> 00:14:30,869
It's what you didn't do.

198
00:14:30,960 --> 00:14:34,111
- Where do you learn this?
- Some things you learn by doing.

199
00:14:34,200 --> 00:14:37,988
Riding a bike, driving a car,
pleasing a woman.

200
00:14:38,080 --> 00:14:42,676
- I can't ride a bike or drive a car.
- Or, apparently, please a woman.

201
00:14:42,760 --> 00:14:47,117
I need specific instructions -
a list of techniques or a sequence of moves.

202
00:14:47,200 --> 00:14:50,192
- I'm not the guy to ask.
- You've slept with 10,000 women.

203
00:14:50,280 --> 00:14:52,475
Our relationship is about what's up here.

204
00:14:52,560 --> 00:14:57,350
What you need to do
is talk to someone more... earthy.

205
00:15:05,320 --> 00:15:08,153
As a psychiatrist,
I'm bound by patient confidentiality.

206
00:15:08,240 --> 00:15:14,110
In the absence of a warrant, I can't divulge the
specifics of my meetings with Nestor Olivos.

207
00:15:14,200 --> 00:15:16,998
I can tell you that
he was at extreme risk of suicide.

208
00:15:17,080 --> 00:15:19,878
There are no indications
he was on antidepressants.

209
00:15:19,960 --> 00:15:24,511
- I can only make recommendations.
- Was he depressed enough to hang himself?

210
00:15:24,600 --> 00:15:29,833
He was alienated by culture, language, his
handicap, his own social awkwardness, yes.

211
00:15:29,920 --> 00:15:35,074
Thank you for coming down, Dr Petty.
As we suspected, suicide.

212
00:15:35,160 --> 00:15:38,630
A depressed and Ionely boy
hangs himself over the holiday.

213
00:15:38,720 --> 00:15:43,111
So how does the son of an ambassador go
missing for two weeks and nobody notices?

214
00:15:43,200 --> 00:15:46,749
The school thought
Nestor was vacationing with his roommate.

215
00:15:46,840 --> 00:15:52,278
The school requested and received
a waiver from Ambassador Olivos.

216
00:15:52,360 --> 00:15:55,591
I was in Venezuela last year.
It's unstable politically.

217
00:15:55,680 --> 00:15:58,990
The family received threats -
we were cognisant of that -

218
00:15:59,080 --> 00:16:02,755
but you aren't suggesting
that some kind of Venezuelan hit squad

219
00:16:02,840 --> 00:16:05,149
assassinated a student at Hanover Prep?

220
00:16:05,240 --> 00:16:09,552
Like the doctor said, it's a simple case
of a depressed boy ending his life,

221
00:16:09,640 --> 00:16:11,995
not a Tom Clancy novel.

222
00:16:12,080 --> 00:16:16,756
Yeah. We'll start with Nestor's roommate
tomorrow morning.

223
00:16:18,480 --> 00:16:21,119
It's your investigation.

224
00:16:26,360 --> 00:16:29,352
♪ <i>Everybody's looking for something</i>

225
00:16:30,480 --> 00:16:32,118
Hey.

226
00:16:32,200 --> 00:16:36,352
- I'll say this. She's tall.
- Temperance Brennan, meet Sid, the owner.

227
00:16:36,440 --> 00:16:40,069
- Hey. Bone lady.
- The sign says "Wong Foo's".

228
00:16:40,160 --> 00:16:42,913
Family name changed at Ellis Island.

229
00:16:43,000 --> 00:16:45,468
- I'll get your meal.
- But we didn't order.

230
00:16:45,560 --> 00:16:49,030
Sid knows what people want
better than they do.

231
00:16:49,120 --> 00:16:52,078
Nestor's bones are normal.
Not brittle in any way.

232
00:16:52,160 --> 00:16:54,276
This is my getaway place, you know?

233
00:16:54,360 --> 00:16:57,670
The grooves left in the branch
are too deep for Nestor's weight.

234
00:16:57,760 --> 00:16:59,591
Please, everyone, just sit down.

235
00:16:59,680 --> 00:17:04,629
Eggs and larva show that the insects which
fed on the body are indigenous to the tree,

236
00:17:04,720 --> 00:17:07,792
which means he died there
approximately ten to 14 days ago.

237
00:17:07,880 --> 00:17:10,792
- I'll have the seven-organ soup.
- You don't order.

238
00:17:10,880 --> 00:17:14,919
He didn't void. Somebody hangs themselves,
bodily fluids everywhere.

239
00:17:15,000 --> 00:17:18,629
There was plenty of effluent in his clothes,
but postdecomposition.

240
00:17:18,720 --> 00:17:21,951
As the body swells, it bursts.
How does he know what you want?

241
00:17:22,040 --> 00:17:23,917
- He has a knack.
- His name is Sid.

242
00:17:24,000 --> 00:17:26,992
Birds ate his eyes, ears,
worked their way into the skull.

243
00:17:27,080 --> 00:17:29,878
Birds pecking - could that crack the hyoid?

244
00:17:29,960 --> 00:17:33,669
No. It's caused by the rope against his throat,
not postmortem.

245
00:17:33,760 --> 00:17:36,320
You put a sensitive adolescent
in a prep school,

246
00:17:36,400 --> 00:17:40,871
add alienation, cultural differences,
pressure from high-achieving parents.

247
00:17:40,960 --> 00:17:43,315
- It could be suicide.
- It's not a suicide.

248
00:17:43,400 --> 00:17:46,312
Because Booth thinks
prep schools turn out criminals.

249
00:17:46,400 --> 00:17:48,550
We all went to private school.

250
00:17:48,640 --> 00:17:52,349
- We fight criminals. We're crime-fighters.
- No. Not... You're...

251
00:17:52,440 --> 00:17:56,194
- I'm just saying it's not a suicide.
- I'm a big believer in instinct.

252
00:17:56,280 --> 00:17:59,352
Finally a squint with an open mind.

253
00:17:59,440 --> 00:18:03,149
You have no idea how open-minded I can be.

254
00:18:03,680 --> 00:18:07,992
<i>(Sid)</i> What's with these pictures?
This is a restaurant. People come here to eat.

255
00:18:08,080 --> 00:18:11,709
What's the matter with you?
What the hell did you bring in my place?

256
00:18:11,800 --> 00:18:14,951
- I had nothing to do with it.
- This is exactly what I want.

257
00:18:15,040 --> 00:18:19,431
- It's amazing. The guy definitely has a knack.
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> Ooh!

258
00:18:19,520 --> 00:18:21,511
- You do take orders.
- Of course we do.

259
00:18:21,600 --> 00:18:24,592
But it's always better
when you leave it to me. Booth.

260
00:18:24,680 --> 00:18:28,150
All right, I'll take care of it.
The boy died ten to 14 days ago?

261
00:18:28,240 --> 00:18:30,117
Bugs buzz, but they do not lie.

262
00:18:30,200 --> 00:18:33,875
Hodgins is very good at using insects
to ascertain the time of death.

263
00:18:33,960 --> 00:18:38,511
How do you explain an email that was
sent seven days ago from Nova Scotia?

264
00:18:38,600 --> 00:18:41,114
See? Look at that. It stinks.

265
00:18:41,200 --> 00:18:44,510
Go ahead, smell it.
You know you want to smell it. It stinks.

266
00:18:44,600 --> 00:18:47,194
- Don't smell that.
- No, no, you gotta taste it.

267
00:18:47,280 --> 00:18:51,319
- Angela, it's so good. Mm.
- That's really gross.

268
00:18:51,880 --> 00:18:55,873
- <i>(Booth) You and Nestor were roommates?</i>
- <i>Yes, sir.</i>

269
00:18:55,960 --> 00:19:00,556
- <i>You invited him over for the vacation?</i>
- <i>We have a summer home on Cape Breton.</i>

270
00:19:00,640 --> 00:19:02,835
<i>Nestor decided to go back to Venezuela.</i>

271
00:19:02,920 --> 00:19:06,356
- What did the other kids say about Nestor?
- Nestor was different.

272
00:19:06,440 --> 00:19:10,228
He used to be deaf so he talked like...
Some kids called him "retard".

273
00:19:10,320 --> 00:19:13,949
- Tucker, don't say retard.
- I never called him that.

274
00:19:14,040 --> 00:19:18,272
He went to church even though nobody
made him go. People thought that was weird.

275
00:19:18,360 --> 00:19:23,070
- Did Nestor have a girlfriend?
- There was a girl he liked. He never said who.

276
00:19:23,160 --> 00:19:27,517
- Tucker, you're lying to a federal agent.
- Careful, Agent Booth.

277
00:19:27,600 --> 00:19:31,832
An email was sent to Nestor's parents
saying what a great time he was having.

278
00:19:31,920 --> 00:19:35,799
The only thing is
that Nestor was already dead.

279
00:19:35,880 --> 00:19:38,030
- Was it you?
- I'd prefer he didn't answer.

280
00:19:38,120 --> 00:19:41,669
No, Dawn. If it was Tucker, he has to admit it.

281
00:19:42,720 --> 00:19:46,156
- You know the dodge.
- You backed him up cos he was with a girl.

282
00:19:46,240 --> 00:19:49,198
- Tucker!
- I know. I'm sorry, but he begged me.

283
00:19:49,280 --> 00:19:52,511
- What girl?
- I don't know. I thought Nestor made her up.

284
00:19:52,600 --> 00:19:55,273
I sent an email. That's all.

285
00:20:01,440 --> 00:20:03,635
Dr Brennan,

286
00:20:03,720 --> 00:20:06,871
can you spare a moment
for the Venezuelan ambassador?

287
00:20:06,960 --> 00:20:08,951
Thank you.

288
00:20:10,000 --> 00:20:12,355
Is there something I can do for you?

289
00:20:12,440 --> 00:20:16,911
I understand that you are very good
at yourjob, Dr Brennan.

290
00:20:17,000 --> 00:20:21,312
- But I think you are not a mother, correct?
- No. I'm not a mother.

291
00:20:22,960 --> 00:20:25,349
Please watch this.

292
00:20:29,880 --> 00:20:34,829
All a mother wants to know
is that she has raised her child well,

293
00:20:34,920 --> 00:20:37,559
that he will grow up to be a good man.

294
00:20:38,520 --> 00:20:40,511
I will never see this.

295
00:20:40,600 --> 00:20:43,433
I will never know.

296
00:20:46,000 --> 00:20:48,594
The day Nestor received his implant...

297
00:20:48,680 --> 00:20:50,318
<i>Nestor.</i>

298
00:20:51,320 --> 00:20:52,958
<i>Te amo, mi amor.</i>

299
00:20:53,040 --> 00:20:56,635
- The first day he could hear.
- The first thing he heard was my voice.

300
00:20:56,720 --> 00:21:00,633
<i>Te amo, mi amor. Yo... Sí...</i>

301
00:21:00,720 --> 00:21:04,110
His mother's voice. I told him I loved him.

302
00:21:04,840 --> 00:21:10,039
<i>Yo te amo. ¿Me entiendes?</i>
<i>Dile a papi que nos quiere. Dile que...</i>

303
00:21:10,120 --> 00:21:15,990
The child who has lived through this miracle
would never take his own life.

304
00:21:17,000 --> 00:21:18,831
You're a scientist.

305
00:21:18,920 --> 00:21:22,959
You need more than
a mother's reassurance, fine.

306
00:21:23,040 --> 00:21:27,955
My husband and I have many enemies.
That is why I sent Nestor to Hanover.

307
00:21:28,040 --> 00:21:30,713
They promised us that he would be safe.

308
00:21:30,800 --> 00:21:33,837
What if they failed?
They would not want to admit it.

309
00:21:33,920 --> 00:21:37,959
They would do everything they could
to bias you toward suicide.

310
00:21:38,040 --> 00:21:41,635
I promise you I will find out the truth.

311
00:21:44,040 --> 00:21:46,031
Thank you.

312
00:21:56,400 --> 00:21:59,312
Swan dive, cannonball, cherry bomb -

313
00:21:59,400 --> 00:22:02,676
no matter how he jumps,
the hyoid does not break.

314
00:22:02,760 --> 00:22:04,910
What about added weight?

315
00:22:05,000 --> 00:22:08,595
We figure an added strain of 90 kilos
to snap the hyoid.

316
00:22:08,680 --> 00:22:12,070
90 kilos is just under 200 pounds.
The weight of a muscular man.

317
00:22:12,160 --> 00:22:15,277
The Venezuelan hit-squad thing?
For one thing, it's nuts.

318
00:22:15,360 --> 00:22:18,875
And another,
the guy would have to be about 20 feet tall.

319
00:22:18,960 --> 00:22:24,159
I'm out of alternative scenarios
to explain this hyoid break.

320
00:22:32,760 --> 00:22:37,197
- <i>(Booth)</i> I want to take a look at his room.
- What exactly do you hope to find?

321
00:22:40,480 --> 00:22:43,597
- Stay here.
- Yeah, right. That's gonna happen.

322
00:22:58,880 --> 00:23:01,474
- You all right?
- Are you?

323
00:23:03,560 --> 00:23:05,755
Check his ID.

324
00:23:07,640 --> 00:23:13,237
His name's Tovar Comara.
He's security at the Venezuelan embassy.

325
00:23:13,320 --> 00:23:16,278
If he's security, why'd he run?

326
00:23:22,640 --> 00:23:25,950
We would like know what Señor Comara
was doing in Nestor's room.

327
00:23:26,040 --> 00:23:30,033
I asked Señor Comara
to go to Nestor's room to prove a point.

328
00:23:30,120 --> 00:23:34,477
- That suicide was not the only possibility.
- Proof that an outsider can get in.

329
00:23:34,560 --> 00:23:39,315
The school informed me that his death was
a suicide, that anything else was impossible.

330
00:23:39,400 --> 00:23:44,190
We proved them correct.
I failed to escape without being detected.

331
00:23:44,280 --> 00:23:45,713
The school lied.

332
00:23:45,800 --> 00:23:50,078
Dr Brennan already declared
your sors death a homicide.

333
00:23:50,160 --> 00:23:53,709
- I apologise. I was misinformed.
- I won't be pressing any charges.

334
00:23:53,800 --> 00:23:55,597
<i>(ambassador)</i> Thank you.

335
00:23:56,760 --> 00:23:59,433
Please excuse me.

336
00:24:03,880 --> 00:24:06,599
<i>Tenemos otra diligencia en media hora.</i>

337
00:24:06,680 --> 00:24:10,958
- Do you think he was killed by outsiders?
- Not Venezuelan insurgents.

338
00:24:11,040 --> 00:24:16,114
They would make a statement,
not fake a suicide. This hanging...

339
00:24:17,360 --> 00:24:19,874
- <i>Huele mala.</i>
- Hm.

340
00:24:24,800 --> 00:24:28,475
Sure, you know, someone says
"it smells" in a Spanish accent

341
00:24:28,560 --> 00:24:32,633
and all of a sudden you're like,
"Hm. Interesting."

342
00:24:32,720 --> 00:24:37,032
- <i>(Bones)</i> What are we looking for?
- I talked to Nestor's teachers, a few students.

343
00:24:37,120 --> 00:24:38,997
He was a Ioner.

344
00:24:39,080 --> 00:24:44,518
Well, I mean, he went to his classes, but, you
know, mainly he just stayed here in his room.

345
00:24:44,600 --> 00:24:50,630
That's it. So I figured we'd come here
and you'd do your little anthropologist thing.

346
00:24:50,720 --> 00:24:52,711
OK.

347
00:24:56,200 --> 00:25:00,591
He liked music. Heavy percussion,
low frequencies for the most part.

348
00:25:00,680 --> 00:25:03,353
The stuff he probably liked
before the implant.

349
00:25:03,440 --> 00:25:05,829
He could feel the vibrations in his chest.

350
00:25:05,920 --> 00:25:09,833
After the implant,
he started enjoying stuff with more melody.

351
00:25:09,920 --> 00:25:13,435
He was growing. He enjoyed it.

352
00:25:13,520 --> 00:25:17,957
- Enjoyment is the opposite of suicide.
- You've decided this isn't a suicide.

353
00:25:18,040 --> 00:25:21,999
You're collecting evidence to support that
and missing indicators.

354
00:25:22,080 --> 00:25:28,076
So why'd he throw this away? It's flute music.
That's reason enough, but where's the case?

355
00:25:35,680 --> 00:25:38,638
- These aren't organised.
- Well, girls organise.

356
00:25:38,720 --> 00:25:44,352
Guys are more organic, you know?
Good stuff up to the left, crap... <i>(whistles)</i>

357
00:25:44,440 --> 00:25:46,431
Bottom right.

358
00:25:47,880 --> 00:25:50,110
Look at that.

359
00:25:52,400 --> 00:25:56,234
I mean, if he hated it, why'd he reburn it?

360
00:25:57,840 --> 00:25:59,751
This isn't a CD.

361
00:25:59,840 --> 00:26:01,831
It's a DVD.

362
00:26:02,960 --> 00:26:05,793
I should've known.
It's a 15-year-old boy. It's porn.

363
00:26:05,880 --> 00:26:07,996
Wait.

364
00:26:13,120 --> 00:26:16,112
- That's our hanging victim.
- This is pretty kinky stuff.

365
00:26:16,200 --> 00:26:20,113
I need to know where and when it was shot,
anything else that might help.

366
00:26:20,200 --> 00:26:23,476
- I need stills and a close-up of the girl's face.
- <i>(burps)</i>

367
00:26:23,560 --> 00:26:26,677
Thanks, Booth.
My seven-organ soup is repeating on me.

368
00:26:26,760 --> 00:26:29,399
Well, you ordered.
You should've left it to Sid.

369
00:26:29,480 --> 00:26:32,313
Let's see what the school
has to say about this.

370
00:26:32,400 --> 00:26:37,793
That was not wild and kinky sex.
It was very, very basic beginner stuff.

371
00:26:37,880 --> 00:26:40,838
Just so you know.

372
00:26:40,920 --> 00:26:44,435
Angela, you got any bicarbonate? <i>(groans)</i>

373
00:26:48,160 --> 00:26:51,835
- <i>(Leo)</i> We've seen this kind of thing.
- Kids recording themselves?

374
00:26:51,920 --> 00:26:55,674
Young people are more jaded
than they used to be. They swap these tapes.

375
00:26:55,760 --> 00:26:58,718
- Surprised to see Nestor.
- But not to see the girl?

376
00:26:58,800 --> 00:27:01,792
- How is that relevant?
- You know a better question?

377
00:27:01,880 --> 00:27:06,635
Why do you think you get to decide what's
relevant? You're a principal of a high school.

378
00:27:06,720 --> 00:27:10,554
- We need all the sex tapes you confiscated.
- Absolutely not.

379
00:27:10,640 --> 00:27:13,950
I'll just get a warrant,
and in the application for a warrant,

380
00:27:14,040 --> 00:27:17,669
I'll include your admission
that you let students swap sex tapes.

381
00:27:17,760 --> 00:27:20,274
He's not refusing
to provide you with the tapes.

382
00:27:20,360 --> 00:27:22,749
"Absolutely not" sounds like a refusal.

383
00:27:22,840 --> 00:27:26,879
When we confiscate the tapes,
we turn them over to local law enforcement.

384
00:27:26,960 --> 00:27:30,953
- Sheriff Roach knew about this?
- No need for a warrant. We're cooperating.

385
00:27:31,040 --> 00:27:35,830
- Was the girl also a student here?
- It's time we bring in a lawyer to advise us.

386
00:27:35,920 --> 00:27:38,912
Or you take my advice.
If you don't answer my questions,

387
00:27:39,000 --> 00:27:42,993
I'll take you down
to FBI headquarters in handcuffs.

388
00:27:43,080 --> 00:27:45,753
He'll do it. He doesn't like you.

389
00:27:49,520 --> 00:27:51,511
<i>(Ronson)</i> Her name is Camden Destry.

390
00:27:51,600 --> 00:27:54,478
<i>Nestor Olivos? I knew him.</i>

391
00:27:54,560 --> 00:27:56,596
<i>He's kinda famous since he died.</i>

392
00:27:56,680 --> 00:27:59,478
<i>Poor kid. To take his own life.</i>

393
00:28:00,480 --> 00:28:03,438
- <i>Were you romantically involved?</i>
- <i>No.</i>

394
00:28:03,520 --> 00:28:05,988
Camden is too young to date seriously.

395
00:28:09,880 --> 00:28:14,749
Tell me when you've seen enough
to start telling the truth.

396
00:28:15,760 --> 00:28:21,312
- <i>(man)</i> This is outrageous, Agent Booth.
- Oh, my God. I can't believe this.

397
00:28:23,320 --> 00:28:26,790
- Oh, my God! Where did that come from?
- Mr Booth, I must protest.

398
00:28:26,880 --> 00:28:31,749
I'm tired of being lied to
so excuse me if I'm indelicate.

399
00:28:32,440 --> 00:28:34,670
Let's start over, shall we?

400
00:28:34,760 --> 00:28:37,877
Did you know Nestor Olivos?

401
00:28:37,960 --> 00:28:40,394
Were you romantically involved?

402
00:28:40,480 --> 00:28:43,677
Why would he do that?
Why would Nestor tape us?

403
00:28:43,760 --> 00:28:45,830
I loved him.

404
00:28:48,440 --> 00:28:50,192
<i>(sobs)</i>

405
00:28:55,120 --> 00:28:58,078
So let me get this right.
<i>I'm</i> tactless and insensitive?

406
00:28:58,160 --> 00:29:02,233
She lied to a federal agent in the investigation
of the death of a boy she loves.

407
00:29:02,320 --> 00:29:04,356
You know what? These kids all lie.

408
00:29:04,440 --> 00:29:08,319
That school teaches them
that they're above the rest of us. They're not.

409
00:29:08,400 --> 00:29:11,392
- You're the least objective person I've met.
- Thanks.

410
00:29:11,480 --> 00:29:14,153
- It's not a compliment.
- Something's wrong.

411
00:29:14,240 --> 00:29:16,276
The school, the tapes, Sheriff Roach.

412
00:29:16,360 --> 00:29:21,036
This mess you're uncovering, it smells,
but it doesn't add up to murder, not logically.

413
00:29:21,120 --> 00:29:26,069
- Maybe If you looked for more than facts...
- If you opened your mind, we'd find the truth.

414
00:29:26,160 --> 00:29:29,357
- Brought you the tapes.
- How many?

415
00:29:29,440 --> 00:29:32,193
All of them.
Do you think I'm withholding evidence?

416
00:29:32,280 --> 00:29:36,273
Hanover Prep gets you elected, you look
the other way when you see these tapes.

417
00:29:36,360 --> 00:29:38,635
Kids having sex? There's no law against it.

418
00:29:38,720 --> 00:29:42,076
Let's hope that's the worst thing that we find.

419
00:29:49,080 --> 00:29:53,073
You're right
about the school serving pudding.

420
00:29:53,160 --> 00:29:56,152
"Stirring the pudding." It means...

421
00:29:56,240 --> 00:30:00,392
Melodee Destry.
That's... that's Camders mother.

422
00:30:00,480 --> 00:30:03,199
Is that... is that Nestor Olivos she's with?

423
00:30:03,880 --> 00:30:05,916
No.

424
00:30:06,000 --> 00:30:09,549
That's Nestor's roommate, Tucker Pattison.

425
00:30:17,600 --> 00:30:20,512
- How long was the relationship?
- Couple of months.

426
00:30:20,600 --> 00:30:23,797
- Tucker is the victim of statutory rape.
- When did it end?

427
00:30:23,880 --> 00:30:26,678
- That was the last time.
- Why Nestor's bed?

428
00:30:26,760 --> 00:30:29,672
- I don't know.
- Because you knew where the camera was.

429
00:30:29,760 --> 00:30:32,638
Mrs Destry gave me money, you know?
To keep quiet.

430
00:30:32,720 --> 00:30:36,235
Nestor said, "How much would she pay
to stop her husband seeing a tape?"

431
00:30:36,320 --> 00:30:38,834
Nestor set up a drop and got $5,000.

432
00:30:38,920 --> 00:30:42,754
He said we should do it again,
but I told him I was gonna tell my parents.

433
00:30:42,840 --> 00:30:49,313
Even if it meant getting kicked out of
Hanover. Next thing I know, he killed himself.

434
00:30:50,000 --> 00:30:52,594
I figured it was my fault.

435
00:30:56,240 --> 00:31:00,950
<i>(Hodgins)</i> Tabanid pupal casings show
the boy ingested a heavy dose of ketamine.

436
00:31:01,040 --> 00:31:03,759
Somebody dosed him?
That's why he didn't struggle.

437
00:31:03,840 --> 00:31:07,469
Or - a wild thought -
he took it himself for fun like most kids do.

438
00:31:07,560 --> 00:31:09,676
I had sex with Naomi in Palaeontology.

439
00:31:09,760 --> 00:31:12,513
- Actually in Palaeontology?
- No, at her place.

440
00:31:12,600 --> 00:31:17,151
I thought it went great, but I could be wrong.
Apparently what I think is kinky is basic.

441
00:31:17,240 --> 00:31:21,552
Since she never called me, I wonder
if it's because I lack imagination in the sack.

442
00:31:21,640 --> 00:31:25,110
You know what? I think
this is more of a guy-guy conversation.

443
00:31:25,200 --> 00:31:27,509
Yeah. I was wondering.

444
00:31:27,600 --> 00:31:29,272
<i>(Hodgins burps and groans)</i>

445
00:31:29,360 --> 00:31:31,510
Dude, minty burp is still burp.

446
00:31:31,600 --> 00:31:33,909
Well, who took me to Wong Salmonella's?

447
00:31:34,000 --> 00:31:36,798
You know what? Just go back to Sid.

448
00:31:36,880 --> 00:31:40,031
Let him bring you your meal.
The heartburn will disappear.

449
00:31:40,120 --> 00:31:42,350
- Heartburn.
- What?

450
00:31:42,440 --> 00:31:45,989
Hodgins has heartburn because acid
is rising into his oesophagus.

451
00:31:46,080 --> 00:31:48,833
The ketamine
could've made Nestor regurgitate.

452
00:31:48,920 --> 00:31:53,038
The rope would hold gastric juices
in the upper throat and weaken the hyoid.

453
00:31:53,120 --> 00:31:55,554
Digestive juices are hydrochloric acid.

454
00:31:55,640 --> 00:31:59,758
When you're not busy, could I ask you
a few questions about sexual positions?

455
00:31:59,840 --> 00:32:03,196
If you even try, I will take my gun
and shoot you between the eyes.

456
00:32:03,280 --> 00:32:06,716
These marks here,
that's consistent with hydrochloric acid.

457
00:32:06,800 --> 00:32:09,837
- I don't like this.
- I'll run it through the Angelator.

458
00:32:09,920 --> 00:32:13,799
Replace the values for the hyoid bone mass
with these coefficients.

459
00:32:13,880 --> 00:32:18,954
That will replicate bone deterioration as
the hyoid is being digested by stomach acid.

460
00:32:19,040 --> 00:32:23,079
<i>(Angela)</i> I'm applying a timeline
and running in fast forward.

461
00:32:23,160 --> 00:32:27,597
<i>(Bones)</i> The gastric juices trapped
by the noose in Nestor's oesophagus

462
00:32:27,680 --> 00:32:30,478
actually digest the hyoid over time.

463
00:32:30,560 --> 00:32:33,199
Wait. There. The hyoid cracked.

464
00:32:33,280 --> 00:32:35,271
196.3 hours.

465
00:32:35,360 --> 00:32:37,430
Just over eight days.

466
00:32:38,000 --> 00:32:41,356
- This finding is congruent with suicide.
- I do not accept that.

467
00:32:41,440 --> 00:32:45,877
It's a fact. You can't not accept a fact.
I have to amend my cause-of-death report.

468
00:32:45,960 --> 00:32:51,671
You'll stop my investigation. The school's
covering up a murder. You're helping them.

469
00:33:01,480 --> 00:33:03,869
<i>(Angela)</i> Honey.

470
00:33:05,160 --> 00:33:09,358
Did you everjust believe something
despite the evidence?

471
00:33:09,440 --> 00:33:11,795
Just know it was true?

472
00:33:12,800 --> 00:33:15,917
No. I've hoped things.

473
00:33:16,000 --> 00:33:20,755
But I've always known the difference
between hope and fact.

474
00:33:20,840 --> 00:33:24,071
You know, all that's left of this boy
is a table full of bones.

475
00:33:24,160 --> 00:33:26,355
Everyone he's ever known has an agenda.

476
00:33:26,440 --> 00:33:29,716
His parents, school,
even the cop investigating his death.

477
00:33:29,800 --> 00:33:35,272
I'm the only one who cares about the truth
of what Nestor's life came to, good or bad.

478
00:33:35,360 --> 00:33:38,636
And I know the truth is more important
than anything else.

479
00:33:38,720 --> 00:33:42,759
You know... or you hope it's true?

480
00:33:45,320 --> 00:33:49,393
Suicide is the most rational,
logical explanation.

481
00:33:49,480 --> 00:33:53,917
What I believe doesn't matter.
What makes me sad doesn't matter.

482
00:33:57,720 --> 00:34:00,280
Look at this face.

483
00:34:00,360 --> 00:34:03,352
He did not kill himself.

484
00:34:03,440 --> 00:34:07,956
Angela, I need a little more proof
than a nice drawing.

485
00:34:08,600 --> 00:34:10,989
I can do that.

486
00:34:22,600 --> 00:34:26,752
OK, this is not from the DVD. It's a quick
snippet that was on Nestor's hard drive.

487
00:34:26,840 --> 00:34:31,789
Somebody tried to erase it,
but Zack and I got some of it back.

488
00:34:36,680 --> 00:34:39,717
Angela, zoom in on that necklace.

489
00:34:41,200 --> 00:34:45,796
A little sea horse? Come on.
What kind of blackmailer does that?

490
00:34:45,880 --> 00:34:48,519
It's sweet. It's a clueless kid in love.

491
00:34:48,600 --> 00:34:51,512
That's evidence he didn't commit suicide?
A sea horse?

492
00:34:51,600 --> 00:34:54,034
A kid doesn't give a gift cos he's in love.

493
00:34:54,120 --> 00:34:58,079
- He does it cos he wants a little loving.
- Rerun that.

494
00:34:58,160 --> 00:35:02,153
That cynicism you affect, Booth,
it's your way of hiding a romantic nature.

495
00:35:02,240 --> 00:35:04,959
There. Stop. Play again.

496
00:35:06,840 --> 00:35:08,796
- There. She rolled her eyes.
- What?

497
00:35:08,880 --> 00:35:12,634
- No. I didn't see it either.
- Play it in stop motion.

498
00:35:12,720 --> 00:35:15,757
Zoom in. There.

499
00:35:15,840 --> 00:35:17,831
Slow motion.

500
00:35:23,880 --> 00:35:27,236
- How'd you see that?
- Wait. That girl knew the camera was there.

501
00:35:27,320 --> 00:35:30,198
- She looked at it.
- She isn't a victim. She's in on it.

502
00:35:30,280 --> 00:35:33,909
You don't roll your eyes to yourself.
You do that for someone else.

503
00:35:34,000 --> 00:35:38,278
- What do we do now?
- Now a public-school education comes in.

504
00:35:38,360 --> 00:35:40,999
"Divide and conquer"
was the playground motto.

505
00:35:41,520 --> 00:35:44,432
What would help
is if you told me why he killed himself.

506
00:35:44,520 --> 00:35:47,512
<i>(Bones)</i> Then we can close
the murder investigation.

507
00:35:47,600 --> 00:35:51,115
- Why is Tucker here?
- Oh, Tucker, he said some things.

508
00:35:51,200 --> 00:35:54,351
- What things?
- What he said doesn't make you look good.

509
00:35:54,440 --> 00:35:57,989
I believe him. Agent Booth says
it was only fair to hear your side.

510
00:35:58,080 --> 00:36:03,871
If your stories match up,
I'll be able to drop the murder investigation.

511
00:36:03,960 --> 00:36:08,192
I find it hard to believe that it was your idea
for Tucker to seduce your mother.

512
00:36:08,280 --> 00:36:12,193
- It wasrt. She hit on Tucker.
- No, wait, wait. Can they do this?

513
00:36:12,280 --> 00:36:15,033
- They're fishing. Don't say a word.
- I wasrt fishing.

514
00:36:15,120 --> 00:36:20,399
Tucker was all "Stacy's Mom" about it.
I just sort of gave him permission.

515
00:36:20,480 --> 00:36:22,357
- It was funny.
- Please stop this.

516
00:36:22,440 --> 00:36:27,275
Mom, deal with it, OK?
You're the one that's the perv, so...

517
00:36:28,400 --> 00:36:33,030
When my mom gave Tucker money to keep
him quiet, we got the idea to blackmail her.

518
00:36:33,120 --> 00:36:37,318
I was mad at her, I guess.
Then Tucker said it was my turn.

519
00:36:37,400 --> 00:36:40,756
Nestor was rich, Ionely, Catholic,
and he had a thing for you.

520
00:36:40,840 --> 00:36:46,790
He was cute. People didn't notice because
of the way he talked, but he was really cute.

521
00:36:46,880 --> 00:36:49,792
I liked him.

522
00:36:49,880 --> 00:36:54,749
We made the tape and showed it to Nestor.
It made him really upset.

523
00:36:54,840 --> 00:36:56,990
Really upset.

524
00:36:57,080 --> 00:37:00,789
- Because you said you'd show his mother?
- Or because I broke his heart.

525
00:37:00,880 --> 00:37:04,873
I still can't believe he killed himself.
I'm really sorry he did that.

526
00:37:04,960 --> 00:37:07,713
What Camden did was wrong,
which she acknowledged.

527
00:37:07,800 --> 00:37:11,076
She isn't responsible
for an unstable boy's overreaction.

528
00:37:11,160 --> 00:37:12,798
I said I'm sorry.

529
00:37:12,880 --> 00:37:16,350
I'm placing you under arrest
for the murder of Nestor Olivos.

530
00:37:16,440 --> 00:37:19,557
What? She's admitted to blackmail. That's all.

531
00:37:19,640 --> 00:37:21,676
He was going to go to the headmaster,

532
00:37:21,760 --> 00:37:25,958
so you dosed him with ketamine
and hauled him up into the tree.

533
00:37:26,040 --> 00:37:31,751
- The DNA traces in the rope will prove that.
- Plus you've already confessed to the motive.

534
00:37:31,840 --> 00:37:37,551
If I cooperate and tell you everything
Tucker did, do I get some sort of deal?

535
00:37:39,200 --> 00:37:41,998
That depends on what else you got.

536
00:37:44,800 --> 00:37:50,397
The headmaster and the head of security will
both lose theirjobs. The sheriff will resign.

537
00:37:50,480 --> 00:37:54,712
The two kids who killed your son
are both in custody.

538
00:37:54,800 --> 00:37:56,438
Thank you.

539
00:37:56,520 --> 00:38:00,069
We're very sorry for your loss.

540
00:38:04,120 --> 00:38:06,111
Ambassador Olivos.

541
00:38:09,240 --> 00:38:15,315
You told me that all a mother wants
is to know that she's raised her child well,

542
00:38:15,400 --> 00:38:20,520
that your biggest regret is you'll never know if
Nestor would've grown up to be a good man.

543
00:38:20,600 --> 00:38:22,750
But he was a good man.

544
00:38:23,880 --> 00:38:27,270
He died because
he was trying to do the right thing.

545
00:38:35,760 --> 00:38:38,513
Very impressive, Temperance.

546
00:38:38,600 --> 00:38:41,433
Got that one right.

547
00:38:51,200 --> 00:38:56,035
When you're with someone, the gymnastics
aren't what matter. It's who you are.

548
00:38:56,120 --> 00:39:01,148
- It's your intentions and how much you care.
- If you don't want to help me, just say so.

549
00:39:01,240 --> 00:39:07,554
All right. I'm gonna let you in on a secret.
This is a female secret.

550
00:39:07,640 --> 00:39:12,668
Go to Naomi and tell her that
you don't know anything about lovemaking.

551
00:39:12,760 --> 00:39:17,231
Sex, yeah. Lovemaking, you're a blank slate.

552
00:39:17,320 --> 00:39:21,996
You'll do anything she wants if she just
introduces you to the secrets of love.

553
00:39:22,080 --> 00:39:25,993
She'll be more interested
than if you were the most imaginative lover.

554
00:39:26,080 --> 00:39:29,675
- That is totally counterintuitive.
- Just do it, Z-man.

555
00:39:29,760 --> 00:39:33,036
Reap the benefits of my sexual wisdom.

556
00:39:36,400 --> 00:39:40,439
Oh, no. This isn't gonna work.
I mean, this is my place. Sid.

557
00:39:40,520 --> 00:39:45,036
As long as they keep it down on the subject
of corpses and bodily fluids, I have no beef.

558
00:39:45,120 --> 00:39:47,270
OK, that is amazing. I had heartburn.

559
00:39:47,360 --> 00:39:51,114
I asked Sid to bring me something
and now the heartburrs gone.

560
00:39:51,200 --> 00:39:55,113
- Man, I love this place.
- <i>(Booth)</i> OK, fine. New rules.

561
00:39:55,200 --> 00:39:58,112
That counter is mine. That booth is yours.

562
00:39:58,200 --> 00:40:01,954
Everything else around here,
all right, mine. All right?

563
00:40:02,040 --> 00:40:05,316
Mine. M-i-n-e. Mine.

564
00:40:17,680 --> 00:40:21,275
I've been thinking about
your whole "something stinks" aptitude.

565
00:40:21,360 --> 00:40:23,590
Oh, yeah?

566
00:40:23,680 --> 00:40:26,752
I think you have a knack
for reading body language.

567
00:40:26,840 --> 00:40:31,277
Stress in the voice, other indicators.
It's not mysterious, but it is impressive.

568
00:40:31,360 --> 00:40:35,512
In the future, I will try to accord it
an appropriate degree of objective won'th.

569
00:40:35,600 --> 00:40:38,239
Thank you, Temperance. I appreciate that.

570
00:40:38,320 --> 00:40:40,880
So...

571
00:40:40,960 --> 00:40:45,238
what part of "this is mine"
did you not understand?

572
00:40:48,440 --> 00:40:50,749
Want me to say it in Latin?

573
00:40:56,240 --> 00:40:58,231
<i>Absit invidia.</i>

574
00:41:12,360 --> 00:41:14,555
Nice.

575
00:41:44,960 --> 00:41:47,793
Visiontext Subtitles: Sarah Johnston

576
00:41:50,280 --> 00:41:51,599
What's that mean?

577
00:41:52,360 --> 00:41:54,351
ENGLISH SDH

