1
00:00:04,280 --> 00:00:06,589
- <i>(Bones)</i> Where are we?
- An access shaft

2
00:00:06,680 --> 00:00:10,798
to an underwater aqueduct
which has never been activated.

3
00:00:10,880 --> 00:00:12,598
I mean, geographically?

4
00:00:12,680 --> 00:00:16,719
Beneath Wisconsin and Massachusetts
Avenues, near the National Cathedral.

5
00:00:16,800 --> 00:00:19,314
How far down? We seem very far down.

6
00:00:19,400 --> 00:00:22,870
- Oh, about 60 feet, so far.
- Is there any other way?

7
00:00:22,960 --> 00:00:26,919
<i>(Booth)</i> It's a maze down here, but
this was the fastest way to get to the body.

8
00:00:27,000 --> 00:00:30,595
These lines have load tolerances
that are more than adequate.

9
00:00:30,680 --> 00:00:34,878
What about shock tolerance?
The rope jerks, kinetic energy increases

10
00:00:34,960 --> 00:00:38,396
- and snap, we fall to our deaths.
- <i>(all)</i> Hey!

11
00:00:38,480 --> 00:00:41,313
OK. Let's say we just stop the chatter.

12
00:00:46,240 --> 00:00:52,270
City workers found it. Public works are under
federal jurisdiction, so this is your party.

13
00:00:57,720 --> 00:00:59,278
<i>(Booth)</i> Oh.

14
00:00:59,360 --> 00:01:03,069
- What's at the top of that shaft?
- Utility tunnel accessing steam pipes.

15
00:01:03,160 --> 00:01:05,355
- May I borrow your gun?
- Why do you want it?

16
00:01:05,440 --> 00:01:07,670
I'm not gonna shoot anyone, I promise.

17
00:01:07,760 --> 00:01:10,832
It's not a hammer, or anything.

18
00:01:10,920 --> 00:01:16,313
We've been working together for months,
Booth. A little trust would be nice.

19
00:01:17,320 --> 00:01:19,834
- Careful.
- OK. Hold this.

20
00:01:25,320 --> 00:01:29,029
Now they'll eat each other
and leave our remains alone.

21
00:01:29,120 --> 00:01:32,829
You know, you do know I have
to file a report with the review board

22
00:01:32,920 --> 00:01:35,309
each time I discharge a round
from my weapon?

23
00:01:35,400 --> 00:01:40,155
Pictures, Zack. The rats scattered the remains,
so give me a five-metre radius.

24
00:01:40,240 --> 00:01:43,915
The velocity of the fall
shattered her body on impact.

25
00:01:44,000 --> 00:01:46,389
Tibias and fibulas broken below the knees.

26
00:01:46,480 --> 00:01:49,313
- Vertebrae compressed and shattered.
- "Her"?

27
00:01:49,400 --> 00:01:52,756
Yeah. I just hope that she was dead
before the rats got to her.

28
00:01:52,840 --> 00:01:55,957
Oh, God. Any idea
how long she's been down here?

29
00:01:56,040 --> 00:01:58,838
We should get answers
when Hodgins analyses the bugs,

30
00:01:58,920 --> 00:02:01,229
but rats could strip a body in days.

31
00:02:01,320 --> 00:02:04,312
Shirt, pants, but no jacket or shoes.

32
00:02:05,280 --> 00:02:07,953
No way rats could carry that off.

33
00:02:09,040 --> 00:02:10,792
Excuse me?

34
00:02:11,880 --> 00:02:13,552
Sir? Sir!

35
00:02:13,640 --> 00:02:18,555
What the hell? Bones! Easy!
What the hell are you doing? Bones!

36
00:02:18,640 --> 00:02:21,200
Bones, you don'tjust
run after guys in the dark.

37
00:02:21,280 --> 00:02:24,989
He didn't need any light.
He knew exactly where he was going.

38
00:02:25,080 --> 00:02:27,719
Yeah, that's creepy.

39
00:02:27,800 --> 00:02:29,995
He lives down here.

40
00:03:02,560 --> 00:03:07,680
The victim had a pin in her knee from a skiing
injury so we matched the serial numbers.

41
00:03:07,760 --> 00:03:10,638
Her name's Marni Hunter, 24.

42
00:03:10,720 --> 00:03:13,359
1.7 metres tall. Left-handed.

43
00:03:13,440 --> 00:03:16,716
- Documentary filmmaker.
- Reported missing ten days ago.

44
00:03:16,800 --> 00:03:19,678
- Police find the guy?
- Your mole man? No.

45
00:03:19,760 --> 00:03:24,675
I've heard of them. They patch into electrical
grids down there. Some can even tap cable.

46
00:03:24,760 --> 00:03:26,751
I'd set time of death at ten days,

47
00:03:26,840 --> 00:03:29,434
- when the missing persons report was filed.
- Sure?

48
00:03:29,520 --> 00:03:32,478
See the ratio of fly larvae
to Silphidae beetles?

49
00:03:32,560 --> 00:03:34,152
Ten days. I believe you.

50
00:03:34,240 --> 00:03:39,030
She fell approximately 40 feet and landed
feet first, which explains the crushed tibias.

51
00:03:39,120 --> 00:03:41,190
- That what killed her?
- Not necessarily.

52
00:03:41,280 --> 00:03:45,159
Her skull sustained traumatic injuries
inconsistent with a feet-first fall.

53
00:03:45,240 --> 00:03:50,519
We found blood and bone chips on exposed
pipes jutting from the ventilation shaft.

54
00:03:50,600 --> 00:03:53,751
- So that's what killed her?
- No, not necessarily.

55
00:03:53,840 --> 00:03:55,592
The fingernails are clean.

56
00:03:55,680 --> 00:04:00,231
If she were falling, she would claw at the wall
to slow her descent. It's instinctual.

57
00:04:00,320 --> 00:04:04,359
- So she was dead before the fall.
- No, not necessarily.

58
00:04:04,440 --> 00:04:07,671
Bones, please. Just tell me.

59
00:04:07,760 --> 00:04:10,593
She may have simply been unconscious.

60
00:04:16,880 --> 00:04:22,716
Mr Garfield, why did you wait two days to file
the missing persons report on your fiancée?

61
00:04:22,800 --> 00:04:26,270
Marni is a documentary filmmaker. Was.

62
00:04:26,360 --> 00:04:29,272
Very dedicated -
she immersed herself in each project.

63
00:04:29,360 --> 00:04:32,875
It's not odd for her to stay out in the field
without coming home.

64
00:04:32,960 --> 00:04:35,838
You get invested in your work,
time can get away from you.

65
00:04:35,920 --> 00:04:38,593
<i>(sighs)</i> That's what Marni always said.

66
00:04:38,680 --> 00:04:42,229
- You didn't worry about her down there?
- She's been all over the world.

67
00:04:42,320 --> 00:04:45,915
Rwanda, Latin America,
the Balkans, the Middle East.

68
00:04:46,000 --> 00:04:50,073
- I was just glad to have her home.
- You two were engaged.

69
00:04:50,160 --> 00:04:54,711
- We'd finally set a date.
- I'm very sorry for your loss.

70
00:04:54,800 --> 00:04:56,870
Did her work take her into the tunnels?

71
00:04:56,960 --> 00:05:02,671
Her latest project, the last couple of months,
is about the maze of tunnels beneath the city.

72
00:05:02,760 --> 00:05:05,399
That's what she'd cut together so far.

73
00:05:06,360 --> 00:05:08,999
- <i>You need to drink...</i>
- I told her to be careful.

74
00:05:09,080 --> 00:05:11,514
A lot of those guys are pretty nuts.

75
00:05:11,600 --> 00:05:15,559
It's fascinating.
A fully functional shadow society.

76
00:05:15,640 --> 00:05:17,915
Did you ever go down there with her?

77
00:05:18,000 --> 00:05:20,719
- Who did she work with?
- Marni worked alone.

78
00:05:20,800 --> 00:05:24,793
She did her own camerawork and sound.
It's very raw - that's her style.

79
00:05:24,880 --> 00:05:29,874
She never appeared on camera. She thought
the film should be about the subject, not her.

80
00:05:29,960 --> 00:05:33,475
That's true. As an anthropologist
you immerse yourself in a culture

81
00:05:33,560 --> 00:05:36,711
without distorting it
with your own presence.

82
00:05:36,800 --> 00:05:39,758
It's another reason to work alone.

83
00:05:39,840 --> 00:05:42,912
So you found her at the bottom
of an air shaft?

84
00:05:43,000 --> 00:05:44,991
You think one of these people...?

85
00:05:45,080 --> 00:05:47,719
Her skull has unexplained damage.
Shattering on...

86
00:05:47,800 --> 00:05:51,713
<i>(clears throat)</i> We're still investigating,
Mr Garfield.

87
00:05:56,440 --> 00:06:00,638
<i>- Hey, Harold.</i>
<i>- Hey, Helen. What you doing down here?</i>

88
00:06:00,720 --> 00:06:03,075
Wait a minute.

89
00:06:03,160 --> 00:06:05,196
Wait. Freeze!

90
00:06:05,920 --> 00:06:07,990
That's the man I saw in the tunnel.

91
00:06:08,080 --> 00:06:10,389
Marni ever mention this guy to you?

92
00:06:10,480 --> 00:06:14,792
No. The blonde woman is Helen... something.

93
00:06:14,880 --> 00:06:17,075
She's a social worker, I think.

94
00:06:17,160 --> 00:06:19,071
Runs a shelter over on 26th.

95
00:06:19,400 --> 00:06:23,439
Marni came to the shelter. She heard I worked
with what she called "mole people".

96
00:06:23,520 --> 00:06:25,750
She asked me to introduce her to them.

97
00:06:25,840 --> 00:06:29,799
- Spend a lot of time down here?
- It's kinda my beat, I guess you'd say.

98
00:06:29,880 --> 00:06:32,314
- Did you resent her intrusion?
- Why do you ask?

99
00:06:32,400 --> 00:06:36,188
It's an ordered society. Marni and her cameras
might've been disruptive.

100
00:06:36,280 --> 00:06:41,308
These people are here for a reason.
They have a right to privacy. I respect that.

101
00:06:41,400 --> 00:06:44,517
I'm not sure a documentary filmmaker does.

102
00:06:44,600 --> 00:06:48,832
- Disruptive enough to make enemies?
- Perhaps. It's tough to know these people.

103
00:06:48,920 --> 00:06:53,277
Isn't that what Marni was trying to do?
Get to know them, explain them to the world?

104
00:06:53,360 --> 00:06:56,272
No offence, Dr Brennan,
but I find that a bit naive.

105
00:06:56,360 --> 00:07:00,069
Herjob was to sell her films.
What she was doing was exploitive.

106
00:07:00,160 --> 00:07:03,277
Maybe one of these people'd agree with you.

107
00:07:04,280 --> 00:07:07,272
There's the man you're looking for.
Harold Overmeyer.

108
00:07:07,360 --> 00:07:09,749
Marni called him the Mayor of Moletown.

109
00:07:09,840 --> 00:07:12,115
I imagine she thought that was clever.

110
00:07:12,200 --> 00:07:15,749
<i>(Bones)</i> He's mediating a dispute.
He has alpha-male status.

111
00:07:15,840 --> 00:07:19,594
- How did Harold respond to her?
- My impression was he liked her.

112
00:07:19,680 --> 00:07:23,639
But, again,
nobody really knows these people.

113
00:07:32,320 --> 00:07:35,232
I brought you some food, Harold.

114
00:07:36,440 --> 00:07:39,113
I have enough food.

115
00:07:39,480 --> 00:07:42,074
- What do you want?
- I'd like to ask a few questions.

116
00:07:42,160 --> 00:07:45,755
I'm not required to answer any questions.
Not required.

117
00:07:45,840 --> 00:07:48,877
That's correct. Harold has rights.

118
00:07:48,960 --> 00:07:55,149
Miss, do you wanna step back? You're
interfering with a criminal investigation.

119
00:07:56,520 --> 00:07:59,432
Did you know Marni Hunter?

120
00:08:03,960 --> 00:08:08,078
- You saw what happened, didn't you?
- You guys are trespassing. Go away.

121
00:08:08,160 --> 00:08:11,596
- OK, buddy, that's it. Let's go.
- Whoa, whoa. Booth.

122
00:08:11,680 --> 00:08:13,989
This man is obviously someone important.

123
00:08:14,080 --> 00:08:16,913
Important?
He lives in a cardboard box underground.

124
00:08:17,000 --> 00:08:20,470
In <i>this</i> society he has status.
Give him his due.

125
00:08:20,560 --> 00:08:23,154
Treat him with respect.

126
00:08:24,960 --> 00:08:27,918
OK, Mr Overmeyer,
we got off on the wrong foot.

127
00:08:28,000 --> 00:08:30,912
I'm Special Agent Seeley Booth from the FBI.

128
00:08:31,000 --> 00:08:36,074
I would appreciate it very much if you would
grant us the advantage of your expertise

129
00:08:36,160 --> 00:08:38,469
as we investigate Marni Hunter's death.

130
00:08:39,840 --> 00:08:41,796
Fair enough.

131
00:08:41,880 --> 00:08:44,269
Oh.

132
00:08:44,360 --> 00:08:49,957
Mr Overmeyer, I saw you in the tunnel
near where we found Marni Hunter's remains.

133
00:08:50,040 --> 00:08:55,398
- Checking the tunnels.
- Checking the tunnels or checking on Marni?

134
00:08:55,480 --> 00:08:57,152
I warned her.

135
00:08:57,240 --> 00:09:00,789
So you two were friends
beyond being observer and observed?

136
00:09:00,880 --> 00:09:03,394
You talk like her.
You making a documentary too?

137
00:09:03,480 --> 00:09:06,950
- No, but there are things we need to...
- That's my stuff.

138
00:09:07,040 --> 00:09:08,678
Bones.

139
00:09:08,760 --> 00:09:11,513
Harold, is this Marni's video camera?

140
00:09:13,400 --> 00:09:16,073
You'd better go now. You can go now!

141
00:09:16,160 --> 00:09:18,674
Booth, this clothing has blood all over it.

142
00:09:18,760 --> 00:09:21,832
- "Give him his due", huh?
- I think it belonged to Marni.

143
00:09:21,920 --> 00:09:24,115
Afraid you're gonna have to come with us.

144
00:09:24,200 --> 00:09:26,475
What? No! I can't leave.

145
00:09:26,560 --> 00:09:30,075
There are bone fragments.
I'm gonna take these back to the lab.

146
00:09:30,160 --> 00:09:32,435
No! You don't understand!

147
00:09:32,520 --> 00:09:35,876
She wanted me to have it.
She wanted me to have that!

148
00:09:38,520 --> 00:09:42,479
I find scrap metal, that's all.
That's why I go deep.

149
00:09:42,560 --> 00:09:44,835
You don't have to say anything.

150
00:09:44,920 --> 00:09:47,639
You're not here because you scavenge.
You know that.

151
00:09:47,720 --> 00:09:51,030
It's too bright in here.
Too... too bright in here.

152
00:09:51,120 --> 00:09:55,910
I know you have a distinguished military
record, Harold. 10th Special Forces Group.

153
00:09:56,000 --> 00:09:57,797
I was with the Rangers.

154
00:09:57,880 --> 00:10:02,874
What, so you gonna tell me, "Harold, I know
what you've been through. I been there too."

155
00:10:02,960 --> 00:10:05,155
"I know how you ended up
how you ended up."

156
00:10:05,240 --> 00:10:09,074
- You telling me that?
- Yeah, I'm telling you that.

157
00:10:10,080 --> 00:10:13,117
- I killed people.
- You saved five of your men.

158
00:10:14,800 --> 00:10:18,190
- By shooting a pregnant woman.
- She had a grenade in her hand.

159
00:10:18,280 --> 00:10:21,272
She had a child in her arms.

160
00:10:22,720 --> 00:10:26,429
I shot her... and the grenade went off.

161
00:10:27,320 --> 00:10:30,357
She died right away.

162
00:10:33,080 --> 00:10:35,071
But that kid...

163
00:10:36,040 --> 00:10:38,156
He took a while.

164
00:10:38,240 --> 00:10:42,438
He kept looking at me, but I...

165
00:10:42,520 --> 00:10:45,478
You did what a soldier had to do.

166
00:10:45,560 --> 00:10:49,838
Yeah. You know, I was a good soldier.
I was a very good soldier.

167
00:10:49,920 --> 00:10:53,356
But a pretty bad human being.

168
00:10:53,440 --> 00:10:55,510
A pretty bad human being.

169
00:10:56,720 --> 00:10:59,109
What happened to Marni?

170
00:11:00,760 --> 00:11:04,036
Ah. I hadrt seen her in days, you know?

171
00:11:04,880 --> 00:11:07,189
That's why I went to go take a look.

172
00:11:08,240 --> 00:11:10,834
Rats were all over her, man.

173
00:11:10,920 --> 00:11:13,150
All over her!

174
00:11:13,240 --> 00:11:17,074
- How did you end up with her things?
- Well, I was gonna sell them.

175
00:11:17,160 --> 00:11:19,594
She would've wanted me to have those.

176
00:11:19,680 --> 00:11:22,877
So you had nothing to do with her death?

177
00:11:26,320 --> 00:11:28,197
Um...

178
00:11:28,280 --> 00:11:30,589
l-I gave her something.

179
00:11:30,680 --> 00:11:33,717
- And that's why she died.
- What did you give her?

180
00:11:33,800 --> 00:11:36,075
I'm advising you not to say anything else.

181
00:11:36,160 --> 00:11:39,630
You know what? I think it's best
I not talk about this any more,

182
00:11:39,720 --> 00:11:41,392
not cause any more trouble.

183
00:11:41,480 --> 00:11:44,074
- I gotta go.
- No, Harold, you can't. Not yet.

184
00:11:44,160 --> 00:11:47,152
- It's too bright in here. I gotta go.
- Harold...

185
00:11:50,400 --> 00:11:52,391
I never wanted her to die.

186
00:11:52,480 --> 00:11:55,597
But she wouldn't listen. I warned her.

187
00:11:56,680 --> 00:11:58,671
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Pride" by Syntax)</i>

188
00:12:03,440 --> 00:12:05,954
♪ <i>It's made up of lonely moments</i>

189
00:12:06,040 --> 00:12:10,318
♪ <i>There was always a moment there</i>
<i>when I knew</i>

190
00:12:14,120 --> 00:12:16,759
♪ <i>You always gave instalments</i>

191
00:12:16,840 --> 00:12:20,674
♪ <i>Always knew you concentrated and grew</i>

192
00:12:24,840 --> 00:12:27,479
♪ <i>And I believe in reinvention</i>

193
00:12:27,560 --> 00:12:30,996
♪ <i>Do you believe that life is holding the clue?</i>

194
00:12:35,800 --> 00:12:38,439
♪ <i>Take away all the lonely moments</i>

195
00:12:38,520 --> 00:12:42,479
♪ <i>Give me full communication with you</i>

196
00:12:50,640 --> 00:12:54,474
I finished the skull. We should be able
to determine cause of death.

197
00:12:54,560 --> 00:12:59,998
You haven't eaten all day. I have some
killer yellowtail here and spicy tuna rolls.

198
00:13:00,080 --> 00:13:02,310
Time gets away from me sometimes.

199
00:13:03,320 --> 00:13:05,754
- What?
- The victim used to say that.

200
00:13:05,840 --> 00:13:09,549
- You think the homeless mole guy killed her?
- Booth does.

201
00:13:09,640 --> 00:13:13,155
He had her camera and bloody clothes.
Plus he's killed people before.

202
00:13:13,240 --> 00:13:17,119
- As a soldier. Socially sanctioned.
- Booth's killed as a law enforcer.

203
00:13:17,200 --> 00:13:20,590
What if, from mole mars point of view,
Marni was a criminal?

204
00:13:20,680 --> 00:13:23,877
Marni Hunter was an observer.
By definition, passive.

205
00:13:24,640 --> 00:13:27,712
- Like you?
- Yes. Exactly.

206
00:13:29,080 --> 00:13:30,798
Are you getting at something?

207
00:13:30,880 --> 00:13:35,670
- I just wish you were a little more scared.
- I'm careful.

208
00:13:35,760 --> 00:13:39,514
<i>(scoffs)</i> Running after a murderer
in the dark is not being an observer.

209
00:13:39,600 --> 00:13:40,999
Booth told you?

210
00:13:41,080 --> 00:13:46,313
More and more of your work
is outside of this lab, running after bad guys.

211
00:13:46,400 --> 00:13:48,550
Just promise me you'll be careful.

212
00:13:48,640 --> 00:13:53,919
Every society has its fringe dwellers,
and every society fears its fringe dwellers.

213
00:13:54,000 --> 00:13:58,039
Usually cos they're an example
of what happens when you fail in that society.

214
00:13:58,120 --> 00:14:01,032
But they are seldom dangerous, in reality.

215
00:14:01,120 --> 00:14:04,237
This is what you do
when things get too close to home -

216
00:14:04,320 --> 00:14:06,470
you get all analytical and academic.

217
00:14:06,560 --> 00:14:10,439
I just want you to know that maybe
Marni Hunter did the same thing,

218
00:14:10,520 --> 00:14:13,114
and now she's dead.

219
00:14:17,240 --> 00:14:21,279
We've got most of the skull. There's just
a piece missing the size of a quarter.

220
00:14:21,360 --> 00:14:24,033
Why are missing pieces
always the size of quarters

221
00:14:24,120 --> 00:14:26,395
and tumours always the size of grapefruits?

222
00:14:26,480 --> 00:14:30,234
Those are rhetorical questions
I'm not supposed to answer, right?

223
00:14:30,320 --> 00:14:33,915
- These are not simply random abrasions.
- What are they?

224
00:14:34,000 --> 00:14:36,639
Marni's skull was fractured
by a midair impact.

225
00:14:36,720 --> 00:14:40,349
There's a radiating fracture
centred above her right temporal bone.

226
00:14:40,440 --> 00:14:44,035
But this damage is isolated
on the <i>left</i> side of her skull.

227
00:14:44,120 --> 00:14:47,396
A girl can't bang both sides of her head
as she falls down a shaft?

228
00:14:47,480 --> 00:14:52,110
From the fracture pattern,
it appears to be a sharp, pointed weapon.

229
00:14:52,200 --> 00:14:55,954
Harold said he'd given the victim
something he wished he hadrt.

230
00:14:56,040 --> 00:14:58,315
Could this have been it?

231
00:14:58,400 --> 00:15:01,676
- <i>(Zack)</i> Fragments of Latin.
- Roman numerals.

232
00:15:01,760 --> 00:15:04,911
- You know who knows about that stuff?
- You show it to him.

233
00:15:05,000 --> 00:15:08,879
I am not taking possession of
that piece of evidence. <i>You</i> show it to him.

234
00:15:08,960 --> 00:15:10,188
<i>(Hodgins sighs)</i>

235
00:15:10,280 --> 00:15:15,912
Armour. Roman cuirass. Doric columns,
common around the first century BC.

236
00:15:16,000 --> 00:15:19,436
The mole guy gave something to the victim
he thinks got her killed.

237
00:15:19,520 --> 00:15:21,078
Of course, he's crazy.

238
00:15:21,160 --> 00:15:24,755
This could be valuable.
Let's have Miss Montenegro x-ray it.

239
00:15:24,840 --> 00:15:28,719
Stress from the initial pressing
should show what's been worn away.

240
00:15:28,800 --> 00:15:31,872
I was hoping you'd take possession
of this piece of evidence.

241
00:15:31,960 --> 00:15:34,474
And the paperwork that goes along with it?

242
00:15:34,560 --> 00:15:37,677
I wasrt born yesterday, Dr Hodgins.

243
00:15:42,720 --> 00:15:44,073
You don't need me for this.

244
00:15:44,160 --> 00:15:45,639
- Yes, I do.
- Why?

245
00:15:45,720 --> 00:15:48,837
I have not taken official possession
of this evidence.

246
00:15:48,920 --> 00:15:51,229
Fascinating.

247
00:15:51,320 --> 00:15:53,197
1778.

248
00:15:53,280 --> 00:15:56,556
It appears to be an official seal
of some kind.

249
00:16:00,160 --> 00:16:02,196
Oh, my God.

250
00:16:05,760 --> 00:16:08,228
- Arert you gonna go after him?
- Nope.

251
00:16:08,320 --> 00:16:12,074
- Why not?
- He's now in charge of that medallion.

252
00:16:12,160 --> 00:16:14,435
Yes!

253
00:16:14,520 --> 00:16:17,671
- Treasure?
- It's an official vault seal.

254
00:16:17,760 --> 00:16:21,070
Manufactured by the War Office.
It was established in 1778.

255
00:16:21,160 --> 00:16:23,879
The Latin <i>sigli</i> and <i>thesaur</i>
tie it to the Treasury.

256
00:16:23,960 --> 00:16:26,520
- A bank vault kind of a vault?
- Much better.

257
00:16:26,600 --> 00:16:31,151
The War Office established several vaults
under the city to safekeep cultural treasures.

258
00:16:31,240 --> 00:16:33,071
- They must all be empty by now.
- No.

259
00:16:33,160 --> 00:16:37,358
Several were unaccounted for
after a series of cave-ins in the early 1900s.

260
00:16:37,440 --> 00:16:40,557
So this seal came off a vault of treasure
beneath the city?

261
00:16:40,640 --> 00:16:45,156
It could contain currency, gold ingots,
paintings and engravings.

262
00:16:45,240 --> 00:16:48,437
The original draft
of Lincolrs inaugural address.

263
00:16:48,520 --> 00:16:50,590
This could be an extraordinary find.

264
00:16:50,680 --> 00:16:54,958
We have to find these artefacts
before they're stolen or sold off.

265
00:16:55,040 --> 00:16:58,077
- What's the monetary value of this thing?
- Priceless.

266
00:16:58,160 --> 00:17:00,276
You can't put a value on our heritage.

267
00:17:00,360 --> 00:17:04,319
Well, I think someone did.
That's why Marni's dead.

268
00:17:09,720 --> 00:17:12,439
Harold, is this what you gave Marni Hunter?

269
00:17:12,520 --> 00:17:15,080
Yeah. She liked it.

270
00:17:15,160 --> 00:17:17,674
Where'd you get it?

271
00:17:17,760 --> 00:17:20,069
Beyond the perimeter.

272
00:17:20,160 --> 00:17:21,434
Harold?

273
00:17:21,520 --> 00:17:23,431
Harold, you have to trust us.

274
00:17:23,520 --> 00:17:27,399
We just want to find who killed Marni.
And you can help.

275
00:17:31,120 --> 00:17:33,714
You killed people.

276
00:17:33,800 --> 00:17:37,190
Maybe this is your chance to put that right.

277
00:17:37,280 --> 00:17:41,068
You said you wished
you hadrt given it to her. Why?

278
00:17:41,160 --> 00:17:43,879
- Did you take it from someone?
- The blonde.

279
00:17:44,320 --> 00:17:48,518
- It was hers, and I shouldn't have taken it.
- A blonde killed Marni?

280
00:17:48,600 --> 00:17:52,832
Marni went too deep.
That's the blonde's territory.

281
00:17:52,920 --> 00:17:57,516
- Does the blonde woman have a name?
- People around me die.

282
00:17:57,600 --> 00:18:00,034
- Marni died.
- There'll always be casualties.

283
00:18:00,120 --> 00:18:05,353
What's important is to recognise the enemy
and take 'em out so more people aren't hurt.

284
00:18:06,080 --> 00:18:09,629
- Can you take us down there, Harold?
- No. It's beyond the perimeter.

285
00:18:09,720 --> 00:18:13,474
I took Marni beyond the perimeter.
I won't make that same mistake again.

286
00:18:13,560 --> 00:18:16,199
I won't make that mistake again.

287
00:18:21,560 --> 00:18:24,597
- The social worker.
- Why? Because she's a blonde?

288
00:18:24,680 --> 00:18:27,069
Why didn't she want Marni poking around?

289
00:18:27,160 --> 00:18:30,232
She thought the documentary
was exploiting the homeless.

290
00:18:30,320 --> 00:18:32,390
- You buy that?
- Obviously you don't.

291
00:18:32,480 --> 00:18:36,234
You wanna know a better reason
for not wanting someone poking around?

292
00:18:36,320 --> 00:18:39,517
- A mythical treasure?
- Ever see <i>Treasure of the Sierra Madre</i>?

293
00:18:39,600 --> 00:18:45,436
It doesn't matter if the treasure is mythical.
People will still kill if they think it exists.

294
00:18:45,520 --> 00:18:47,238
- It did exist.
- What?

295
00:18:47,320 --> 00:18:52,269
In the movie, it's gold dust. People think
it didn't exist, so it blew away. But it did exist.

296
00:18:52,360 --> 00:18:54,794
But no one got it, is the point.

297
00:18:55,280 --> 00:18:57,271
All of a sudden, you know a movie.

298
00:18:57,360 --> 00:18:59,954
- Everybody knows that movie.
- <i>(cellphone rings)</i>

299
00:19:00,040 --> 00:19:01,598
- Brennan.
- <i>It's Hodgins.</i>

300
00:19:01,680 --> 00:19:04,319
Your victim was in some other tunnel
before she died.

301
00:19:04,400 --> 00:19:08,234
- Facts before conclusions.
- <i>Her clothing shows traces of diamond dust.</i>

302
00:19:08,320 --> 00:19:11,437
That suggests
a much older system of tunnels.

303
00:19:11,520 --> 00:19:15,433
Industrial diamonds were used
in blast-hole drilling in the 19th century.

304
00:19:15,520 --> 00:19:19,149
Hm. It's near a vault. It makes sense.

305
00:19:20,400 --> 00:19:24,393
"Good job, Hodgins.
What would we do without you?"

306
00:19:24,480 --> 00:19:29,634
So Marni was killed near a vault
and then dragged to the shaft.

307
00:19:29,720 --> 00:19:31,676
Harold will know where that vault is.

308
00:19:31,760 --> 00:19:35,196
Maybe you could try the
"We're brothers-in-arms" thing on him.

309
00:19:35,280 --> 00:19:40,752
OK, that what you just said right there, Bones,
that was cynical. It was glib and cynical.

310
00:19:40,840 --> 00:19:42,796
- Really?
- Yes, really.

311
00:19:42,880 --> 00:19:45,519
I know what that guy has been through.

312
00:19:46,640 --> 00:19:50,553
You killed a pregnant woman
who was holding a child?

313
00:19:52,400 --> 00:19:57,599
If you really want to know what I've done,
I'll tell you. But be ready for the truth.

314
00:20:03,120 --> 00:20:05,953
Good choice, Bones.

315
00:20:09,240 --> 00:20:11,674
- Harold is afraid of me?
- Does he have any reason?

316
00:20:11,760 --> 00:20:14,433
He fears the world.
Why else does he live underground?

317
00:20:14,520 --> 00:20:16,238
- He's paying penance.
- What?

318
00:20:16,320 --> 00:20:19,869
You catch murderers to pay your penance,
Harold lives underground.

319
00:20:19,960 --> 00:20:22,838
Did you ever tell Marni
you found her film exploitative?

320
00:20:22,920 --> 00:20:25,514
Of course. I'm honest.
I told her I wouldn't help.

321
00:20:25,600 --> 00:20:28,592
- So she turned to Harold as a guide.
- And two other guys.

322
00:20:28,680 --> 00:20:32,798
- What two other guys?
- She took climbing lessons, all that stuff.

323
00:20:32,880 --> 00:20:35,758
When you told Marni she was exploitive,
how did she react?

324
00:20:35,840 --> 00:20:39,116
She said that showing the truth
couldn't be exploitive.

325
00:20:39,200 --> 00:20:40,269
I agree with her.

326
00:20:40,360 --> 00:20:42,715
Truth doesn't mean the same thing
to everyone.

327
00:20:42,800 --> 00:20:45,519
- Harold said he was afraid of me?
- Of a blonde.

328
00:20:45,600 --> 00:20:48,433
- How do you know it wasrt Charlize Theron?
- Who's that?

329
00:20:48,520 --> 00:20:51,796
An actress. She's being sarcastic.
Thank you for your help.

330
00:20:51,880 --> 00:20:56,317
You amaze me. You know <i>Treasure of</i>
<i>the Sierra Madre</i> but not Charlize Theron.

331
00:20:56,400 --> 00:20:59,915
You know who you are?
You're my grandmother.

332
00:21:05,200 --> 00:21:07,760
OK. Here's the recreation.

333
00:21:14,920 --> 00:21:17,195
Here are the wounds.

334
00:21:17,280 --> 00:21:22,434
Those skull fractures are centred
above the left parietal lobe.

335
00:21:23,960 --> 00:21:26,838
OK, the lasers can measure
the angle of the attack

336
00:21:26,920 --> 00:21:30,071
and the amount of damage
done to the living bone of the skull.

337
00:21:30,160 --> 00:21:33,914
3.3mm indentation into the bone
at the deepest point,

338
00:21:34,000 --> 00:21:36,639
which trailed off to 0.04mm.

339
00:21:37,080 --> 00:21:39,514
<i>(Zack)</i> A glancing blow.

340
00:21:40,560 --> 00:21:43,028
Yeah. She saw it coming.

341
00:21:43,120 --> 00:21:46,669
The angle of attack
was between 50 and 53 degrees.

342
00:21:46,760 --> 00:21:50,150
Meaning the attacker struck from above.

343
00:21:51,480 --> 00:21:55,439
- And from the victim's right.
- So the attacker was left-handed.

344
00:21:55,840 --> 00:21:58,115
She was only struck once.

345
00:21:58,200 --> 00:22:01,078
Sometimes that's all it takes.

346
00:22:06,600 --> 00:22:09,273
Good job, bro. Take care.

347
00:22:09,360 --> 00:22:12,238
- Kyle Montrose and Duke Dalliel?
- Yeah.

348
00:22:12,320 --> 00:22:13,992
We're from the FBI.

349
00:22:14,080 --> 00:22:18,198
We have credit-card receipts showing
you gave Marni Hunter climbing lessons.

350
00:22:18,280 --> 00:22:22,910
If anyone can talk the FBI
into getting her a refund, it's Marni. <i>(laughs)</i>

351
00:22:23,000 --> 00:22:25,560
She's dead.

352
00:22:25,640 --> 00:22:28,473
- What? Oh, my God.
- What happened?

353
00:22:28,560 --> 00:22:31,279
She was found in a ventilation shaft
beneath the city.

354
00:22:31,360 --> 00:22:33,271
Did... did she fall?

355
00:22:33,360 --> 00:22:35,920
We told her not to go down there.
It's too dangerous.

356
00:22:36,000 --> 00:22:39,879
Marni's dead? That's... God.

357
00:22:39,960 --> 00:22:42,679
We gave her some climbing lessons -
rappelling -

358
00:22:42,760 --> 00:22:45,558
but not enough for her
to do spelunking on her own.

359
00:22:45,640 --> 00:22:47,517
Did you ever go into the tunnels?

360
00:22:47,600 --> 00:22:50,831
No way. The whole point of rock climbing
is to head for the sky.

361
00:22:50,920 --> 00:22:53,480
- Did she ever ask you to?
- Yes. Yes, she did.

362
00:22:53,560 --> 00:22:56,836
She was doing
some sort of documentary and...

363
00:22:56,920 --> 00:22:59,957
- God. She fell?
- That's what we're investigating.

364
00:23:00,040 --> 00:23:03,157
- You seem shook up.
- Well, yeah. Someone you know dies...

365
00:23:03,240 --> 00:23:08,075
I'm sorry, sir, but I gotta ask.
Were you and Marni... intimate?

366
00:23:08,160 --> 00:23:11,152
Yeah, we had a thing, but we broke up.

367
00:23:12,080 --> 00:23:17,518
She had a fiancé, and I was always very clear
that I didn't want to marry anyone.

368
00:23:17,600 --> 00:23:20,592
But... I liked her.

369
00:23:22,480 --> 00:23:24,630
God, it's just terrible.

370
00:23:24,720 --> 00:23:27,473
Did her fiancé know about you?

371
00:23:27,560 --> 00:23:30,074
I don't know.

372
00:23:30,160 --> 00:23:32,879
I can't believe this.

373
00:23:36,760 --> 00:23:42,312
Yes, I was aware there was another guy.
Marni was never sneaky.

374
00:23:42,400 --> 00:23:47,235
- <i>(Bones)</i> Did you know who it was?
- No. She told me it was over.

375
00:23:47,320 --> 00:23:50,551
Romantic triangle.
Makes for a pretty compelling motive.

376
00:23:50,640 --> 00:23:55,191
- You mean for me? I didn't kill Marni.
- She was sleeping with another man.

377
00:23:55,280 --> 00:23:58,636
Why didn't you tell us
that your wedding was called off?

378
00:23:58,720 --> 00:24:01,553
- Because it's humiliating.
- It make you angry?

379
00:24:01,640 --> 00:24:06,191
Of course it made me angry. And depressed,
and made me question my manood. All that.

380
00:24:06,280 --> 00:24:10,034
What do you want from me?
I didn't kill Marni.

381
00:24:10,880 --> 00:24:15,476
- She always came back to me.
- So this wasrt the first time?

382
00:24:15,560 --> 00:24:16,788
No.

383
00:24:16,880 --> 00:24:20,350
The fact that she was sleeping around
is gonna make it tougher.

384
00:24:20,440 --> 00:24:23,716
- Why?
- Mythical treasure versus jealous men?

385
00:24:23,800 --> 00:24:25,756
- That's stupid.
- No, it's not.

386
00:24:25,840 --> 00:24:29,037
Jealousy is the oldest motive
for murder in the world.

387
00:24:29,120 --> 00:24:33,238
A man getting involved with Marni should
know she's adventurous and independent.

388
00:24:33,320 --> 00:24:36,039
Horrible coffee.
Yeah, with a cheating heart?

389
00:24:36,120 --> 00:24:39,715
Well, she didn't hide anything.
She was direct and honest.

390
00:24:39,800 --> 00:24:43,315
Bones, you do realise
you are discussing motive right now?

391
00:24:43,400 --> 00:24:46,437
Psychology, not hard evidence.

392
00:24:46,520 --> 00:24:49,114
It won't happen again.

393
00:24:51,560 --> 00:24:55,235
We really need you to show us
where you got this, Harold.

394
00:24:56,080 --> 00:24:58,310
It's only safe on this side of the perimeter.

395
00:24:58,400 --> 00:25:02,518
Then just take us to the perimeter
and you point the rest of the way.

396
00:25:02,600 --> 00:25:03,669
No.

397
00:25:03,760 --> 00:25:08,356
Harold, those people you live with,
they depend on you.

398
00:25:08,960 --> 00:25:11,190
What about them?

399
00:25:11,280 --> 00:25:14,113
It's up to you to keep them safe.

400
00:25:16,720 --> 00:25:20,235
You know, you don't have to live down here.
There are alternatives.

401
00:25:20,320 --> 00:25:22,390
No, not for me.

402
00:25:23,440 --> 00:25:26,193
You're hiding.
You have to face your demons.

403
00:25:26,280 --> 00:25:32,310
Living here, this is the only way I can pay so
I won't have to go to hell for what I've done.

404
00:25:32,400 --> 00:25:34,868
There are programmes
that help people like you.

405
00:25:34,960 --> 00:25:36,837
- "People like me"?
- Mentally ill.

406
00:25:36,920 --> 00:25:40,913
Bones, simmer down. You might want to
just sidle up to the issue a little easier.

407
00:25:41,000 --> 00:25:46,120
I like it. Someone's honest, says the truth.
You don't lie, I guess.

408
00:25:46,200 --> 00:25:49,351
No, I don't lie. Agent Booth and I
would be glad to help you.

409
00:25:49,440 --> 00:25:51,908
- This is as far as I go.
- It doesn't have to be that way.

410
00:25:52,000 --> 00:25:55,231
He means it's the perimeter.
This is as far as he agreed to take us.

411
00:25:55,320 --> 00:25:58,118
Beyond this, it's not safe.

412
00:25:58,200 --> 00:26:02,512
<i>(Bones)</i> OK, how much farther
to where you found the medallion?

413
00:26:02,600 --> 00:26:06,115
- You'll see. It's down there.
- You stay here.

414
00:26:06,200 --> 00:26:08,998
Between one soldier to another,
you got my back?

415
00:26:09,080 --> 00:26:11,469
I never left my men.

416
00:26:37,000 --> 00:26:41,949
Cave-in. Dead end.
We came all the way down here for nothing.

417
00:26:49,360 --> 00:26:51,749
Not quite.

418
00:26:59,280 --> 00:27:01,555
This is a very old skeleton.

419
00:27:01,640 --> 00:27:03,790
Male, mid-30s.

420
00:27:03,880 --> 00:27:06,678
There's no clothing
because it simply rotted away.

421
00:27:06,760 --> 00:27:09,513
Buttons. Bone for the shirt,
pewter for the pants.

422
00:27:09,600 --> 00:27:14,230
Brass eyelets for the boots,
a belt buckle - also pewter.

423
00:27:14,320 --> 00:27:18,518
This is a half-inch button
from the Union Army Corps of Engineers.

424
00:27:18,600 --> 00:27:20,318
By Union Army, you mean...

425
00:27:20,400 --> 00:27:21,992
- Civil War.
- <i>(whistles)</i>

426
00:27:22,080 --> 00:27:25,550
Plus the fact that Hodgins found
diamond dust on this skeleton too,

427
00:27:25,640 --> 00:27:29,076
I think Marni Hunter was killed
in a Civil War-era tunnel.

428
00:27:29,160 --> 00:27:31,958
These pellets are commonly known
as birdshot.

429
00:27:32,040 --> 00:27:35,874
Pellet size 12,
0.73 inches in diameter, made of lead.

430
00:27:35,960 --> 00:27:37,473
Also Civil War vintage.

431
00:27:37,560 --> 00:27:42,429
The spread pattern suggests not a shotgun
but a muzzle-Ioaded pistol like a LeMat.

432
00:27:42,520 --> 00:27:46,195
- If you don't mind some conjecture.
- You're the boss.

433
00:27:46,280 --> 00:27:49,192
This fellow knew where
something of value was stored.

434
00:27:49,280 --> 00:27:51,999
Came down with an accomplice.

435
00:27:52,440 --> 00:27:56,638
I apologise. I've been hanging around Booth
way too much.

436
00:27:56,720 --> 00:27:59,553
It's a valid hypothesis.
No doubt one of many.

437
00:27:59,640 --> 00:28:02,234
They argued.
One killed the other for the treasure.

438
00:28:02,320 --> 00:28:06,074
Doesrt that mean the vault will be empty
when we find it?

439
00:28:06,160 --> 00:28:08,116
Oh, my God. They got me too.

440
00:28:08,200 --> 00:28:12,637
If the vault had been looted years ago,
the artefacts would've surfaced, been sold off.

441
00:28:12,720 --> 00:28:14,312
It must still be down there.

442
00:28:14,400 --> 00:28:18,473
I'll pull all the city plans
from the mid-19th century to the present.

443
00:28:18,560 --> 00:28:22,439
We have to save what we can. Is there
any way to discover who these bastards are?

444
00:28:22,520 --> 00:28:25,273
Zack, take a cast of Marni Hunter's skull.

445
00:28:25,360 --> 00:28:28,272
See if we can be specific
about the murder weapon.

446
00:28:31,320 --> 00:28:34,153
Harold could give you enough
for a sketch of the blonde.

447
00:28:34,240 --> 00:28:37,550
You said he was suspicious.
What if I can't get him to trust me?

448
00:28:37,640 --> 00:28:41,918
- You're nervous.
- I'm not nervous. I'm scared.

449
00:28:42,000 --> 00:28:45,436
I don't know how to talk to crazy people.
Unless I'm dating them.

450
00:28:45,520 --> 00:28:47,988
I'm not sure he's actually clinically insane.

451
00:28:48,080 --> 00:28:50,833
I don't know how to talk to people
who live underground

452
00:28:50,920 --> 00:28:53,309
and who might've tossed
a filmmaker down a hole.

453
00:28:53,400 --> 00:28:56,198
Just be honest with him, Ange.

454
00:28:56,280 --> 00:28:59,955
Treat him with respect. You're good at that.

455
00:29:09,720 --> 00:29:12,188
You're scared of me.

456
00:29:13,200 --> 00:29:15,589
- Yes.
- Why?

457
00:29:15,680 --> 00:29:17,875
You live underground.

458
00:29:18,680 --> 00:29:21,592
Yes. I find it very bright up here.

459
00:29:45,840 --> 00:29:47,956
How does this work?

460
00:29:48,040 --> 00:29:49,632
Um...

461
00:29:49,720 --> 00:29:53,030
You tell me what the blonde looks like
and I draw her.

462
00:29:53,120 --> 00:29:55,236
Like, height, weight, hair colour?

463
00:29:55,320 --> 00:29:58,232
Yeah, yeah, but... more.

464
00:29:58,960 --> 00:30:01,030
More?

465
00:30:01,120 --> 00:30:03,395
Yes. You know, how she seemed to you.

466
00:30:03,960 --> 00:30:07,475
You know, your, uh... your impressions.

467
00:30:09,280 --> 00:30:11,669
Her eyes are dead.

468
00:30:11,760 --> 00:30:14,991
She sees you and doesn't at the same time.

469
00:30:15,080 --> 00:30:17,310
- You mean like that?
- Yeah.

470
00:30:21,120 --> 00:30:23,236
Her mouth was small.

471
00:30:24,240 --> 00:30:28,518
Stern. Little... lip line.

472
00:30:33,080 --> 00:30:35,878
Mould filled in
the missing sections of the skull.

473
00:30:35,960 --> 00:30:39,669
It shows the entry point of the injury
has a very distinctive shape.

474
00:30:39,760 --> 00:30:42,194
Enlarge the image.

475
00:30:43,400 --> 00:30:47,996
It's a T. It's not a knife or a hammer
that I've seen before.

476
00:30:48,080 --> 00:30:52,073
Make a list of possible implements
using the size and force of the damage.

477
00:30:52,920 --> 00:30:56,037
Marni's fiancé found
some raw footage of her documentary.

478
00:30:56,120 --> 00:30:58,315
<i>A dark labyrinth.</i>

479
00:30:58,400 --> 00:31:01,153
<i>A warren of tunnels and fissures,</i>

480
00:31:01,240 --> 00:31:04,789
<i>forgotten coal cellars,</i>
<i>sewer lines, storm drains,</i>

481
00:31:04,880 --> 00:31:09,317
<i>subbasements, access shafts,</i>
<i>easements and crawlspaces -</i>

482
00:31:09,400 --> 00:31:12,312
<i>some as old as the city itself.</i>

483
00:31:12,400 --> 00:31:15,870
Bones... I thought she worked alone.

484
00:31:15,960 --> 00:31:18,155
Who's running the camera?

485
00:31:18,240 --> 00:31:22,358
<i>... shelter, for a place to hide</i>
<i>from the evils of the world.</i>

486
00:31:22,880 --> 00:31:25,440
<i>Others are looking for treasure.</i>

487
00:31:25,520 --> 00:31:28,432
She might've started out
to make a documentary,

488
00:31:28,520 --> 00:31:31,956
but she wound up using Harold
so she could loot the treasure.

489
00:31:32,040 --> 00:31:34,759
Doesrt mean she deserves to die.

490
00:31:34,840 --> 00:31:36,717
<i>And who are these treasure hunters?</i>

491
00:31:36,800 --> 00:31:40,315
<i>Not the homeless,</i>
<i>who scrounge for bits of metal.</i>

492
00:31:40,400 --> 00:31:42,197
<i>Some are Civil War enthusiasts...</i>

493
00:31:42,280 --> 00:31:46,831
<i>And some are remarkably handsome</i>
<i>adventurers!</i>

494
00:31:47,640 --> 00:31:50,598
<i>I... am so sorry!</i>

495
00:31:50,680 --> 00:31:56,198
- They said they never went underground.
- Son of a bitches lied to us.

496
00:31:59,880 --> 00:32:03,873
The murder weapon is a sharp-edged
instrument with a handle. Not a hatchet.

497
00:32:03,960 --> 00:32:06,679
Those climbers haven't been
back to their apartment.

498
00:32:06,760 --> 00:32:10,469
- I think the weapon was a climbing axe.
- How about this?

499
00:32:10,560 --> 00:32:14,712
While exploring those tunnels with Marni,
the climbers find something valuable.

500
00:32:14,800 --> 00:32:18,873
Marni wants to put it in her film,
the climbers want to take it for themselves.

501
00:32:18,960 --> 00:32:20,552
Wham on the head, down the shaft.

502
00:32:20,640 --> 00:32:23,598
Logical to think they're there now,
emptying that vault.

503
00:32:23,680 --> 00:32:27,514
- That was a total bust.
- Harold couldn't provide a description?

504
00:32:27,600 --> 00:32:30,956
Yeah, he provided me
with a description all right.

505
00:32:31,040 --> 00:32:33,031
That's the blonde Harold keeps seeing?

506
00:32:33,120 --> 00:32:36,635
This is what happens when you ask
for information from the mentally ill.

507
00:32:36,720 --> 00:32:38,711
- Where did you get that?
- I drew it.

508
00:32:38,800 --> 00:32:41,598
That, Miss Montenegro, is a Raeburn.

509
00:32:41,680 --> 00:32:45,514
Sir Henry Raeburn
painted a number of these studies.

510
00:32:45,600 --> 00:32:48,831
Extremely rare now. Very valuable.

511
00:32:48,920 --> 00:32:51,559
There.

512
00:32:51,640 --> 00:32:53,631
Hm. Damn, I'm good.

513
00:32:53,720 --> 00:32:57,599
Miss Eleanor Urquhart,
painted in 1793 by Sir Henry Raeburn.

514
00:32:57,680 --> 00:33:01,309
- Missing since 1862. Worth over $200,000.
- <i>(whistles)</i>

515
00:33:01,400 --> 00:33:04,517
If Harold saw that,
he's seen the inside of the vault.

516
00:33:04,600 --> 00:33:06,397
- Let's go.
- <i>(Bones)</i> Booth!

517
00:33:06,480 --> 00:33:11,429
It's a labyrinth down there. You can't
blunder around in the dark looking for them.

518
00:33:11,520 --> 00:33:14,193
Maybe you won't have to.

519
00:33:14,760 --> 00:33:18,469
I entered modern and historical plans,
including shafts and tunnels,

520
00:33:18,560 --> 00:33:20,039
plus the newer schematics.

521
00:33:20,120 --> 00:33:23,908
There's also oral accounts
of tunnel construction and passages.

522
00:33:24,000 --> 00:33:27,231
Wow. All that exists under the city?

523
00:33:27,320 --> 00:33:29,356
Yes. What we can corroborate.

524
00:33:29,440 --> 00:33:33,991
Good point, Bones - you know,
not rushing off to find those guys.

525
00:33:34,080 --> 00:33:38,232
- <i>(Bones)</i> How accurate is this?
- Blue is modern. Near 100% accurate.

526
00:33:38,320 --> 00:33:41,153
- Yellow is historical.
- <i>(Goodman)</i> Estimate, 80%.

527
00:33:41,240 --> 00:33:46,519
Red represents less exact renderings from
stories, memoirs, accounts from city workers.

528
00:33:46,600 --> 00:33:50,559
If this treasure exists,
it probably exists in one of the red tunnels.

529
00:33:50,640 --> 00:33:55,077
That Civil War victim was near the cave-in.
Maybe the treasure's on the other side.

530
00:33:55,160 --> 00:33:58,152
Inductive, reductive or deductive?

531
00:33:58,800 --> 00:34:00,756
- Deductive.
- As you wish.

532
00:34:00,840 --> 00:34:05,152
Miss Montenegro, please remove all tunnels
containing power, cable or utility lines.

533
00:34:05,240 --> 00:34:10,109
- And fibre optics.
- Yes. Also steam tunnels and transit access?

534
00:34:13,080 --> 00:34:15,036
What about diamond dust?

535
00:34:15,120 --> 00:34:17,918
You said there was diamond dust
in the old tunnels.

536
00:34:18,000 --> 00:34:21,629
There was also diamond dust
on the Civil War guy.

537
00:34:21,720 --> 00:34:23,790
So, what? I'm not allowed to help now?

538
00:34:23,880 --> 00:34:27,429
- That's inductive logic.
- We agreed on deductive.

539
00:34:27,520 --> 00:34:31,798
Sorry. I'm just... you know,
trying to think outside your box.

540
00:34:37,320 --> 00:34:42,394
Can you indicate where we found Marni
Hunter's body, and the Civil War victim?

541
00:34:42,480 --> 00:34:45,597
<i>(Booth)</i> Cos if Marni was killed
near the treasure and moved,

542
00:34:45,680 --> 00:34:48,319
and Civil War guy
was murdered by his accomplice...

543
00:34:48,400 --> 00:34:49,833
Mm. Gotcha.

544
00:34:49,920 --> 00:34:52,514
Can you connect the two bodies?

545
00:34:57,840 --> 00:35:00,229
This one's the closest.

546
00:35:01,160 --> 00:35:05,039
- There's no way to get there.
- Can you put some more blue lines back?

547
00:35:06,200 --> 00:35:10,671
Just a guess. Just throwing it out there.
You know, sue me.

548
00:35:12,080 --> 00:35:15,959
And connect
where Marni Hunter's body was found.

549
00:35:16,040 --> 00:35:18,600
Somewhere along that line is the treasure.

550
00:35:18,680 --> 00:35:20,511
What's that blue line?

551
00:35:20,600 --> 00:35:22,795
Storm sewer. H15-B.

552
00:35:22,880 --> 00:35:25,075
The weapon was a Hank's climbing axe.

553
00:35:29,480 --> 00:35:31,516
This is a situation where I need a gun.

554
00:35:31,600 --> 00:35:35,275
We're gonna have six FBI Tac Team members
do the dirty work.

555
00:35:35,360 --> 00:35:37,794
We'll just watch. What's your 20, Tac Team 3?

556
00:35:37,880 --> 00:35:40,997
- <i>According to this map, we're with you.</i>
- They aren't with us.

557
00:35:41,080 --> 00:35:44,595
I realise that, Bones.
Re-orient, Tac Team 3.

558
00:35:44,680 --> 00:35:47,148
<i>Suggest you wait for rendezvous, Booth.</i>

559
00:35:47,240 --> 00:35:49,276
Ten-four, Tac Team 3.

560
00:35:49,360 --> 00:35:53,319
I bet Ticktock Team is here -
two levels above us.

561
00:35:53,400 --> 00:35:57,757
Don't call them Ticktock Team, OK?
They're Tac Team. It's short for "tactical".

562
00:35:57,840 --> 00:36:01,230
- Can I just have a gun until they get here?
<i>- (Booth sighs)</i>

563
00:36:01,320 --> 00:36:05,233
Here. It's not for shooting rats.
Or psychos with climbing axes.

564
00:36:05,320 --> 00:36:07,390
So, what do we do? Just wait?

565
00:36:07,480 --> 00:36:10,392
No. We just... reconnoitre.

566
00:36:10,480 --> 00:36:12,550
In.

567
00:36:16,640 --> 00:36:18,631
<i>(clatter)</i>

568
00:36:19,920 --> 00:36:22,912
Easy. Watch yourself.

569
00:36:23,000 --> 00:36:24,991
<i>(rats squeak)</i>

570
00:36:34,640 --> 00:36:37,234
<i>(Booth)</i> Wow. What have we got here?

571
00:36:37,320 --> 00:36:40,676
Tac Team 3, this is Booth. What's your six?

572
00:36:40,760 --> 00:36:42,239
<i>Stand by, Booth.</i>

573
00:36:42,320 --> 00:36:45,596
- They're lost.
- They're not lost.

574
00:36:52,680 --> 00:36:54,750
What's that - a lucky quarter?

575
00:36:54,840 --> 00:36:58,913
This could be the missing piece
from Marni Hunter's skull.

576
00:36:59,000 --> 00:37:00,513
OK.

577
00:37:00,600 --> 00:37:03,068
- Think she was killed here?
- It's plausible.

578
00:37:03,160 --> 00:37:05,469
Don't get all gushy on me.

579
00:37:05,560 --> 00:37:08,358
- Ticktock 3.
- <i>Did you just call us "Ticktock"?</i>

580
00:37:08,440 --> 00:37:11,352
Tac Team 3, stand by.

581
00:37:11,440 --> 00:37:12,839
<i>(clinking)</i>

582
00:37:12,920 --> 00:37:15,115
Do you hear that?

583
00:37:16,120 --> 00:37:18,111
Yeah.

584
00:37:26,680 --> 00:37:29,148
That's the blonde woman.

585
00:37:32,040 --> 00:37:35,715
- This is locked. We gotta get in there.
- Arert we waiting for Ticktock 3?

586
00:37:35,800 --> 00:37:40,510
They might not find us. If we go after them,
these guys'll go. I wanna catch 'em in the act.

587
00:37:40,600 --> 00:37:42,238
We can go in through here.

588
00:37:42,320 --> 00:37:47,189
We go in there, you are responsible for
whoever's on your left. Put your gun on him.

589
00:37:47,280 --> 00:37:50,829
- How'll I know whether to shoot?
- If you wonder whether to shoot, shoot.

590
00:37:50,920 --> 00:37:53,673
- Let you do the talking?
- I took that one for granted.

591
00:37:54,200 --> 00:37:58,239
- Maybe we should've brought bigger bags.
- <i>(laughs)</i>

592
00:38:01,080 --> 00:38:04,152
- FBI. Hands in the air.
- Yeah, hands in the air.

593
00:38:05,280 --> 00:38:09,034
- We're not armed.
- They don't shoot people for trespassing.

594
00:38:09,120 --> 00:38:12,351
They do for murder.
Put your hands on your head.

595
00:38:12,440 --> 00:38:15,591
- Do it.
- Murder? What murder?

596
00:38:15,680 --> 00:38:19,309
I'm throwing you restraints.
Put 'em on Duke. Now.

597
00:38:19,400 --> 00:38:22,437
- How can we climb out?
- Would you rather go out in body bags?

598
00:38:22,520 --> 00:38:25,353
- Put on the restraints!
- <i>(clears throat)</i>

599
00:38:25,440 --> 00:38:28,432
- Let you do the talking. Got it.
- You think we killed Marni?

600
00:38:28,520 --> 00:38:32,035
- She was killed with a climbing axe.
- Duke, sit down.

601
00:38:32,120 --> 00:38:37,672
Bones, gimme your gun. Take the restraints
out of my belt, put 'em on Kyle.

602
00:38:39,480 --> 00:38:41,596
Is that cocked? Cos where it's pointed...

603
00:38:41,680 --> 00:38:44,035
- You're safe.
- Killed with a climbing axe?

604
00:38:44,120 --> 00:38:48,238
She was gonna put this treasure in her
documentary. It would've cost you a fortune.

605
00:38:48,320 --> 00:38:51,073
So one of you killed her.
Who's left-handed?

606
00:38:51,160 --> 00:38:55,073
It's best to have this explanation
after the bad guys are incapacitated.

607
00:38:55,160 --> 00:38:57,230
Why? <i>(gasps)</i>

608
00:38:57,320 --> 00:38:59,959
You killed her for this?

609
00:39:01,120 --> 00:39:05,591
- That's why.
- I'll try to remember that for next time.

610
00:39:18,560 --> 00:39:23,429
You regained one of the great cultural finds
of the century - a glimpse of Civil War life.

611
00:39:23,520 --> 00:39:26,478
Marni wanted to document
the treasure, not steal it.

612
00:39:26,560 --> 00:39:29,472
So Duke killed her
and threw her down a bottomless pit.

613
00:39:29,560 --> 00:39:34,315
Kyle wasrt so innocent himself.
He hit Duke in the crypt with a candlestick.

614
00:39:34,400 --> 00:39:38,313
Kyle hit the Duke
with a candlestick in the crypt.

615
00:39:38,400 --> 00:39:41,039
That's very good. Very good.

616
00:39:41,120 --> 00:39:42,269
Right?

617
00:39:42,360 --> 00:39:44,476
What? What's the joke?

618
00:39:44,560 --> 00:39:47,313
Well...

619
00:39:47,400 --> 00:39:49,152
- Clue?
- What clue?

620
00:39:51,000 --> 00:39:53,594
- What clue?
- Unbelievable, Bones.

621
00:39:54,400 --> 00:39:57,278
- What's funny?
- I have no idea.

622
00:39:59,760 --> 00:40:02,035
Harold's being released.

623
00:40:02,680 --> 00:40:05,717
You found a place for him?

624
00:40:06,600 --> 00:40:09,160
Yes.

625
00:40:12,560 --> 00:40:15,028
♪ <i>It's made up of lonely moments</i>

626
00:40:15,120 --> 00:40:17,759
♪ <i>There was always a moment there</i>
<i>when I knew</i>

627
00:40:17,840 --> 00:40:23,153
- <i>(man)</i> Great to have you back here, man.
- <i>(man #2)</i> Good to see you, Harold.

628
00:40:23,240 --> 00:40:26,118
♪ <i>You always gave instalments</i>

629
00:40:26,200 --> 00:40:30,751
♪ <i>Always knew you concentrated and grew</i>

630
00:40:33,760 --> 00:40:36,593
♪ <i>And I believe in reinvention</i>

631
00:40:36,680 --> 00:40:41,470
♪ <i>Do you believe that life is holding the clue?</i>

632
00:40:44,760 --> 00:40:47,593
♪ <i>Take away all the lonely moments</i>

633
00:40:47,680 --> 00:40:52,151
♪ <i>Give me full communication with you</i>

634
00:40:55,400 --> 00:40:58,073
♪ <i>Your smile</i>

635
00:40:58,160 --> 00:41:00,390
♪ <i>Shine a little light</i>

636
00:41:00,480 --> 00:41:03,313
♪ <i>All right</i>

637
00:41:06,400 --> 00:41:08,630
♪ <i>And don't hide</i>

638
00:41:08,720 --> 00:41:11,029
♪ <i>Shine a little light</i>

639
00:41:11,480 --> 00:41:14,199
♪ <i>Give up on your pride</i>

640
00:41:17,280 --> 00:41:19,953
♪ <i>Do you believe in reinvention?</i>

641
00:41:20,040 --> 00:41:23,635
♪ <i>Do you believe that life is holding the clue?</i>

642
00:41:28,120 --> 00:41:30,953
♪ <i>Any way to face the silence</i>

643
00:41:31,040 --> 00:41:35,033
♪ <i>Any way to face the pain that kills you</i>

644
00:41:36,240 --> 00:41:38,470
♪ <i>And don't hide</i>

645
00:41:38,560 --> 00:41:41,199
♪ <i>Shine a little light</i>

646
00:41:41,280 --> 00:41:44,272
♪ <i>Give up on your pride</i>

647
00:42:05,960 --> 00:42:10,715
Visiontext Subtitles: Katherine Appleby

648
00:42:15,600 --> 00:42:16,919
What's that mean?

649
00:42:17,680 --> 00:42:19,671
ENGLISH SDH

