1
00:00:23,840 --> 00:00:27,628
<i>(cell phone rings)</i>

2
00:00:30,720 --> 00:00:33,393
<i>(speaking Arabic)</i>

3
00:00:43,240 --> 00:00:45,708
<i>(horns blaring)</i>

4
00:00:53,000 --> 00:00:54,877
<i>(cell phone rings)</i>

5
00:00:57,960 --> 00:01:01,316
<i>(phone continues ringing)</i>

6
00:01:14,480 --> 00:01:17,278
<i>(screaming)</i>

7
00:01:18,960 --> 00:01:20,871
<i>(sirens blaring)</i>

8
00:01:22,680 --> 00:01:24,432
Bones! Over here.

9
00:01:24,520 --> 00:01:28,229
- Where have you been?
- There's a lot going on here.

10
00:01:28,320 --> 00:01:31,312
They're with me.
Dr Temperance Brennan, Angela Montenegro.

11
00:01:31,400 --> 00:01:34,119
- I need ID.
- Check the list. Homeland Security.

12
00:01:34,200 --> 00:01:36,714
She's the forensic anthropologist.

13
00:01:36,800 --> 00:01:40,190
- They're clear.
- Thanks. Come on.

14
00:01:40,280 --> 00:01:44,193
- God, what's that smell?
- Burnt flesh. Are there a lot of injuries?

15
00:01:44,280 --> 00:01:47,113
Four known dead, 15 injured.

16
00:01:47,200 --> 00:01:48,599
Oh, my God.

17
00:01:52,080 --> 00:01:53,832
Details. Whatever you have.

18
00:01:53,920 --> 00:01:58,232
Not much. Middle Eastern man, mid-30s,
pulled up to the café and the carjust blew.

19
00:01:58,320 --> 00:02:02,154
Registered to Hamid Masruk, head of
the Arab-American Friendship League.

20
00:02:02,240 --> 00:02:05,630
- Why do you need me?
- <i>(agent)</i> We're hoping we're wrong.

21
00:02:05,720 --> 00:02:08,871
Masruk is a White House consultant
on Arab relations.

22
00:02:08,960 --> 00:02:11,030
Had lunch with the president last week.

23
00:02:11,120 --> 00:02:14,351
Agent Gibson, Homeland Security.
Dr Temperance Brennan, Angela Montenegro.

24
00:02:14,440 --> 00:02:18,115
If Masruk was involved,
we have a huge national security problem.

25
00:02:18,200 --> 00:02:22,591
Not to mention a very humiliated president.
The press is already running with this.

26
00:02:22,680 --> 00:02:27,231
- If you think I'm gonna alter my findings...
- Not at all. Maybe it's not Masruk.

27
00:02:27,320 --> 00:02:30,630
We need to be sure.
Booth says you're the best.

28
00:02:33,800 --> 00:02:38,191
I need gloves and masks for the retrieval
team, medical bags and vegetable oil.

29
00:02:38,280 --> 00:02:39,395
Vegetable oil?

30
00:02:39,480 --> 00:02:44,634
The oil will loosen the body parts stuck to
the metal, like a steak on a grill that sticks.

31
00:02:44,720 --> 00:02:46,073
It's OK. I trust you.

32
00:02:46,160 --> 00:02:50,870
- Should I photograph the scene?
- Focus on a 30-meter radius from the blast.

33
00:02:55,440 --> 00:02:57,556
OK to pick up?

34
00:03:03,680 --> 00:03:08,276
- It's OK to be upset.
- I wish this is the worst thing I'd seen.

35
00:03:08,360 --> 00:03:12,592
You know, uh...
I don't think I can... Sorry.

36
00:03:19,840 --> 00:03:23,276
- Well, if you can't either...
- No, I'm cool.

37
00:03:26,400 --> 00:03:28,470
Zack, I need two more evidence bags.

38
00:03:29,200 --> 00:03:32,351
Facial epidermis
and the fingertips are decimated.

39
00:03:32,440 --> 00:03:35,830
We can't ID anything from the flesh.
It's basically carbon.

40
00:03:35,920 --> 00:03:38,753
We're missing the lower left leg
and the lumbar spine.

41
00:03:38,840 --> 00:03:41,991
Here's C2 and the right ischium.

42
00:03:42,080 --> 00:03:45,709
Smokey had access to the president.
Why would he attack a café?

43
00:03:45,800 --> 00:03:47,836
- Smokey?
- It's how I deal with stress.

44
00:03:47,920 --> 00:03:53,199
Targeting everyday places causes panic.
The economy is crippled. It's Terrorism 101.

45
00:03:53,280 --> 00:03:55,555
Take the clothes,
see what you can find.

46
00:03:55,640 --> 00:04:00,316
Cologne, laundry detergent -
anything we can link to Masruk's home.

47
00:04:00,400 --> 00:04:04,518
- I'll grab particulates to ID the bomb.
- Isn't that the FBI's job?

48
00:04:04,600 --> 00:04:09,037
You trust the FBI? They'll suppress
whatever they need to cover their asses.

49
00:04:09,120 --> 00:04:10,519
A portion of the clavicle.

50
00:04:10,600 --> 00:04:11,953
- Are you listening?
- No.

51
00:04:12,040 --> 00:04:16,431
They have a separate division
so their hands are always clean. In 1970...

52
00:04:16,520 --> 00:04:19,557
Jack! We're trying to work.

53
00:04:19,640 --> 00:04:22,996
Someone seems really defensive
about the FBI lately.

54
00:04:23,080 --> 00:04:27,278
- Booth is just a government stooge.
- This has nothing to do with Booth.

55
00:04:27,360 --> 00:04:30,875
I don't enjoy squints on my team
any more than you like me on yours.

56
00:04:30,960 --> 00:04:34,396
But we're supposed to be
working together, OK?

57
00:04:34,480 --> 00:04:37,472
Sure. So, what do we do?
Group hug?

58
00:04:37,560 --> 00:04:41,792
- Agent Gibson here will oversee things.
- I'll try not to be in the way.

59
00:04:41,880 --> 00:04:44,519
- We don't need to be overseen.
- It's not your call.

60
00:04:44,600 --> 00:04:49,196
- How soon can we get the DNA match?
- That'll take days. I can get a match sooner.

61
00:04:49,280 --> 00:04:54,035
- You're gonna be able to ID him from that?
- Asking stuff like that <i>is</i> in the way.

62
00:04:54,120 --> 00:05:00,195
Remove any flesh and particulates and then
macerate him - if that's all right with you.

63
00:05:04,000 --> 00:05:07,754
Don't touch the table.
Don't touch the table.

64
00:05:09,080 --> 00:05:12,834
- This is my lab. I'm a scientist, a doctor.
- So I've heard.

65
00:05:12,920 --> 00:05:16,151
Could you work if someone
was looking over your shoulder?

66
00:05:16,240 --> 00:05:20,438
- I've developed a tolerance.
- I don't see the advantage of compromise.

67
00:05:20,520 --> 00:05:23,557
It's a terrorist attack.
It's bigger than you and me.

68
00:05:23,640 --> 00:05:26,234
- The job is the same.
- No, it's not!

69
00:05:26,320 --> 00:05:29,278
We're dealing with someone
who devalues a culture,

70
00:05:29,360 --> 00:05:32,511
terrorising people
by using God to justify mass murder.

71
00:05:32,600 --> 00:05:34,636
You're making it personal.

72
00:05:34,720 --> 00:05:38,952
It is personal, Bones.
All of us die a little bit on one like this.

73
00:05:46,080 --> 00:05:51,552
All the trace evidence has been stripped.
Hodgins scavenged as much as he could.

74
00:05:51,640 --> 00:05:53,995
OK. Let's get started.

75
00:06:00,720 --> 00:06:03,393
What the hell are those?

76
00:06:03,480 --> 00:06:06,836
<i>Dermestes maculatus.</i>

77
00:06:08,480 --> 00:06:13,838
Flesh-eating beetles.
It's how we clean the bones of burn victims.

78
00:06:16,440 --> 00:06:18,158
<i>(cell phone rings)</i>

79
00:06:22,760 --> 00:06:23,749
Gibson.

80
00:06:23,840 --> 00:06:25,910
- <i>This is the president.</i>
- Yes, sir.

81
00:06:26,000 --> 00:06:30,391
<i>- We need this ID. Make this a priority.</i>
- Yes, sir.

82
00:06:32,240 --> 00:06:35,835
The president wants to know
how long the ID's gonna take.

83
00:06:35,920 --> 00:06:38,434
Why don't you ask <i>them</i>?

84
00:07:23,280 --> 00:07:27,193
You have made a mistake.
It can't be my husband.

85
00:07:27,280 --> 00:07:32,479
My brother was no terrorist.
He hated those people. Read his speeches.

86
00:07:32,560 --> 00:07:36,394
- We aren't making any accusations.
- It's all over the news.

87
00:07:36,480 --> 00:07:38,471
We can't control the press.

88
00:07:38,560 --> 00:07:43,395
How about your men? They've searched
our house, talked to our friends.

89
00:07:43,480 --> 00:07:46,870
Until we can identify the body,
we have to investigate.

90
00:07:46,960 --> 00:07:49,030
So identify the body.

91
00:07:49,120 --> 00:07:52,715
The longer you wait...
Do you know what it's like for us?

92
00:07:52,800 --> 00:07:55,075
His body was fragmented by the blast.

93
00:07:55,160 --> 00:07:58,470
- We're still retrieving pieces...
<i>- (Booth raps table)</i>

94
00:08:01,560 --> 00:08:05,348
I understand how difficult this is,
not knowing.

95
00:08:05,440 --> 00:08:09,274
I'll work as quickly as I can
to get you what you need.

96
00:08:09,360 --> 00:08:13,797
That's why I asked for his history. Where
he grew up, any injuries from his youth,

97
00:08:13,880 --> 00:08:15,393
medical records.

98
00:08:15,480 --> 00:08:17,948
Of course.

99
00:08:18,040 --> 00:08:21,191
I brought you what you asked for.

100
00:08:21,280 --> 00:08:23,191
Thank you.

101
00:08:24,000 --> 00:08:26,195
We lived just like you.

102
00:08:26,280 --> 00:08:30,637
We came to this country because we love it.
We are Americans.

103
00:08:30,720 --> 00:08:33,678
It can't be Hamid. It can't.

104
00:08:35,680 --> 00:08:38,831
My husband was not a terrorist.

105
00:08:44,880 --> 00:08:47,872
It could be a perchlorate.
Would that be used in a bomb?

106
00:08:47,960 --> 00:08:52,351
Yeah, but this is a crystalline structure,
aluminum-based.

107
00:08:53,400 --> 00:08:56,312
OK, I'm back. How are we doing?

108
00:08:56,400 --> 00:09:00,359
I have his detergent brand, cologne,
shampoo. He died a well-groomed man.

109
00:09:00,440 --> 00:09:01,953
- Thanks.
- Dr Brennan...

110
00:09:02,040 --> 00:09:05,191
- The bones done yet?
- I'll check the beetles.

111
00:09:05,280 --> 00:09:06,918
Whatever you have there...

112
00:09:07,000 --> 00:09:10,675
It's a piece of paper with some writing on it.

113
00:09:18,280 --> 00:09:20,589
Hard at work?

114
00:09:20,680 --> 00:09:22,671
There's a shocker.

115
00:09:24,160 --> 00:09:26,151
I just saw his wife.

116
00:09:26,240 --> 00:09:30,028
She gave me his medical records,
photographs.

117
00:09:30,560 --> 00:09:34,439
Apparently he was ill.
They were testing for lupus.

118
00:09:34,520 --> 00:09:37,353
Which would explain the face.

119
00:09:37,440 --> 00:09:39,396
Must've been painful.

120
00:09:41,560 --> 00:09:43,994
Look, I...

121
00:09:44,080 --> 00:09:50,428
I know that you needed help out there
at the crime scene, and I wanted to, but...

122
00:09:50,520 --> 00:09:52,112
It's OK.

123
00:09:54,360 --> 00:10:00,310
You see it. I don't any more.
I don't know what's worse.

124
00:10:01,000 --> 00:10:03,070
You holding up OK?

125
00:10:04,080 --> 00:10:05,069
<i>(sighs)</i>

126
00:10:05,160 --> 00:10:10,154
His wife doesn't believe it was him.
I've gotta give her an ID.

127
00:10:10,240 --> 00:10:13,198
Whatever I can do.

128
00:10:13,280 --> 00:10:15,430
Yeah, I know.

129
00:10:15,520 --> 00:10:18,193
- And about this weekend...
- I don't know.

130
00:10:18,280 --> 00:10:22,239
Come on. I know this great club.
They play trip hop and trance.

131
00:10:22,320 --> 00:10:25,232
- I don't know what that means.
- We'll grab Booth.

132
00:10:25,320 --> 00:10:26,992
- No.
- I think he likes you.

133
00:10:27,080 --> 00:10:29,355
If I were you, I'd buy a ticket on that ride.

134
00:10:29,440 --> 00:10:33,353
I'll be busy this weekend.
Even after the ID, I have these.

135
00:10:33,440 --> 00:10:34,953
Remains from World War I?

136
00:10:35,040 --> 00:10:38,350
That's what the Institute pays me for.
I've got hundreds of these.

137
00:10:38,440 --> 00:10:41,557
And they can't wait one more weekend?

138
00:10:41,640 --> 00:10:45,315
They've got relatives.
They've waited long enough.

139
00:10:45,400 --> 00:10:47,516
It's not that scary, Brennan.

140
00:10:47,600 --> 00:10:50,717
You have a few drinks,
you move to the music.

141
00:10:50,800 --> 00:10:53,360
You might even smile.

142
00:10:53,440 --> 00:10:55,317
<i>(knocking)</i>

143
00:10:55,400 --> 00:10:57,470
The bones are clean.

144
00:10:57,560 --> 00:11:02,076
I've gotta run.
You hang around. I may need you.

145
00:11:04,840 --> 00:11:09,755
Comparing remains to details
provided of Hamid Masruk.

146
00:11:09,840 --> 00:11:13,628
Age 37, of Afghani origin.

147
00:11:13,720 --> 00:11:19,636
Texture of pubic symphysis indicates age
of bone consistent with Masruk, as is height.

148
00:11:19,720 --> 00:11:25,113
Complexity of cranial vault sutures matches
the statistical probability of Eurasian descent.

149
00:11:25,200 --> 00:11:29,432
Too bad we can't tell why he did it.
Isn't that what we all want to know?

150
00:11:29,520 --> 00:11:34,150
Uneven growth patterns in the vertebrae
indicate malnourishment as a child.

151
00:11:34,240 --> 00:11:39,234
Consistent with the diet where Masruk
was from. Probably evident on the calvarium?

152
00:11:39,320 --> 00:11:42,153
Why don't you reconstruct the skull,
check it out.

153
00:11:42,240 --> 00:11:45,118
My first cranial reconstruction.

154
00:11:46,280 --> 00:11:50,239
Evidence of multiple fractures
to the bottoms of the feet.

155
00:11:50,320 --> 00:11:57,271
Consistent with methods of torture used
in Afghanistan and with Masruk's history.

156
00:11:57,360 --> 00:12:00,830
I'm convinced. We have a statistical match.

157
00:12:00,920 --> 00:12:03,354
- So Masruk is the bomber?
- Yes.

158
00:12:03,440 --> 00:12:09,072
- What about the skull he's reconstructing?
- He wants to learn. Is that OK with you?

159
00:12:09,160 --> 00:12:14,109
For a forensic ID, we have all we need.
Now I'd like to get this data to Booth.

160
00:12:14,200 --> 00:12:16,589
- I'll take it.
- No, I don't think so.

161
00:12:16,680 --> 00:12:18,989
I work with Booth. That's my deal.

162
00:12:19,080 --> 00:12:21,196
Dr Brennan, I have jurisdiction.

163
00:12:21,280 --> 00:12:26,638
Then why don't I destroy my notes and let
<i>you</i> guarantee the identity of the remains?

164
00:12:28,600 --> 00:12:33,435
It's best to just ride it out... like an earthquake.

165
00:12:34,880 --> 00:12:36,871
<i>(knock on door)</i>

166
00:12:41,000 --> 00:12:43,036
- Bones.
- Yeah.

167
00:12:43,120 --> 00:12:45,998
- Did we have an appointment?
- No. I...

168
00:12:46,080 --> 00:12:49,834
It's him. Masruk is the bomber.

169
00:12:53,760 --> 00:12:57,309
I guess the wife didn't know
the husband very well.

170
00:12:57,400 --> 00:12:58,992
Hey.

171
00:13:01,520 --> 00:13:03,431
Hi. Sorry.

172
00:13:03,520 --> 00:13:07,035
Tessa, this is Brennan.
Tessa Jankow, Dr Temperance Brennan.

173
00:13:07,120 --> 00:13:08,917
Oh, hi.

174
00:13:09,000 --> 00:13:12,072
- I've heard a lot about you.
- Really?

175
00:13:13,720 --> 00:13:17,998
- Tessa's an attorney.
- Corporate. Keeping the fat cats fat.

176
00:13:18,080 --> 00:13:24,428
I was studying a cranial fissure on a corporate
attorney last week. Of course, he was... dead.

177
00:13:24,520 --> 00:13:27,398
- Interesting.
- Thanks.

178
00:13:29,080 --> 00:13:31,514
<i>(zipping)</i>

179
00:13:31,600 --> 00:13:36,515
The Bureau. I was just heading there. Santana
called, said something about the bombing.

180
00:13:36,600 --> 00:13:40,275
And I thought you were at the lab.
Maybe you should come.

181
00:13:40,360 --> 00:13:43,397
- Sure.
- See you later?

182
00:13:51,440 --> 00:13:55,149
- What is so funny?
- I never figured you'd be in a relationship.

183
00:13:55,240 --> 00:13:56,719
Why? What's wrong with me?

184
00:13:56,800 --> 00:14:01,999
Not wrong. You have alpha-male attributes
associated with a solitary existence.

185
00:14:02,080 --> 00:14:05,550
- Me? <i>You're</i> solitary.
- We werert talking about me.

186
00:14:05,640 --> 00:14:08,200
- I was.
- I wasrt. Look, I'm happy for you.

187
00:14:08,280 --> 00:14:12,796
Relationships have anthropological meaning.
No society can survive if sexual bonds...

188
00:14:12,880 --> 00:14:16,634
- What the hell are you talking about?
- Booth? You got that ID?

189
00:14:16,720 --> 00:14:19,871
- Yeah. It was Masruk.
- That's too bad.

190
00:14:19,960 --> 00:14:24,875
- He killed four people and injured 15.
- The report came back from Ballistics.

191
00:14:24,960 --> 00:14:28,953
The explosives were under the car
with a trigger connected to the odometer.

192
00:14:29,040 --> 00:14:32,112
- Masruk was murdered.
- So Masruk wasrt a terrorist.

193
00:14:32,200 --> 00:14:35,317
Somebody tried to make him
look like one. Any leads on who?

194
00:14:35,400 --> 00:14:38,676
That's why we're paying you, Booth.

195
00:14:45,000 --> 00:14:47,514
We're very sorry, Mrs Masruk.

196
00:14:47,600 --> 00:14:53,470
I told you Hamid was the victim,
but you couldn't imagine a peace-Ioving Arab.

197
00:14:53,560 --> 00:14:55,471
- That's not true.
- No?

198
00:14:55,560 --> 00:15:01,112
"We must investigate everything because
we believe your husband was a good man."

199
00:15:01,200 --> 00:15:02,553
Is that the truth?

200
00:15:02,640 --> 00:15:06,918
No. They searched your house because
Muslim extremists declared war on the US.

201
00:15:07,000 --> 00:15:10,037
Preliminary findings
made your husband a suspect...

202
00:15:10,120 --> 00:15:13,635
It's not Bureau policy
to target or profile any ethnic group.

203
00:15:13,720 --> 00:15:17,190
It wasrt our intention.
We understand why you're offended.

204
00:15:17,280 --> 00:15:18,315
- I can't.
- Bones!

205
00:15:18,400 --> 00:15:22,154
What? She's been a part
of a criminal investigation.

206
00:15:22,240 --> 00:15:26,358
It's unfortunate
her husband's ethnicity is a factor,

207
00:15:26,440 --> 00:15:28,556
but to say it isn't is disingenuous.

208
00:15:28,640 --> 00:15:35,239
- I have to apologise for Dr Brennan.
- It's fine. Honesty is always a welcome relief.

209
00:15:36,040 --> 00:15:39,510
So when can I bury him?
When can I give him peace?

210
00:15:39,600 --> 00:15:43,991
There are body parts I'm still examining.
Others are still seared to...

211
00:15:44,080 --> 00:15:47,516
I'm sure Mrs Masruk
doesn't need to know the details.

212
00:15:47,600 --> 00:15:53,277
If I can retrieve more remains of her husband,
Muslim law requires that I do.

213
00:15:53,360 --> 00:15:58,354
I spent some time in Iraq identifying bodies.

214
00:15:58,440 --> 00:16:04,959
I'll give you whatever I can
so that he can be purified for burial.

215
00:16:05,040 --> 00:16:07,759
Thank you.

216
00:16:07,840 --> 00:16:09,990
Is that all?

217
00:16:10,080 --> 00:16:14,153
One last thing. A few calls
were made to his cell phone

218
00:16:14,240 --> 00:16:16,754
from your house minutes before the blast.

219
00:16:16,840 --> 00:16:22,153
Yes. We argued. It was a family matter.

220
00:16:22,240 --> 00:16:26,791
My final words to him were words of anger.

221
00:16:26,880 --> 00:16:30,236
I'm very sorry. It must be very painful.

222
00:16:30,320 --> 00:16:33,676
You look very happy in that picture.

223
00:16:33,760 --> 00:16:36,069
Yes.

224
00:16:37,680 --> 00:16:43,630
Thank you. If there's anything else
that you can think of, just give us a call.

225
00:16:46,760 --> 00:16:49,115
I think she's having an affair...

226
00:16:50,680 --> 00:16:52,750
personally.

227
00:16:53,280 --> 00:16:57,353
- She was having an affair.
- That's an offensive assumption.

228
00:16:57,440 --> 00:16:58,953
All the signs are there.

229
00:16:59,040 --> 00:17:02,271
You can't make wild accusations
based on a feeling.

230
00:17:02,360 --> 00:17:08,276
That photograph is evidence as solid as
the markers you pick up looking at bones.

231
00:17:08,360 --> 00:17:12,433
The evidence I find is empirical.
Your evidence is conjecture.

232
00:17:12,520 --> 00:17:18,755
She dyed her hair, lost weight, used Botox.
She's still feeling guilty over their last fight.

233
00:17:18,840 --> 00:17:23,038
You are an insufferable, arrogant... man!

234
00:17:23,120 --> 00:17:26,908
I thought women wanted us
to understand them.

235
00:17:27,000 --> 00:17:29,833
A magician never wants to reveal her tricks.

236
00:17:29,920 --> 00:17:31,831
- This is private.
- I'm not here.

237
00:17:31,920 --> 00:17:35,833
You think you know women just because
you live with some sexy lawyer?

238
00:17:35,920 --> 00:17:39,037
- You live with a sexy lawyer?
- She has her own place.

239
00:17:39,120 --> 00:17:43,159
He thinks because Masruk's wife
had a makeover, she was having an affair.

240
00:17:43,240 --> 00:17:46,755
- I'm with him.
- There is no concrete proof.

241
00:17:46,840 --> 00:17:48,319
- Boobs perkier?
- Mm-hm.

242
00:17:48,400 --> 00:17:51,278
If you're so sure,
why didn't you confront her?

243
00:17:51,360 --> 00:17:53,828
If her boyfriend were involved,
she'd warn him.

244
00:17:53,920 --> 00:17:56,639
- Very good.
- I'm a constant surprise.

245
00:17:56,720 --> 00:18:01,475
All right, great. I will be in the lab
getting us some real data.

246
00:18:01,560 --> 00:18:06,554
So, how many nights a week
does "sexy" sleep over?

247
00:18:14,240 --> 00:18:17,949
- How is it coming?
- The fragments won't piece together.

248
00:18:18,040 --> 00:18:21,237
I'd like to return the remains to the widow
before <i>her</i> demise.

249
00:18:21,320 --> 00:18:27,668
I'm doing my best. The integrity of the bone
is compromised. Whether it's from the blast...

250
00:18:27,760 --> 00:18:30,558
I examined the chemicals
used in the explosives.

251
00:18:30,640 --> 00:18:32,790
They can have a degenerative effect.

252
00:18:32,880 --> 00:18:35,758
Not this quickly. Excuse me.

253
00:18:39,720 --> 00:18:44,157
Unusually soft bone tissue.
This has nothing to do with the blast.

254
00:18:44,240 --> 00:18:47,357
I owe you an apology, Zack.
Do you have his medicals?

255
00:18:51,840 --> 00:18:55,594
Stiffjoints, facial disfigurement.

256
00:18:55,680 --> 00:18:59,036
There's a trabecular pattern
his doctors couldn't have seen.

257
00:18:59,120 --> 00:19:00,872
Could be a degenerative disease.

258
00:19:00,960 --> 00:19:03,679
How does his condition
figure into the murder?

259
00:19:03,760 --> 00:19:09,198
Now it's a murder. Before, it was terrorism
because we didn't have all the facts.

260
00:19:09,280 --> 00:19:11,271
Check for lupus and Paget's.

261
00:19:11,360 --> 00:19:13,351
- Got enough tissue?
- I can manage.

262
00:19:13,440 --> 00:19:18,434
He might've been exposed to a toxin,
which would mean his brother was, too.

263
00:19:18,520 --> 00:19:22,911
He's exhibiting similar symptoms.
I'll get the brother's medicals.

264
00:19:23,000 --> 00:19:25,992
I graduated top of my class, Rhodes scholar,

265
00:19:26,080 --> 00:19:28,719
youngest in the Academy
of Physical Sciences,

266
00:19:28,800 --> 00:19:30,916
but she still makes me feel like a cretin.

267
00:19:31,000 --> 00:19:32,752
She apologised to me.

268
00:19:41,600 --> 00:19:44,114
Yes, I am a Christian.

269
00:19:44,200 --> 00:19:48,671
- And Hamid is Muslim. And Sahar?
- I converted.

270
00:19:48,760 --> 00:19:53,276
Hamid could never accept it. Religious
differences cause too many problems.

271
00:19:53,360 --> 00:19:56,670
It seems to be
a consistent fact throughout history.

272
00:19:56,760 --> 00:19:58,432
Please.

273
00:19:59,400 --> 00:20:02,836
I tried to make peace with my brother,
but it was difficult.

274
00:20:02,920 --> 00:20:05,229
There was more than religion between us.

275
00:20:05,320 --> 00:20:09,996
- Sahar mentioned some family problems.
- Yes.

276
00:20:10,080 --> 00:20:15,916
- I can understand how delicate that can be.
- Did she tell you any more than that?

277
00:20:16,000 --> 00:20:22,473
No. But if you have any other information
that could help us in the investigation...

278
00:20:22,560 --> 00:20:23,754
It's not my place.

279
00:20:23,840 --> 00:20:27,879
We're just trying to find out
who killed your brother.

280
00:20:30,760 --> 00:20:35,197
Sahar was seeing another man.
But I can't believe she'd hurt my brother.

281
00:20:35,280 --> 00:20:39,273
Do you know who this other man is,
or is itjust a feeling you have?

282
00:20:39,360 --> 00:20:44,593
I've met him. Ali Ladjavardi. He worked
with Hamid at the Friendship League.

283
00:20:44,680 --> 00:20:46,875
I wanted Hamid to confront Ladjavardi.

284
00:20:46,960 --> 00:20:51,875
- Did you both have contact with Ladjavardi?
- Yes, once. A meal.

285
00:20:51,960 --> 00:20:55,999
I brought Hamid to meet him.
Sharing a meal is a gesture of peace.

286
00:20:56,080 --> 00:21:01,438
I was trying to save their marriage.
But they were not gonna stop their affair.

287
00:21:01,520 --> 00:21:05,069
- So I told Hamid to repudiate her.
- Sorry?

288
00:21:05,160 --> 00:21:08,152
In Muslim law
it's a method of divorce called <i>talak</i>.

289
00:21:08,240 --> 00:21:10,231
I still respected his traditions.

290
00:21:10,320 --> 00:21:14,836
You and your brother seem
to share a medical condition.

291
00:21:15,760 --> 00:21:17,910
Yes. Why is that important?

292
00:21:18,000 --> 00:21:22,790
She's just trying to figure out the condition.
It's part of the investigation.

293
00:21:22,880 --> 00:21:24,996
- Have you seen a doctor?
- Yes.

294
00:21:25,080 --> 00:21:29,870
He believes it's genetic. He was gonna
call Hamid's physician to discuss it.

295
00:21:29,960 --> 00:21:32,633
Would you mind if we saw
your medical records?

296
00:21:32,720 --> 00:21:37,635
Of course not.
If I could be helped, I welcome it.

297
00:21:43,320 --> 00:21:47,029
Apparently they live together
a few days a week.

298
00:21:47,120 --> 00:21:49,793
But he was very clear
that she has her own place.

299
00:21:49,880 --> 00:21:53,270
- Should you be intruding into their lives?
- Yeah. Absolutely.

300
00:21:53,360 --> 00:21:57,592
Negative for lupus and Paget's. I'll do
a scraping for environmental contaminants.

301
00:21:57,680 --> 00:22:01,275
I found these -
flecks caught onto the torn edges of bone.

302
00:22:01,360 --> 00:22:06,559
- I still think Brennan has a shot with Booth.
- She says she's not interested.

303
00:22:06,640 --> 00:22:10,997
- Methinks the lady doth protest too much.
- Maybe she protesteth just enough.

304
00:22:11,080 --> 00:22:14,072
Please. She's been sleeping alone for months.

305
00:22:14,160 --> 00:22:18,073
She has enough pent-up sexual energy
to power a small Midwestern city.

306
00:22:18,160 --> 00:22:22,551
This looks like gypsum.
It wouldn't cause any organic damage.

307
00:22:22,640 --> 00:22:25,950
It was probably used
to insulate the explosives.

308
00:22:26,040 --> 00:22:28,793
I bet the FBI doesn't know that yet.

309
00:22:28,880 --> 00:22:33,192
I'm gonna go check out this girlfriend.

310
00:22:36,720 --> 00:22:42,431
<i>I'm not proud of the affair. I admired Hamid.</i>
<i>But Sahar and I are in love. I can't change it.</i>

311
00:22:42,520 --> 00:22:45,193
- You had access to his car.
- That's ridiculous.

312
00:22:45,280 --> 00:22:49,910
You also had contact with his brother,
who said you werert friendly with Hamid.

313
00:22:50,000 --> 00:22:54,278
Have you been in the middle of a messy
relationship? Or are you a perfect man?

314
00:22:54,360 --> 00:22:59,195
- I'd prefer to ask the questions.
- I have the right to an attorney.

315
00:22:59,280 --> 00:23:03,193
Of course. I would never
deny anyone his rights.

316
00:23:03,840 --> 00:23:05,751
Mr Ladjavardi?

317
00:23:05,840 --> 00:23:10,277
I'm Agent Santana. We're sorry for
the inconvenience. You're free to go.

318
00:23:10,360 --> 00:23:11,554
Thank you.

319
00:23:13,800 --> 00:23:16,360
- You're finished.
- He was a prime suspect.

320
00:23:16,440 --> 00:23:20,433
He's a mole for Homeland Security.
They planted him in the League.

321
00:23:20,520 --> 00:23:22,112
He admitted the affair.

322
00:23:22,200 --> 00:23:24,555
<i>Homeland Security says he's clean.</i>

323
00:23:24,640 --> 00:23:27,996
- They do not want his cover blown.
- But, sir...

324
00:23:28,080 --> 00:23:31,629
Do I look like I'm discussing this?

325
00:23:41,160 --> 00:23:43,151
<i>(horn blaring)</i>

326
00:23:43,240 --> 00:23:45,470
- Come on.
- You want me to drive?

327
00:23:45,560 --> 00:23:49,473
- No. Why?
- You're angry.

328
00:23:49,560 --> 00:23:52,677
- I'm not angry.
- You're gonna kill somebody.

329
00:23:52,760 --> 00:23:56,230
I'm not angry. Believe me,
you do not want to see me angry.

330
00:23:56,320 --> 00:24:00,074
- This is me accepting reality.
- OK. My mistake.

331
00:24:00,160 --> 00:24:05,518
My superiors make the decisions. If they don't
think them through, that's not my problem.

332
00:24:05,600 --> 00:24:10,754
If I were you, I'd be mad. They're preventing
you from doing a proper investigation.

333
00:24:10,840 --> 00:24:14,116
I'm a grown-up. I'll deal.

334
00:24:14,200 --> 00:24:18,751
You know the thing where you ask for
the strength to change the things that you can

335
00:24:18,840 --> 00:24:21,673
and the wisdom to know the difference?

336
00:24:21,760 --> 00:24:24,354
- Not really.
- Well, it's a good thing.

337
00:24:24,440 --> 00:24:26,158
- Who do you ask?
- For what?

338
00:24:26,240 --> 00:24:30,597
- For the strength and the wisdom.
- God.

339
00:24:30,680 --> 00:24:34,195
- And it works?
- Can we talk about something else?

340
00:24:34,280 --> 00:24:37,113
- Sure. Tessa?
- No. Why do you want to talk about Tessa?

341
00:24:37,200 --> 00:24:39,998
Why not? I'm sorry.
We won't talk about Tessa.

342
00:24:40,080 --> 00:24:44,710
I prefer if we just talk about things
you like to talk about, like dead bodies.

343
00:24:44,800 --> 00:24:48,031
Sure. You killed a lot of people
when you were a sniper?

344
00:24:48,120 --> 00:24:50,759
- Maybe we shouldn't talk.
- Cos you're angry.

345
00:24:50,840 --> 00:24:53,593
I'm not angry. I'm not.

346
00:24:55,440 --> 00:25:01,436
We'll find out who killed him, Booth.
We've got Hamid's body.

347
00:25:04,040 --> 00:25:06,600
You can always count on the dead.

348
00:25:09,080 --> 00:25:11,878
I want the brother's medicals
matched to Hamid's.

349
00:25:11,960 --> 00:25:13,871
I'm starting on a tox screen.

350
00:25:13,960 --> 00:25:19,034
The doctor suspected a genetic condition.
Are we overlooking something? What's that?

351
00:25:19,120 --> 00:25:23,591
We used the trace elements to
rebuild the bomb. It might give you a link.

352
00:25:23,680 --> 00:25:27,070
- Isn't the FBI working on that?
- Yes. This is just for fun.

353
00:25:27,160 --> 00:25:30,869
- To see who's better?
- Maybe. A little. Yeah.

354
00:25:30,960 --> 00:25:34,191
- Good luck.
- ♪ Ta-da.

355
00:25:34,280 --> 00:25:36,271
Nice job.

356
00:25:40,840 --> 00:25:45,311
No wonder you had such trouble.
Look at the spread of the trabecular pattern.

357
00:25:45,400 --> 00:25:48,437
- Microscopic fissures, like cracks.
- I knew that.

358
00:25:48,520 --> 00:25:50,715
- I don't think so.
- Can we focus?

359
00:25:50,800 --> 00:25:55,635
The spread is too rapid for any bone disease
or genetic condition. It's definitely a toxin.

360
00:25:55,720 --> 00:25:59,793
- Is there any surviving marrow to test?
- I'll try and find some.

361
00:25:59,880 --> 00:26:01,871
Let's do it.

362
00:26:26,640 --> 00:26:28,631
<i>(mute dialogue)</i>

363
00:26:47,560 --> 00:26:50,518
The marrow's degraded.
I can give you basics.

364
00:26:50,600 --> 00:26:55,799
- The liver function was impaired.
- His body was trying to get rid of the poison.

365
00:26:55,880 --> 00:26:59,634
- There is trouble in paradise.
- I beg your pardon?

366
00:26:59,720 --> 00:27:02,234
Tessa does not feel secure
in that relationship.

367
00:27:02,320 --> 00:27:04,675
- She's threatened by you.
- You talked to her?

368
00:27:04,760 --> 00:27:09,880
Even though she has a phenomenal figure,
she was chowing down on a fat-free muffin.

369
00:27:09,960 --> 00:27:15,956
And she was reading a book about unsolved
FBI cases. She's obviously feeling insecure.

370
00:27:16,040 --> 00:27:18,554
- She's spying for you?
- No! No.

371
00:27:18,640 --> 00:27:23,270
It's difficult to sublimate
intense sexual attraction.

372
00:27:23,360 --> 00:27:25,794
- And we hear it's been a while.
- OK, stop.

373
00:27:25,880 --> 00:27:31,477
- He is there for the taking, honey.
- OK, I couldn't get his medical records.

374
00:27:33,480 --> 00:27:36,040
- What?
- Uh, nothing.

375
00:27:36,120 --> 00:27:40,955
- Trying to track down the doctor?
- It's a toxin. We can't determine what kind.

376
00:27:41,040 --> 00:27:44,191
Too bad the liver is cooked.
That could tell us everything.

377
00:27:44,280 --> 00:27:46,077
I need subtitles in here.

378
00:27:46,160 --> 00:27:50,551
The liver is like a filter. It would contain
evidence of any toxins in his system.

379
00:27:50,640 --> 00:27:53,438
But we don't have the liver
or any of the flesh left.

380
00:27:53,520 --> 00:27:56,512
But we do have the beetles.

381
00:27:57,800 --> 00:28:02,237
They ate Hamid's flesh and whatever
organs remained. And you are what you eat.

382
00:28:02,320 --> 00:28:08,555
- So you can ID the poison from the beetles.
- You can't kill them. They have names.

383
00:28:08,640 --> 00:28:12,189
We have to, Zack. Some.

384
00:28:18,400 --> 00:28:23,428
In Thailand, they're sautéed in peanut oil. Mm.

385
00:28:29,800 --> 00:28:32,678
<i>(door opens, closes)</i>

386
00:28:37,160 --> 00:28:40,948
We're gonna have to run a simulation.
Input the skull and give me a face.

387
00:28:41,040 --> 00:28:42,234
You got it.

388
00:28:42,320 --> 00:28:45,437
No more talk about Booth.
You shouldn't have got involved.

389
00:28:45,520 --> 00:28:49,195
- That's what friends are for.
- Please, Angela.

390
00:28:49,280 --> 00:28:50,998
Hey. Where'd you get this?

391
00:28:51,080 --> 00:28:56,552
I'm building it. Theoretical construct of
the bomb based on particulates we gathered.

392
00:28:56,640 --> 00:28:58,790
This isn't yourjob. Bureau's doing this.

393
00:28:58,880 --> 00:29:02,395
Got it! They were poisoned by dioxin,
a very pure form.

394
00:29:02,480 --> 00:29:08,157
It'd stay in the system for years and cause the
facial cysts and bone degeneration we saw.

395
00:29:08,240 --> 00:29:12,518
Give me the levels. Angela can use it
in simulation to give us a date of ingestion.

396
00:29:12,600 --> 00:29:16,115
- How much would it take to poison them?
- Just a little in the food.

397
00:29:16,200 --> 00:29:18,430
Like at that lunch with Sahar's lover.

398
00:29:18,520 --> 00:29:20,511
Impressed?

399
00:29:25,760 --> 00:29:30,914
Dioxin levels were 5600 parts per trillion.

400
00:29:31,000 --> 00:29:35,278
Speed of bone degeneration is an 88%
increase over baseline osteoporosis.

401
00:29:35,360 --> 00:29:40,354
- Date of death was...
- I remember that one. Thanks.

402
00:29:40,440 --> 00:29:43,000
Run the scenario.

403
00:29:47,800 --> 00:29:52,828
- I'll never get used to this.
- Yeah? Chicks with toys?

404
00:29:56,760 --> 00:29:58,239
<i>(Booth)</i> Poor bastard.

405
00:29:58,320 --> 00:30:03,235
Match it to his INS photographs.
See how accurate you are.

406
00:30:03,320 --> 00:30:05,709
Good work, Angela.

407
00:30:10,520 --> 00:30:16,789
Probable date of exposure, about
four months ago. I'd say first week in June.

408
00:30:18,160 --> 00:30:21,869
Let's go pay a little visit to Mr Ladjavardi.

409
00:30:29,960 --> 00:30:35,034
- I thought you were to stay away from him.
- As an FBI agent, I can't disobey my superior.

410
00:30:35,120 --> 00:30:37,111
But you're not an FBI agent.

411
00:30:37,200 --> 00:30:40,112
Hey! Hi. How are you doing?

412
00:30:40,960 --> 00:30:45,875
- What are you doing here? You had orders.
- I just have a couple of quick questions.

413
00:30:45,960 --> 00:30:50,033
Look, I'm not involved in this.
Sahar won't even talk to me any more.

414
00:30:50,120 --> 00:30:52,031
Yeah. I wonder why.

415
00:30:52,120 --> 00:30:54,839
- I'm calling Santana.
- Yeah, I don't think so.

416
00:30:54,920 --> 00:30:57,832
- I'm warning you.
- I wouldn't threaten her if I were you.

417
00:30:57,920 --> 00:31:02,277
I just want to know where you were in June,
to see if you poisoned Hamid and Farid.

418
00:31:02,360 --> 00:31:05,796
- Subtle.
- I'm leaving. That's it.

419
00:31:10,360 --> 00:31:13,955
- Told you. She doesn't like to be touched.
- I didn't poison anybody.

420
00:31:14,040 --> 00:31:18,591
- Then tell me where you were in June.
- In Utah for training with Homeland Security.

421
00:31:18,680 --> 00:31:22,912
I didn't get to DC until August 12th.
Check with the department.

422
00:31:24,560 --> 00:31:27,074
All right. Thanks.

423
00:31:31,160 --> 00:31:36,678
The insulation they used is gypsum-based
with plaster and lead mixed with asbestos.

424
00:31:36,760 --> 00:31:43,438
Pyrobar. It's a fireproof tile developed in 1903.
It was only used for a few years.

425
00:31:43,520 --> 00:31:46,432
It's from the building
the bomb was constructed in.

426
00:31:46,520 --> 00:31:50,479
We find the building
and we find the bomber.

427
00:31:50,720 --> 00:31:54,076
How about this? Sahar wants out
of the marriage, Hamid refuses.

428
00:31:54,160 --> 00:31:57,277
So Sahar poisons him
so she can run off with Ladjavardi.

429
00:31:57,360 --> 00:32:00,670
- It doesn't make sense.
- The first suspect is the spouse.

430
00:32:00,760 --> 00:32:05,356
- Hamid's brother, did she poison him too?
- He's pushing his nose into the marriage.

431
00:32:05,440 --> 00:32:09,149
Sahar is facing a devout Muslim
and a fundamentalist Christian.

432
00:32:09,240 --> 00:32:12,312
Nobody allows divorce.
She's pushed to murder.

433
00:32:12,400 --> 00:32:15,153
- That eschews logic.
- Come on, Bones. Work with me.

434
00:32:15,240 --> 00:32:19,279
It's what we call "positing a scenario".
Don't use the word "eschew".

435
00:32:19,360 --> 00:32:22,591
- What if you and Tessa were to break up?
- I don't want to.

436
00:32:22,680 --> 00:32:26,673
I'm positing a scenario. Tessa wants to
break up, you don't, so she poisons you.

437
00:32:26,760 --> 00:32:29,877
- No, no.
- Then, to make sure, she blows you up.

438
00:32:29,960 --> 00:32:32,428
- Why would Tessa do that?
- Exactly. Thank you.

439
00:32:32,520 --> 00:32:35,876
- That's a bad example.
- You're a couple in love, right?

440
00:32:35,960 --> 00:32:38,076
Why do you keep bringing up Tessa?

441
00:32:38,160 --> 00:32:42,073
What's the big deal? Is it so odd for you
that I have someone in my life?

442
00:32:42,160 --> 00:32:44,674
Talking about couples, it's a natural segue.

443
00:32:44,760 --> 00:32:51,313
You have to quit using the word
"segue" and "eschew". They sound French.

444
00:32:51,400 --> 00:32:55,234
You keep changing the subject.
You're sensitive about you and Tessa.

445
00:32:55,320 --> 00:32:58,437
- Why don't we talk about your boyfriend?
- I don't have one.

446
00:32:58,520 --> 00:33:04,868
You just said that as though it's a good thing.
It's a very sad comment on your personal life.

447
00:33:04,960 --> 00:33:08,669
- Look, you're angry again.
- <i>(cell phone rings)</i>

448
00:33:08,760 --> 00:33:09,795
Brennan.

449
00:33:09,880 --> 00:33:13,634
The bomb insulation was made from Pyrobar,
used by a William Allard.

450
00:33:13,720 --> 00:33:18,316
He was known for developing the
Woodley Park neighbourhood around 1910.

451
00:33:18,400 --> 00:33:23,155
- The bomb was made in Woodley Park.
- That's where Farid lives.

452
00:33:23,240 --> 00:33:24,434
Hold on.

453
00:33:27,440 --> 00:33:33,072
He knew what was poisoning him. Stay
in contact with your boys. We'll need 'em.

454
00:33:33,160 --> 00:33:39,110
We're heading into a very unknown situation.
I think it's best that you just stay in the car.

455
00:33:39,200 --> 00:33:43,671
OK. Then if you have to come in with me,
you stay behind me.

456
00:33:43,760 --> 00:33:46,638
Fine. Just be careful, all right?

457
00:33:47,840 --> 00:33:51,833
OK. Anybody asks, that door was open.
Stay right here.

458
00:33:51,920 --> 00:33:54,115
FBI, Farid!

459
00:33:55,160 --> 00:33:57,833
Show yourself.

460
00:33:57,920 --> 00:33:59,717
OK.

461
00:34:04,400 --> 00:34:05,389
Clear.

462
00:34:05,480 --> 00:34:08,074
- OK, give me Hodgins.
- <i>Yeah.</i>

463
00:34:08,160 --> 00:34:10,355
<i>Farid was making something here.</i>

464
00:34:10,440 --> 00:34:15,878
- I got melted plastic, bottles of chlorine.
- Dioxin. That's how you'd make it.

465
00:34:15,960 --> 00:34:17,598
- Bones!
- Yes?

466
00:34:17,680 --> 00:34:21,912
Insulation. Farid definitely made the bomb.
He killed his brother.

467
00:34:22,000 --> 00:34:23,592
- Stay with me, Hodgins.
- Yeah.

468
00:34:23,680 --> 00:34:27,150
Hamid must've been killed cos
he found his brother making dioxin.

469
00:34:27,240 --> 00:34:29,549
That's probably how they got contaminated.

470
00:34:29,640 --> 00:34:35,158
Come on. Mechanic's guide for Hamid's SUV -
page on the odometer, dog-eared.

471
00:34:39,320 --> 00:34:41,151
He wasrt a Christian.

472
00:34:41,240 --> 00:34:44,391
- "Deceit in the service of Allah is holy."
- The Koran?

473
00:34:44,480 --> 00:34:50,396
No. An imam's twisted interpretation of it
so mass murderers don't have to feel guilt.

474
00:34:50,480 --> 00:34:54,359
He's made another bomb.
It's out there right now.

475
00:34:54,440 --> 00:34:56,158
I'm convinced.

476
00:34:56,240 --> 00:35:00,995
What's the dispersal rate for a bomb
packed with, say, two litres of dioxin?

477
00:35:01,080 --> 00:35:06,677
Homemade device similar to the car bomb?
That could be three to 500 meters.

478
00:35:06,760 --> 00:35:10,992
If the victims werert killed,
they'd develop cancer, blindness, lesions...

479
00:35:11,080 --> 00:35:15,232
Today's date is marked. Call
Homeland Security to secure the apartment.

480
00:35:15,320 --> 00:35:19,791
A convenience-store owner saw Farid
get on a bus and head downtown.

481
00:35:19,880 --> 00:35:23,668
We're not sure what bus. Booth is checking.
If you find anything...

482
00:35:23,760 --> 00:35:26,320
These bus schedules are totally confusing.

483
00:35:26,400 --> 00:35:30,871
His date book had "530" circled.
Check anything that has to do with "530".

484
00:35:30,960 --> 00:35:33,838
Begins, ends, whatever.
I'm not going anywhere.

485
00:35:33,920 --> 00:35:37,230
I still don't understand
why Farid would kill his brother.

486
00:35:37,320 --> 00:35:40,676
Both were developing symptoms.
People would ask questions.

487
00:35:40,760 --> 00:35:43,149
Farid would be exposed.
He had a mission.

488
00:35:43,240 --> 00:35:47,153
How does he think he'll bring about
a better world by blowing people up?

489
00:35:47,240 --> 00:35:52,439
- Fanaticism and logic don't go hand in hand.
- It's almost 5:30. Come on, Angela!

490
00:35:52,520 --> 00:35:53,873
<i>OK, OK.</i>

491
00:35:53,960 --> 00:35:55,757
Three movies start at six.

492
00:35:55,840 --> 00:36:00,038
There's a lecture at Fuller Hall on birds.
I can't imagine that'll be crowded.

493
00:36:00,120 --> 00:36:04,238
And... a peace conference
at the Hamilton Cultural Centre.

494
00:36:04,320 --> 00:36:08,154
There'll be speeches by Arab moderates
and a congressman. That's the one.

495
00:36:08,240 --> 00:36:11,550
- Peace conference, Hamilton Cultural Centre.
- That'll be it.

496
00:36:11,640 --> 00:36:16,236
Gibson, get your boys over to the
Hamilton Cultural Centre, but keep them back.

497
00:36:16,320 --> 00:36:19,596
If we spook this guy, he'll blow himself up.

498
00:36:19,680 --> 00:36:21,432
- Thanks, Angela.
- Bye.

499
00:36:21,520 --> 00:36:24,751
- You don't have to come.
- You gotta be kidding me.

500
00:36:26,880 --> 00:36:28,871
<i>(siren blaring)</i>

501
00:36:33,440 --> 00:36:37,149
<i>(Booth)</i> We'll start down here
and make our way upstairs.

502
00:36:41,200 --> 00:36:44,397
<i>(greeter)</i> Welcome to the Hamilton
Cultural Centre Peace Conference.

503
00:36:44,480 --> 00:36:50,510
We would ask that all delegates check in
before the keynote speaker address.

504
00:36:50,600 --> 00:36:52,830
There are too many ways in.

505
00:36:52,920 --> 00:36:56,993
- Where are the reinforcements?
- They're downstairs tying up the horses.

506
00:36:57,080 --> 00:37:01,153
- Sarcasm doesn't help.
- Mobilising SWAT teams takes time.

507
00:37:01,240 --> 00:37:06,030
And if Farid has the bomb
and spots them, that could be bad.

508
00:37:06,120 --> 00:37:09,590
- If you see him, will you shoot?
- He might not have the bomb.

509
00:37:09,680 --> 00:37:12,114
I'm not taking out a target unless I'm sure.

510
00:37:12,200 --> 00:37:14,998
Is that how you make it easier?
Calling him a target?

511
00:37:15,080 --> 00:37:18,550
You really picked an odd time
to have this conversation.

512
00:37:25,240 --> 00:37:28,073
- Booth.
- Farid?

513
00:37:36,120 --> 00:37:40,318
- There! That's Farid!
- I'm not sure.

514
00:37:40,400 --> 00:37:44,473
His walk is laboured from the dioxin
and the bones in his skull match his picture.

515
00:37:44,560 --> 00:37:48,348
- What if you're wrong?
- It's what I do. Do you really want to wait?

516
00:37:49,320 --> 00:37:52,517
He's carrying something heavy.
It's making his shoulder...

517
00:37:52,600 --> 00:37:56,479
- No, I can't.
- He has all the markers, Booth.

518
00:37:57,040 --> 00:38:00,112
- I need a face. I need a face!
- Farid!

519
00:38:00,200 --> 00:38:03,192
- On the ground!
- He's going for the bomb!

520
00:38:03,280 --> 00:38:06,750
<i>(crowd screaming)</i>

521
00:38:47,800 --> 00:38:53,033
I told them to tell the press
that it was an undercover operation.

522
00:38:53,120 --> 00:38:56,317
But it would be a Rose Garden ceremony.

523
00:38:56,400 --> 00:38:59,551
That's an honour, right?

524
00:38:59,640 --> 00:39:03,076
I thought you FBI guys like your medals.

525
00:39:03,160 --> 00:39:06,835
No pleasure in taking someone's life.

526
00:39:10,160 --> 00:39:12,469
Nothing to celebrate.

527
00:39:12,560 --> 00:39:16,189
You saved so many people, Booth.

528
00:39:16,280 --> 00:39:19,352
Don't forget that.

529
00:39:24,720 --> 00:39:27,188
Want another drink?

530
00:39:29,400 --> 00:39:33,552
Shouldrt you be getting home?

531
00:39:34,320 --> 00:39:37,630
Tessa will be worried about you.

532
00:39:40,560 --> 00:39:42,551
Yeah.

533
00:39:45,320 --> 00:39:47,914
I guess I should.

534
00:39:58,400 --> 00:40:01,597
Thanks for your help, Bones.

535
00:40:01,680 --> 00:40:03,033
Sure.

536
00:40:19,680 --> 00:40:23,798
♪ <i>Have you ever heard the sounds</i>

537
00:40:25,600 --> 00:40:29,036
♪ <i>In the shadows of a song?</i>

538
00:40:31,800 --> 00:40:36,351
♪ <i>Have you ever felt the words</i>

539
00:40:37,400 --> 00:40:41,234
♪ <i>Blow right through from beyond</i>

540
00:40:43,360 --> 00:40:46,079
♪ <i>Cos years pass and people change</i>

541
00:40:49,560 --> 00:40:53,189
♪ <i>The bluest skies can turn to grey</i>

542
00:40:55,440 --> 00:40:58,557
♪ <i>Though it's gonna hurt for now</i>

543
00:40:58,640 --> 00:41:03,111
♪ <i>Every ship must sail away</i>

544
00:41:04,640 --> 00:41:09,475
♪ <i>Every ship must sail away</i>

545
00:41:13,640 --> 00:41:17,713
♪ <i>Though it's gonna hurt for now</i>

546
00:41:19,720 --> 00:41:22,598
♪ <i>Though it's gonna hurt for now</i>

547
00:41:22,680 --> 00:41:28,391
♪ <i>Every ship must sail away</i>

548
00:41:28,800 --> 00:41:32,634
♪ <i>Every ship must sail away</i>

549
00:42:01,920 --> 00:42:04,593
Visiontext Subtitles: Tanja Laden

550
00:42:08,120 --> 00:42:09,473
What's that mean?

551
00:42:10,240 --> 00:42:12,231
ENGLISH SDH

