1
00:00:01,080 --> 00:00:05,551
<i>(Bones)</i> We'll be meeting with agents
from the FAA, the NTSB and local police.

2
00:00:05,640 --> 00:00:08,996
- Booth handles them.
- Plane crashes don't belong to the FBI.

3
00:00:09,080 --> 00:00:11,640
Why not?
FAA is Federal Aviation Administration.

4
00:00:11,720 --> 00:00:16,714
The NTSB stands for National Transportation
Safety Board. That sounds federal. And FBI...

5
00:00:16,800 --> 00:00:18,153
Zack.

6
00:00:18,240 --> 00:00:22,836
- Investigating without Booth, I don't like it.
- Why? He mostly ignores you.

7
00:00:22,920 --> 00:00:27,038
Ignoring me is Booth's way of acknowledging
my presence. It's a guy thing.

8
00:00:27,120 --> 00:00:28,269
<i>(siren)</i>

9
00:00:28,360 --> 00:00:30,351
Here we are.

10
00:00:43,800 --> 00:00:45,074
- Dr Brennan?
- Yes.

11
00:00:45,160 --> 00:00:49,438
- I'm lan Dyson with the NTSB.
- This is my assistant, Zack Addy.

12
00:00:49,520 --> 00:00:54,640
At approximately 0400 last night
a private jet with five passengers on board

13
00:00:54,720 --> 00:00:58,918
reported horizontal stabiliser trouble
200 miles southeast of Norfolk.

14
00:00:59,000 --> 00:01:01,309
Yeager Airport tracked them for 30 minutes

15
00:01:01,400 --> 00:01:04,949
until they dropped off
the radar screen at 0430.

16
00:01:05,040 --> 00:01:09,670
The plane tried to land here when it clipped
some trees and slammed to the ground.

17
00:01:09,760 --> 00:01:14,231
We found another mostly intact body over
near the trees. The rest is bits and pieces.

18
00:01:14,320 --> 00:01:17,312
- What makes this one of our cases?
- I beg your pardon?

19
00:01:17,400 --> 00:01:21,757
We're kind of special. We're elite.
We don't sort through just any set of bodies.

20
00:01:21,840 --> 00:01:25,913
It was a State Department flight with
a bunch of VIPs on board. Special enough?

21
00:01:26,000 --> 00:01:27,877
I apologise if I've offended you.

22
00:01:27,960 --> 00:01:31,635
Usually we have an FBI agent
who mediates our interpersonal encounters.

23
00:01:31,720 --> 00:01:34,029
- We found another skull.
- Two skulls.

24
00:01:34,120 --> 00:01:36,475
Those pieces are from two different skulls.

25
00:01:36,560 --> 00:01:39,836
I'll leave you super-elite types to it.

26
00:01:41,360 --> 00:01:46,229
Zack, we don't need Booth
to "mediate our interpersonal encounters".

27
00:01:46,320 --> 00:01:48,356
OK. Pilot, copilot.

28
00:01:48,440 --> 00:01:51,034
Brings our count to six.

29
00:01:51,120 --> 00:01:56,035
Three mostly intact sets of remains,
one partial and two fragmented.

30
00:01:56,120 --> 00:01:59,192
Obviously bodies are burned to a crisp.

31
00:01:59,280 --> 00:02:02,158
No dermis, very little soft tissue.

32
00:02:02,240 --> 00:02:04,754
Indications of high impact trauma.

33
00:02:04,840 --> 00:02:07,308
Fractures of the thoracic and lumbar
vertebrae

34
00:02:07,400 --> 00:02:11,154
consistent with injuries caused
by the impact of the falling aircraft.

35
00:02:11,240 --> 00:02:14,471
Should I keep talking
as though you're paying attention?

36
00:02:14,560 --> 00:02:16,755
What do you make of this?

37
00:02:21,240 --> 00:02:23,674
- Femur fragment.
- No charring.

38
00:02:23,760 --> 00:02:28,072
- You think this doesn't belong to the crash.
- What are the odds?

39
00:02:28,160 --> 00:02:31,470
Of a crashing plane falling directly
on a human being?

40
00:02:31,560 --> 00:02:34,757
One in ten million.

41
00:02:37,480 --> 00:02:40,153
What I am about to tell you
must not leave this room.

42
00:02:40,240 --> 00:02:43,835
I am philosophically opposed
to institutional secrecy in all forms.

43
00:02:43,920 --> 00:02:46,275
- Fine. Get out.
- <i>(snorts)</i>

44
00:02:46,840 --> 00:02:50,196
Two Communist Chinese trade attachés
were on that plane.

45
00:02:50,280 --> 00:02:53,590
- Both high-ranking party members.
- Obviously we shot it down.

46
00:02:53,680 --> 00:02:56,956
The FAA and the NTSB
can prove that it was an accident.

47
00:02:57,040 --> 00:03:01,989
Also on the manifest was an American
businessman, a pilot and a copilot.

48
00:03:02,080 --> 00:03:04,071
- Five people.
- <i>(Zack)</i> Dr Goodman.

49
00:03:04,160 --> 00:03:07,436
We found six sets of human remains
on that airplane.

50
00:03:07,520 --> 00:03:10,353
And three bone fragments
which were not on the plane.

51
00:03:10,440 --> 00:03:14,274
- Is there any chance they were on the plane?
- As carry-on luggage?

52
00:03:14,360 --> 00:03:17,796
No. Everything on the plane burned.
They were untouched by fire.

53
00:03:17,880 --> 00:03:20,633
Forget about the bone fragments
for the time being.

54
00:03:20,720 --> 00:03:24,474
The State Department is anxious
to find the identity of that sixth person.

55
00:03:24,560 --> 00:03:29,953
No one wishes this to be an international
incident, therefore this is our only priority.

56
00:03:30,040 --> 00:03:32,998
- I disagree.
- For the love of God, why?

57
00:03:33,080 --> 00:03:36,914
Because the plane crash was an accident.
The bone fragments were not.

58
00:03:37,000 --> 00:03:39,514
- How do you know?
- Zack found unusual cut marks.

59
00:03:39,600 --> 00:03:42,831
Cut marks congruent with dismemberment.

60
00:03:42,920 --> 00:03:46,674
People, one hour ago
I received a call from the secretary of state

61
00:03:46,760 --> 00:03:51,595
requesting that the unidentified
extra passenger be our first priority.

62
00:03:51,680 --> 00:03:54,399
So now politics
are more important than murder?

63
00:03:54,480 --> 00:03:58,234
I'm not saying please or being reasonable.
I'm making the decision.

64
00:03:58,320 --> 00:04:02,950
First and foremost, identify that sixth body.

65
00:04:06,640 --> 00:04:08,119
<i>(Bones sighs)</i>

66
00:04:11,200 --> 00:04:15,830
- You got it, or you want me to explain again?
- No, I got it, OK? The plane goes down.

67
00:04:15,920 --> 00:04:18,115
There's an extra body you don't care about

68
00:04:18,200 --> 00:04:21,829
cos you're more interested
in these bone fragments that you found.

69
00:04:21,920 --> 00:04:25,196
- Exactly.
- Oh. This all you got?

70
00:04:25,680 --> 00:04:29,514
So far. A piece of skull,
a chunk of vertebra, part of a femur.

71
00:04:29,600 --> 00:04:33,036
- Not much to go on.
- These come from a person who was hacked.

72
00:04:33,120 --> 00:04:35,714
- Hacked to little bits?
- No, medium-size bits.

73
00:04:35,800 --> 00:04:39,873
- I'm not sure how it turned into little bits yet.
- OK, and I'm here why?

74
00:04:39,960 --> 00:04:45,398
- Dismemberment, little bits... It's a murder.
- FBI has no jurisdiction at a golf course.

75
00:04:45,480 --> 00:04:48,472
- Who does?
- I don't know. Try the PGA.

76
00:04:48,560 --> 00:04:52,473
Uh-huh. You know, you've done a couple
of cases without me and you miss me.

77
00:04:52,560 --> 00:04:54,994
- Zack misses you.
- Zack and I don't even talk.

78
00:04:55,080 --> 00:04:57,833
- He thinks it's a male bonding ritual.
- Maybe.

79
00:04:57,920 --> 00:04:58,955
- No.
- Could be.

80
00:04:59,040 --> 00:05:01,838
- You just told him that.
- It was nicer than shooting him.

81
00:05:01,920 --> 00:05:06,232
Hm! Goodman has ordered me
to investigate the other extra body.

82
00:05:06,320 --> 00:05:10,677
You better get on that. Next time you miss
me, call me. We'll do lunch or something.

83
00:05:10,760 --> 00:05:13,115
- I do not miss you.
- You miss me. Say it.

84
00:05:13,200 --> 00:05:16,590
- I do not miss you.
- Dr Brennan, Agent Booth, you have a visitor.

85
00:05:16,680 --> 00:05:19,558
- No, I don't.
- You miss me. You miss me.

86
00:05:25,400 --> 00:05:27,197
- Dr Temperance Brennan?
- Yes.

87
00:05:27,280 --> 00:05:30,431
- Agent Seeley Booth, I'm Jesse Kane.
- You're Jesse Kane?

88
00:05:30,520 --> 00:05:32,476
- You've heard of me?
- I haven't.

89
00:05:32,560 --> 00:05:35,313
Jesse here's an expert
on missing persons cases.

90
00:05:35,400 --> 00:05:39,234
I've written on missing person laws
and investigative techniques,

91
00:05:39,320 --> 00:05:42,835
interagency cooperation,
jurisdictional dispute.

92
00:05:42,920 --> 00:05:46,993
- I heard about the bones you found.
- I can't really talk about that.

93
00:05:47,080 --> 00:05:51,392
- I don't mean the Communist Chinese.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Communist Chinese?

94
00:05:51,480 --> 00:05:55,792
- The other bones. The fragments.
- How did you hear about the Chinese?

95
00:05:55,880 --> 00:05:58,997
Those pieces of bone
you found at the golf course,

96
00:05:59,080 --> 00:06:02,436
I'm pretty sure that's my dad.

97
00:06:35,960 --> 00:06:41,034
My expertise in missing persons derives
from one thing - my search for my father.

98
00:06:41,120 --> 00:06:44,556
He went missing five years ago
during a trip to Virginia Beach.

99
00:06:44,640 --> 00:06:47,200
What makes you think
the fragments are your father?

100
00:06:47,280 --> 00:06:52,195
There is a question of national security. He's
not supposed to know about the Chinese.

101
00:06:52,280 --> 00:06:57,035
My investigations lead me to conclude my
father was murdered and his body disposed.

102
00:06:57,120 --> 00:06:59,395
- And the police?
- They gave up four years ago.

103
00:06:59,480 --> 00:07:02,711
- No evidence of foul play.
- The investigation was bungled.

104
00:07:02,800 --> 00:07:06,395
The city police didn't have the manpower,
state troopers said it was federal,

105
00:07:06,480 --> 00:07:08,675
and you suggested a private investigator.

106
00:07:08,760 --> 00:07:13,675
It was not bungled, OK? Because there was
no evidence of foul play. It's a common story.

107
00:07:13,760 --> 00:07:18,470
A guy goes in for a pack of cigarettes, he ends
up renting out snorkelling gear in Guam.

108
00:07:19,120 --> 00:07:22,590
He doesn't know what it's like
to lose a parent. You do.

109
00:07:22,680 --> 00:07:25,717
- You wanna back down there?
- How do you know about that?

110
00:07:25,800 --> 00:07:29,554
No offence, but you're a writer,
a well-known scientist. It's out there.

111
00:07:29,640 --> 00:07:31,437
- Plus, you're one of us.
- One of us?

112
00:07:31,520 --> 00:07:34,478
People whose loved ones have vanished.
Both your parents.

113
00:07:34,560 --> 00:07:38,394
OK. How do you know about the Chinese?
Do not look at Dr Brennan, OK?

114
00:07:38,480 --> 00:07:42,268
Whether you like it or not,
this is an issue between you and the FBI.

115
00:07:42,360 --> 00:07:45,716
If body parts are found
where my father disappeared, I know.

116
00:07:45,800 --> 00:07:48,519
Radio chatter, the internet, law enforcement...

117
00:07:48,600 --> 00:07:53,799
That's all I'm prepared to tell you. You mind
if I ask how many bone fragments you found?

118
00:07:53,880 --> 00:07:57,555
Yes, I do.
I don't discuss ongoing investigations.

119
00:07:57,640 --> 00:08:00,837
She doesn't discuss ongoing investigations.

120
00:08:00,920 --> 00:08:04,230
Fair enough.
These are my notes from the last five years.

121
00:08:04,320 --> 00:08:07,232
Every lead, clue,
every person I've talked with is here.

122
00:08:07,320 --> 00:08:13,236
- And why would Dr Brennan care about that?
- Cos it will give her a candidate to eliminate.

123
00:08:13,320 --> 00:08:15,231
He's got a point.

124
00:08:15,320 --> 00:08:18,949
My father's medical records,
pictures, last known whereabouts,

125
00:08:19,040 --> 00:08:22,350
even a connection to the golf course.

126
00:08:22,800 --> 00:08:24,791
Also my phone number.

127
00:08:24,880 --> 00:08:29,908
But don't worry.
If I don't hear from you, you'll hear from me.

128
00:08:33,520 --> 00:08:36,239
Wow. <i>(whistles)</i> Pushy.

129
00:08:37,000 --> 00:08:40,310
Maybe he discovered being pushy
gets cops to pay attention.

130
00:08:40,400 --> 00:08:44,916
- What are you hawking at me for?
- The Chinese, plane crash, that's geopolitics.

131
00:08:45,000 --> 00:08:47,434
This is murder.

132
00:08:48,280 --> 00:08:49,429
Will you help?

133
00:08:51,040 --> 00:08:53,952
Well, you know, I guess
if you're really asking me,

134
00:08:54,040 --> 00:08:56,634
I guess I could, you know,
fudge it with my boss

135
00:08:56,720 --> 00:09:01,953
to make it look like it was attached
to the Chinese plane crash thing.

136
00:09:03,240 --> 00:09:07,392
- We've made progress on the passenger.
- Fill me in.

137
00:09:07,480 --> 00:09:11,473
Nasal ridges indicate she was
a Caucasoid female approximately 5' 10".

138
00:09:11,560 --> 00:09:15,269
Epiphyseal fusion puts her age
somewhere between 20 to 25.

139
00:09:15,360 --> 00:09:17,555
- I have a theory.
- Femme fatale assassin.

140
00:09:17,640 --> 00:09:20,916
- Unregistered flight attendant.
- Young, beautiful girl,

141
00:09:21,000 --> 00:09:25,357
doesn't appear on the in-flight manifest,
group of high-powered politicos?

142
00:09:25,440 --> 00:09:27,431
- Oh.
- Wait, what? What?

143
00:09:27,520 --> 00:09:31,229
Someone might've been doing
his daughter's girlfriend a favour.

144
00:09:31,320 --> 00:09:34,790
- You're so sweet, honey. You really are.
- <i>(Zack)</i> Oh!

145
00:09:34,880 --> 00:09:39,476
You think she was the in-flight entertainment.

146
00:09:40,240 --> 00:09:43,630
Anything you want to tell us
about the bone bits you care about?

147
00:09:43,720 --> 00:09:47,952
Supraorbital margin is rounded,
suggesting a male.

148
00:09:48,040 --> 00:09:52,033
There are signs of osteophytic lipping
or polish on this piece of vertebra.

149
00:09:52,120 --> 00:09:54,190
- Arthritis.
- So middle-aged guy.

150
00:09:54,280 --> 00:09:57,989
Weathering and discoloration suggest
these bones have been out there

151
00:09:58,080 --> 00:10:00,435
for approximately five years.

152
00:10:01,280 --> 00:10:05,717
- I'm going to ask you to help me on this.
- You mean after the Communist thing?

153
00:10:05,800 --> 00:10:07,916
- No, immediately.
- I'm in.

154
00:10:08,000 --> 00:10:10,116
- You want us to defy Dr Goodman?
- I'm in.

155
00:10:10,200 --> 00:10:14,876
Not defy per se.
Do both jobs but... but keep one a secret.

156
00:10:14,960 --> 00:10:17,315
- I'm in.
- We get it. You're a rebel.

157
00:10:17,400 --> 00:10:19,914
Zack, I need you to analyse
the cuts on the bone.

158
00:10:20,000 --> 00:10:21,911
I was kinda hoping to keep my job.

159
00:10:22,000 --> 00:10:25,151
There's not enough skull here
for me to do a reconstruction.

160
00:10:25,240 --> 00:10:28,357
If I gave you a picture
you could tell me if it doesn't match?

161
00:10:28,440 --> 00:10:33,833
I could construct a schematic and see if the
shard fit the skull's shape, if I had a picture.

162
00:10:33,920 --> 00:10:38,118
Has anyone noticed that I was the first
to offer help and apparently I'm useless?

163
00:10:38,200 --> 00:10:42,034
Not true. You're the one that's going
to keep Goodman from finding out.

164
00:10:42,120 --> 00:10:44,111
I'm in.

165
00:10:44,440 --> 00:10:47,079
The fragments are
the same sex and age as my father.

166
00:10:47,160 --> 00:10:49,435
- Yes.
- Thank you.

167
00:10:49,520 --> 00:10:51,670
- It's a long way from conclusive.
- Yeah.

168
00:10:51,760 --> 00:10:56,788
I know at times like these not to get hopeful,
but on the other hand you gotta have hope.

169
00:10:56,880 --> 00:11:00,236
- Even after five years?
- People are found after decades.

170
00:11:00,320 --> 00:11:03,278
After centuries.
You've done some of the finding.

171
00:11:03,360 --> 00:11:07,717
Booth says you've made a living
off of the disappearance of your father.

172
00:11:07,800 --> 00:11:12,237
Six months after my father disappeared,
I found out nobody was looking for him.

173
00:11:12,320 --> 00:11:15,756
Next thing, I was an expert
in motivating the police, victims' rights.

174
00:11:15,840 --> 00:11:20,152
Becoming well known is a by-product
of my search for my father, not the goal.

175
00:11:20,240 --> 00:11:23,118
You should understand my motivation
better than most.

176
00:11:23,200 --> 00:11:28,797
I'm not really interested in bonding
over the loss of my parents.

177
00:11:28,880 --> 00:11:33,237
- Booth is looking over your file now.
- I wasrt looking for his help.

178
00:11:33,320 --> 00:11:37,518
We work together. Booth knows the bone
fragments are evidence of foul play.

179
00:11:37,600 --> 00:11:40,114
That's all the motivation he needed.

180
00:11:40,200 --> 00:11:42,668
You didn't have to lean on him?

181
00:11:44,160 --> 00:11:46,833
Not at all.

182
00:11:46,920 --> 00:11:49,275
If you say so.

183
00:12:00,920 --> 00:12:04,196
One fragment has distinctive
ridge-mark indentations.

184
00:12:04,280 --> 00:12:06,714
- Knife mark.
- Specifically a carving knife.

185
00:12:06,800 --> 00:12:09,598
What about the other ones,
the jagged marks?

186
00:12:09,680 --> 00:12:12,240
Some kind of machine blade.

187
00:12:12,320 --> 00:12:15,630
What? Like a... ajigsaw or a chainsaw?

188
00:12:15,720 --> 00:12:20,840
<i>(clears throat)</i> Are you suggesting a Chinese
diplomat was wielding a chainsaw?

189
00:12:20,920 --> 00:12:22,194
<i>(nervous laugh)</i>

190
00:12:22,280 --> 00:12:28,276
Good one, sir. Very droll.
Zack knows much more about this than I do.

191
00:12:28,360 --> 00:12:33,309
We werert discussing a literal chainsaw cut
but rather the pattern it leaves on the bone.

192
00:12:33,400 --> 00:12:35,595
Right? Zack?

193
00:12:35,680 --> 00:12:40,037
- Blades move in several distinctive ways.
- Several distinctive ways.

194
00:12:40,120 --> 00:12:43,351
Circular, elliptical, segmented.
Chainsaws cut soft materials at high sped.

195
00:12:43,440 --> 00:12:48,036
When cutting hard materials they create
wave-edged walls. This patterrs too linear.

196
00:12:48,120 --> 00:12:51,510
Therefore, no Chinese
chainsaw massacre scenario.

197
00:12:51,600 --> 00:12:53,033
Hm.

198
00:12:53,120 --> 00:12:56,510
Fascinating. What has it to do
with the victims of the plane crash?

199
00:12:56,600 --> 00:13:01,549
We have to reassemble the crash victims and
figure out how their remains were scattered.

200
00:13:01,640 --> 00:13:04,598
Not by being cut up, that's for sure.

201
00:13:04,680 --> 00:13:07,274
Now we've eliminated blades.

202
00:13:10,440 --> 00:13:14,718
- Never freeze on me again.
- I find Dr Goodman scary.

203
00:13:14,800 --> 00:13:19,749
Well, I'm never trusting any of us again.
We're that good at lying, huh?

204
00:13:19,840 --> 00:13:22,718
We're gonna do much better.

205
00:13:24,120 --> 00:13:25,712
<i>(sighs)</i>

206
00:13:26,640 --> 00:13:29,916
Well, you know, I have to admit
Jesse Kane's file on his father

207
00:13:30,000 --> 00:13:33,151
is both well organised and complete. Yep.

208
00:13:33,240 --> 00:13:37,518
- His main suspect is his father's girlfriend.
- Karen Anderson.

209
00:13:37,600 --> 00:13:41,479
No alibi. Since they were living together
at the time of the disappearance,

210
00:13:41,560 --> 00:13:44,791
she remains in the house
and has access to theirjoint accounts.

211
00:13:44,880 --> 00:13:48,270
- How much money are we talking about?
- Max Kane was a stock broker.

212
00:13:48,360 --> 00:13:53,229
He was won'th millions. But after seven years
missing, the courts will declare him dead,

213
00:13:53,320 --> 00:13:56,517
but by that time she could've siphoned out
most of the money.

214
00:13:56,600 --> 00:14:01,993
So I say we go visit Ms Anderson
and we'll know pretty fast if she's a suspect.

215
00:14:02,080 --> 00:14:05,789
- How?
- How? Subtle psychological indicators.

216
00:14:05,880 --> 00:14:11,637
I looked those up on the internet. Body
language, sweat, tonal quality, shifty eyes...

217
00:14:11,720 --> 00:14:17,078
Hey, I don't go poking around your bone
stuff, OK? Just leave the human stuff to me.

218
00:14:17,160 --> 00:14:19,515
Why is Max's disappearance an FBI matter?

219
00:14:19,600 --> 00:14:23,798
- Max's disappearance is not an FBI matter.
- You're an FBI agent.

220
00:14:23,880 --> 00:14:27,077
Human remains were found
during a federal investigation.

221
00:14:27,160 --> 00:14:29,993
Agent Booth is tasked
with the job of identifying them.

222
00:14:30,080 --> 00:14:33,868
I'd like to eliminate Max Kane as a possibility
and move on altogether.

223
00:14:33,960 --> 00:14:38,078
- So this is a pro forma interview?
- Yes. Yes, absolutely.

224
00:14:38,160 --> 00:14:42,312
Because I know Max's son Jesse
accuses me of Max's murder.

225
00:14:42,400 --> 00:14:45,995
- Why do you think he suspects you?
- Because of the age difference,

226
00:14:46,080 --> 00:14:48,150
because I'm still living in the house.

227
00:14:48,240 --> 00:14:51,630
Because after five years I fell in love
with someone new. Who knows?

228
00:14:51,720 --> 00:14:55,554
Some people find it harder than others
to get over the loss of a loved one.

229
00:14:55,640 --> 00:14:57,278
- Bones.
- What?

230
00:14:57,360 --> 00:15:00,318
Jesse got to you, didn't he?

231
00:15:00,400 --> 00:15:03,551
Yeah. The dimples and the sad smile
and melancholy,

232
00:15:03,640 --> 00:15:07,155
on a mission to find his beloved father
and all that.

233
00:15:07,240 --> 00:15:08,832
Jesse didn't love his father?

234
00:15:08,920 --> 00:15:12,879
Max and Jesse didn't speak for the two years
before Max disappeared,

235
00:15:12,960 --> 00:15:15,520
and that was before I came into his life.

236
00:15:15,600 --> 00:15:19,275
- What do you think caused the rift?
- Max cut Jesse off financially.

237
00:15:19,360 --> 00:15:23,831
Max thought Jesse was lazy, running
around New York doing nothing with his life.

238
00:15:23,920 --> 00:15:25,797
Well, Jesse was furious.

239
00:15:35,600 --> 00:15:38,398
Hack marks were caused
by a heidel carving knife.

240
00:15:38,480 --> 00:15:41,836
The osteological profile
suggests postmortem freezing.

241
00:15:41,920 --> 00:15:45,435
Max Kane disappeared midwinter.
What about the jagged cut marks?

242
00:15:45,520 --> 00:15:47,556
This is the part that makes me queasy.

243
00:15:47,640 --> 00:15:50,791
The victim was frozen, dismembered,

244
00:15:50,880 --> 00:15:54,555
- and fed into a wood chipper.
- And spread over a golf course.

245
00:15:54,640 --> 00:15:58,349
Either talk loudly enough so I can hear
all the way or whisper so I can't.

246
00:15:58,440 --> 00:16:02,149
Maybe if we told Goodman this
he'd authorise a change in priorities.

247
00:16:02,240 --> 00:16:06,279
- Or he'd suspend us all for defying him.
- Angela's right.

248
00:16:06,360 --> 00:16:11,753
We're gonna drop this and get back to what
Dr Goodman told us to do in the first place?

249
00:16:11,840 --> 00:16:16,516
No. We are going to keep doing
what we're doing behind Goodmars back.

250
00:16:16,600 --> 00:16:19,398
That's the spirit!

251
00:16:22,440 --> 00:16:24,795
Yeah, it's true.

252
00:16:24,880 --> 00:16:28,156
My father cut me off financially.
I take it you talked to Karen.

253
00:16:28,240 --> 00:16:32,279
- Is there anything else you failed to mention?
- I know I didn't kill my father,

254
00:16:32,360 --> 00:16:35,909
so I'd rather you didn't waste your time
on that line of investigation.

255
00:16:36,000 --> 00:16:38,833
Too late. What happened
between you and your father?

256
00:16:38,920 --> 00:16:42,993
I was enrolled at NYU, but all I really did
was go clubbing and have a good time.

257
00:16:43,080 --> 00:16:46,595
My father was right to cut me off.
I was a disappointment to him.

258
00:16:46,680 --> 00:16:50,434
- But if he could see you now...
- I like to think he can see me now.

259
00:16:50,520 --> 00:16:53,751
Your father is dead.
A dead person can't see anything.

260
00:16:53,840 --> 00:16:56,718
Maybe that's true. Maybe it isn't.

261
00:16:56,800 --> 00:17:01,510
But either way,
at least I know my dad would be proud.

262
00:17:01,600 --> 00:17:04,990
Bones, tell Jesse
what happened to the victim.

263
00:17:05,080 --> 00:17:06,991
- Really?
- What?

264
00:17:07,080 --> 00:17:09,469
Usually you tell me not to tell people.

265
00:17:09,560 --> 00:17:13,394
Well, it can't be worse
than some of the things that I've imagined.

266
00:17:13,480 --> 00:17:19,077
The victim was frozen, dismembered
and fed through a wood chipper.

267
00:17:20,520 --> 00:17:23,796
Bones has figured out
what type of wood chipper was used.

268
00:17:23,880 --> 00:17:27,555
We'll see if one was sold in Virginia Beach.

269
00:17:27,640 --> 00:17:31,679
I can't believe
someone would do that to my dad.

270
00:17:32,320 --> 00:17:35,392
We haven't identified the victim
as your father.

271
00:17:35,480 --> 00:17:40,270
I have our artist comparing the skull fragment
to pictures of your dad.

272
00:17:40,360 --> 00:17:43,477
Could I see the bone fragments?

273
00:17:53,920 --> 00:17:56,480
- This is all of him?
- Yes.

274
00:17:57,080 --> 00:17:59,753
I mean...

275
00:17:59,840 --> 00:18:01,990
It's all of somebody.

276
00:18:02,080 --> 00:18:04,674
He was a big man, my dad.

277
00:18:04,760 --> 00:18:08,469
It's hard to believe
that this is all that's left of him.

278
00:18:08,560 --> 00:18:12,155
How can you get anything
from three small bits of bone?

279
00:18:12,240 --> 00:18:15,038
It's more than a lot of people get.

280
00:18:17,720 --> 00:18:20,837
I know where my dad was
right before he disappeared.

281
00:18:20,920 --> 00:18:26,916
I know my dad met with a client
at the North Star Grill in Virginia Beach.

282
00:18:30,080 --> 00:18:32,833
I know he had meat loaf.

283
00:18:32,920 --> 00:18:34,911
<i>(laughs)</i>

284
00:18:36,520 --> 00:18:41,992
I know he was supposed to meet Karen
at the pier but he didn't show up.

285
00:18:42,880 --> 00:18:49,592
I know she waited two days...
before reporting him gone.

286
00:18:57,800 --> 00:18:59,836
I have a good timeline.

287
00:18:59,920 --> 00:19:02,593
And I have three small bits of bone.

288
00:19:05,080 --> 00:19:11,076
You don't have any of those things
and I realise how hopeless you must feel.

289
00:19:15,680 --> 00:19:18,148
Come with me.

290
00:19:23,600 --> 00:19:25,670
This is all you have?

291
00:19:25,760 --> 00:19:28,274
Yes. You were right about how little it is.

292
00:19:28,360 --> 00:19:32,239
No, I mean this is simply
your copy of the official file.

293
00:19:32,320 --> 00:19:34,117
Yes. What else would there be?

294
00:19:34,200 --> 00:19:38,318
You never tried to hire any private
investigators? Did any poking around?

295
00:19:38,400 --> 00:19:43,110
Well, I'm pretty new at field work.
I've mostly been a lab rat my whole career.

296
00:19:43,200 --> 00:19:46,590
Plus, I trusted the authorities
would do what they could.

297
00:19:46,680 --> 00:19:52,073
The authorities have rooms
filled with files like these, warehouses.

298
00:19:52,160 --> 00:19:57,632
- I'm the authorities. Booth is the authorities.
- Did you ever show this file to Booth?

299
00:19:57,720 --> 00:19:59,995
No. No.

300
00:20:07,120 --> 00:20:09,031
This is where I work.

301
00:20:09,120 --> 00:20:11,998
Uh, which is my cue.

302
00:20:12,080 --> 00:20:13,718
Uh... <i>(clears throat)</i>

303
00:20:13,800 --> 00:20:16,758
Um, Angela, come in. This is Jesse Kane.

304
00:20:16,840 --> 00:20:18,558
- Hello.
- Hi.

305
00:20:18,640 --> 00:20:21,518
Hi. Angela Montenegro.

306
00:20:22,280 --> 00:20:25,590
- What's that?
- Oh, uh, nothing that can't wait.

307
00:20:25,680 --> 00:20:27,796
Is it about my father?

308
00:20:27,880 --> 00:20:31,953
As far as I know,
which is quite far, believe me,

309
00:20:32,040 --> 00:20:35,510
no one has tried to kiss Brennan in this office
and lived to tell.

310
00:20:35,600 --> 00:20:36,715
Angela...

311
00:20:36,800 --> 00:20:41,271
Would one of you please tell me
what that piece of paper is?

312
00:20:41,360 --> 00:20:45,911
It's a, uh... it's a schematic comparing the
skull fragment we found on the golf course

313
00:20:46,000 --> 00:20:47,991
- to pictures of your father.
- And?

314
00:20:48,080 --> 00:20:50,196
It doesn't not match your father.

315
00:20:50,280 --> 00:20:52,510
So it could be him?

316
00:20:52,600 --> 00:20:55,876
Yeah. There's a pretty good chance.

317
00:21:00,200 --> 00:21:03,078
I knew it.

318
00:21:03,160 --> 00:21:05,833
- Are you hooking up?
- We didn't arrange anything.

319
00:21:05,920 --> 00:21:08,275
- Why not?
- Cos you were there, hovering.

320
00:21:08,360 --> 00:21:11,830
- I was not. I was being your wingman.
- What's that?

321
00:21:11,920 --> 00:21:15,196
I was rendering assistance
and enabling where needed.

322
00:21:15,280 --> 00:21:17,271
Booth thinks he might be a suspect.

323
00:21:17,360 --> 00:21:20,477
Now you're just looking for excuses
not to get involved.

324
00:21:20,560 --> 00:21:25,395
Plane crash victim number four,
Captain Jacob Howard, pilot, age 47.

325
00:21:25,480 --> 00:21:29,439
Height five foot six,
weight approximately 167Ib.

326
00:21:29,520 --> 00:21:31,715
Overlay the photograph.

327
00:21:36,080 --> 00:21:38,389
Frontozygomatic sutures line up.

328
00:21:38,480 --> 00:21:42,553
- Cranial meninges are in sync.
- Excellent. That's one more off the list.

329
00:21:42,640 --> 00:21:47,236
Victim number five, Shan Woo Fong, age 56.

330
00:21:47,320 --> 00:21:50,710
Height five foot six,
weight approximately 140Ib.

331
00:21:50,800 --> 00:21:54,509
That's terrific, except we knew
all of these people were on the plane.

332
00:21:54,600 --> 00:21:58,878
What the State Department wants to know
is the identity of our mystery woman.

333
00:21:58,960 --> 00:22:01,952
I hope I can count
on your full energies on this.

334
00:22:02,040 --> 00:22:04,634
If I can be completely honest, sir...

335
00:22:04,720 --> 00:22:09,555
Toxicology reports came back from all six
victims. Pilot and copilot were clean.

336
00:22:09,640 --> 00:22:14,953
Our two Chinese nationals had elevated
levels of alcohol and sildenafil, or Viagra.

337
00:22:15,040 --> 00:22:18,589
And our mystery girl showed traces
of alcohol and cocaine.

338
00:22:18,680 --> 00:22:23,196
So, will the cover-up start now or somewhere
between here and the State Department?

339
00:22:23,280 --> 00:22:27,114
- You were saying about being honest?
- Yes. Regarding the bone shards...

340
00:22:27,200 --> 00:22:31,478
The prostitute was six inches taller
and she had occupational stress markers.

341
00:22:31,560 --> 00:22:36,031
Let's not call her a prostitute yet, Mr Addy.
What occupational markers?

342
00:22:36,120 --> 00:22:39,192
- It's a foot thing.
- She was a fetishist?

343
00:22:39,640 --> 00:22:43,633
Both her cuboid and medial malleolus
show signs of wear.

344
00:22:43,720 --> 00:22:47,554
You can relax, Dr Goodman.
She wore extremely high stiletto heels.

345
00:22:47,640 --> 00:22:50,757
I reconstructed her face
from the partial skull.

346
00:22:52,400 --> 00:22:56,234
- She was hot.
- What's our next move?

347
00:22:56,320 --> 00:23:02,350
We match this reconstruction with escort ads,
both internet and print, in the DC area.

348
00:23:02,440 --> 00:23:04,556
Oh, I'll do that.

349
00:23:04,640 --> 00:23:07,359
What? Was that overly enthusiastic?

350
00:23:07,440 --> 00:23:09,510
Thank you for the update.

351
00:23:09,600 --> 00:23:14,230
- This case continues to be your top priority?
- If I could suggest...

352
00:23:14,320 --> 00:23:19,633
Dr Brennan has been very clear
about your priorities on this, sir.

353
00:23:24,880 --> 00:23:25,915
What's that?

354
00:23:26,000 --> 00:23:29,037
The only Blackmantis wood chipper
in Virginia Beach.

355
00:23:29,120 --> 00:23:32,908
I got the records from the manufacturer
and traced it back to the yard.

356
00:23:33,000 --> 00:23:37,278
- We couldn't find any blood residue.
- That makes sense if the corpse was frozen.

357
00:23:37,360 --> 00:23:40,557
Yeah. Not to mention this has ground up
about 10,000 trees.

358
00:23:40,640 --> 00:23:43,871
I figured you could match the blades
to the cuts on the bones.

359
00:23:43,960 --> 00:23:47,999
Or do something I haven't thought of
much more confusing and scientific.

360
00:23:48,080 --> 00:23:50,071
Booth, you're working this case?

361
00:23:50,160 --> 00:23:53,311
Only two people have had access
to this machine.

362
00:23:53,400 --> 00:23:57,313
A foreman and a maintenance worker
named Ray Sparks. Sparks has ajacket.

363
00:23:57,400 --> 00:24:00,358
What do you say?
You want to come with me to go talk to him?

364
00:24:00,440 --> 00:24:03,159
Told you. It's a guy thing.

365
00:24:03,240 --> 00:24:05,708
- Yes, I'd like to come.
- All right. Here we go.

366
00:24:05,800 --> 00:24:09,554
Let Angela do the matching.
I have something more interesting for you.

367
00:24:09,640 --> 00:24:13,599
- More interesting than escorts?
- Run a dispersal test on the chipper.

368
00:24:13,680 --> 00:24:17,719
- Using what medium?
- Assume the victim was frozen solid.

369
00:24:18,240 --> 00:24:20,800
- No way!
- Correct response would be "Yes way".

370
00:24:20,880 --> 00:24:23,553
Yes way.

371
00:24:28,560 --> 00:24:32,030
You ignore Zack to make him think
you've got some special bond.

372
00:24:32,120 --> 00:24:35,396
- But it works. I'm happy, he's happy.
- It's not the truth.

373
00:24:35,480 --> 00:24:38,278
But it works.
Ray Sparks, I'd like to have a word with you.

374
00:24:38,360 --> 00:24:44,037
Zack wants to fit into the real world
more than anything. You're not helping.

375
00:24:44,120 --> 00:24:47,476
- FBI. Special Agent Booth.
<i>- (crashing)</i>

376
00:24:47,560 --> 00:24:50,154
He went around the back.

377
00:24:51,840 --> 00:24:54,229
No, no. The other way, Bones.

378
00:24:58,280 --> 00:25:00,350
FBI. Freeze.

379
00:25:00,440 --> 00:25:01,509
<i>(grunts)</i>

380
00:25:02,280 --> 00:25:04,430
- Bones, jeez.
<i>- (grunts)</i>

381
00:25:04,520 --> 00:25:07,557
- Ray Sparks?
- Hey, I didn't do nothing wrong!

382
00:25:07,640 --> 00:25:13,510
- I feel like kicking him.
- That's normal after a pursuit. We try not to.

383
00:25:31,120 --> 00:25:33,315
How are we gonna keep this
from Dr Goodman?

384
00:25:33,400 --> 00:25:36,312
Ah, he's having lunch
with the president of Harvard.

385
00:25:36,400 --> 00:25:40,075
What's going on? Why is every guy
from the Jeffersonian out here?

386
00:25:40,160 --> 00:25:43,277
They're scientists.
This is a fascinating inquiry.

387
00:25:43,360 --> 00:25:44,679
Oh, my God.

388
00:25:44,760 --> 00:25:49,436
They're all out here because you're gonna
feed something through this wood chipper.

389
00:25:49,520 --> 00:25:50,999
Notjust something.

390
00:25:51,080 --> 00:25:53,435
Ta-da! A frozen pig!

391
00:25:53,520 --> 00:25:55,317
- <i>(applause)</i>
- Ugh.

392
00:25:55,400 --> 00:25:58,119
Pig bones are almost
identical to human bones.

393
00:25:58,200 --> 00:26:02,557
By feeding the pig through the chipper
we can determine a dispersal pattern.

394
00:26:02,640 --> 00:26:06,428
By comparing the pig's remains
to the fragments found at the golf course

395
00:26:06,520 --> 00:26:09,273
we'll know if this is the chipper
Max was fed through.

396
00:26:09,360 --> 00:26:15,754
Liars. You just want to see what happens
when you toss a pig into a wood chipper.

397
00:26:16,360 --> 00:26:18,351
<i>(crowd cheers)</i>

398
00:26:21,040 --> 00:26:23,713
<i>(Hodgins)</i> Ready? One!

399
00:26:23,800 --> 00:26:25,199
Two!

400
00:26:25,280 --> 00:26:26,918
Three!

401
00:26:27,000 --> 00:26:28,797
<i>(cheering)</i>

402
00:26:56,920 --> 00:27:01,152
OK. What do we got here? Breaking and
entering, assault, drunk, disorderly. Wow.

403
00:27:01,240 --> 00:27:04,516
I've been keeping myself out of trouble
for the past four years.

404
00:27:04,600 --> 00:27:08,434
- How long you been a maintenance worker?
- Since '92.

405
00:27:08,520 --> 00:27:12,035
- You ever meet a guy named Max Kane?
- No.

406
00:27:12,120 --> 00:27:14,554
- Karen Anderson?
- Yeah, I know her.

407
00:27:14,640 --> 00:27:17,438
- How?
- She bartends at the golf course.

408
00:27:17,520 --> 00:27:21,069
You don't strike me as a golfer, Ray. <i>(laughs)</i>

409
00:27:24,280 --> 00:27:27,272
City land is right across the creek
from the course

410
00:27:27,360 --> 00:27:30,875
and I go to the clubhouse
a couple times a week to have lunch.

411
00:27:30,960 --> 00:27:34,236
How did you pay for that house you live in?
That's pretty nice.

412
00:27:34,320 --> 00:27:40,077
You got a hard time sticking to one topic,
huh? My mom left me the house.

413
00:27:40,160 --> 00:27:42,993
She left it to me and my brother Frank
five years ago.

414
00:27:43,080 --> 00:27:45,958
Five years ago Max Kane disappeared.
Karers boyfriend.

415
00:27:46,040 --> 00:27:49,191
So you can see how my suspicions
might be a little aroused.

416
00:27:49,280 --> 00:27:55,230
You know, but the thing is,
I didn't live in Virginia Beach five years ago.

417
00:27:56,800 --> 00:28:00,759
I was in Southampton Correctional Center

418
00:28:00,840 --> 00:28:04,515
doing six months
for skipping out on a DUI warrant.

419
00:28:06,400 --> 00:28:09,358
Guess I don't need a lawyer, right?

420
00:28:09,960 --> 00:28:11,712
<i>(Ray laughs)</i>

421
00:28:12,440 --> 00:28:16,353
There's no way that chipper experiment
was connected to the plane crash.

422
00:28:16,440 --> 00:28:19,193
- Look...
- Don't say anything. Just listen.

423
00:28:19,280 --> 00:28:23,193
Your primary job is to do as I say.
Failing that, yourjob is to fool me.

424
00:28:23,280 --> 00:28:27,990
- You failed to fool me, Dr Hodgins.
- I'd have fooled you if you'd gone to lunch.

425
00:28:28,080 --> 00:28:30,310
I'll find some way to punish you.

426
00:28:30,400 --> 00:28:34,188
Parking, dining privileges, budget reviews.
If it happens again...

427
00:28:34,280 --> 00:28:36,510
- I got it.
- No.

428
00:28:36,600 --> 00:28:38,716
You don't.

429
00:28:39,640 --> 00:28:42,950
You think I'm a kind and fair man.

430
00:28:43,040 --> 00:28:47,192
Egoless, balanced,
ruled by intelligent reflection.

431
00:28:47,280 --> 00:28:49,111
But I do have an ego.

432
00:28:49,200 --> 00:28:53,352
I can be vindictive and petty.

433
00:28:53,440 --> 00:28:56,193
I will take you down

434
00:28:56,280 --> 00:29:01,479
even if it means striking at you
through your friends and co-workers.

435
00:29:03,200 --> 00:29:05,395
Now you understand.

436
00:29:09,400 --> 00:29:12,153
Ray Sparks was in jail
when your father disappeared.

437
00:29:12,240 --> 00:29:14,879
He might have put Karen in touch
with the hit man.

438
00:29:14,960 --> 00:29:19,272
One of the things you lecture about
is that the simplest theory is usually true.

439
00:29:19,360 --> 00:29:22,750
- Usually, not always.
- What's the simplest theory in this case?

440
00:29:22,840 --> 00:29:25,991
Disowned son realises
that his father may remarry...

441
00:29:26,080 --> 00:29:30,119
Booth, are you accusing Jesse
of murdering his own father for money?

442
00:29:30,200 --> 00:29:33,715
- Ever hear of the Menendez brothers?
- I came to you about the bones.

443
00:29:33,800 --> 00:29:38,476
Your father is declared dead, you get
your ineritance before Karen spends it all.

444
00:29:38,560 --> 00:29:40,596
You don't seem too upset about that.

445
00:29:40,680 --> 00:29:43,831
For fours years I've been making enemies
with law enforcement.

446
00:29:43,920 --> 00:29:46,514
Attacking me is a pretty typical response.

447
00:29:46,600 --> 00:29:49,876
Is this one of those times
when you just poke to get reactions?

448
00:29:49,960 --> 00:29:54,238
Listen, Bones. We have to treat him like
a suspect. He is not a member of the team.

449
00:29:54,320 --> 00:29:58,916
Look. I'm like you. I need the truth.

450
00:30:03,560 --> 00:30:05,949
I have to get back to the lab.

451
00:30:09,280 --> 00:30:11,555
Satellite imagery of the golf course.

452
00:30:11,640 --> 00:30:15,189
These three dots show where
the bone fragments were found.

453
00:30:15,280 --> 00:30:18,590
Can you show me the results
of the wood chipper test?

454
00:30:18,680 --> 00:30:22,992
The V shape indicates the maximum distance
a bone fragment could've travelled

455
00:30:23,080 --> 00:30:25,594
given similar wind speeds and temperatures.

456
00:30:25,680 --> 00:30:29,719
OK, and remove the plane crash.
It's irrelevant to this.

457
00:30:29,800 --> 00:30:34,396
The question is, in order to use
the guys' pig-grinding experiment,

458
00:30:34,480 --> 00:30:36,596
where do we place the wood chipper?

459
00:30:36,680 --> 00:30:40,559
I bet the murderer aimed the wood chipper
over the stream.

460
00:30:40,640 --> 00:30:42,790
So the evidence would wash away.

461
00:30:42,880 --> 00:30:44,029
Mm-hm.

462
00:30:44,120 --> 00:30:45,951
What's that?

463
00:30:46,040 --> 00:30:49,350
That is a small access road
for maintenance vehicles.

464
00:30:49,440 --> 00:30:52,238
<i>(Bones)</i> Try putting the wood chipper there.

465
00:30:52,320 --> 00:30:54,914
Oh, frisson of success.

466
00:30:55,000 --> 00:30:58,436
We should see if we can find
any more bone fragments here and here.

467
00:30:58,520 --> 00:31:01,592
Are we closer to identifying
our mystery woman?

468
00:31:01,680 --> 00:31:04,990
Um, I'm not... I'm not certain.

469
00:31:05,080 --> 00:31:08,436
- Brennan is still waiting for an update.
- I saw you come in, sir.

470
00:31:08,520 --> 00:31:11,990
I have a list of possible matches
on our geisha in the sky.

471
00:31:12,080 --> 00:31:15,755
She is Caucasian.
Our mystery woman is definitely Caucasian.

472
00:31:15,840 --> 00:31:18,195
We sent a list to the FBI. They're checking it.

473
00:31:18,280 --> 00:31:24,833
Ah. Well, in that case, you might want to turn
your attention back to the bone fragments.

474
00:31:31,080 --> 00:31:32,911
<i>(knock at door)</i>

475
00:31:39,000 --> 00:31:42,117
I came for the file on my parents.

476
00:31:47,680 --> 00:31:49,113
<i>(sighs)</i>

477
00:31:49,200 --> 00:31:53,432
- You think I might've killed my father.
- No. It's just...

478
00:31:54,720 --> 00:31:57,518
I asked the wrong person to help me, and...

479
00:31:57,600 --> 00:32:00,353
What?

480
00:32:00,440 --> 00:32:05,309
I just don't think it's healthy, what you're
doing. Putting your whole life into this.

481
00:32:05,400 --> 00:32:07,914
And I suppose the way you're doing it,

482
00:32:08,000 --> 00:32:11,470
putting nothing into solving
the disappearance of your parents,

483
00:32:11,560 --> 00:32:14,518
I suppose that's healthy?

484
00:32:16,360 --> 00:32:21,150
We're searching the golf course
for more bone fragments.

485
00:32:23,200 --> 00:32:25,873
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Somewhere A Clock Is Ticking"</i>
<i>by Snow Patrol)</i>

486
00:32:25,960 --> 00:32:30,636
♪ <i>I've got this feeling</i>
<i>that there's something that I missed</i>

487
00:32:30,720 --> 00:32:32,551
♪ <i>I could do most anything to you</i>

488
00:32:32,640 --> 00:32:35,029
♪ <i>Don't you breathe</i>

489
00:32:36,000 --> 00:32:37,513
♪ <i>Don't you breathe</i>

490
00:32:37,600 --> 00:32:39,955
♪ <i>I could do most anything to you</i>

491
00:32:40,040 --> 00:32:44,397
♪ <i>Something happened</i>
<i>that I never understood</i>

492
00:32:44,480 --> 00:32:46,436
♪ <i>I could do most anything to you</i>

493
00:32:46,520 --> 00:32:48,909
♪ <i>You can't leave</i>

494
00:32:49,800 --> 00:32:51,313
♪ <i>You can't leave</i>

495
00:32:51,400 --> 00:32:54,392
♪ <i>I could do most anything to you</i>

496
00:33:13,600 --> 00:33:17,434
We found a piece of finger
with the nail attached, and underneath...

497
00:33:17,520 --> 00:33:19,511
Polyurethane. The tough stuff.

498
00:33:19,600 --> 00:33:22,717
The victim was scraping at something
before he died.

499
00:33:22,800 --> 00:33:25,439
I can't identify this bone anomaly.

500
00:33:25,520 --> 00:33:30,469
It's full of osteoids, thick.
Maybe part of the mandible.

501
00:33:30,560 --> 00:33:33,438
Human, something odd
with the cell structure.

502
00:33:33,520 --> 00:33:37,798
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> A wood chipper wouldn't do that.
- It's a nonmalignant bone tumour.

503
00:33:37,880 --> 00:33:41,555
I need the most recent bone scans
from Max Kane's medical records.

504
00:33:41,640 --> 00:33:42,868
Hodgins.

505
00:33:42,960 --> 00:33:44,951
It's Booth.

506
00:33:46,680 --> 00:33:49,831
The locals arrested Jesse
for attacking Karen Anderson.

507
00:33:49,920 --> 00:33:52,559
Jesse showed up at Karers house
to confront her.

508
00:33:52,640 --> 00:33:57,794
He was ranting about his dad. Eddie tried
to throw him out. They exchanged punches.

509
00:33:57,880 --> 00:34:01,759
- That doesn't mean he isn't the killer.
- I know.

510
00:34:01,840 --> 00:34:06,868
He might have done this just to make us think
that he was angry at her, all right? He's smart.

511
00:34:06,960 --> 00:34:09,349
Do you think Jesse murdered his father?

512
00:34:09,440 --> 00:34:14,275
Bones, all I'm saying is we look into murders,
we can't let our heartstrings get all plucked.

513
00:34:14,360 --> 00:34:17,113
We poke at people's wounds,
make 'em bleed a little.

514
00:34:17,200 --> 00:34:20,431
Make 'em tell us things
that they normally wouldn't tell us.

515
00:34:20,520 --> 00:34:25,275
We gotta be willing to be hard on them, even
when we know we're no different than them.

516
00:34:25,360 --> 00:34:29,831
- You didn't answer my question.
- Well, I have an opinion. You want to know?

517
00:34:29,920 --> 00:34:32,309
- I'd say he didn't do it.
- Me too.

518
00:34:32,400 --> 00:34:35,756
I'm going off my gut.
I mean, what... what's persuading you?

519
00:34:35,840 --> 00:34:40,118
The bone fragments at the golf course,
they didn't come from Max Kane.

520
00:34:40,200 --> 00:34:43,397
That's great. You knew that
when you asked me what I thought.

521
00:34:43,480 --> 00:34:45,755
You testing out my instincts, Bones?

522
00:34:45,840 --> 00:34:48,308
Poking and prodding.

523
00:34:48,400 --> 00:34:50,755
I learned from the best.

524
00:34:55,240 --> 00:34:57,595
It's not my dad?

525
00:34:57,680 --> 00:35:01,559
- No. We don't know who it is yet.
- How can you be certain?

526
00:35:02,240 --> 00:35:06,791
We found ajuxtacortical chondroma,
a nonmalignant bone tumour.

527
00:35:06,880 --> 00:35:10,873
- Your dad's X-rays showed no sign of one.
- Maybe he got it after the X-rays.

528
00:35:10,960 --> 00:35:14,316
The X-rays were taken
two months before he disappeared.

529
00:35:14,400 --> 00:35:20,794
It's a slow-growing tumour. It would've taken
years to get to the size and density we found.

530
00:35:20,880 --> 00:35:26,876
Look, I'm gonna see if I can get this assault
stuff to go away and get you out of here.

531
00:35:28,160 --> 00:35:30,549
I'm sorry, Jesse.

532
00:35:30,640 --> 00:35:32,471
For what?

533
00:35:32,560 --> 00:35:35,199
Suspecting that I killed my own father?

534
00:35:35,280 --> 00:35:38,078
No. I'm not sorry for that.

535
00:35:41,880 --> 00:35:45,589
I know what it's like
not to know what happened.

536
00:35:46,840 --> 00:35:49,434
I know how painful that can be.

537
00:35:50,920 --> 00:35:53,195
And I'm sorry for you.

538
00:36:00,080 --> 00:36:02,514
If the bones aren't Kane's
who's our dead guy?

539
00:36:02,600 --> 00:36:07,390
Send out a description of the chondroma to
hospitals, see if it leads to missing patients.

540
00:36:07,480 --> 00:36:10,597
Yeah, we can do that. List the pertinents.

541
00:36:10,680 --> 00:36:12,910
Me? Are you talking directly to me?

542
00:36:13,000 --> 00:36:16,595
Yeah. My eyes are looking at you,
my mouth is aimed in your direction.

543
00:36:16,680 --> 00:36:19,592
But what about our guy thing?
If you're speaking to me,

544
00:36:19,680 --> 00:36:21,750
then does this mean I'm not on the team?

545
00:36:21,840 --> 00:36:25,116
Zack, let's concentrate on the work.

546
00:36:25,200 --> 00:36:26,713
- Pertinents?
- Pertinents.

547
00:36:26,800 --> 00:36:31,351
The victim died. We don't know how. He was
frozen, dismembered with a carving knife

548
00:36:31,440 --> 00:36:34,000
and pushed through
a Blackmantis 1200 wood chipper.

549
00:36:34,080 --> 00:36:36,719
The exact chipper
you fed the frozen pig through.

550
00:36:36,800 --> 00:36:41,078
- The exact chipper Ray Sparks had access to.
- But Ray Sparks was in jail.

551
00:36:41,160 --> 00:36:44,516
- Ray was in jail when Max disappeared.
- Our victim isn't Max.

552
00:36:44,600 --> 00:36:47,160
Who else would Ray Sparks
have motive to kill?

553
00:36:47,240 --> 00:36:50,710
- The victim is a middle-aged male...
- His brother.

554
00:36:50,800 --> 00:36:53,268
- What motive?
- They both inerited the house.

555
00:36:53,360 --> 00:36:58,036
OK, you guys, you look at that tumour,
and Bones and I will go talk to Ray. Come on.

556
00:36:58,120 --> 00:37:02,079
- While you're there, look for a large freezer.
- Why?

557
00:37:02,160 --> 00:37:06,039
- The body was frozen.
- Polyurethane is a common liner in freezers.

558
00:37:06,120 --> 00:37:11,672
We found it under the victim's fingernail,
like he was scratching to get out.

559
00:37:15,120 --> 00:37:20,592
The detectives say Sparks claims his brother
was alive and well the last time he saw him.

560
00:37:20,680 --> 00:37:24,150
He might've been for 30 minutes
until he ran out of air in here.

561
00:37:24,240 --> 00:37:28,711
My guys found claw marks
on the inner linings on both sides.

562
00:37:28,800 --> 00:37:34,033
What kind of person could lock
a living human being in a freezer?

563
00:37:35,080 --> 00:37:37,799
- <i>(Booth)</i> What is that?
- <i>(Bones)</i> A fingernail.

564
00:37:39,640 --> 00:37:41,631
His own brother.

565
00:37:52,080 --> 00:37:53,513
Hey.

566
00:37:53,600 --> 00:37:55,511
Booth got you out.

567
00:37:55,600 --> 00:38:00,390
1200 bucks bail. I promised to stay away
from Karen and Eddie.

568
00:38:00,480 --> 00:38:02,789
We solved the case.

569
00:38:03,600 --> 00:38:07,070
- I'm sorry it's not your father.
- <i>(sighs)</i>

570
00:38:09,000 --> 00:38:11,389
We identified the victim.

571
00:38:11,480 --> 00:38:14,153
His name was Frank Sparks.

572
00:38:16,480 --> 00:38:19,711
I'm sorry I couldn't help you, Jesse.

573
00:38:20,880 --> 00:38:23,189
How do you live with it?

574
00:38:23,280 --> 00:38:29,276
- What? The disappearance of my parents?
- The fact that nobody's looking.

575
00:38:30,800 --> 00:38:35,476
I never thought about it that way
until I met you.

576
00:38:37,920 --> 00:38:40,639
There's a Zen koan.

577
00:38:40,720 --> 00:38:45,077
It says that if you want to find something,

578
00:38:45,160 --> 00:38:47,799
you have to stop looking.

579
00:38:48,800 --> 00:38:54,557
I can't do that. My dad's watching
and I don't want to disappoint him again.

580
00:39:05,760 --> 00:39:11,039
Even if you don't believe it, I know your
parents are somewhere proud of what you do.

581
00:39:13,480 --> 00:39:15,869
That's not rational but...

582
00:39:18,040 --> 00:39:20,429
I love the thought of that.

583
00:39:38,840 --> 00:39:41,912
- How did Jesse take it?
- Like an orphan.

584
00:39:42,720 --> 00:39:45,951
- What?
- That's just... That's a little poetic for you.

585
00:39:46,040 --> 00:39:48,952
I didn't mean it that way.

586
00:39:49,800 --> 00:39:54,237
- <i>(clears throat)</i> I want to ask you a favour.
- Oh, jeez. Another favour.

587
00:39:54,320 --> 00:39:58,871
I wonder if you wouldn't mind
taking a look at this.

588
00:39:58,960 --> 00:40:01,155
File on your parents?

589
00:40:02,240 --> 00:40:04,151
Yeah, OK.

590
00:40:04,240 --> 00:40:07,630
Do you want to think about it?
It's a pretty big favour.

591
00:40:07,720 --> 00:40:09,836
You'd do it for me.

592
00:40:09,920 --> 00:40:12,070
Yeah, I would.

593
00:40:13,440 --> 00:40:16,477
I'm proud you asked, Temperance.

594
00:40:17,280 --> 00:40:21,831
Uh, Dr Brennan? Uh, Angela wants to know
if we should order anything for you.

595
00:40:21,920 --> 00:40:25,276
No, I'm not staying. Thanks, Zack.

596
00:40:25,360 --> 00:40:30,275
Guess we caught another one, right?
All for one and one for all?

597
00:40:30,360 --> 00:40:36,674
I'll take a look at this and see what they
didn't give you, and I'll get back to you, OK?

598
00:40:36,760 --> 00:40:38,830
Back to ignoring Zack?

599
00:40:38,920 --> 00:40:42,799
All right, look. I know you don't approve
but, you know, it works for us.

600
00:40:42,880 --> 00:40:45,997
- It worked for him, so I...
- Yeah, I get it.

601
00:40:46,080 --> 00:40:48,958
And it... it's kinda sweet.

602
00:40:50,560 --> 00:40:53,836
Hey, you know, your people are my people.

603
00:40:54,360 --> 00:40:57,238
I have "people"?

604
00:40:57,800 --> 00:40:59,392
Hey,

605
00:40:59,480 --> 00:41:01,471
I have people.

606
00:41:03,640 --> 00:41:09,192
♪ <i>Is there anybody in there?</i>

607
00:41:09,280 --> 00:41:12,033
♪ <i>How do you feel?</i>

608
00:41:12,120 --> 00:41:15,271
♪ <i>Are you aware</i>

609
00:41:15,360 --> 00:41:20,673
♪ <i>When you lay your head to sleep at night?</i>

610
00:41:20,760 --> 00:41:23,558
♪ <i>How do you breathe?</i>

611
00:41:23,640 --> 00:41:26,200
♪ <i>How can you live</i>

612
00:41:26,920 --> 00:41:32,233
♪ <i>In a world made of make-believe?</i>

613
00:41:32,320 --> 00:41:35,710
♪ <i>How do you dream?</i>

614
00:42:00,960 --> 00:42:03,793
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke

615
00:42:07,720 --> 00:42:09,039
What's that mean?

616
00:42:09,800 --> 00:42:11,791
ENGLISH SDH

