1
00:00:01,080 --> 00:00:04,311
<i>(man) 7:30 right now.</i>
<i>Coming up, a recap of a disturbing story...</i>

2
00:00:04,400 --> 00:00:07,710
<i>(man #2) Skeletal remains discovered</i>
<i>by a group of students...</i>

3
00:00:07,800 --> 00:00:10,268
<i>(woman) The remains</i>
<i>have not been identified.</i>

4
00:00:10,360 --> 00:00:13,238
<i>There's no word</i>
<i>as to whether foul play is suspected.</i>

5
00:00:13,320 --> 00:00:17,711
Dale, the word most repeated
by the young witnesses we spoke to: Horror,

6
00:00:17,800 --> 00:00:20,439
as in "it looked like a horror movie".

7
00:00:20,520 --> 00:00:23,796
Now we're going to go to another break.

8
00:00:23,880 --> 00:00:29,796
I hate press cases. More than three cameras
show, some detective kicks it to his captain

9
00:00:29,880 --> 00:00:32,269
who kicks it up to the chief and to the FBI.

10
00:00:32,360 --> 00:00:35,636
And you, bang, kick it down to me.
Which I thank you for, sir.

11
00:00:35,720 --> 00:00:38,712
I want this closed.
I don't want to pick up Sunday's <i>Post</i>

12
00:00:38,800 --> 00:00:43,396
and read, "Church kids find mystery corpse
dressed for Halloween, FBI clueless."

13
00:00:43,480 --> 00:00:47,359
I guarantee you won't read that, sir.
OK, I'm on it. Bones.

14
00:00:47,440 --> 00:00:49,908
- I got here as soon as I could.
- Yeah, great.

15
00:00:50,000 --> 00:00:54,471
- I pull you from anything important?
- A 9,600-year-old Caucasoid female skeleton.

16
00:00:54,560 --> 00:00:56,949
It was found in the Kunlun mountains
in China.

17
00:00:57,040 --> 00:01:00,953
An investigation is under way.
I'm contributing stress-marker analysis.

18
00:01:01,040 --> 00:01:05,431
I think you're gonna find this
very interesting too.

19
00:01:10,760 --> 00:01:11,909
Ooh.

20
00:01:12,000 --> 00:01:13,911
<i>(Bones)</i> What the hell is he wearing?

21
00:01:14,000 --> 00:01:17,276
It's lightweight. Composite.

22
00:01:17,360 --> 00:01:21,672
Some kind of sexual bondage suit.
And there's that bag. That's full of maggots.

23
00:01:21,760 --> 00:01:26,709
That looks like cellulose in there, degraded
from bodily tissues and decomposing fat.

24
00:01:26,800 --> 00:01:28,836
And maggots.

25
00:01:30,920 --> 00:01:34,879
Tibial fractures and ground disturbance
suggest total body impact.

26
00:01:34,960 --> 00:01:39,112
- OK, so did he jump or was he pushed?
- <i>(Bones)</i> That's what we have to figure out.

27
00:01:39,200 --> 00:01:43,751
We can take the skeleton in.
Give you a report maybe after next week.

28
00:01:43,840 --> 00:01:49,631
No. Just tell me if I'm looking at a murder.
Maybe, you know, pull a quick ID?

29
00:01:49,720 --> 00:01:55,636
- Don't use your charm smile on me.
- What? It's a mark of respect, that's all.

30
00:01:56,440 --> 00:01:59,318
Epiphyseal union
with the diaphysis on the ankles

31
00:01:59,400 --> 00:02:02,790
suggests the victim
was between 14 and 18 years old.

32
00:02:02,880 --> 00:02:07,396
1.6m tall, of very slight build, suggesting
he was at the younger end of the scale.

33
00:02:07,480 --> 00:02:11,314
That tracks with the bag.
The cellulose we found is a graphic novel.

34
00:02:11,400 --> 00:02:13,311
- A what?
- It's a comic book.

35
00:02:13,400 --> 00:02:14,992
I never read comic books.

36
00:02:15,080 --> 00:02:18,231
Really? I had you pegged
for a graphic novel nut.

37
00:02:18,320 --> 00:02:21,790
The face and cranial vault are badly fractured.

38
00:02:21,880 --> 00:02:26,158
Blows have sent fracture lines between
the mid-frontal and anterior buttresses.

39
00:02:26,240 --> 00:02:28,629
- Why?
- <i>Star Wars, Star Trek</i>,

40
00:02:28,720 --> 00:02:30,711
<i>Stargate, Battlestar Galactica</i>.

41
00:02:30,800 --> 00:02:33,109
Focusing, gentlemen.

42
00:02:33,200 --> 00:02:35,395
Conclusion, a brutal assault killed him.

43
00:02:35,480 --> 00:02:39,189
He was dropped after he was already dead.

44
00:02:39,280 --> 00:02:42,875
His killer wanted it to look like a suicide.

45
00:02:44,800 --> 00:02:47,758
Get his dentals into the NCIC,
see if we can find a match.

46
00:02:47,840 --> 00:02:50,070
Zack, call Stockholm and Beijing.

47
00:02:50,160 --> 00:02:53,914
Our research data on the other thing
is going to be delayed.

48
00:02:54,360 --> 00:02:58,353
- <i>(Booth)</i> It's Warren Granger, age 17.
- <i>(Bones)</i> 17. Small for his age.

49
00:02:58,440 --> 00:03:00,908
Home-schooled. GED obtained last summer.

50
00:03:01,000 --> 00:03:06,711
Mother and stepfather reported him missing
from this very block two months ago.

51
00:03:06,800 --> 00:03:12,352
Bones, if you want to sit this part out, I know
you got some ancient Chinese bones waiting.

52
00:03:12,440 --> 00:03:14,635
No. I'm on this now.

53
00:03:21,360 --> 00:03:23,828
<i>(Bones)</i> It looks like every other house.

54
00:03:23,920 --> 00:03:27,708
<i>(Booth)</i> Every family has its secrets, Bones.

55
00:03:30,360 --> 00:03:32,954
This was Warrers room.

56
00:03:34,240 --> 00:03:37,391
No one's has been up here
since the detective looked it over.

57
00:03:37,480 --> 00:03:40,552
The news said there was
hardly anything left of him.

58
00:03:40,640 --> 00:03:42,631
<i>(sobs)</i>

59
00:03:43,880 --> 00:03:48,749
Can you think of anyone who might've
wanted to harm Warren in any way?

60
00:03:48,840 --> 00:03:53,356
He was always by himself.
No friends, no enemies.

61
00:03:53,800 --> 00:03:58,112
Spent all his time up here
with his comic books and toys.

62
00:03:58,200 --> 00:04:02,398
He was a Ionely kid.
Died before he even had a life.

63
00:04:02,480 --> 00:04:05,233
I really thought he had just run away.

64
00:04:10,640 --> 00:04:12,437
We tried.

65
00:04:12,520 --> 00:04:16,991
Tried to get him out of this place
into some kind of real life.

66
00:04:17,080 --> 00:04:19,753
I even got him ajob at the bowling alley,

67
00:04:19,840 --> 00:04:21,592
but...

68
00:04:21,680 --> 00:04:25,468
he just spent all his money on this... stuff.

69
00:04:26,360 --> 00:04:28,669
Unbelievable.

70
00:04:28,760 --> 00:04:30,751
<i>(sighs)</i>

71
00:04:32,600 --> 00:04:34,636
Quite the collection of comic books.

72
00:04:34,720 --> 00:04:39,430
Hodgins said that the cellulose mass
was a graphic novel.

73
00:04:39,520 --> 00:04:43,911
He sent it to Angela for analysis and recovery.

74
00:04:44,000 --> 00:04:45,797
- Sweet.
- Sweet?

75
00:04:45,880 --> 00:04:51,318
This is <i>Batman</i> number 127 featuring "The
Hammer of Thor". This is won'th about $300.

76
00:04:51,400 --> 00:04:54,710
- Booth, are you a nerd?
- First of all, you mean "geek".

77
00:04:54,800 --> 00:04:58,713
And, no, I'm not. It's quite normal
for an American male to read comic books.

78
00:04:58,800 --> 00:05:01,917
I can't believe you have
anything in common with Warren.

79
00:05:02,000 --> 00:05:05,470
Oh, you mean isolated
with an inner secret life? No.

80
00:05:05,560 --> 00:05:08,074
Hey, I'd say <i>you</i> were more like Warren.

81
00:05:08,160 --> 00:05:10,355
<i>(phone vibrates)</i>

82
00:05:12,360 --> 00:05:17,150
Zack discovered some significant hairline
parry fractures on the right and left ulnae.

83
00:05:17,240 --> 00:05:20,277
- That's his arms.
- I know ulna means forearm.

84
00:05:20,360 --> 00:05:24,638
I pay attention. I also know
that parry fracture means the kid fought back.

85
00:05:24,720 --> 00:05:28,395
Small stature, a geek, and he fought back.

86
00:05:28,480 --> 00:05:31,438
He also got thrown from a roof.

87
00:05:33,640 --> 00:05:38,111
There's nothing but games on here.
There's no journal, there's no documents.

88
00:05:38,200 --> 00:05:42,830
Nothing personal. What did he do
at his desk? I mean, there's a light.

89
00:05:42,920 --> 00:05:47,232
The rug's worn.
He used this area for something. What was it?

90
00:05:47,320 --> 00:05:50,596
Probably where he read his comic books.

91
00:05:59,400 --> 00:06:04,633
I think Warren sat here
and wrote longhand with a ballpoint pen.

92
00:06:04,720 --> 00:06:08,076
That's pretty retro for a geek.

93
00:06:08,160 --> 00:06:13,029
Well, at least we know where
he got the idea for a costume. <i>Citizen 14.</i>

94
00:06:13,120 --> 00:06:15,111
<i>(Bones)</i> A superhero.

95
00:06:48,360 --> 00:06:54,799
Hodgins dried out and separated the pages.
I digitised them and adjusted for ink seepage.

96
00:06:54,880 --> 00:06:58,953
- Was this printed commercially?
- <i>(Angela)</i> No. It's handmade.

97
00:06:59,040 --> 00:07:02,510
- That's what he was writing.
- A comic book starring himself.

98
00:07:02,600 --> 00:07:06,229
A shy adolescent young man
renders himself as a superhero.

99
00:07:06,320 --> 00:07:10,518
Alone in that room all the time. Maybe
Warren got consumed by his own fantasy.

100
00:07:10,600 --> 00:07:14,354
- You think he was out fighting crime?
- Well, the boy got beaten to a pulp

101
00:07:14,440 --> 00:07:17,750
wearing his superhero outfit
in the heaviest crime area of DC.

102
00:07:17,840 --> 00:07:19,796
As you know, being a writer yourself,

103
00:07:19,880 --> 00:07:24,078
Warrers comic book could be infused
with his real-life fears and conflicts.

104
00:07:24,160 --> 00:07:26,276
Especially in the case of an adolescent.

105
00:07:26,360 --> 00:07:28,669
- Can you retrieve any more of this?
- Yeah.

106
00:07:28,760 --> 00:07:31,115
Fine. What's our next step?

107
00:07:31,200 --> 00:07:35,113
Oh, we'll go see if Warren had any friends
his mother didn't know about.

108
00:07:37,760 --> 00:07:41,435
Wait. Warren Granger was
the skeleton corpse those kids found?

109
00:07:41,520 --> 00:07:44,353
Yeah. Sounds like you were close.

110
00:07:44,440 --> 00:07:47,193
How long was he laying there
all dead like that?

111
00:07:47,280 --> 00:07:50,716
- <i>(Bones)</i> For a while.
- How well did you know Warren, Mr Ellis?

112
00:07:50,800 --> 00:07:53,598
He came in here all the time.

113
00:07:53,680 --> 00:07:55,955
You know, he... he knew his stuff.

114
00:07:56,040 --> 00:07:58,076
He was a nice kid.

115
00:07:58,880 --> 00:08:02,634
- Really nice guy.
- Something you're not telling us?

116
00:08:02,720 --> 00:08:05,188
- What do you mean?
- You seem a little nervous.

117
00:08:05,280 --> 00:08:09,319
Well, you just told me that someone I know
is this rotting skeletal corpse

118
00:08:09,400 --> 00:08:12,312
- that's been all over the news.
- <i>(thumping, music)</i>

119
00:08:12,400 --> 00:08:14,834
Is there a party upstairs?

120
00:08:14,920 --> 00:08:19,789
Oh, it's the, uh, Doomsday Group.
I rent it out Thursday nights.

121
00:08:22,160 --> 00:08:26,551
Hey, wait.
Um, Warren was actually one of them.

122
00:08:26,640 --> 00:08:30,553
Oh. That's a handy thing to remember.
Anything else you forget to mention?

123
00:08:30,640 --> 00:08:33,359
No, that's... that's it, I think.

124
00:08:33,440 --> 00:08:35,556
<i>(heavy rock music)</i>

125
00:08:42,560 --> 00:08:45,552
- <i>(boy)</i> I can't take that away.
- We can't break out of...

126
00:08:45,640 --> 00:08:48,200
Excuse me.
This is a private function. Goodbye.

127
00:08:48,280 --> 00:08:52,751
Go ahead. Don't let me stop you from...
What are you doing, exactly?

128
00:08:52,840 --> 00:08:57,595
Guys, this is actually a real live woman.
Something you don't see often.

129
00:08:57,680 --> 00:09:00,274
And like I said, this is a private function, so...

130
00:09:00,360 --> 00:09:03,511
It's the FBI. All right?
Turn it off for a minute, please.

131
00:09:03,600 --> 00:09:05,716
<i>(boy)</i> FBI?

132
00:09:05,800 --> 00:09:09,270
I'm Yasutani the Terrible.
I speak for this clan.

133
00:09:09,960 --> 00:09:14,875
OK, well, we'd like to ask you a few questions
if you're not too, uh... busy.

134
00:09:14,960 --> 00:09:17,428
The costumes, the social awkwardness,

135
00:09:17,520 --> 00:09:21,399
the active fantasy life -
the victim would fit into this subgrouping.

136
00:09:21,480 --> 00:09:24,916
OK, hey, Mr Yakatori the Horrible.

137
00:09:25,000 --> 00:09:27,434
- What's your real name?
- Jeremy Kuznetsky.

138
00:09:27,520 --> 00:09:29,954
Do any of you people know Warren Granger?

139
00:09:30,040 --> 00:09:33,953
- Something happened to Warren?
- Warrers dead. He was murdered.

140
00:09:34,040 --> 00:09:38,033
No, I never said anything about him
being murdered. Neither did the press.

141
00:09:38,120 --> 00:09:43,035
Obviously if you're the FBI he was murdered.
You don't investigate people hit by a bus.

142
00:09:43,120 --> 00:09:45,270
OK. Whers the last time you saw Warren?

143
00:09:45,360 --> 00:09:48,193
- <i>(Jeremy)</i> A couple months ago when he left.
- Left?

144
00:09:48,280 --> 00:09:52,637
Citizen 14 was one of us
until he went psycho and bugged out.

145
00:09:52,720 --> 00:09:55,314
- Called us all posers.
- Pathetic fantasists.

146
00:09:55,400 --> 00:10:00,315
- Was he wearing his, um... outfit?
- His identity, yeah.

147
00:10:00,400 --> 00:10:03,233
- Why do you wear these identities?
- For the game.

148
00:10:03,320 --> 00:10:07,108
- How serious do you take it?
- It's only fun if you take it seriously.

149
00:10:07,200 --> 00:10:11,159
- You always play here?
- "Play" is not exactly the right verb, OK?

150
00:10:11,240 --> 00:10:15,392
Shut up! Shut up! Who cares?
Didrt you hear? Warren is dead!

151
00:10:15,480 --> 00:10:17,357
It's OK, Minnow.

152
00:10:17,440 --> 00:10:19,476
- What's your name?
- Blue Minnow.

153
00:10:19,560 --> 00:10:22,836
When I ask your names,
I want the ones your parents gave you.

154
00:10:22,920 --> 00:10:26,469
Abigail Zealy. Citizen 14 was my partner.

155
00:10:26,560 --> 00:10:29,597
Is that what you call Warren? Citizen 14?

156
00:10:29,680 --> 00:10:32,877
Citizen 14 was my partner.
Warren was my friend.

157
00:10:32,960 --> 00:10:35,872
He was a little more than that.

158
00:10:37,360 --> 00:10:39,476
Hey, hey, hey, hey.

159
00:10:42,560 --> 00:10:46,758
I don't like to judge an entire subculture,
but those people gave me the creeps.

160
00:10:46,840 --> 00:10:49,035
That's because they are creepy.

161
00:10:49,120 --> 00:10:53,272
What I mean is those kids werert
your harmless tutor-you-in-math geeks.

162
00:10:53,360 --> 00:10:57,035
They were the, you know,
set-the-school-on-fire geeks.

163
00:10:57,120 --> 00:10:59,793
Dark nerds. Columbine nerds.

164
00:10:59,880 --> 00:11:03,668
Columbine? You think Yasutani the Terrible
is capable of murder?

165
00:11:03,760 --> 00:11:06,877
I think they get high, they play these games,

166
00:11:06,960 --> 00:11:10,999
they lose their grip on reality
and they believe they are these characters.

167
00:11:11,080 --> 00:11:13,799
You mean like Warren, out fighting crime?

168
00:11:13,880 --> 00:11:17,555
You know, hey, maybe Warren and that guy,
the leader, Yasahama...

169
00:11:17,640 --> 00:11:20,108
- Yasutani the Terrible.
- Yeah.

170
00:11:20,200 --> 00:11:22,031
Maybe him and that guy,

171
00:11:22,120 --> 00:11:25,874
they got into this, you know, magic fight
and it became real.

172
00:11:25,960 --> 00:11:31,318
So you're saying it wasrt Warren who was
murdered, it was his character, Citizen 14.

173
00:11:31,400 --> 00:11:35,313
They're so delusional they don't even know
they've committed a crime.

174
00:11:35,400 --> 00:11:39,188
I'll get Hodgins to see if there's any signs
of drug use in Warrers hair.

175
00:11:40,040 --> 00:11:44,477
Oh, I managed to get some of the text
back from this panel. Cheerful little tyke.

176
00:11:44,560 --> 00:11:46,676
The writer was in pain.

177
00:11:47,120 --> 00:11:50,795
And I don't think it was purely
the adolescent angst of the outsider.

178
00:11:50,880 --> 00:11:54,111
I'd go so far as to say
it wasrt even psychological pain.

179
00:11:54,200 --> 00:11:57,954
He's afraid of actual physical death.

180
00:11:58,040 --> 00:12:00,235
Can you pull all that from a comic book?

181
00:12:00,320 --> 00:12:03,790
Writers reveal more of themselves
than they intend on every page.

182
00:12:03,880 --> 00:12:08,032
I never bought all that English 101 stuff.
Sometimes a river is just a river.

183
00:12:08,120 --> 00:12:11,271
All due respect, but my writing is pure fiction.

184
00:12:11,360 --> 00:12:16,195
I fear you reveal much more of your
world view in your writing than you realise.

185
00:12:16,280 --> 00:12:17,269
Such as?

186
00:12:17,360 --> 00:12:21,751
Such as, archaeologists make good
administrators because they enjoy tedium.

187
00:12:21,840 --> 00:12:26,994
Artists are doomed to a life of Ioneliness cos
they can't think beyond instant gratification.

188
00:12:27,080 --> 00:12:30,231
Such as, FBI guys are hot
and Angela wants to have sex with me.

189
00:12:30,320 --> 00:12:31,878
<i>(Angela)</i> Yeah.

190
00:12:33,280 --> 00:12:37,273
All I'm suggesting is that while Dr Goodman
goes through Warrers writing,

191
00:12:37,360 --> 00:12:41,592
we should concentrate on the hypotheses
congruent with forensic evidence.

192
00:12:41,680 --> 00:12:45,673
I'm going to take another look
at Warren Granger's remains.

193
00:12:45,760 --> 00:12:49,753
In the last 24 hours I've read several dozen
comic books and graphic novels.

194
00:12:49,840 --> 00:12:52,229
Did Hodgins find any sign of drug use?

195
00:12:52,320 --> 00:12:54,311
No.

196
00:12:54,400 --> 00:12:58,279
They're quite interesting.
The graphic novels especially.

197
00:12:58,360 --> 00:13:00,635
After you clean the bones, look for scoring

198
00:13:00,720 --> 00:13:03,871
on the occipital condyle
and the inferior nuchal line.

199
00:13:03,960 --> 00:13:06,633
They're basically a retelling
of the Greek myths

200
00:13:06,720 --> 00:13:09,757
with all superheroes standing in for Hercules.

201
00:13:09,840 --> 00:13:11,910
Half god, half human.

202
00:13:12,000 --> 00:13:13,911
OK, be very careful here.

203
00:13:14,000 --> 00:13:20,189
X-ray shows fragmentation of the cervical
vertebrae consistent with sharp force trauma.

204
00:13:20,280 --> 00:13:25,718
Invulnerability, super strength,
heightened senses, telekinesis...

205
00:13:26,680 --> 00:13:30,275
I'd love to have some of those powers.

206
00:13:30,360 --> 00:13:32,749
Why?

207
00:13:32,840 --> 00:13:38,631
- L-I don't really know. Is that an odd desire?
- Why fantasise? You're smart.

208
00:13:38,720 --> 00:13:42,998
In some ways my intelligence is a handicap.
Well, for one thing, I'm weird.

209
00:13:43,080 --> 00:13:47,790
For another, I tend to make people feel stupid
and they resent me for it.

210
00:13:47,880 --> 00:13:51,350
I suspect it's the same for superpowers.

211
00:13:54,080 --> 00:13:56,548
The victim was stabbed
at the base of the spine.

212
00:13:56,640 --> 00:13:59,552
The spinal cord was severed.
That's what killed him.

213
00:13:59,640 --> 00:14:02,518
I'll clean the bones and try to match a weapon
to the damage.

214
00:14:02,600 --> 00:14:05,910
Which will make you a real hero
in the real world.

215
00:14:07,880 --> 00:14:12,476
In this restored panel from the second
and final volume of <i>Citizen 14</i>

216
00:14:12,560 --> 00:14:16,519
we begin to see a female presence,
beautiful, ethereal,

217
00:14:16,600 --> 00:14:19,319
which he calls the Opalescence.

218
00:14:19,400 --> 00:14:21,960
A girl he literally can't approach.

219
00:14:23,120 --> 00:14:25,953
What if Warren was only...

220
00:14:26,040 --> 00:14:29,874
you know, supplying
his own masturbatory materials?

221
00:14:29,960 --> 00:14:34,272
Yes. Lonely adolescent boy.
But the story moves beyond that dimension.

222
00:14:34,360 --> 00:14:38,194
Here we see the idolised female Opalescence

223
00:14:38,280 --> 00:14:42,876
cowering before a dark male figure
referred to only as the Twisted.

224
00:14:42,960 --> 00:14:47,875
So Citizen 14 wants to rescue
the Opalescence from the Twisted.

225
00:14:47,960 --> 00:14:50,793
Could this be Warrers mother
and stepfather?

226
00:14:50,880 --> 00:14:56,113
There are elements of romantic love.
This girl surrounded by blue...

227
00:14:58,760 --> 00:15:04,312
You know, they did mention that one of
those comic-book geeks was a blue girl.

228
00:15:04,400 --> 00:15:06,914
I'd say she's definitely won'th questioning.

229
00:15:07,000 --> 00:15:11,551
- <i>(Booth)</i> Blue Minnow. That's your alter ego.
- Abigail Zealy is my alter ego.

230
00:15:11,640 --> 00:15:14,916
Did you, Abigail, have a relationship
with Warren Granger?

231
00:15:15,000 --> 00:15:18,595
Or did the Blue Minnow
have a relationship with Citizen 14?

232
00:15:18,680 --> 00:15:22,559
- Or any combination thereof?
- Neither.

233
00:15:22,640 --> 00:15:25,677
Warren had a girlfriend. At Capital Bowl.

234
00:15:25,760 --> 00:15:29,799
- What's the girlfriend's name, Abby?
- He never told us her name.

235
00:15:29,880 --> 00:15:32,519
It was just a physical thing

236
00:15:32,600 --> 00:15:35,751
and... and it was almost over.

237
00:15:35,840 --> 00:15:39,435
Warren and I had a connection.
He couldn't deny that.

238
00:15:39,520 --> 00:15:44,435
Before he disappeared,
he gave me his entire Neil Gaiman collection,

239
00:15:44,520 --> 00:15:46,556
his favourite work beside his own.

240
00:15:46,640 --> 00:15:51,555
In his own work he describes a woman
known as the Opalescence.

241
00:15:51,640 --> 00:15:55,076
Do you believe that's supposed to be you?

242
00:15:55,160 --> 00:15:57,390
What do you think?

243
00:15:57,480 --> 00:16:00,517
We think it's another girl entirely.

244
00:16:02,480 --> 00:16:05,153
Does that bother you?

245
00:16:05,240 --> 00:16:07,310
OK...

246
00:16:07,400 --> 00:16:10,790
Maybe the others told you I'm obsessed.
I know.

247
00:16:10,880 --> 00:16:14,111
Because they never got Warren like I did.

248
00:16:14,200 --> 00:16:18,159
He was right. They are posers.

249
00:16:18,240 --> 00:16:20,913
- But Warren wasrt?
- Warren believed.

250
00:16:21,000 --> 00:16:25,152
He believed in truth.
He believed in doing what was right.

251
00:16:25,240 --> 00:16:27,276
He <i>was</i> Citizen 14.

252
00:16:27,360 --> 00:16:29,351
Citizen 14 is real.

253
00:16:29,440 --> 00:16:34,958
- Warren didn't fit in with the others?
- I just said! Warren was better!

254
00:16:35,760 --> 00:16:38,115
He was a really nice guy.

255
00:16:38,200 --> 00:16:41,431
Were you aware that Jeremy Kuznetsky

256
00:16:41,520 --> 00:16:44,512
and Kenneth Vert

257
00:16:44,600 --> 00:16:46,477
have police records?

258
00:16:46,560 --> 00:16:48,357
Yeah.

259
00:16:48,440 --> 00:16:51,830
It's nothing interesting, though.

260
00:16:51,920 --> 00:16:55,071
It's, like, vandalism and trespassing.

261
00:16:55,160 --> 00:16:57,196
You can't take them seriously.

262
00:16:57,280 --> 00:17:00,078
- What, as criminals?
- As anything.

263
00:17:00,160 --> 00:17:02,833
OK. Well, what would be interesting
as a crime?

264
00:17:02,920 --> 00:17:05,309
Something that took courage.

265
00:17:05,400 --> 00:17:08,039
Something that meant something.

266
00:17:08,120 --> 00:17:10,076
Like murder?

267
00:17:10,160 --> 00:17:12,355
Yeah. Like murder.

268
00:17:17,640 --> 00:17:21,349
Warren Granger on the night he died,
wearing his costume.

269
00:17:21,440 --> 00:17:23,431
Start the sequence.

270
00:17:25,600 --> 00:17:28,990
Cause of death was a severed spinal cord.

271
00:17:32,200 --> 00:17:34,998
- We can rule out Abigail Zealy.
- How do you figure?

272
00:17:35,080 --> 00:17:38,709
Abigail doesn't have enough strength
to sever Warrers spinal cord.

273
00:17:38,800 --> 00:17:42,679
What about his stepdad?
Or the other kids at the comic shop?

274
00:17:42,760 --> 00:17:46,639
Well, if the physicality of the murderer
is between 5'10 and 6'1,

275
00:17:46,720 --> 00:17:50,030
I'd say yes to them all,
depending on the weapon.

276
00:17:54,200 --> 00:17:56,589
What had he done
to make somebody so angry?

277
00:17:56,680 --> 00:18:00,958
Zack's cleaning the bones now. Maybe
we'll find something that we've missed.

278
00:18:01,680 --> 00:18:05,195
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> What are you reading?
- <i>(Zack)</i> I'm doing research.

279
00:18:05,280 --> 00:18:09,558
- By reading a comic book?
- Intensely allegorical modern myths.

280
00:18:09,640 --> 00:18:12,393
- You're reading Bugs Bunny.
- On the surface, yes.

281
00:18:12,480 --> 00:18:15,836
But if you dig deeper,
the subtext becomes apparent.

282
00:18:15,920 --> 00:18:19,037
The conflict is representative
of the Darwinian struggle

283
00:18:19,120 --> 00:18:21,395
between avians and mammals for dominance.

284
00:18:21,480 --> 00:18:24,438
Based on Bugs giving Daffy
a cigar made out of dynamite?

285
00:18:24,520 --> 00:18:26,317
Yeah.

286
00:18:26,920 --> 00:18:30,549
And then here he explodes, but not really.

287
00:18:31,480 --> 00:18:34,153
- You have a problem, my man.
- What?

288
00:18:34,240 --> 00:18:38,870
- It looks like you degraded the bones.
- Impossible. It's only a 4% peroxide solution.

289
00:18:38,960 --> 00:18:42,635
Then what's that bubbling and pitting
on the periosteum?

290
00:18:42,720 --> 00:18:48,716
- A 4% solution wouldn't cause that.
- Is it some kind of systemic deterioration?

291
00:18:51,840 --> 00:18:56,311
- <i>(Zack)</i> Intertrochanteric crest is eaten away.
- What do you think it is?

292
00:18:56,400 --> 00:18:58,595
This kid was sick.

293
00:19:08,560 --> 00:19:11,313
- You smell that?
- Yes, I do.

294
00:19:11,400 --> 00:19:13,277
You know what that is, Bones?

295
00:19:13,360 --> 00:19:15,351
Wax, popcorn...

296
00:19:16,400 --> 00:19:18,038
feet, deodorant...

297
00:19:18,120 --> 00:19:23,035
- That is America, Bones.
- You keep your bowling ball in the car?

298
00:19:23,120 --> 00:19:28,717
Oh, I figure we ask a few questions about
Warren Granger, maybe bowl a few frames.

299
00:19:28,800 --> 00:19:32,793
- Nothing like sport to take the edge off...
- This is not a sport.

300
00:19:32,880 --> 00:19:36,714
- How do you figure?
- There's no physical benefit, so it's like golf.

301
00:19:36,800 --> 00:19:38,950
It's not a sport. It's an activity.

302
00:19:39,040 --> 00:19:43,875
Could you please, maybe just for once,
try not to piss everyone off around you?

303
00:19:43,960 --> 00:19:46,235
Yeah. Sorry.

304
00:19:46,320 --> 00:19:49,073
Are you good at this... sport?

305
00:19:49,160 --> 00:19:52,038
My average is over 200,
less than two opens per game.

306
00:19:52,120 --> 00:19:56,033
One match I had 211 strikes out of 431 shots.

307
00:19:56,120 --> 00:19:59,192
- 29 opens in 39 games.
- What does that mean?

308
00:19:59,280 --> 00:20:02,272
- I won bowling awards.
- I won the Marshall H Dixon Award

309
00:20:02,360 --> 00:20:05,557
for my paper on George Romanes
and physiological selection.

310
00:20:05,640 --> 00:20:08,552
My God, it's like we lead parallel lives.

311
00:20:08,640 --> 00:20:11,996
- You need shoes?
- Yeah. Uh, looking for the manager.

312
00:20:12,520 --> 00:20:15,478
Ted McGruder. FBI, huh?

313
00:20:15,560 --> 00:20:18,518
We're investigating the death
of one of your employees.

314
00:20:18,600 --> 00:20:20,238
Warren Granger.

315
00:20:20,320 --> 00:20:22,151
Warren?

316
00:20:22,240 --> 00:20:25,789
He didn't show up for his paycheck.
I thought he found anotherjob

317
00:20:25,880 --> 00:20:30,271
and didn't want to give notice.
He's weird like that. Good kid, though.

318
00:20:30,360 --> 00:20:32,112
- <i>(boy)</i> Bye-bye!
- <i>(laughter)</i>

319
00:20:32,200 --> 00:20:34,634
Aw, don't pout!

320
00:20:34,720 --> 00:20:37,792
Ted, I talked to them
but they just keep giving me lip.

321
00:20:37,880 --> 00:20:42,431
Luce, these people are with the FBI.
They're here about Warren Granger.

322
00:20:42,520 --> 00:20:45,671
- Warren? What about him?
- He's deceased.

323
00:20:45,760 --> 00:20:48,399
Oh, my God.

324
00:20:48,480 --> 00:20:52,996
- I told you he didn't quit.
- I was wrong. This is my wife, Lucy.

325
00:20:53,080 --> 00:20:55,753
- Sorry.
- That's OK.

326
00:20:55,840 --> 00:21:01,119
- How often do those kids come in here?
- <i>(Ted)</i> Those jokers? Weekends, mostly.

327
00:21:01,200 --> 00:21:04,590
They used to come in a lot more
but in these crazy costumes.

328
00:21:04,680 --> 00:21:08,992
I told them I'd allow it on Halloween
but that's it.

329
00:21:09,080 --> 00:21:14,518
Warrers girlfriend here? We were informed
that Warrers girlfriend worked here.

330
00:21:14,600 --> 00:21:18,195
If you ever met Warren
you'd know he's not the girlfriend type of kid.

331
00:21:18,280 --> 00:21:22,398
There was a girl
who came by to see him sometimes.

332
00:21:24,560 --> 00:21:27,279
Yeah. Yeah, that's her.
L-I don't know her name,

333
00:21:27,360 --> 00:21:30,352
but I don't think Warren
was all that glad to see her.

334
00:21:30,440 --> 00:21:33,876
If she called,
he'd ask me to tell her that he wasrt here.

335
00:21:33,960 --> 00:21:34,949
Brennan.

336
00:21:35,040 --> 00:21:41,149
- Maybe he was just trying to dodge her.
- Excuse me just one moment, please.

337
00:21:41,240 --> 00:21:43,390
OK, slow down, Zack, and repeat that.

338
00:21:43,480 --> 00:21:48,679
Hypercellularity with total effacement
of the marrow space. Osteoblasts at 26%.

339
00:21:48,760 --> 00:21:52,070
OK. Good work, Zack.
Keep working on the weapon ID.

340
00:21:52,160 --> 00:21:54,390
I take it we're not getting any bowling in?

341
00:21:54,480 --> 00:22:00,271
Zack said that if Warren hadrt been murdered
two months ago, he'd be dead by now.

342
00:22:02,680 --> 00:22:05,353
When you said Warren was sick,
you meant leukaemia?

343
00:22:05,440 --> 00:22:06,509
Yes.

344
00:22:06,600 --> 00:22:09,273
But by the time he was 11,
he was in remission.

345
00:22:09,360 --> 00:22:15,230
The hypercellular activity I saw
is only present in advanced cancer cases.

346
00:22:15,320 --> 00:22:17,959
He must have been very ill.

347
00:22:18,040 --> 00:22:19,871
You didn't notice?

348
00:22:19,960 --> 00:22:23,270
We tried to be there for Warren,
but he wouldn't let us in.

349
00:22:23,360 --> 00:22:27,319
Right when you thought you'd built
a bridge of trust, he'd quit on you.

350
00:22:27,400 --> 00:22:29,994
He quit trying to face reality.

351
00:22:32,520 --> 00:22:35,478
Maybe your son didn't want you
to have to face it.

352
00:22:35,560 --> 00:22:40,315
I mean, he knew his situation was dire,
and he decided to tough it out on his own.

353
00:22:42,880 --> 00:22:45,952
Yes. He saw what it did to me the first time.

354
00:22:46,040 --> 00:22:50,909
It's not that he quit.
It's that he didn't want me to suffer.

355
00:22:59,000 --> 00:23:02,629
You said her son didn't tell her he was sick
to make her feel better.

356
00:23:02,720 --> 00:23:05,393
- You don't believe that?
- People don't do that.

357
00:23:05,480 --> 00:23:08,313
- So you told her that to make her feel better?
- Right.

358
00:23:08,400 --> 00:23:15,033
You just did what you said people don't do.
I wonder why he didn't tell his mother.

359
00:23:15,120 --> 00:23:18,510
Maybe he was caught up in the romance
of being a dying superhero.

360
00:23:18,600 --> 00:23:21,194
Adolescent angst, all that.

361
00:23:21,280 --> 00:23:24,272
- What do you really think?
- <i>(sighs)</i>

362
00:23:25,240 --> 00:23:28,710
The truth is, I think the boy was looking
how to be a man.

363
00:23:28,800 --> 00:23:31,598
All on his own.
He was doing the best that he could.

364
00:23:31,680 --> 00:23:33,910
Heroes don't whine about being sick.

365
00:23:34,000 --> 00:23:38,391
- Something like that. Poor kid.
- Did they know about the leukaemia?

366
00:23:38,480 --> 00:23:40,869
- No. He kept it a secret.
- Tough guy, huh?

367
00:23:40,960 --> 00:23:45,033
You were right. The kid knew he was
facing death. This changes motivation.

368
00:23:45,120 --> 00:23:47,759
- The killer's motivation?
- Warren Granger's.

369
00:23:47,840 --> 00:23:50,035
He was emboldened
by knowing he would die.

370
00:23:50,120 --> 00:23:53,476
- He went looking for a fight.
- He went looking for the Twisted.

371
00:23:53,560 --> 00:24:00,238
Wait. Wait. We are allowing the comic-book
story to generate too many hypotheses.

372
00:24:00,320 --> 00:24:03,118
I only heard
the "go get the bad guy" hypothesis.

373
00:24:03,200 --> 00:24:05,316
- It's too general.
- <i>(Bones)</i> Yes.

374
00:24:05,400 --> 00:24:09,154
Perhaps the Opalescence
represented Warrers better nature

375
00:24:09,240 --> 00:24:13,950
and the Twisted was a reflection
of his darker sexual impulses -

376
00:24:14,040 --> 00:24:17,874
a theme I assume is common
in teenage fiction.

377
00:24:17,960 --> 00:24:19,951
And the drawings...

378
00:24:21,440 --> 00:24:23,556
Hello? Bones?

379
00:24:23,640 --> 00:24:25,949
The drawings.

380
00:24:26,040 --> 00:24:30,477
Warren wrote the comics, but there was
no evidence that he knew how to draw.

381
00:24:30,560 --> 00:24:34,189
Dr Brennan, I found an extra piece of bone
I can't account for.

382
00:24:34,520 --> 00:24:36,829
Someone else drew the comic.

383
00:24:38,120 --> 00:24:39,189
Stew Ellis.

384
00:24:39,280 --> 00:24:41,475
- What about him?
- Look.

385
00:24:41,560 --> 00:24:46,588
Warren Granger wrote this comic book
but it was drawn by Stew Ellis.

386
00:24:49,720 --> 00:24:53,429
I told you, I knew Warren from the store, OK?
He was a serious investor.

387
00:24:53,520 --> 00:24:56,114
- Did he owe you money, Stew?
- What?

388
00:24:56,200 --> 00:25:01,558
Was it creative differences
or was it you just didn't get enough credit?

389
00:25:02,560 --> 00:25:05,199
<i>(sighs)</i> No, it was none of that.

390
00:25:05,280 --> 00:25:09,034
Look, why didn't you tell me
you were partners when I asked you earlier?

391
00:25:09,120 --> 00:25:14,035
Cos we had a big argument.
I didn't want you to think I had a motive.

392
00:25:14,120 --> 00:25:18,079
OK. What did you argue about?
Abigail Zealy?

393
00:25:18,160 --> 00:25:22,278
- No, man. Just merchandising.
- You argued about merchandising?

394
00:25:22,360 --> 00:25:25,432
Yeah. Warren thought he deserved 70%
for the concept,

395
00:25:25,520 --> 00:25:27,909
but I think since I did the drawings, I...

396
00:25:28,000 --> 00:25:30,389
- Do you have a publisher?
- No.

397
00:25:30,480 --> 00:25:36,715
And now we never will. Look, if you think
that I killed Warren, I'm not that stupid, man.

398
00:25:36,800 --> 00:25:42,511
- So, who do you think killed Warren?
- I... I don't know. Definitely not me, OK?

399
00:25:42,600 --> 00:25:46,673
Well, Stew, as of this moment,
you're the prime suspect in Warrers murder.

400
00:25:46,760 --> 00:25:48,910
<i>(sighs)</i> Why?

401
00:25:49,000 --> 00:25:53,471
You lied about your relationship with Warren.
If I were you, I would think really hard

402
00:25:53,560 --> 00:25:56,791
if there's anything else you haven't told me.

403
00:25:56,880 --> 00:25:59,155
All right. Abby.

404
00:25:59,240 --> 00:26:01,879
Abby?

405
00:26:03,720 --> 00:26:05,153
Triangle.

406
00:26:05,240 --> 00:26:10,030
I hooked up with her a few times,
but she was obsessed with Warren.

407
00:26:10,120 --> 00:26:15,114
- So, you did argue about her?
- No, man. Warren never wanted Abby.

408
00:26:15,560 --> 00:26:17,676
It made you jealous that she wanted him?

409
00:26:17,760 --> 00:26:20,877
Dude, Abby's cute
in a chick geek kind of way,

410
00:26:20,960 --> 00:26:24,236
but she's not that kind of Betty
you go to the death chamber for.

411
00:26:24,320 --> 00:26:27,517
OK. You're one of those guys
who's way too good at lying.

412
00:26:27,600 --> 00:26:30,637
Dude, I'm an artist. What do you want?

413
00:26:31,680 --> 00:26:37,755
I found the extra piece of bone
lodged here in the odontoid process of C2.

414
00:26:39,720 --> 00:26:45,670
L-I went through all the chipping and damage
again but I can't find where it came from.

415
00:26:45,760 --> 00:26:49,309
- <i>(Bones)</i> It's not from the cervical vertebrae.
- Oh, it's not?

416
00:26:49,400 --> 00:26:53,029
It's from a long bone,
probably the deltoid process of a humerus.

417
00:26:53,120 --> 00:26:57,750
- An arm bone?
- I need you to set up the microtome.

418
00:26:57,840 --> 00:27:00,673
And get me paraffin
and an embedding mould.

419
00:27:00,760 --> 00:27:03,194
- Are you prepping your own bone slide?
- Yes.

420
00:27:03,280 --> 00:27:06,317
- Usually I do that for you.
- This is a tough one, Zack.

421
00:27:06,400 --> 00:27:10,996
The piece is small and I need to make sure
there's enough left for a DNA sample.

422
00:27:11,080 --> 00:27:13,719
Wait. Warren Granger's arm bones
are complete.

423
00:27:13,800 --> 00:27:17,236
This extra bone fragment
didn't come from Warren Granger.

424
00:27:17,320 --> 00:27:20,630
Warren was the victim of a violent attack.
He fought back.

425
00:27:20,720 --> 00:27:24,838
It's possible that during that struggle
he struck his attacker

426
00:27:24,920 --> 00:27:27,309
with the same weapon
that was used to kill him.

427
00:27:27,400 --> 00:27:32,110
Which means that piece of bone
could've come from his murderer.

428
00:27:34,360 --> 00:27:36,351
<i>(exhales)</i>

429
00:27:38,640 --> 00:27:40,631
What are you doing?

430
00:27:40,720 --> 00:27:42,711
<i>(exhales)</i>

431
00:27:43,600 --> 00:27:47,673
Breathing dissipates static electricity
and makes it easier to cut.

432
00:27:47,760 --> 00:27:50,069
You seem nervous.

433
00:27:50,160 --> 00:27:56,235
If I get this right I'll be able to tell you the age,
sex and race of Warren Granger's killer.

434
00:27:57,840 --> 00:28:00,229
- Stew was the artist.
- <i>(exhales)</i>

435
00:28:00,320 --> 00:28:05,075
Really? You think he killed Warren
over artistic differences?

436
00:28:05,160 --> 00:28:08,152
- He also had a thing for Abby.
- Wow.

437
00:28:08,240 --> 00:28:12,950
Yeah. For a recluse, Warren Granger,
he had his thumb in a lot of pies.

438
00:28:13,040 --> 00:28:16,828
You said before
that Warren reminded you of me.

439
00:28:16,920 --> 00:28:18,831
You think I'm just like him,

440
00:28:18,920 --> 00:28:24,472
that he hid from life by immersing himself
in a fantasy world where he fought crime,

441
00:28:24,560 --> 00:28:29,873
and I do the same thing,
only I don't have superpowers. I...

442
00:28:29,960 --> 00:28:33,316
- I have science.
- No, Bones, you do fight crime.

443
00:28:33,400 --> 00:28:38,599
It's not a fantasy. As far as any normal person
is concerned, you do have superpowers.

444
00:28:38,680 --> 00:28:41,114
- You're just saying that.
- I don't do that.

445
00:28:41,200 --> 00:28:46,672
Yes, you do. You lied to Warren Granger's
mother to make her feel better.

446
00:28:46,760 --> 00:28:49,274
That seems to be your superpower.

447
00:28:49,360 --> 00:28:52,432
Look, this piece of bone you're analysing,

448
00:28:52,520 --> 00:28:55,751
how did it get lodged
in Warren Granger's neck?

449
00:28:55,840 --> 00:29:00,436
It was deposited by the same weapon
that severed his spinal cord.

450
00:29:00,520 --> 00:29:03,239
Doesrt make it the killer's bone.

451
00:29:05,680 --> 00:29:08,478
You're thinking a separate murder victim?

452
00:29:08,560 --> 00:29:10,471
Opalescence?

453
00:29:10,560 --> 00:29:13,518
The woman he loved.

454
00:29:13,600 --> 00:29:16,194
- I don't think she's dead.
- Why?

455
00:29:16,280 --> 00:29:18,316
<i>(Bones)</i> This is an arm bone.

456
00:29:18,400 --> 00:29:22,757
Has anyone we've seen on this case
been favouring her arm?

457
00:29:22,840 --> 00:29:24,512
Not that I've noticed.

458
00:29:24,600 --> 00:29:28,673
That's because you're not an anthropologist...

459
00:29:29,680 --> 00:29:32,194
- with superpowers.
- Ha.

460
00:29:32,720 --> 00:29:35,439
That's good. <i>(laughs)</i>

461
00:29:37,720 --> 00:29:40,314
Oh. Hello.

462
00:29:40,400 --> 00:29:43,551
- Any news about Warren?
- We're still in the initial phase.

463
00:29:43,640 --> 00:29:49,272
You didn't happen to keep that last payroll
cheque for Warren that you told me about?

464
00:29:49,360 --> 00:29:52,397
- By law I have to, yeah.
- You mind digging that out for us?

465
00:29:52,480 --> 00:29:54,550
I apologise for the inconvenience.

466
00:29:54,640 --> 00:29:57,438
I guess. It's probably in the file somewhere.

467
00:29:57,520 --> 00:30:01,718
- What do you need the paycheck for?
- <i>(Booth)</i> Ah, it's technical.

468
00:30:01,800 --> 00:30:03,597
Mrs McGruder,

469
00:30:03,680 --> 00:30:07,468
- what's wrong with your left side?
- Why would you ask me that?

470
00:30:07,560 --> 00:30:12,680
I noticed how you held yourself the last time
I was here. I didn't think anything of it...

471
00:30:12,760 --> 00:30:15,513
- What?
- She wants to know how you hurt yourself.

472
00:30:15,600 --> 00:30:19,798
You walk as though your left ribs are cracked.
Also, you favour your left arm.

473
00:30:19,880 --> 00:30:21,233
Oh! I, um...

474
00:30:21,320 --> 00:30:23,550
l-I fell on the lanes.

475
00:30:23,640 --> 00:30:25,835
They're very slippery.

476
00:30:25,920 --> 00:30:29,879
Falling would bruise a number of ribs.
You're favouring only one or two.

477
00:30:29,960 --> 00:30:33,077
The type of damage done by a fist.

478
00:30:35,080 --> 00:30:37,640
Look, were you and Warren close?

479
00:30:37,720 --> 00:30:39,756
He was a nice kid.

480
00:30:40,640 --> 00:30:42,870
A really nice kid.

481
00:30:42,960 --> 00:30:45,110
Here it is.

482
00:30:45,200 --> 00:30:49,034
You two want to bowl a few frames?
Got some empty lanes.

483
00:30:49,120 --> 00:30:52,999
- I'll see you in the comic books, buster.
- What?

484
00:30:53,080 --> 00:30:55,469
<i>(Booth)</i> Thanks. I'll get this back to you.

485
00:30:55,560 --> 00:30:57,596
It's, "See you in the funny pages."

486
00:30:57,680 --> 00:31:00,478
OK, I took a liberty. Her husband beats her.

487
00:31:00,560 --> 00:31:02,915
Bones, talk about multiple hypotheses!

488
00:31:03,000 --> 00:31:05,468
It's a leap, yes, but it was bound to happen,

489
00:31:05,560 --> 00:31:09,189
me spending so much time with you.
I mean that as a compliment.

490
00:31:09,280 --> 00:31:14,149
OK. So Warrers former boss is the Twisted
and the boss's wife is the Opalescence.

491
00:31:14,240 --> 00:31:16,435
- Go back and arrest him.
- It's not enough.

492
00:31:16,520 --> 00:31:19,751
For that, we need something
just a little bit more real.

493
00:31:19,840 --> 00:31:22,559
- Evidence.
- Cold hard facts, baby.

494
00:31:34,360 --> 00:31:38,114
Dr Brennan,
based on your histology and the DNA,

495
00:31:38,200 --> 00:31:41,795
the bone found on Warrers neck
came from a Caucasian male, mid 30s.

496
00:31:41,880 --> 00:31:44,952
McGruder.
What? Can you get any more specific?

497
00:31:45,040 --> 00:31:48,510
- We need the weapon.
- I can get a warrant for whatever you want.

498
00:31:48,600 --> 00:31:50,909
We don't know what we're looking for.

499
00:31:51,000 --> 00:31:54,515
We hit a dead end reverse-engineering it
from the mark on the neck.

500
00:31:54,600 --> 00:31:57,319
- Too much fragmentation.
- <i>(Bones)</i> Wait.

501
00:31:57,400 --> 00:32:00,676
You said that in books
you could find the real-world version.

502
00:32:00,760 --> 00:32:05,550
- Yeah. If you know you, it's pretty obvious.
- Well, give me an example.

503
00:32:05,640 --> 00:32:10,555
In your book, your partner's a former Olympic
boxer who spoke six different languages.

504
00:32:10,640 --> 00:32:12,949
In real life, you got me.

505
00:32:13,040 --> 00:32:18,637
So what you're saying is that
reality falls far, far short of the fictional.

506
00:32:18,720 --> 00:32:19,709
Yeah.

507
00:32:19,800 --> 00:32:21,995
Thanks a lot, Bones.

508
00:32:23,000 --> 00:32:28,996
Warren Granger's spinal cord was severed
by something sharp, but not a knife.

509
00:32:30,200 --> 00:32:33,112
OK, if it wasrt a knife, what was it?

510
00:32:33,560 --> 00:32:37,553
The closest match I could find would be
a corkscrew or a Tibetan skull knife,

511
00:32:37,640 --> 00:32:42,111
but neither of them explain how foreign bone
was left lodged in the vertebrae.

512
00:32:42,200 --> 00:32:47,433
- Pull up Citizen 14's weapon thing.
- It was a boomerang thing, like a sonic gun.

513
00:32:47,520 --> 00:32:51,229
A laser cutlass. That thing that allowed him
to hear through walls.

514
00:32:51,320 --> 00:32:55,552
We're looking for something that has
a drabber version in the real world.

515
00:32:55,640 --> 00:32:57,995
Why would he be killed by his own weapon?

516
00:32:58,080 --> 00:33:01,595
He had it on him the night
he decided to confront Ted McGruder.

517
00:33:01,680 --> 00:33:05,468
- Citizen 14's arsenal.
- What's that?

518
00:33:05,560 --> 00:33:09,473
His main weapon. It's a three-sided
throwing knife that returns to him.

519
00:33:09,560 --> 00:33:15,271
None of them make the wounds that resemble
the one that severed Warrers spinal cord.

520
00:33:15,360 --> 00:33:17,351
- It was just an idea.
- Bones...

521
00:33:17,440 --> 00:33:20,910
No. L-I fell into the exact thing
that I warned you about.

522
00:33:21,000 --> 00:33:25,039
Developing too many hypotheses
not grounded in fact.

523
00:33:25,120 --> 00:33:28,351
No. Bones, I know exactly
which drab real-world thing

524
00:33:28,440 --> 00:33:31,512
was used to murder Warren Granger.

525
00:33:32,720 --> 00:33:35,996
<i>(Booth)</i> He wants to feel like a hero.
He's facing a damsel in distress.

526
00:33:36,080 --> 00:33:39,470
- Lucy is ten years older.
- It's not the damsel part that matters.

527
00:33:39,560 --> 00:33:42,552
It's the distress that appealed to the kid.
I mean, look.

528
00:33:42,640 --> 00:33:45,154
It wasrt about sex or romance. It never was.

529
00:33:45,240 --> 00:33:49,313
He wanted to make a difference in the world
before he died.

530
00:33:51,800 --> 00:33:54,394
I told you he was more like you than me.

531
00:33:54,480 --> 00:33:57,040
<i>(radio) 22705. Dispatch.</i>

532
00:33:57,120 --> 00:33:58,599
22705.

533
00:33:58,680 --> 00:34:02,355
<i>Unit sent to suspect's residence</i>
<i>reports the domicile is empty.</i>

534
00:34:02,440 --> 00:34:05,989
- What about the wife?
- <i>Negative. Search team is inside the house.</i>

535
00:34:06,080 --> 00:34:08,469
<i>It's empty. Signs of flight.</i>

536
00:34:09,920 --> 00:34:12,115
Affirmative, Dispatch.

537
00:34:12,640 --> 00:34:15,234
He beats her
but she takes off with him anyway?

538
00:34:15,320 --> 00:34:17,515
Spousal abuse syndrome.

539
00:34:19,160 --> 00:34:21,469
- Dispatch, 22705.
- <i>Dispatch.</i>

540
00:34:21,560 --> 00:34:25,473
Can you send a backup unit
to Capital Bowl, 1123 Seabolt?

541
00:34:26,560 --> 00:34:31,270
Domestic disturbances are always weird, OK?
The woman gets beat on by her husband,

542
00:34:31,360 --> 00:34:36,150
the cavalry saves her. You'd think she'd be
on the same side as the rescuers, but...

543
00:34:36,240 --> 00:34:40,119
- You're saying watch out for the wife.
- <i>(door squeaks)</i>

544
00:34:40,200 --> 00:34:42,919
All I'm saying is just stay alert.

545
00:34:43,000 --> 00:34:45,355
- OK, Bones?
- OK.

546
00:34:45,440 --> 00:34:48,557
- <i>(Lucy)</i> Ted, why are we doing this?
- <i>(Ted)</i> Shut up!

547
00:34:48,640 --> 00:34:51,871
- You didn't do anything.
- I swear, if you don't shut up...

548
00:34:51,960 --> 00:34:56,272
- I know you wouldn't hurt Warren.
- <i>(Booth)</i> Of course he would.

549
00:34:56,360 --> 00:34:59,432
- He likes to beat up people weaker than him.
- We're closed.

550
00:34:59,520 --> 00:35:03,638
You left your door unlocked. Probably
an oversight due to your state of panic.

551
00:35:03,720 --> 00:35:06,951
Yeah. Lights were on.
You see, we suspected a robbery.

552
00:35:07,040 --> 00:35:10,157
- Say, you have a bevel knife?
- A what?

553
00:35:10,240 --> 00:35:14,392
- It's a triangular three-sided knife.
- To clean out bowling ball holes.

554
00:35:14,480 --> 00:35:17,631
Say, I used to have one.
You wouldn't have one around here?

555
00:35:17,720 --> 00:35:20,439
You need a warrant to take any of my stuff.

556
00:35:20,520 --> 00:35:23,239
Lucy, we need a bevel knife.

557
00:35:27,720 --> 00:35:30,075
- We keep one in here.
- Shut up, Lucy!

558
00:35:30,160 --> 00:35:35,029
Why don't you smack her around a little bit
there, Ted, huh? Keep your woman in line.

559
00:35:57,720 --> 00:35:59,551
Yeah.

560
00:35:59,640 --> 00:36:02,029
- This could've done it.
- Say, Bones.

561
00:36:02,120 --> 00:36:05,237
That, uh, bone chip -
second victim or murderer?

562
00:36:05,320 --> 00:36:08,710
Well, for Warrers sake,
I hope it was the murderer.

563
00:36:08,800 --> 00:36:12,236
- Me, too.
- What are you talking about? Get out of here.

564
00:36:12,320 --> 00:36:14,880
- It'd be his left arm.
- What?

565
00:36:14,960 --> 00:36:19,078
Warren was right-handed, so the wound
would be on your husband's left arm.

566
00:36:19,160 --> 00:36:21,116
- Oh, my God.
- Bones...

567
00:36:21,760 --> 00:36:24,433
- <i>(Ted cries out)</i>
- <i>(gasps)</i>

568
00:36:24,520 --> 00:36:26,317
<i>(Bones)</i> Right there.

569
00:36:28,280 --> 00:36:31,511
<i>(Booth)</i> I got him. I got him.
I got him. I got him. All right.

570
00:36:31,600 --> 00:36:35,513
Aw, hell, Bones, it looks like you opened up
an old wound there. Let's go.

571
00:36:35,600 --> 00:36:38,034
You're under arrest. I hate a wife-beater.

572
00:36:38,120 --> 00:36:41,999
Almost as much as I hate
someone who kills a dying kid.

573
00:36:51,680 --> 00:36:55,116
Warren knew what Ted did to you.

574
00:36:55,200 --> 00:36:58,988
- Did you tell him?
- <i>(Lucy)</i> I didn't have to. He saw one night.

575
00:36:59,080 --> 00:37:02,755
Ted hit me, and Warren...

576
00:37:05,320 --> 00:37:08,357
- Warren ran away.
- Why didn't you go to the police?

577
00:37:08,440 --> 00:37:12,035
Because... it's not all the time.

578
00:37:12,120 --> 00:37:17,990
It's just when things go bad and he's
under a lot of strain. Ted has a bad temper.

579
00:37:18,080 --> 00:37:23,029
- Warren wanted to rescue you.
- Oh, my God.

580
00:37:23,120 --> 00:37:27,955
He probably just wanted to intimidate
your husband. Stop him from attacking you.

581
00:37:28,040 --> 00:37:31,077
Warren stabbed your husband in the arm
with the knife.

582
00:37:31,160 --> 00:37:32,912
Ted took the knife away from him.

583
00:37:33,000 --> 00:37:36,993
It wouldn't have been hard.
The boy was very ill.

584
00:37:37,080 --> 00:37:39,116
After that, it's like you said.

585
00:37:39,200 --> 00:37:41,794
Your husband has a bad temper.

586
00:37:46,600 --> 00:37:50,434
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Feel It Now"</i>
<i>by Black Rebel Motorcycle Club)</i>

587
00:37:53,280 --> 00:37:57,671
♪ <i>And all my sorrows awaken</i>

588
00:37:59,760 --> 00:38:04,880
♪ <i>And all my fears run down</i>

589
00:38:06,320 --> 00:38:10,836
♪ <i>I turn myself into an angel</i>

590
00:38:12,720 --> 00:38:18,158
♪ <i>I run myself into the ground</i>

591
00:38:18,240 --> 00:38:21,152
♪ <i>I'm on my own</i>

592
00:38:21,240 --> 00:38:26,030
♪ <i>I'm sure I'll feel it now</i>

593
00:38:28,000 --> 00:38:30,195
♪ <i>I'm on my own</i>

594
00:38:30,280 --> 00:38:35,308
♪ <i>I'm sure I'll know it now</i>

595
00:38:38,040 --> 00:38:42,431
♪ <i>And all the reasons invading</i>

596
00:38:44,760 --> 00:38:49,151
♪ <i>Twist and turn my aching soul</i>

597
00:38:51,400 --> 00:38:55,996
♪ <i>I leave myself behind in pieces</i>

598
00:38:57,320 --> 00:39:02,110
♪ <i>I know you'll need them when I'm gone</i>

599
00:39:03,640 --> 00:39:06,518
♪ <i>I'll never see again</i>

600
00:39:06,720 --> 00:39:09,075
♪ <i>I'll never see again</i>

601
00:39:09,160 --> 00:39:11,674
♪ <i>The worst has come</i>

602
00:39:11,760 --> 00:39:15,230
♪ <i>I've fallen in</i>

603
00:39:15,320 --> 00:39:17,959
♪ <i>I'm on my own</i>

604
00:39:18,040 --> 00:39:23,273
♪ <i>I'm sure I'll feel it now</i>

605
00:39:24,400 --> 00:39:27,073
♪ <i>I'm on my own</i>

606
00:39:27,160 --> 00:39:31,472
♪ <i>I'm sure I'll feel it now</i>

607
00:39:33,360 --> 00:39:35,954
♪ <i>I'm on my own</i>

608
00:39:36,040 --> 00:39:41,034
♪ <i>I'm sure I'll know it now</i>

609
00:40:09,520 --> 00:40:14,275
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke

610
00:40:18,680 --> 00:40:19,999
What's that mean?

611
00:40:20,760 --> 00:40:22,751
ENGLISH SDH

