1
00:00:01,360 --> 00:00:04,511
- Welcome to the dungeon.
- Why do the FBI stick their morgues

2
00:00:04,600 --> 00:00:06,556
in the most depressing basement?

3
00:00:06,640 --> 00:00:11,509
Don't be such a snob. Not everyone gets to
play in a million-dollar lab with skylights.

4
00:00:11,600 --> 00:00:14,797
It's because as a society
we feel the need to hide death away

5
00:00:14,880 --> 00:00:18,316
and people who deal with the dead
are viewed as freaks.

6
00:00:18,400 --> 00:00:21,392
This guy you're about to meet,
Harry, he's a bit twisted.

7
00:00:21,480 --> 00:00:24,597
You think I get a rush when I work,
that I'm titillated.

8
00:00:24,680 --> 00:00:26,989
Choice of words, Bones. Choice of words.

9
00:00:27,520 --> 00:00:29,511
<i>(whistles)</i>

10
00:00:30,600 --> 00:00:33,990
- Agent Booth.
- Harry Tepper, meet Dr Temperance Brennan.

11
00:00:34,080 --> 00:00:35,877
- I've read her.
- Hello.

12
00:00:35,960 --> 00:00:41,557
She's good. Read your novel too.
The heroine's very aggressive.

13
00:00:41,640 --> 00:00:43,596
Harry. You wanna...?

14
00:00:46,760 --> 00:00:50,150
OK, everybody, meet Ted Macy.
Body was found in a national park.

15
00:00:50,240 --> 00:00:52,834
Coroner wrote it off
as an accidental drowning,

16
00:00:52,920 --> 00:00:55,639
but we must investigate
every death on federal land.

17
00:00:55,720 --> 00:01:00,555
During my examination, I found he had a
crushed larynx that didn't seem accidental.

18
00:01:00,640 --> 00:01:03,996
- This is a corpse. With skin.
- She is good.

19
00:01:04,080 --> 00:01:06,196
Why am I here? I don't work with skin.

20
00:01:06,280 --> 00:01:10,910
I didn't bring you here to examine the body.
I want you to see what they found in his hand.

21
00:01:11,000 --> 00:01:12,558
Harry?

22
00:01:12,640 --> 00:01:14,631
Bone?

23
00:01:18,600 --> 00:01:21,558
- What is that?
- It's a phalanx.

24
00:01:21,640 --> 00:01:23,835
Finger bone.
Figured she'd know that.

25
00:01:23,920 --> 00:01:27,754
I'd figure any medical examiner
would know not to compromise evidence.

26
00:01:27,840 --> 00:01:30,991
- Is this Lysol IC?
- We use it to decontaminate remains.

27
00:01:31,080 --> 00:01:35,517
Are you trying to break down the surface
of the bone? Wreak havoc on the marrow?

28
00:01:35,600 --> 00:01:37,556
- Did you even dilute this?
- Bones!

29
00:01:37,640 --> 00:01:42,839
What? You've removed particulates and
trace elements that could lead us to his killer.

30
00:01:42,920 --> 00:01:46,435
- Is this your first day on the job?
- 18 years next month.

31
00:01:48,360 --> 00:01:51,272
<i>(Booth)</i> 18 years.

32
00:01:51,360 --> 00:01:53,749
- <i>(door slams)</i>
- She's intense.

33
00:01:56,880 --> 00:01:59,189
- Native American.
- British colonial.

34
00:01:59,280 --> 00:02:01,714
- American revolutionary.
- What are we playing?

35
00:02:01,800 --> 00:02:04,394
Dr Brennan, the destroyer of evidence is here.

36
00:02:04,480 --> 00:02:08,029
OK, I assume that's ajoke.
Did Harry really mess up that bone?

37
00:02:08,120 --> 00:02:10,714
He dissolved any particulates on the surface.

38
00:02:10,800 --> 00:02:14,554
- But we were able to save valuable attributes.
- Like what?

39
00:02:14,640 --> 00:02:18,599
Alternating sclerotic and porotic areas
on subperiosteal surface

40
00:02:18,680 --> 00:02:22,992
demonstrates that whoever this was
suffered from tertiary syphilis.

41
00:02:23,080 --> 00:02:26,072
Tertiary syphilis? Wow, that's the worst.

42
00:02:26,160 --> 00:02:28,469
It was a common ailment in the 17th century.

43
00:02:28,560 --> 00:02:31,711
- Which is where the bone dates from.
- Say what?

44
00:02:31,800 --> 00:02:35,839
We ran a radio carbon dating test.
The finger's over 300 years old.

45
00:02:35,920 --> 00:02:38,992
- <i>(Bones)</i> A unique find.
- I'll change to French trapper.

46
00:02:39,080 --> 00:02:42,550
- You can't change yours.
- Booth, where did they find the victim?

47
00:02:42,640 --> 00:02:47,350
Some resort town next to a federal
seaside preserve - Assateague Island.

48
00:02:47,440 --> 00:02:50,591
- That's where the money pit is.
- Money pit?

49
00:02:50,680 --> 00:02:55,196
Legend is Assateague Island
is where Blackbeard buried his treasure.

50
00:02:55,280 --> 00:03:00,354
For 300 years people have tried to find it.
They've dug it out to 150ft but found nothing.

51
00:03:00,440 --> 00:03:04,274
Every time they come close,
they trigger a baffle that floods the pit.

52
00:03:04,360 --> 00:03:07,432
- Booby traps.
- The body was found at a dig site.

53
00:03:07,520 --> 00:03:11,513
This is the first concrete evidence
that the treasure is more than a legend.

54
00:03:11,600 --> 00:03:14,956
- This is from a man who buried the treasure.
- Pure conjecture.

55
00:03:15,040 --> 00:03:16,996
- A pirate.
- Pirate?

56
00:03:17,080 --> 00:03:19,640
- It's a pirate.
- You can't change yours.

57
00:03:19,720 --> 00:03:22,314
The victim finds evidence the treasure exists.

58
00:03:22,400 --> 00:03:26,029
Somebody else wants it.
Certainly that's a good motive for murder.

59
00:03:26,120 --> 00:03:28,634
We gotta get to that dig site.
I'll be glad to help.

60
00:03:28,720 --> 00:03:31,359
- I can handle it.
- Come on, man. Share the wealth.

61
00:03:31,440 --> 00:03:34,512
We are looking for answers,
Jack, not treasure.

62
00:03:34,600 --> 00:03:37,831
- Do you really think that treasure exists?
- What do you think?

63
00:03:37,920 --> 00:03:39,433
<i>(Booth laughs)</i>

64
00:03:39,520 --> 00:03:41,511
Why are you guys smiling?

65
00:03:42,080 --> 00:03:44,674
Pirates!

66
00:03:44,760 --> 00:03:47,069
It's a guy thing, sweetie.

67
00:03:57,240 --> 00:03:59,231
Mm-hm. <i>(smacks lips)</i>

68
00:04:09,760 --> 00:04:12,433
So the dead guy, Macy, ran the dig.

69
00:04:12,520 --> 00:04:16,308
With his partner Hardewicke.
He was hired by anyone with money to burn.

70
00:04:16,400 --> 00:04:18,709
People would do that? Sane people?

71
00:04:18,800 --> 00:04:21,837
- Look for treasure?
- Isn't that what archaeologists do?

72
00:04:21,920 --> 00:04:25,799
Archaeologists use evidence
on which to base their explorations,

73
00:04:25,880 --> 00:04:28,348
not some pirate movie
they saw when they were ten.

74
00:04:28,440 --> 00:04:31,637
Yeah, well, that 300-year-old bone
that we just found

75
00:04:31,720 --> 00:04:35,235
sort of changes things now,
doesn't it, there, matey?

76
00:04:35,320 --> 00:04:37,993
- What's going on over there?
- I tried to stop him.

77
00:04:38,080 --> 00:04:40,799
That's Branson Rose.
The mayor told me to let him in.

78
00:04:40,880 --> 00:04:45,078
- Branson Rose is funding this dig?
- Has for two years. Heard he was pulling out.

79
00:04:45,160 --> 00:04:47,754
- I'll take it from here.
- Who's Branson Rose?

80
00:04:47,840 --> 00:04:53,278
The billionaire adventurer. He made
his fortune making aircraft for the military.

81
00:04:53,360 --> 00:04:57,911
Owns about half the world. He has that reality
show that goes all over the world and...

82
00:04:58,000 --> 00:05:02,278
Still no TV. Why do I even bother? I...

83
00:05:02,360 --> 00:05:06,751
- You can't pull out now. We got a contract.
- So sue. But I doubt you have the resources.

84
00:05:06,840 --> 00:05:08,796
Mr Rose, we just broke 200ft.

85
00:05:08,880 --> 00:05:11,997
- If you pull out now, you'll miss out...
- <i>(clears throat)</i>

86
00:05:12,080 --> 00:05:15,152
- I've been hearing that for two years.
- Uh, excuse me.

87
00:05:15,240 --> 00:05:18,755
- Macy knew it. He felt it. We're this close.
- Excuse me.

88
00:05:18,840 --> 00:05:23,197
Two years, $2 million, there's nothing
down there, Giles. Macy died for nothing.

89
00:05:23,280 --> 00:05:25,669
FBI! You're all under arrest.

90
00:05:26,880 --> 00:05:29,440
You don't get to say that.
I've got the badge.

91
00:05:29,520 --> 00:05:32,239
- The FBI's involved now?
- Murder on federal land.

92
00:05:32,320 --> 00:05:34,959
- We like to poke around a little.
- Murder?

93
00:05:35,040 --> 00:05:37,235
Yeah. Murder.

94
00:05:38,320 --> 00:05:41,995
- You said it was an accident.
- That's what I thought.

95
00:05:42,080 --> 00:05:44,071
Oh, my God.

96
00:05:47,200 --> 00:05:49,760
He found something.

97
00:05:49,840 --> 00:05:52,877
Put my stuff back now!

98
00:05:52,960 --> 00:05:56,509
What did Macy find
that would be won'th killing him for?

99
00:06:30,440 --> 00:06:35,719
In 1832, a team of six men looking for the
treasure were killed when a shaft collapsed.

100
00:06:35,800 --> 00:06:39,918
- Blackbeard's curse, man.
- A curse? We're scientists.

101
00:06:40,000 --> 00:06:45,632
Look at this. 1902. Two men disappeared
while digging. Never found their bodies.

102
00:06:45,720 --> 00:06:49,872
- Oh, that's very cursey.
- So you believe in pirates?

103
00:06:49,960 --> 00:06:54,875
Pirates aren't Santa, Zack. They did exist.
They did have treasures and they did bury it.

104
00:06:54,960 --> 00:06:57,155
I had an eye patch when I was six.

105
00:06:57,240 --> 00:07:00,118
Who didn't, my friend? Who didn't?

106
00:07:00,200 --> 00:07:02,589
It's not necessary to lead me like a child.

107
00:07:02,680 --> 00:07:05,194
I'd rather not have
more evidence compromised.

108
00:07:05,280 --> 00:07:07,953
- You're squeezing my arm very tightly.
- Sorry.

109
00:07:08,040 --> 00:07:10,190
No, no. It's OK.

110
00:07:10,280 --> 00:07:13,158
- You can give it to Dr Hodgins.
- What is this?

111
00:07:13,240 --> 00:07:17,153
Soil and water collected
from Ted Macy's throat and lungs.

112
00:07:17,240 --> 00:07:19,879
He was found floating at the top of the shaft.

113
00:07:19,960 --> 00:07:22,030
We need you to do your dirt thing.

114
00:07:22,120 --> 00:07:25,795
Match the slime to the crime.
Make sure that's where he was killed.

115
00:07:25,880 --> 00:07:29,509
I'd like to look at X-rays
of the victim's skeleton.

116
00:07:29,600 --> 00:07:31,989
- Bossy.
- Do not go there.

117
00:07:32,080 --> 00:07:36,915
I need to determine if he died at the top
or died at the bottom and floated up.

118
00:07:37,000 --> 00:07:39,958
- I need silt abstracts from both levels.
- We'll get those.

119
00:07:40,040 --> 00:07:45,319
No, no. No. The soil looks like an odd mixture
of clay, plagioclase feldspar, pyroxene.

120
00:07:45,400 --> 00:07:49,871
- I really wouldn't trust anyone else.
- You just want to look for treasure.

121
00:07:49,960 --> 00:07:51,188
Wha...?

122
00:07:51,280 --> 00:07:55,876
I am a serious scientist merely trying
to do my job as well as possible.

123
00:07:55,960 --> 00:08:00,636
That shaft is over 200ft deep, you know?
Requires an experienced diver.

124
00:08:00,720 --> 00:08:04,838
I am a certified cave diver,
which means I can go deeper than 200ft.

125
00:08:04,920 --> 00:08:07,480
I dove Mayan Blue, Dos Ojos, Tortuga.

126
00:08:07,560 --> 00:08:09,630
- Ever dive Naharon?
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> Once.

127
00:08:09,720 --> 00:08:14,032
- I named Naharon.
- Well, then, how can you say no to me?

128
00:08:14,120 --> 00:08:16,793
OK. Butjust to collect soil samples.

129
00:08:16,880 --> 00:08:18,996
Of course.

130
00:08:19,080 --> 00:08:23,596
- You dive too?
- I have the time because I don't own a TV.

131
00:08:23,680 --> 00:08:26,752
- You wear a rubber suit, then.
- Uh...

132
00:08:31,120 --> 00:08:35,955
Accidents happen, you know? Macy and I
were prepared for that. But murder?

133
00:08:36,040 --> 00:08:38,793
Murder, wow. Anything I can do to help, OK?

134
00:08:38,880 --> 00:08:42,509
We'll talk about that later.
I want to get Hodgins down that shaft.

135
00:08:42,600 --> 00:08:47,116
Dane McGinnis. He's the best I know.
He's worked for us for years.

136
00:08:47,200 --> 00:08:52,354
- Agent Booth? Are you Agent Booth?
- <i>(laughs)</i> Sorry. Stay behind the yellow tape.

137
00:08:52,440 --> 00:08:56,718
I'm Mayor Ney. Your men keep pushing
our tourists further and further back.

138
00:08:56,800 --> 00:09:00,315
Mayor? Wow. I hope you didn't look like that
when they elected you.

139
00:09:00,400 --> 00:09:04,871
Blackbeard's treasure is what keeps the
economy here running. The mayor gets that.

140
00:09:04,960 --> 00:09:07,633
- Sometimes too intensely.
- Hey, I'm not ashamed.

141
00:09:07,720 --> 00:09:10,188
I've increased tourism 63% since I took office.

142
00:09:10,280 --> 00:09:13,352
I can boost it more
if the tourists could get a closer look.

143
00:09:13,440 --> 00:09:17,035
- It's a murder scene, not a show.
- Blackbeard's curse.

144
00:09:17,120 --> 00:09:20,430
Macy would've wanted to give a little back
to the town he loved.

145
00:09:20,520 --> 00:09:22,875
The police are telling them no pictures.

146
00:09:22,960 --> 00:09:26,270
- Who is this? The pirate queen?
- That's right. My wife Katie.

147
00:09:26,360 --> 00:09:29,989
Great. You just tell the tourists
the bad view is part of the curse.

148
00:09:30,080 --> 00:09:33,789
Will you escort the pirate and his wench
behind the yellow tape?

149
00:09:33,880 --> 00:09:35,199
<i>(Katie)</i> Frank!

150
00:09:35,280 --> 00:09:37,748
So Dane, he's an experienced guy?

151
00:09:37,840 --> 00:09:41,196
- I've worked with hundreds. He's the best.
- All right.

152
00:09:41,280 --> 00:09:45,034
I hope this guy knows what he's doing.
It's tight down there.

153
00:09:45,120 --> 00:09:47,554
Avast, ye lubbers!

154
00:09:52,920 --> 00:09:55,036
<i>(Giles)</i> Dane, let's get him ready.

155
00:10:01,280 --> 00:10:05,512
- You think it's a pirate?
- It's a finger from the left hand of a male.

156
00:10:05,600 --> 00:10:09,229
- That's all I'm sure of so far.
- Worth killing for?

157
00:10:09,320 --> 00:10:13,029
I worked a case once where a woman
was killed, dismembered and burned

158
00:10:13,120 --> 00:10:15,998
because her friend thought
she'd taken her slippers.

159
00:10:16,080 --> 00:10:18,310
- Cheery.
- Maybe they're right.

160
00:10:18,400 --> 00:10:21,039
Maybe this man died burying the treasure.

161
00:10:21,120 --> 00:10:25,750
Ironic. Stealing all that,
never enjoying the spoils.

162
00:10:25,840 --> 00:10:28,149
So you believe there's treasure?

163
00:10:28,240 --> 00:10:30,435
I believe there's greed.

164
00:10:31,240 --> 00:10:33,435
That's the real curse.

165
00:10:37,800 --> 00:10:41,031
All right, safety line, air hose.

166
00:10:41,120 --> 00:10:46,194
- Either one breaks, you ain't coming back up.
- You gotta work on your bedside manner.

167
00:10:46,280 --> 00:10:48,635
I don't wanna be responsible for a weekender

168
00:10:48,720 --> 00:10:51,996
who buys it down there
because he thinks he's better than he is.

169
00:10:52,080 --> 00:10:54,116
You want to go down, don't you?

170
00:10:54,200 --> 00:10:58,079
It's my shaft, OK?
I've been working it ten years.

171
00:10:58,160 --> 00:11:02,073
The feds, they say it's a crime scene,
so I can't help.

172
00:11:02,160 --> 00:11:03,957
You're helping me.

173
00:11:04,040 --> 00:11:06,110
Why can't he just use the tank?

174
00:11:06,200 --> 00:11:10,432
Because about 100ft down
that shaft gets a little cosy.

175
00:11:10,520 --> 00:11:15,469
- You ain't afraid of a tight squeeze, are you?
- Gloves.

176
00:11:15,560 --> 00:11:19,075
Take it slow. A lot of stuff
to catch your hose on on the way down.

177
00:11:19,160 --> 00:11:22,038
- Yeah, I saw the pictures Rose took.
- <i>(laughs)</i> Rose.

178
00:11:22,120 --> 00:11:25,157
He never went as far as you're going.
No one has.

179
00:11:25,240 --> 00:11:28,357
Maybe he shouldn't try.
People have died down there.

180
00:11:28,440 --> 00:11:31,159
I know. My brother was one of them.

181
00:11:33,640 --> 00:11:37,997
- I'm going all the way down. What's at 200ft?
- We just hit 200 last week.

182
00:11:38,080 --> 00:11:39,911
You're gonna have to tell me.

183
00:11:40,000 --> 00:11:42,468
- Well, I'm ready.
- OK.

184
00:12:14,840 --> 00:12:19,994
- <i>(Dane)</i> He better be as good as he says he is.
- <i>(Booth)</i> You just take care of him, all right?

185
00:12:26,280 --> 00:12:30,193
- <i>(Dane)</i> Hodgins, you read me?
- <i>I hear you loud and clear.</i>

186
00:12:30,280 --> 00:12:34,751
<i>(Dane) There's some jagged edges.</i>
<i>Keep clear of them.</i>

187
00:12:36,080 --> 00:12:37,877
Whoa, whoa, whoa.

188
00:12:37,960 --> 00:12:39,029
Hodgins.

189
00:12:39,120 --> 00:12:41,793
- <i>It's warm.</i>
- Passing the first flood trap.

190
00:12:41,880 --> 00:12:43,916
We lost our first man there.

191
00:12:44,000 --> 00:12:48,312
- There's wood here below the limestone.
- Does he make any sense to you?

192
00:12:48,400 --> 00:12:51,278
Yeah. He's passing the site
of the first pit collapse.

193
00:12:51,360 --> 00:12:53,954
It's tight down here.

194
00:12:54,040 --> 00:12:57,669
There's a lot of debris.
I'm not sure if I can squeeze through.

195
00:12:57,760 --> 00:12:59,796
Hey, this guy swims like a squid.

196
00:12:59,880 --> 00:13:01,757
- He swims like a squint.
- What?

197
00:13:01,840 --> 00:13:05,071
- Never mind.
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> OK, I'm clear now.

198
00:13:05,160 --> 00:13:08,709
Good picture too.
We can't get resolution like that.

199
00:13:08,800 --> 00:13:11,268
He's a geek.
You ever find anything down here?

200
00:13:11,360 --> 00:13:13,954
- Not yet.
- Ten years of nothing, you keep trying?

201
00:13:14,040 --> 00:13:17,555
- It's all about the search, man.
- He's at 170ft.

202
00:13:20,640 --> 00:13:22,949
180.

203
00:13:24,360 --> 00:13:27,511
90. No one's ever been this deep.

204
00:13:28,240 --> 00:13:30,071
He's at 200.

205
00:13:30,160 --> 00:13:32,993
<i>(Hodgins) Touchdown. I am on the bottom.</i>

206
00:13:33,080 --> 00:13:35,753
<i>Visibility is surprisingly good.</i>

207
00:13:36,200 --> 00:13:39,476
<i>Wait a minute.</i>
<i>There's... there's something here.</i>

208
00:13:40,120 --> 00:13:41,678
- Holy...
- What is that?

209
00:13:41,760 --> 00:13:43,955
- <i>Oh, my...</i>
- <i>(Giles)</i> Is that...?

210
00:13:46,880 --> 00:13:49,553
- <i>(Dane)</i> Oh, my God.
- It's there! <i>(laughs)</i>

211
00:13:50,440 --> 00:13:52,112
<i>(cheers)</i>

212
00:13:52,200 --> 00:13:54,191
<i>(Dane)</i> Can you believe that?

213
00:13:56,040 --> 00:13:58,508
<i>(Bones)</i> I'm amazed
you found a complete skeleton.

214
00:13:58,600 --> 00:14:01,592
<i>(Zack)</i> C-14 dating matches at 300 years.

215
00:14:01,680 --> 00:14:05,070
Subject is male. Early 20s.

216
00:14:05,160 --> 00:14:09,392
Approximately five feet six inches.

217
00:14:09,480 --> 00:14:12,631
Legs are bowed, result of calcium
and phosphate deficiency.

218
00:14:12,720 --> 00:14:16,633
He had rickets as a child
but his upper body is well developed.

219
00:14:16,720 --> 00:14:20,110
Epiphyseal separation in the long bones.

220
00:14:20,200 --> 00:14:25,354
Sunken sternum forms scorbutic rosary
at costochondral margin.

221
00:14:25,440 --> 00:14:28,750
- He had scurvy and tertiary syphilis.
- What's with "tertiary"?

222
00:14:28,840 --> 00:14:34,039
- Isn't plain old syphilis bad enough?
- Scurvy, syphilis... Pirate.

223
00:14:34,120 --> 00:14:39,877
Anthropological evidence supports the claim
that Blackbeard executed his burial crews.

224
00:14:39,960 --> 00:14:41,234
OK.

225
00:14:41,320 --> 00:14:44,232
- Let's say it's a pirate.
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> Yes!

226
00:14:44,320 --> 00:14:46,914
This would be an extraordinary find.

227
00:14:47,000 --> 00:14:53,075
- And opens up the reality of the treasure.
- It would be stupid to dismiss anything.

228
00:14:53,160 --> 00:14:58,359
But we need to discover why the ossein isn't
fully decomposed from being waterlogged.

229
00:14:58,440 --> 00:15:02,319
50ft down the shaft is a layer of blue putty
consisting of silicon and clay.

230
00:15:02,400 --> 00:15:06,109
- It forms a watertight seal.
- That explains the bones' condition.

231
00:15:06,200 --> 00:15:11,558
I took samples of the same clay between 200
and 207ft. Something is buried down there.

232
00:15:11,640 --> 00:15:15,553
- These bones were on top of it.
- Macy was killed cos of something he found.

233
00:15:15,640 --> 00:15:18,677
The silt in his throat confirms
he was killed at the top.

234
00:15:18,760 --> 00:15:20,716
After he swam back up with the treasure.

235
00:15:21,480 --> 00:15:25,393
Special Agent Booth.
I hate to interrupt your investigation,

236
00:15:25,480 --> 00:15:30,554
but there's an angry billionaire in my office
and he won't go away.

237
00:15:30,640 --> 00:15:34,952
It's simple. You have something that belongs
to me and I'm not leaving without it.

238
00:15:35,040 --> 00:15:39,033
A day ago, you couldn't wait to leave,
cut your losses. You remember that?

239
00:15:39,120 --> 00:15:42,715
- A lot can change in a day.
- Yeah. For Ted Macy, a lot changed.

240
00:15:42,800 --> 00:15:46,839
I'm sorry about Ted, but I'll be damned
if the federal government swoops in

241
00:15:46,920 --> 00:15:49,275
and steals what I've been trying to find.

242
00:15:49,360 --> 00:15:53,751
- I fail to see what this has to do with us.
- Those bones belong to me.

243
00:15:53,840 --> 00:15:55,876
They were uncovered at my site.

244
00:15:55,960 --> 00:16:01,273
I was granted a permit to dig there
and keep what was found.

245
00:16:01,360 --> 00:16:04,477
My attorneys assure me
you have no claim to those bones.

246
00:16:04,560 --> 00:16:07,393
Your attorney wants to go to court
for the next 20 years

247
00:16:07,480 --> 00:16:09,869
and buy himself a vacation home in Tuscany,

248
00:16:09,960 --> 00:16:14,556
but the fact is when Ted Macy was murdered,
your property became our evidence.

249
00:16:14,640 --> 00:16:17,518
It's going to stay that way
until we find the killer.

250
00:16:17,600 --> 00:16:21,036
<i>(laughs)</i> I was hoping to settle this amicably.

251
00:16:21,120 --> 00:16:25,113
- Really? Because we haven't seen that yet.
- Nah.

252
00:16:25,200 --> 00:16:27,953
This will be a headache.
He has important friends.

253
00:16:28,040 --> 00:16:31,032
Why is he so upset?
It's not like he needs the money.

254
00:16:31,120 --> 00:16:35,671
But his partners do. Macy and Hardewicke
were going to split what they found.

255
00:16:35,760 --> 00:16:37,955
- But Macy is dead.
- Exactly.

256
00:16:38,040 --> 00:16:41,510
Leaving Hardewicke
with a bigger piece of the pie.

257
00:16:41,600 --> 00:16:44,956
<i>(Giles)</i> This is from our very first dig together.

258
00:16:45,040 --> 00:16:49,716
We found this chest buried under a flood
drain up in Smith Cove in New England.

259
00:16:49,800 --> 00:16:54,590
There was no treasure, butjust to unearth
something that old, had that much history...

260
00:16:54,680 --> 00:16:57,990
- We were hooked.
- I glanced through your company history.

261
00:16:58,080 --> 00:17:01,072
Business was slow
since you didn't find any treasure.

262
00:17:01,160 --> 00:17:04,197
- You were getting fewer clients.
- It's been difficult.

263
00:17:04,280 --> 00:17:07,590
Branson Rose was almost your last chance.

264
00:17:07,680 --> 00:17:10,240
Somebody always wants to look for treasure.

265
00:17:10,320 --> 00:17:11,719
- Really?
- Yeah.

266
00:17:11,800 --> 00:17:16,078
If Rose pulls out you'd get a lot of publicity.
Could end up sinking your business.

267
00:17:16,160 --> 00:17:20,756
Macy found something and we'll share
the find with Rose. 50% for him, 50 for us.

268
00:17:20,840 --> 00:17:22,796
Exactly.

269
00:17:22,880 --> 00:17:29,274
Oh, I see. More for me if Macy's out of
the picture, right? You're forgetting one thing.

270
00:17:29,360 --> 00:17:31,749
- Macy was like family to me.
- Really?

271
00:17:31,840 --> 00:17:36,391
Look at this. See that? I got that
pulling Macy out of a sinkhole back in '93.

272
00:17:36,480 --> 00:17:38,710
He's got of scars on him because of me too.

273
00:17:38,800 --> 00:17:43,669
How'd you get all those bruises
around your scar there, huh?

274
00:17:43,760 --> 00:17:46,433
- The mayor.
- How's the mayor figure into all this?

275
00:17:46,520 --> 00:17:50,911
His wife. You saw her, right? Well, Macy was
a bit of a hound, if you know what I mean.

276
00:17:51,000 --> 00:17:54,913
- He was sleeping with the pirate queen?
- The mayor got suspicious.

277
00:17:55,000 --> 00:17:58,515
I ended up taking the heat for Macy
because Macy's like my brother.

278
00:17:58,600 --> 00:18:02,559
That pirate can kick. I'm lucky
he didn't have time to load that flintlock.

279
00:18:02,640 --> 00:18:04,551
- <i>(crashing)</i>
- Charlie!

280
00:18:05,000 --> 00:18:09,516
What? No! Put that down!
Leave it there! What are you doing?

281
00:18:12,960 --> 00:18:14,996
Zack? Zack!

282
00:18:15,080 --> 00:18:17,833
- What did you do with the bones?
- Nothing.

283
00:18:17,920 --> 00:18:21,515
I left them on the table just like you asked.

284
00:18:23,120 --> 00:18:25,759
Where the hell are my bones?

285
00:18:28,120 --> 00:18:31,635
Bones don'tjust disappear!
I thought this was a secure facility.

286
00:18:31,720 --> 00:18:37,352
You assured me this was a secure facility.
This never would've happened at Stanford!

287
00:18:37,440 --> 00:18:40,876
- We spend $0.75 million on security.
- Obviously not enough!

288
00:18:40,960 --> 00:18:43,190
I want my bones. Did you find my bones?

289
00:18:43,280 --> 00:18:46,033
- Whoa. Maybe you wanna chill a little?
- Chill?

290
00:18:46,120 --> 00:18:48,236
- You know, take a pill?
- Listen, dude.

291
00:18:48,320 --> 00:18:53,269
My lab was violated, my bones were stolen,
so I think I'll remain warm for a while longer.

292
00:18:53,360 --> 00:18:55,749
Maybe you should focus on your breathing.

293
00:18:55,840 --> 00:18:58,559
- Count to ten. Have a shot of Jack.
- A shot of Jack.

294
00:18:58,640 --> 00:19:02,474
We're doing everything we can.
I promise you we're gonna find your bones.

295
00:19:02,560 --> 00:19:05,711
But you have to allow us to do ourjob.

296
00:19:05,800 --> 00:19:08,997
I guess I wasrt helping
all that much, was I?

297
00:19:09,560 --> 00:19:12,233
I...

298
00:19:12,320 --> 00:19:14,788
- I'm...
- "Sorry."

299
00:19:16,280 --> 00:19:18,748
- It's cool.
- Hey, look on the bright side.

300
00:19:18,840 --> 00:19:21,912
This whole theft thing
could be good for us, right?

301
00:19:22,000 --> 00:19:25,390
Whoever took the bones obviously
had something to do with the murder.

302
00:19:25,480 --> 00:19:28,916
On-duty security personnel
are giving an account of their rounds.

303
00:19:29,000 --> 00:19:32,390
- Off-duty personnel as well.
- <i>(Zack)</i> They didn't get everything.

304
00:19:32,480 --> 00:19:36,996
- I thought all the bones were on the table?
- I was examining the original finger bone.

305
00:19:37,080 --> 00:19:39,913
So it was in my room.

306
00:19:40,000 --> 00:19:45,028
There is something
they don't want us to find on this bone.

307
00:19:45,120 --> 00:19:48,157
Everyone knew Macy.
Helped Frank get elected.

308
00:19:48,240 --> 00:19:51,516
So you would categorise your relationship
as just friends?

309
00:19:51,600 --> 00:19:55,639
Yeah, friends. It's a small town.
We're all friends.

310
00:19:55,720 --> 00:19:58,553
Well, whoever killed Macy wasrt too friendly.

311
00:19:58,640 --> 00:20:01,438
He wouldn't hurt a soul. Macy.

312
00:20:01,520 --> 00:20:03,351
He was a sweet guy.

313
00:20:03,440 --> 00:20:09,470
The way you're talking about him,
it seems like you were more than just friends.

314
00:20:09,560 --> 00:20:12,438
Hardewicke told you, right?
Like he's such a saint.

315
00:20:12,520 --> 00:20:16,877
- How involved were the two of you?
- It was just one of those things, you know?

316
00:20:16,960 --> 00:20:19,872
I wasrt gonna leave Frank or anything.

317
00:20:19,960 --> 00:20:24,636
I guess I wanted to be with a real adventurer
rather than a guy who dresses up like one.

318
00:20:24,720 --> 00:20:27,234
Frank went after Hardewicke.
He thought it was him.

319
00:20:27,320 --> 00:20:30,312
You think Frank killed him? You saw Frank.

320
00:20:30,400 --> 00:20:35,520
Yeah, he's a little unstable and he finds
out somebody made a fool of him twice, I...

321
00:20:35,600 --> 00:20:38,512
It's Hardewicke and the rich guy
you should look at.

322
00:20:38,600 --> 00:20:41,637
Macy said they were fighting
over the money they spent.

323
00:20:41,720 --> 00:20:45,349
Said Hardewicke wanted
to break up the company.

324
00:20:45,440 --> 00:20:48,000
Well, we're looking into everyone. Thanks.

325
00:20:48,080 --> 00:20:51,470
Sure. But all this coming up again...

326
00:20:52,960 --> 00:20:55,679
just try not to ruin my marriage, OK?

327
00:20:55,760 --> 00:21:00,914
I made a mistake. But I love that stupid pirate
and I don't want to lose him.

328
00:21:01,000 --> 00:21:04,993
Well, thanks for talking to me. I'll be in touch.

329
00:21:08,600 --> 00:21:12,718
The surface on the phalanx doesn't have
any particulates that I can recover.

330
00:21:12,800 --> 00:21:18,511
The solution the ME used dissolved anything
that was lodged in any surface irregularities.

331
00:21:18,600 --> 00:21:21,512
Who'd clean a bone
before extracting all information?

332
00:21:21,600 --> 00:21:25,388
- Not everyone is as thorough as we are, Zack.
- So true. So true.

333
00:21:25,480 --> 00:21:29,996
- I wonder if there was gold dust on it.
- You should have a parrot on your shoulder.

334
00:21:30,080 --> 00:21:34,153
- You're not curious?
- Yes, about the facts.

335
00:21:34,240 --> 00:21:39,439
There's a small hole along
the distal articular facet of the finger.

336
00:21:39,520 --> 00:21:42,159
It could be a foramen
or something else, man-made.

337
00:21:42,240 --> 00:21:44,435
- A weapon?
- <i>(Bones)</i> Maybe.

338
00:21:44,880 --> 00:21:47,917
See if you can find any possible matches.

339
00:21:48,000 --> 00:21:51,197
- I wonder if there are similar marks on Macy?
- I'll find out.

340
00:21:51,280 --> 00:21:54,989
And don't let that bone out of your sight.

341
00:21:59,240 --> 00:22:02,755
Dr Brennan thought you might've overlooked
a weapon of some kind.

342
00:22:02,840 --> 00:22:05,149
He wasrt killed by any weapon.

343
00:22:05,240 --> 00:22:07,231
He was strangled.

344
00:22:07,320 --> 00:22:09,959
The larynx is crushed. It's plain.

345
00:22:10,040 --> 00:22:14,556
C2 through C4 are fractured. That wouldn't
have occurred if you were strangled.

346
00:22:14,640 --> 00:22:17,438
If the victim was shaken
while being strangled...

347
00:22:17,520 --> 00:22:22,071
The fractures are all left to right,
approximately 45° angles on each bone.

348
00:22:22,160 --> 00:22:24,993
That means the head
was jerked to the left and up,

349
00:22:25,080 --> 00:22:27,548
making sure that the spinal cord would tear.

350
00:22:27,640 --> 00:22:30,074
The larynx was crushed when his neck broke.

351
00:22:30,160 --> 00:22:34,950
I'm always open to being corrected. Why do
you think there might have been a weapon?

352
00:22:35,040 --> 00:22:38,271
I saw a perforation in the finger bone
you put in the solvent.

353
00:22:38,360 --> 00:22:41,796
Did you damage the bone?
Poke it? Stick it in some way?

354
00:22:41,880 --> 00:22:44,553
Still angry. OK, no.

355
00:22:44,640 --> 00:22:49,156
I handled it according to protocol.
Rubber gloves, right into the solvent.

356
00:22:49,240 --> 00:22:54,519
Something damaged that bone
and it didn't happen 300 years...

357
00:22:56,120 --> 00:22:58,680
Wait a minute.

358
00:23:01,520 --> 00:23:06,150
I have alternatives that could've caused
the hole. This is an acupuncture needle.

359
00:23:06,240 --> 00:23:08,310
Come on. He was healed to death?

360
00:23:08,400 --> 00:23:11,551
This is a filament used for an angioplasty.

361
00:23:11,640 --> 00:23:13,835
Hand me the wire.

362
00:23:19,680 --> 00:23:22,069
- <i>(Booth)</i> What you doing?
- Diminished fluorescence.

363
00:23:22,160 --> 00:23:25,516
That only happens if the bones
have been cleaned and treated.

364
00:23:25,600 --> 00:23:29,070
These bones didn't start out in the shaft.
They were placed there.

365
00:23:29,160 --> 00:23:30,957
What?

366
00:23:31,960 --> 00:23:34,269
Who's got 300-year-old bones?

367
00:23:37,720 --> 00:23:40,154
I assure you everything here is authentic.

368
00:23:40,240 --> 00:23:43,038
I curated this exhibit
for the Jeffersonian myself.

369
00:23:43,120 --> 00:23:45,714
Could you please open the case?

370
00:23:46,880 --> 00:23:49,678
This is a beautiful specimen

371
00:23:49,760 --> 00:23:51,557
found in Jamaica.

372
00:23:51,640 --> 00:23:53,790
We believe he sailed with Henry Morgan.

373
00:23:53,880 --> 00:23:57,270
- He's never been on a boat in his life.
- That's absurd.

374
00:23:58,120 --> 00:24:01,635
- Oh, my God.
- These bones are artificial. It's acrylic.

375
00:24:01,720 --> 00:24:03,756
Not bone.

376
00:24:03,840 --> 00:24:07,435
You can see on the real bone the hole
where the wire was threaded

377
00:24:07,520 --> 00:24:10,751
when the bones were assembled for display.

378
00:24:10,840 --> 00:24:12,671
Then where is the rest of my sailor?

379
00:24:12,760 --> 00:24:16,799
He was planted in Assateague Island
to make the treasure business seem real.

380
00:24:16,880 --> 00:24:19,075
- But somebody found out.
- Who?

381
00:24:19,520 --> 00:24:21,909
A murderer.

382
00:24:27,120 --> 00:24:29,395
<i>(Cullen)</i> Let me see if I got this straight.

383
00:24:29,480 --> 00:24:34,270
The pirate bones you recovered
came from the Jeffersonian to start with.

384
00:24:34,360 --> 00:24:37,352
- Correct.
- 300-year-old bones from our pirate exhibit.

385
00:24:37,440 --> 00:24:40,352
- Recovered by one of your people?
- <i>(Booth)</i> Dr Hodgins.

386
00:24:40,440 --> 00:24:44,592
Who brought them back to the Jeffersonian
where they were stolen again?

387
00:24:44,680 --> 00:24:47,717
- Restolen, sir.
- You got a security problem, Dr Goodman.

388
00:24:47,800 --> 00:24:50,155
And you may have a murder problem.

389
00:24:50,240 --> 00:24:53,391
But I'm on top of it.
You didn't have to come down here, sir.

390
00:24:53,480 --> 00:24:56,677
I got a call from someone
at the Department of Defense.

391
00:24:56,760 --> 00:24:59,797
Defense? How do they figure
into a murder investigation?

392
00:24:59,880 --> 00:25:02,110
Branson Rose has friends in high places.

393
00:25:02,200 --> 00:25:05,556
They don't like it when the guy
who builds their bombers is unappy.

394
00:25:05,640 --> 00:25:10,760
- Are they afraid he'll bomb them?
- Is that squint humour? I'm not laughing.

395
00:25:10,840 --> 00:25:14,719
Defense doesn't need a reason to go to war
and I won't be their next target.

396
00:25:14,800 --> 00:25:18,952
- We haven't ruled Rose out as a suspect.
- You're too busy looking for your bones.

397
00:25:19,040 --> 00:25:22,350
- Let's not get personal.
- Rose wants to keep playing in the mud

398
00:25:22,440 --> 00:25:27,560
and his big-shot friends will see that happens
unless we come up with some answers fast.

399
00:25:27,640 --> 00:25:33,192
At this point, it appears as if the stolen bones
are being used to, you know, salt the shaft.

400
00:25:33,280 --> 00:25:36,078
- Salt the shaft?
- An investor spends $1 million.

401
00:25:36,160 --> 00:25:39,550
He gets antsy when nothing happens,
then pirate bones appear

402
00:25:39,640 --> 00:25:43,030
and the golden goose keeps,
you know, laying those eggs.

403
00:25:43,120 --> 00:25:45,759
OK, that is a convoluted metaphor, Booth.

404
00:25:45,840 --> 00:25:50,755
- It's a hoax, Dr Brennan, like Piltdown Man.
- Oh, got it. Why can't you be clear like that?

405
00:25:50,840 --> 00:25:53,798
- Assuming the bones were stolen...
- Restolen.

406
00:25:53,880 --> 00:25:56,997
...so you wouldn't find out they were bogus,
how did you?

407
00:25:57,080 --> 00:25:59,036
- How did I what?
- From the finger.

408
00:25:59,120 --> 00:26:03,272
Would you like Dr Brennan
to take you through the process?

409
00:26:03,360 --> 00:26:06,670
- I really wouldn't. So, who do you like?
- I like the partner.

410
00:26:06,760 --> 00:26:08,955
- Hardewicke.
- Access, motive, ability.

411
00:26:09,040 --> 00:26:13,750
The FBI will provide whatever help you need
to solve your breach of security.

412
00:26:13,840 --> 00:26:15,751
You work the partner angle.

413
00:26:19,880 --> 00:26:22,440
Well, my father worked the fishing boat.

414
00:26:22,520 --> 00:26:26,672
His dad before that. Heck, me and my brother,
we never knew anything but the sea.

415
00:26:26,760 --> 00:26:30,070
Hunting for treasure
just sort of grew out of that, I guess.

416
00:26:30,160 --> 00:26:33,391
- Any regrets?
- Sure. My brother.

417
00:26:33,840 --> 00:26:35,717
- Yeah.
- Yeah.

418
00:26:35,800 --> 00:26:38,519
That and the fact
that they might shut us down.

419
00:26:38,600 --> 00:26:41,672
Not if we find something, huh?

420
00:26:41,760 --> 00:26:44,877
I thought you were gonna be
just another deskjockey

421
00:26:44,960 --> 00:26:48,839
who read a few books and was looking
for something to brighten up his life.

422
00:26:48,920 --> 00:26:50,831
I'd be down that shaft right now

423
00:26:50,920 --> 00:26:55,038
if Big Brother didn't have the minimum
time requirement between dives.

424
00:26:55,480 --> 00:26:59,439
You deserve to be here. You really do.

425
00:26:59,520 --> 00:27:01,511
Thanks for that.

426
00:27:02,440 --> 00:27:07,150
I guess it's all right to tell you,
the bones were planted.

427
00:27:09,760 --> 00:27:14,754
- You don't seem surprised.
- Nothing surprises me out of that pit.

428
00:27:14,840 --> 00:27:16,592
Nah.

429
00:27:16,680 --> 00:27:20,593
I mean, you dig down far enough,
you come out in hell.

430
00:27:20,680 --> 00:27:24,992
So, uh, if you don't find anything,
are you gonna shut us down?

431
00:27:25,080 --> 00:27:27,594
Hey, I'm not FBI! I'm just a scientist.

432
00:27:27,680 --> 00:27:30,672
It's a crime scene.
I'm surprised they let you down there.

433
00:27:30,760 --> 00:27:35,436
I'm an expert in silt, plants and insects.
That's right. I got three doctorates.

434
00:27:35,520 --> 00:27:36,157
Whoa!

435
00:27:36,240 --> 00:27:40,358
When you got three doctorates and you need
more samples, who's gonna argue?

436
00:27:40,440 --> 00:27:44,638
One doctorate, yeah, maybe they argue.
But three?

437
00:27:46,000 --> 00:27:49,390
You want to go back down again, don't you?

438
00:27:51,880 --> 00:27:55,111
- I could use your help, man.
- You got the bug, man!

439
00:27:55,200 --> 00:27:58,112
Hey, like I said, I am the bug man.

440
00:27:58,200 --> 00:27:59,952
<i>(laughter)</i>

441
00:28:01,640 --> 00:28:05,428
- How do you know the bones are fake?
- Thieves didn't get everything.

442
00:28:05,520 --> 00:28:10,753
- A stroke of luck for the good guys.
- We'll find out how those bones were stolen.

443
00:28:10,840 --> 00:28:12,671
You still think I did it, don't you?

444
00:28:12,760 --> 00:28:15,479
Why were you going
to break up the company?

445
00:28:15,560 --> 00:28:18,836
- Katie Ney told you that.
- What makes you think it was Katie?

446
00:28:18,920 --> 00:28:23,357
That was a stock part of Macy's seduction
technique and it was very effective.

447
00:28:23,440 --> 00:28:28,594
"I risk my life down in that hole
while my partner stays safe topside."

448
00:28:28,680 --> 00:28:32,275
That's how he positioned himself
as the heroic explorer.

449
00:28:32,360 --> 00:28:36,433
- Which he was, when it came to the ladies.
- Your partnership was intact?

450
00:28:36,520 --> 00:28:41,878
Till death did us part. I'll tell you what, I'm
gonna give you guys full access to the books.

451
00:28:41,960 --> 00:28:44,235
You don't even need a search warrant.

452
00:28:44,320 --> 00:28:49,269
There's not a single way
in which my life is better off without Macy.

453
00:28:49,360 --> 00:28:51,954
Like I said, I miss the man.

454
00:28:55,200 --> 00:28:58,272
The bones were stolen twice.
The first time from the exhibit,

455
00:28:58,360 --> 00:29:00,954
the second time from the Medico-Legal Lab.

456
00:29:01,040 --> 00:29:04,237
The security in the lab is tighter
so the camera is continuous

457
00:29:04,320 --> 00:29:07,232
but the camera in the rotunda is stop-action.

458
00:29:07,320 --> 00:29:13,111
I started with the lab theft because we know
the bones were stolen between 9pm and 6am.

459
00:29:13,200 --> 00:29:17,478
OK, watch... here.

460
00:29:17,560 --> 00:29:20,518
- The bones are gone.
- Notice the time code.

461
00:29:21,440 --> 00:29:24,637
- <i>(Goodman)</i> What's that?
- The camera was turned off.

462
00:29:24,720 --> 00:29:27,917
The camera was turned off
for one minute and 46 seconds.

463
00:29:28,000 --> 00:29:32,790
It would take a lot less time than that to enter
the room, gather up the bones and escape.

464
00:29:34,400 --> 00:29:36,118
Now.

465
00:29:36,200 --> 00:29:37,838
- Dr Goodman?
- Yes?

466
00:29:37,920 --> 00:29:41,674
Can I ask, why are we doing this investigation
instead of security?

467
00:29:41,760 --> 00:29:45,036
We shouldn't walk too quickly.
It would arouse suspicion.

468
00:29:45,120 --> 00:29:47,998
I'm happy to help
but we have security professionals.

469
00:29:48,080 --> 00:29:50,594
Can we tell if those tapes
have been doctored?

470
00:29:50,680 --> 00:29:54,753
Yeah, since they're physical magnetic tapes,
not stored digitally.

471
00:29:54,840 --> 00:29:57,229
I always did like analogue. Now I know why.

472
00:29:57,320 --> 00:30:01,757
I'm only an amateur at this. I'm sure
the security department is better equipped...

473
00:30:01,840 --> 00:30:05,150
Afternoon, Paul. Best to Susan.
I hope Johnny feels better.

474
00:30:05,240 --> 00:30:10,792
- <i>(Paul)</i> Thank you, Dr Goodman.
- OK, you don't want to talk about it. I get it.

475
00:30:10,880 --> 00:30:14,555
- Sir?
- Hit your stopwatch, Miss Montenegro.

476
00:30:14,640 --> 00:30:16,551
35.6 seconds.

477
00:30:16,640 --> 00:30:18,915
For a round trip, one minute ten seconds,

478
00:30:19,000 --> 00:30:22,037
leaving 30 seconds
to bag the bones and get back.

479
00:30:22,120 --> 00:30:24,111
Get back where?

480
00:30:25,440 --> 00:30:27,670
Oh. Huh.

481
00:30:27,760 --> 00:30:30,991
- Wow. You must think I'm an idiot.
- I was grandstanding.

482
00:30:31,080 --> 00:30:36,996
We find out what guards were on duty during
the two thefts and we might have our thief.

483
00:30:37,080 --> 00:30:41,278
- I didn't see the harm.
- In stealing human remains?

484
00:30:41,360 --> 00:30:44,750
After 300 years
it's not like he's got a family grieving for him.

485
00:30:44,840 --> 00:30:48,276
- Think of me as a grieving parent.
- Grand theft, that's eight years.

486
00:30:48,360 --> 00:30:50,715
- If I don't kill you.
- Come on.

487
00:30:50,800 --> 00:30:53,951
What's a bunch of old bones like that won'th?
Nothing.

488
00:30:54,040 --> 00:30:56,634
- How much did you get?
- A couple of hundred bucks.

489
00:30:56,720 --> 00:31:02,670
Yeah. So this, uh... <i>(coughs)</i> wire transfer
into your bank for ten grand, what's that?

490
00:31:02,760 --> 00:31:04,751
Ineritance?

491
00:31:05,880 --> 00:31:08,758
<i>(Bones)</i> Who did you steal them for?

492
00:31:09,880 --> 00:31:13,236
- We didn't do the name exchange thing.
- Somebody approached you?

493
00:31:13,320 --> 00:31:15,311
Yeah.

494
00:31:16,640 --> 00:31:20,155
- Let's see. OK. Which one was it?
- Which time?

495
00:31:22,480 --> 00:31:24,471
The first time.

496
00:31:24,920 --> 00:31:26,672
<i>(guard)</i> Him.

497
00:31:26,760 --> 00:31:29,149
But he looked better.

498
00:31:29,240 --> 00:31:31,276
- And the second time?
- Uh...

499
00:31:32,040 --> 00:31:33,917
Him.

500
00:31:34,000 --> 00:31:36,389
Look, guys, I'm cooperating.

501
00:31:36,480 --> 00:31:41,031
All right? I will give back the money. I will
quit my job. How's about we call it even?

502
00:31:41,120 --> 00:31:44,396
You need a better screening process
down at the museum.

503
00:31:44,480 --> 00:31:48,712
- Ironic, given we contract that out to the FBI.
- The...

504
00:31:48,800 --> 00:31:49,869
<i>(</i>d <i>bagpipes)</i>

505
00:31:49,960 --> 00:31:54,272
- You think he's dangerous?
- Grand theft? Murder? Yeah.

506
00:31:54,360 --> 00:31:56,874
The music. Shh. It's down there.

507
00:31:56,960 --> 00:32:00,032
It's not music. It's bagpipes. Whoa.

508
00:32:02,400 --> 00:32:05,039
Mr Hardewicke?

509
00:32:10,040 --> 00:32:12,349
Mr Hard...

510
00:32:12,440 --> 00:32:13,509
Oh.

511
00:32:16,240 --> 00:32:19,915
Maybe we're looking for someone else.

512
00:32:23,680 --> 00:32:25,352
The larynx was crushed.

513
00:32:25,440 --> 00:32:29,035
- Is that your cause-of-death ruling?
- We gonna have another fight?

514
00:32:29,120 --> 00:32:33,193
If you keep pushing like that,
it's gonna be me who smacks you around.

515
00:32:33,280 --> 00:32:37,353
How do you know that won't work
for me just as well?

516
00:32:38,320 --> 00:32:40,788
You ruled that Macy died
from a crushed larynx.

517
00:32:40,880 --> 00:32:44,998
A crushed larynx is fatal.
Ergo, it results in death.

518
00:32:45,080 --> 00:32:48,789
- You were wrong then and you're wrong now.
- See? He likes it!

519
00:32:48,880 --> 00:32:52,714
I need to see both sets of X-rays.
His and Macy's.

520
00:32:55,720 --> 00:32:59,679
It's not always about being right or wrong.

521
00:32:59,760 --> 00:33:06,029
It's about the dialogue. Intense conversation
is the most wonderful kind of intercourse.

522
00:33:06,120 --> 00:33:07,917
This guy is a pervert.

523
00:33:08,000 --> 00:33:11,834
Damage between C2 and C4, 45° angle,

524
00:33:11,920 --> 00:33:15,037
exact same pattern of injury as Macy.

525
00:33:15,120 --> 00:33:20,638
His head was wrenched around, probably
while the other hand crushed the larynx.

526
00:33:20,720 --> 00:33:22,915
Must frustrate you that I missed that.

527
00:33:23,000 --> 00:33:27,118
Wait. That's a Special Forces move.
Crush the larynx so he can't scream.

528
00:33:27,200 --> 00:33:31,671
- You've done that to people?
- No. Our murderer is Special Forces.

529
00:33:31,760 --> 00:33:35,196
Your internet bio says you spent time
in Special Air Services.

530
00:33:35,280 --> 00:33:37,794
Mr Rose has led a diverse and full life.

531
00:33:37,880 --> 00:33:40,713
How did you feel when you found out
the site was salted?

532
00:33:40,800 --> 00:33:43,553
- I was disappointed.
- Just disappointed?

533
00:33:43,640 --> 00:33:47,155
I wasrt irked enough to kill Ted Macy.
Can we get to the point?

534
00:33:47,240 --> 00:33:48,832
What is Special Air Services?

535
00:33:48,920 --> 00:33:54,119
The SAS is widely regarded as one of
the finest Special Forces units in the world.

536
00:33:54,200 --> 00:33:58,432
- See any active service?
- <i>(man)</i> Mr Rose does not discuss specifics.

537
00:33:58,520 --> 00:34:01,910
I don't exploit my role in operations
which cost men their lives.

538
00:34:02,000 --> 00:34:05,754
If all you're interested in is my history,
there's a bio on my website.

539
00:34:05,840 --> 00:34:12,109
We wanted to know if your reputation is for
real. We'll just contact the SAS. They'll tell us.

540
00:34:12,200 --> 00:34:14,191
- Well, look...
- Fine.

541
00:34:15,400 --> 00:34:17,595
Don't expect a speedy response.

542
00:34:18,120 --> 00:34:19,678
- Bones!
- That's assault!

543
00:34:19,760 --> 00:34:22,752
Would a Special Forces guy
have been able to stop that?

544
00:34:22,840 --> 00:34:26,833
- I don't know. You got the jump on him there.
- This one won't be a surprise.

545
00:34:26,920 --> 00:34:28,478
- You ready?
- What?

546
00:34:28,560 --> 00:34:30,949
This is common assault. Charges will be laid.

547
00:34:31,040 --> 00:34:33,554
No way he's special ops.
It's a bunch of PR crap.

548
00:34:33,640 --> 00:34:37,030
- No more questions.
- I demand she be arrested for assault!

549
00:34:37,120 --> 00:34:39,111
Shut up, Kendall.

550
00:34:40,880 --> 00:34:45,396
Think I want it all over the newspapers that
I'm taking a woman to court for slapping me?

551
00:34:45,720 --> 00:34:50,271
- You won't get into trouble for this?
- Three degrees. Just doing some research.

552
00:34:50,360 --> 00:34:55,070
I am telling you, salted or not,
there is something at the bottom of that shaft.

553
00:34:55,160 --> 00:34:57,276
I never got to go all the way down.

554
00:34:57,360 --> 00:35:00,352
The bones were on wood.
I want to see what's underneath.

555
00:35:00,440 --> 00:35:04,752
- I always thought it'd be me who'd find it.
- Hey, all for one and one for all, right?

556
00:35:04,840 --> 00:35:08,515
- That was <i>The Three Musketeers.</i>
- They were always piratey to me.

557
00:35:08,600 --> 00:35:10,989
- Let's do this.
- Let's do it.

558
00:35:17,360 --> 00:35:19,351
Hey.

559
00:35:44,440 --> 00:35:46,749
Dispatch, 22705.

560
00:35:46,840 --> 00:35:51,470
Last name McGinnis, first name Dane. I need
to know which military branch he served in.

561
00:35:51,560 --> 00:35:54,472
<i>(radio) Affirmative, 22705. Stand by.</i>

562
00:35:54,560 --> 00:35:57,074
- Why Dane?
- He said Hodgins swam like a squid.

563
00:35:57,160 --> 00:35:59,196
Squint. He must've said squint.

564
00:35:59,280 --> 00:36:04,070
No, I said squint, OK? Dane said squid,
which is military slang for a sailor.

565
00:36:04,160 --> 00:36:06,196
Is this what they call a Hail Mary pass?

566
00:36:06,640 --> 00:36:08,995
- <i>(Hodgins) You receiving?</i>
- Loud and clear.

567
00:36:09,080 --> 00:36:10,911
<i>Man, it's muddy today.</i>

568
00:36:11,000 --> 00:36:14,788
Yeah? Usually it clears up
past the first flood channel at 12m.

569
00:36:14,880 --> 00:36:18,429
d Yo, ho, ho and a bottle of rum

570
00:36:18,520 --> 00:36:23,913
Don't conjure up any ghosts. There's too
many down there waiting to claim your ass.

571
00:36:24,000 --> 00:36:26,594
Ghosts? Right.

572
00:36:27,840 --> 00:36:31,674
<i>22705, Dispatch.</i>
<i>McGinnis, Dane, served in the navy.</i>

573
00:36:31,760 --> 00:36:35,070
<i>Rating, chief petty officer,</i>
<i>Naval Special Warfare.</i>

574
00:36:35,160 --> 00:36:38,391
- Oh, yeah. Had to be.
- What?

575
00:36:48,480 --> 00:36:51,313
- Guy was a Navy SEAL.
- So? You were a guide.

576
00:36:51,400 --> 00:36:55,837
A Ranger. I was a Ranger, Bones, OK?
I was not a guide.

577
00:36:55,920 --> 00:36:59,799
Guides, they show you waterfalls,
they sell you cookies. I was a Ranger.

578
00:36:59,880 --> 00:37:03,316
<i>(Bones)</i> What's he doing at the shaft?

579
00:37:03,400 --> 00:37:06,312
- Are Rangers afraid of SEALs?
- What? Come on. No.

580
00:37:06,400 --> 00:37:12,270
Rangers aren't afraid of anybody. All right?
SEALs are pretty good, though.

581
00:37:23,920 --> 00:37:27,151
- Hey, Dane.
- Oh, hey. What's up?

582
00:37:27,240 --> 00:37:29,117
- We know it was you.
- Bones.

583
00:37:29,200 --> 00:37:32,033
- You have a gun. What's he got?
- Somebody in the shaft.

584
00:37:32,120 --> 00:37:34,793
- How far down am I?
- Is that Hodgins?

585
00:37:34,880 --> 00:37:37,394
<i>Hey, Dane?</i>

586
00:37:37,480 --> 00:37:39,710
<i>I can't read my depth display.</i>

587
00:37:42,760 --> 00:37:44,671
Hey, is something going on?

588
00:37:45,120 --> 00:37:48,078
<i>Is there anybody up there?</i>
<i>Why don't you answer me?</i>

589
00:37:48,160 --> 00:37:51,436
CPO McGinnis, step away from the air hose.

590
00:37:51,520 --> 00:37:55,399
Yeah? Well, I need you
to toss that gun into the shaft,

591
00:37:55,480 --> 00:37:59,189
and toss me your keys,
and handcuff yourselves to that crane.

592
00:37:59,280 --> 00:38:03,751
I take your truck. Otherwise, I am going to cut
this hose and your buddy's gonna die.

593
00:38:03,840 --> 00:38:07,196
- Yeah. Do that.
- Bones... Not gonna happen.

594
00:38:07,280 --> 00:38:10,238
<i>If you can hear me, tug on the air hose.</i>

595
00:38:10,320 --> 00:38:15,269
I feel a blast of cold water. It's a spring
or some kind of conduit from the ocean.

596
00:38:15,360 --> 00:38:17,476
It's clear water. Visibility is better.

597
00:38:17,560 --> 00:38:20,154
You killed two men. I can't let you drive away.

598
00:38:20,240 --> 00:38:26,315
Those guys. Putting fake bones in there,
making the whole thing into a con job.

599
00:38:26,400 --> 00:38:29,710
My brother died down there
looking for that treasure.

600
00:38:29,800 --> 00:38:34,669
A lot of good men did. This was their life.
Those men dishonoured them.

601
00:38:34,760 --> 00:38:38,594
Dane, can you hear me, man?
I am on the bottom.

602
00:38:38,680 --> 00:38:41,399
You good enough to take that shot
before I cut this?

603
00:38:41,480 --> 00:38:43,471
- Pretty good.
- Just pretty good?

604
00:38:43,560 --> 00:38:45,915
Please. I'm working.

605
00:38:47,680 --> 00:38:51,719
<i>I'm gonna need some more slack in the line,</i>
<i>Dane. I mean, what's going on?</i>

606
00:38:51,800 --> 00:38:54,314
<i>I'll get a sample.</i>

607
00:38:54,400 --> 00:38:58,154
I can see where the shaft wall
has collapsed before.

608
00:39:00,400 --> 00:39:03,472
<i>Oh, my God. Holy...</i>

609
00:39:03,560 --> 00:39:04,709
<i>Damn!</i>

610
00:39:04,800 --> 00:39:08,315
<i>Can you see this, Dane?</i>

611
00:39:08,400 --> 00:39:09,958
- What is it?
- Take a look.

612
00:39:10,040 --> 00:39:12,349
Yeah. I do, you'll shoot me.

613
00:39:13,480 --> 00:39:14,993
<i>(laughs)</i>

614
00:39:15,080 --> 00:39:17,389
Dane? Can you see this, man?

615
00:39:17,480 --> 00:39:19,630
- It's a gold coin.
- Yeah.

616
00:39:19,720 --> 00:39:22,280
Probably something else
they stole from the museum.

617
00:39:22,360 --> 00:39:25,477
<i>This is real! It's a big...</i>

618
00:39:28,240 --> 00:39:31,630
You want to see it,
you're going to have to bring Hodgins up.

619
00:39:31,720 --> 00:39:35,508
Please. He's down there
because he believes.

620
00:39:36,320 --> 00:39:39,437
He's no different than you,
no different than your brother.

621
00:39:39,520 --> 00:39:41,590
Bring him up.

622
00:39:41,680 --> 00:39:44,274
<i>(Bones)</i> Do it for your brother.

623
00:39:55,840 --> 00:39:58,798
An original Breen 984 half doubloon,

624
00:39:58,880 --> 00:40:02,077
designed by Ephraim Brasher,
engraved by Ephraim Brasher,

625
00:40:02,160 --> 00:40:06,551
and, hold your breath,
gentlemen and ladies, 204 grains.

626
00:40:06,640 --> 00:40:09,598
- A real gold pirate coin.
- How many more are down there?

627
00:40:09,680 --> 00:40:13,559
Rose agreed to have the museum
do the authentication of the treasure.

628
00:40:13,640 --> 00:40:16,154
- There won't be any more.
- Why do you say that?

629
00:40:16,240 --> 00:40:19,391
I was down there.
It's not gonna give it up that easily.

630
00:40:19,480 --> 00:40:22,756
- The treasure's been located.
- I'm sure it's been located before.

631
00:40:22,840 --> 00:40:24,831
I'll take that.

632
00:40:27,040 --> 00:40:28,632
<i>(frustrated sigh)</i>

633
00:40:29,440 --> 00:40:34,719
- You think he's happy to be back home?
- Well, he looks that way to me.

634
00:40:34,800 --> 00:40:36,358
<i>(laughter)</i>

635
00:40:38,280 --> 00:40:39,838
Ha.

636
00:40:39,920 --> 00:40:41,911
- He's not happy.
- What do you mean?

637
00:40:42,000 --> 00:40:45,549
Hodgins is right. He'd be a lot happier
at the bottom of that shaft.

638
00:40:45,640 --> 00:40:47,915
With the other pirates.

639
00:40:49,400 --> 00:40:53,029
- Arrr!
- Arrr, matey. Arrr!

640
00:40:53,120 --> 00:40:55,475
<i>(Booth)</i> Arrr!

641
00:41:21,920 --> 00:41:24,036
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke

642
00:41:28,160 --> 00:41:29,479
What's that mean?

643
00:41:30,240 --> 00:41:32,231
ENGLISH SDH

