1
00:00:01,080 --> 00:00:03,958
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Winter Wonderland" by Jewel)</i>

2
00:00:04,040 --> 00:00:08,113
♪ <i>Sleigh bells ring, are you listening?</i>

3
00:00:08,200 --> 00:00:12,591
♪ <i>In the lane snow is glistening</i>

4
00:00:12,680 --> 00:00:16,753
♪ <i>A beautiful sight, we're happy tonight</i>

5
00:00:16,840 --> 00:00:20,355
♪ <i>Walking in a winter wonderland</i>

6
00:00:21,400 --> 00:00:23,960
- Sweetie.
- Angela, I don't want to.

7
00:00:24,040 --> 00:00:26,031
Sweetie, could you stop galloping?

8
00:00:26,120 --> 00:00:29,351
Better able to withstand pressure
when you can't catch me.

9
00:00:29,440 --> 00:00:30,793
Call it a favour.

10
00:00:30,880 --> 00:00:33,633
How is me going to
a company Christmas party a favour?

11
00:00:33,720 --> 00:00:36,280
- Remember what happened last year?
- I didn't go.

12
00:00:36,360 --> 00:00:39,636
Exactly. It took me weeks
to collect all those photocopies.

13
00:00:39,720 --> 00:00:43,952
I need you. Friends don't let friends
photocopy their butts at company parties.

14
00:00:44,040 --> 00:00:46,918
- There's a secret Santa.
- I don't like secret Santa.

15
00:00:47,000 --> 00:00:51,391
The idea that we are forced by convention
to exchange meaningless gifts...

16
00:00:51,480 --> 00:00:55,519
Yeah. If you rearrange "secret Santa",
though, you get "secret Satan".

17
00:00:55,600 --> 00:01:00,196
- What possible meaning could that have?
- I've already had an eggnog, if you can't tell.

18
00:01:00,280 --> 00:01:04,956
How am I gonna enjoy this party knowing
that my best friend in the world is in the lab,

19
00:01:05,040 --> 00:01:07,679
eyeball to eyeball with Skeletor?

20
00:01:07,760 --> 00:01:11,070
- Who?
- He's a can'toon villain who looks like...

21
00:01:11,160 --> 00:01:15,790
You know, his name is self-explanatory.
Would you please just come to this party?

22
00:01:15,880 --> 00:01:16,869
Phew.

23
00:01:16,960 --> 00:01:20,669
- 20 minutes.
- Bones. All right.

24
00:01:20,760 --> 00:01:24,275
- Merry Christmas, Seeley.
- Oh, wow. Oof!

25
00:01:24,360 --> 00:01:26,351
- What are you? An elf?
- Yes.

26
00:01:26,440 --> 00:01:28,908
What's wrong with a little Christmas spirit?

27
00:01:29,000 --> 00:01:31,992
- What's the context?
- A property on Dupont Circle,

28
00:01:32,080 --> 00:01:35,959
where Congress puts up
agricultural specialists, or something.

29
00:01:36,040 --> 00:01:41,034
They're digging to put in a solarium and they
find a fallout shelter with a skeleton inside.

30
00:01:41,120 --> 00:01:45,033
- How long was it in there?
- It was built in the '50s. That A-bomb panic.

31
00:01:45,120 --> 00:01:48,749
- It's not a suicide.
- Why? Hole in the head, the gun - suicide.

32
00:01:48,840 --> 00:01:52,674
He shoots himself in the head and
somehow his arm ends up across his chest?

33
00:01:52,760 --> 00:01:55,399
Bring the skeleton. I'll prove it wasrt suicide.

34
00:01:55,480 --> 00:01:57,675
Merry Christmas, Bones. <i>(whistles)</i>

35
00:01:57,760 --> 00:02:02,436
- Come on, boys, bring it in.
- Oh, no. We're going to the company party.

36
00:02:02,520 --> 00:02:06,229
Go ahead. I'll do a cursory examination
and meet you in a few minutes.

37
00:02:06,320 --> 00:02:09,278
All right. There you go. Wow.

38
00:02:09,360 --> 00:02:14,434
Booth, will you escort Angela to the party and
make sure she doesn't photocopy her butt?

39
00:02:14,520 --> 00:02:18,957
No, I can't do that. I got some last-minute
Christmas shopping that I gotta do.

40
00:02:19,040 --> 00:02:23,591
- It's not last-minute until tomorrow.
- Come on, Bones. Bones. I gotta...

41
00:02:23,680 --> 00:02:25,636
- Come on.
- Jeez.

42
00:02:26,440 --> 00:02:28,237
<i>(Zack)</i> Stop.

43
00:02:30,160 --> 00:02:31,957
Stop!

44
00:02:36,000 --> 00:02:38,150
Turn.

45
00:02:38,240 --> 00:02:42,916
Your robot reminds me of you. You tell it
to turn, it stops. You tell it to stop, it turns.

46
00:02:43,000 --> 00:02:46,231
You ask it to take out garbage,
it watches reruns of <i>Firefly</i>.

47
00:02:46,320 --> 00:02:51,269
After I fix the voice recognition protocols, this
is going to blow those gomers at MIT away.

48
00:02:51,360 --> 00:02:54,716
We've got about half a litre
of pure alcohol here.

49
00:02:54,800 --> 00:02:58,429
Dump it in the eggnog,
we've got the best Christmas party in history.

50
00:03:14,840 --> 00:03:17,308
- I brought eggnog.
- I can't drink while I work.

51
00:03:17,400 --> 00:03:20,676
- Good thing I didn't bring it for you.
- Crystal is after you.

52
00:03:20,760 --> 00:03:23,354
Like Alien after Predator.

53
00:03:23,440 --> 00:03:25,237
Sit!

54
00:03:28,080 --> 00:03:30,389
<i>(robot falls then whirs)</i>

55
00:03:34,280 --> 00:03:37,829
- What have you got there?
- Two open tickets to Paris.

56
00:03:37,920 --> 00:03:41,196
One-way. Pan Transit Airlines.

57
00:03:41,280 --> 00:03:44,238
- They're blank.
- Pan Transit went bust in the '60s.

58
00:03:44,320 --> 00:03:48,438
- I thought you were at the party.
- It's not a party, it's a Star Wars convention.

59
00:03:48,520 --> 00:03:52,593
- This was still in the skull.
- <i>(whistles)</i>

60
00:03:52,680 --> 00:03:55,877
.22 calibre, matches the gun.
Did you open up the suitcase?

61
00:03:55,960 --> 00:03:57,075
- Nope.
- Why not?

62
00:03:57,160 --> 00:03:59,674
Its contents could compromise
my objectivity.

63
00:03:59,760 --> 00:04:03,799
- Yeah, like a name and address?
- I prefer unbiased initial observations.

64
00:04:03,880 --> 00:04:07,429
- Is that pure alcohol?
- Yes, Dr Brennan.

65
00:04:07,520 --> 00:04:11,832
You think Goodman will let you spike
the eggnog after the Fourth of July fiasco?

66
00:04:11,920 --> 00:04:14,753
- We may have to rethink.
- Zack, clean these bones.

67
00:04:14,840 --> 00:04:16,831
- Now?
- Ha! Burnt.

68
00:04:16,920 --> 00:04:19,992
And I need <i>you</i> to search the clothing
for insect evidence.

69
00:04:20,080 --> 00:04:22,469
Jeez, Bones, merry Christmas.

70
00:04:22,560 --> 00:04:24,869
<i>(Angela)</i> OK. You people listen to me.

71
00:04:24,960 --> 00:04:28,839
There is a party going on upstairs, OK?
A Christmas party.

72
00:04:28,920 --> 00:04:34,278
We're going up there. We're gonna talk to
some people, sing some carols, drink eggnog.

73
00:04:34,360 --> 00:04:38,239
You are going to kiss me under the mistletoe.
On the lips.

74
00:04:38,320 --> 00:04:41,551
I might kiss you guys under the mistletoe too.

75
00:04:41,640 --> 00:04:45,030
Maybe even you.
In a festive, nonlesbian manner.

76
00:04:45,120 --> 00:04:47,634
But we are going to that party.

77
00:04:51,760 --> 00:04:54,911
- Put on a mask. I'm taking core samples.
- OK.

78
00:04:55,000 --> 00:04:57,195
<i>(drill whirs)</i>

79
00:05:13,720 --> 00:05:15,278
<i>(electronic click)</i>

80
00:05:15,360 --> 00:05:17,794
<i>(alarm)</i>

81
00:05:22,600 --> 00:05:25,068
- What's that?
- Biological contamination.

82
00:05:30,640 --> 00:05:31,959
<i>(Hodgins)</i> Zack!

83
00:05:33,360 --> 00:05:34,952
Whoa!

84
00:05:35,040 --> 00:05:39,238
- The doors seal automatically. Don't worry.
- What do you mean, don't worry?

85
00:05:39,320 --> 00:05:41,550
Don't panic until we know what it is.

86
00:05:41,640 --> 00:05:43,631
- What what is?
- We might know.

87
00:05:43,720 --> 00:05:47,349
I cut into the fallout shelter bones
and the biohazard alarm went off.

88
00:05:47,440 --> 00:05:50,477
- Were you conforming to autopsy protocol?
- One of us was.

89
00:05:50,560 --> 00:05:52,994
The other was drinking an eggnog.

90
00:05:53,080 --> 00:05:56,231
And you didn't have your mask on? Oh!

91
00:06:03,800 --> 00:06:07,315
- <i>The pathogen is coccidioidomycosis.</i>
- Valley fever?

92
00:06:07,400 --> 00:06:11,871
<i>It was picked up in the scanner</i>
<i>in the discharge vent at Mr Addy's station.</i>

93
00:06:11,960 --> 00:06:15,316
- What's valley fever?
- A fungus that can lead to pneumonia,

94
00:06:15,400 --> 00:06:17,709
spontaneous abortion. Death.

95
00:06:17,800 --> 00:06:21,952
The alarm sounded after Mr Addy
cut into a human bone. That was the source.

96
00:06:22,040 --> 00:06:26,158
- <i>Was he following autopsy protocol?</i>
- Of course. However...

97
00:06:26,240 --> 00:06:28,913
I was drinking an eggnog.

98
00:06:29,000 --> 00:06:31,309
<i>And he's with you, breathing the same air.</i>

99
00:06:31,400 --> 00:06:35,871
I got into the decontamination shower with
Zack. Havert I been through enough hell?

100
00:06:35,960 --> 00:06:38,918
- Is he contagious?
- <i>He may have inaled the spores, yes.</i>

101
00:06:39,000 --> 00:06:44,393
OK. It must suck to be Hodgins, but the rest
of us didn't inale. So it's OK that I go, right?

102
00:06:44,480 --> 00:06:47,358
Dr Hodgins may have exhaled
the spores all over us.

103
00:06:47,440 --> 00:06:52,514
<i>We must impose quarantine. Valley fever</i>
<i>can be fatal, and we can't risk a pandemic.</i>

104
00:06:52,600 --> 00:06:55,558
<i>Just calm down and let us</i>
<i>handle things from this side.</i>

105
00:06:55,640 --> 00:06:59,872
Anyone besides me worried
that a guy dressed like Santa is in charge?

106
00:06:59,960 --> 00:07:01,598
<i>Merry Christmas.</i>

107
00:07:01,680 --> 00:07:04,592
You know what?
If this is fatal, I will shoot both of you.

108
00:07:05,040 --> 00:07:07,190
Maybe you guys could go get dressed.

109
00:07:48,640 --> 00:07:53,475
I zapped the bones with ultraviolet light and
put them on the isolation table, so no spores.

110
00:07:53,560 --> 00:07:56,313
I found this
sewn into the lining of his clothing.

111
00:07:56,400 --> 00:08:01,076
- A womars wedding band.
- Two tickets to Paris, a picture forms.

112
00:08:01,160 --> 00:08:04,311
Don't form pictures.
Accumulate evidence. Dental work?

113
00:08:04,400 --> 00:08:07,836
Acrylic resins in the interior fillings
from the 1940s.

114
00:08:07,920 --> 00:08:13,711
Childhood tibia break. Bad enough that he
walked with a limp. Also, he wore a toupee.

115
00:08:13,800 --> 00:08:17,270
- It hasn't degraded.
- It's made of a synthetic called Dynel.

116
00:08:17,360 --> 00:08:19,954
It couldn't have looked good.

117
00:08:20,040 --> 00:08:23,874
This is a cocktail of four antifungal drugs,
including amphotericin B.

118
00:08:23,960 --> 00:08:27,669
You'll be taking ketoconazole,
fluconazole and itraconazole.

119
00:08:27,760 --> 00:08:29,318
Then we can leave?

120
00:08:29,400 --> 00:08:32,756
We won't know for a couple of days
if the fungus took hold in you.

121
00:08:32,840 --> 00:08:35,957
Whoa! You're saying that
we're stuck here over Christmas?

122
00:08:36,040 --> 00:08:40,318
Look, you know, I have... places to go.

123
00:08:40,400 --> 00:08:42,834
- I have obligations.
- We all have.

124
00:08:42,920 --> 00:08:45,673
- I'm supposed to go to Quebec.
- Whose fault is this?

125
00:08:45,760 --> 00:08:48,558
Who forced me to go to the party
where I drank too much?

126
00:08:48,640 --> 00:08:51,996
Who never should have cut a bone
with a drunken fool in the room?

127
00:08:52,080 --> 00:08:55,993
- Who brought us human remains?
- You're saying that this is my fault?

128
00:08:56,080 --> 00:09:00,676
- You knew Dr Brennan could not resist.
- I could have resisted had I been in Niger.

129
00:09:00,760 --> 00:09:03,991
- You're blaming me.
- We'll have sleeping bags delivered.

130
00:09:04,080 --> 00:09:08,756
Have your loved ones call me and we'll set up
a safe quarantine visit on Christmas Eve.

131
00:09:08,840 --> 00:09:10,956
Oh, and be prepared for side effects.

132
00:09:11,040 --> 00:09:13,190
Nausea, fever, insomnia?

133
00:09:13,280 --> 00:09:16,511
In rare cases euphoria,
dream state, mild hallucinations.

134
00:09:16,600 --> 00:09:17,953
I'll take that.

135
00:09:18,040 --> 00:09:21,112
- Early symptoms mimic a cold.
- What if it manifests?

136
00:09:21,200 --> 00:09:24,875
Treatment involves painful
injections into the base of the brain.

137
00:09:24,960 --> 00:09:31,433
You know what? I never realised
how pretty all this shiny stuff is.

138
00:09:31,520 --> 00:09:34,751
That is so not fair.

139
00:09:41,520 --> 00:09:46,435
Tomorrow I was leaving for Quebec. You
wanna know the true meaning of Christmas?

140
00:09:46,520 --> 00:09:51,753
It's being inside a 300-year-old inn with a
masseuse when there's 10ft of snow outside.

141
00:09:51,840 --> 00:09:56,391
Christmas is going home to Michigan and
cutting a Christmas tree with your brothers,

142
00:09:56,480 --> 00:10:00,314
and you all decorate it together -
brothers, sisters, nieces, nephews.

143
00:10:00,400 --> 00:10:02,914
40 people who love you
and are happy to see you.

144
00:10:03,000 --> 00:10:07,039
That, my friend,
is the true meaning of Christmas.

145
00:10:09,200 --> 00:10:13,432
Nah, I'm gonna have to go
with the masseuse on this one.

146
00:10:13,520 --> 00:10:17,957
What are those little tiny lights
dancing on the ceiling?

147
00:10:18,960 --> 00:10:23,715
For the third time, those are minute firings
of neurons on your optic nerve

148
00:10:23,800 --> 00:10:26,314
due to a reaction to the antifungal cocktail.

149
00:10:26,400 --> 00:10:28,550
Wow! <i>(laughs)</i>

150
00:10:28,640 --> 00:10:31,108
They're beautiful.

151
00:10:31,200 --> 00:10:34,158
You are stoned, Agent Booth.

152
00:10:34,960 --> 00:10:36,837
Oh, good.

153
00:10:36,920 --> 00:10:41,948
Let's hope it lasts long enough to keep this
from being the worst Christmas of my life.

154
00:10:42,040 --> 00:10:45,350
What are you complaining about?
I don't like to boast,

155
00:10:45,440 --> 00:10:48,398
but I am the spirit of Christmas in my house.

156
00:10:48,480 --> 00:10:53,190
I have a wife and twin 5-year-old daughters.

157
00:10:53,280 --> 00:10:57,512
We have family traditions. The most
important is being together for Christmas.

158
00:10:57,600 --> 00:11:00,068
Wow. They're beautiful.

159
00:11:01,680 --> 00:11:03,955
You know...

160
00:11:04,040 --> 00:11:06,838
I have a kid too.

161
00:11:07,560 --> 00:11:09,596
His name's Parker.

162
00:11:09,680 --> 00:11:15,630
He's four years old. His mother wouldn't
marry me so my parental rights are totally f...

163
00:11:15,720 --> 00:11:19,759
- Vague?
- That's Christmassier than what I thought.

164
00:11:19,840 --> 00:11:23,071
- He's a fine-Iooking boy.
- I get him part of Christmas Day.

165
00:11:23,160 --> 00:11:29,554
I get him an excellent present every year,
something really cool. But this year...

166
00:11:29,640 --> 00:11:32,518
Yes. This year...

167
00:11:33,400 --> 00:11:37,279
What are those little lights
on the ceiling again?

168
00:11:37,360 --> 00:11:40,432
I know it's against your nature,
but I need your help.

169
00:11:40,520 --> 00:11:43,557
- For what?
- To make Christmas.

170
00:11:43,640 --> 00:11:45,631
Why? Because we're the girls?

171
00:11:45,720 --> 00:11:50,555
Yes. We have to decorate
and we have to make our own secret Santa.

172
00:11:50,640 --> 00:11:53,074
You called it "secret Satan" before.

173
00:11:54,080 --> 00:11:59,313
It's all so tragic. The cheap wedding ring
sewn into his suit. Two tickets to Paris.

174
00:11:59,400 --> 00:12:03,837
It makes you wonder, who was the girl?
Can you imagine what it was like for her?

175
00:12:03,920 --> 00:12:07,799
Waiting and wondering,
never knowing what happened.

176
00:12:07,880 --> 00:12:11,475
- I don't have to imagine.
- What do you mean?

177
00:12:12,600 --> 00:12:16,149
- I tell you what I'm gonna do for Christmas.
- Good. Thank you.

178
00:12:16,240 --> 00:12:18,993
At last you decide to take part.

179
00:12:19,080 --> 00:12:21,230
I'm gonna solve a murder.

180
00:12:34,800 --> 00:12:37,837
Bones, it's after midnight. Hm?

181
00:12:37,920 --> 00:12:42,596
Christmas Eve day. Both an eve and a day,
it's a Christmas miracle.

182
00:12:42,680 --> 00:12:45,638
Still enjoying your medication, I see.

183
00:12:49,200 --> 00:12:53,034
OK. So, what are we looking at?

184
00:12:53,120 --> 00:12:56,999
There are traces of lead and nickel
on the guy's osteological profile.

185
00:12:57,080 --> 00:12:59,116
You don't seem upset to miss Christmas.

186
00:12:59,200 --> 00:13:02,556
Indications are that Christ,
if he existed, was born in spring,

187
00:13:02,640 --> 00:13:06,269
and the celebration of his birth
was shifted to the winter solstice

188
00:13:06,360 --> 00:13:08,669
so early Christians werert persecuted.

189
00:13:08,760 --> 00:13:12,389
- Hm. Who are you? The Christmas killer?
- It's the truth.

190
00:13:12,480 --> 00:13:16,268
It sounds like the truth
cos it's so rational, right?

191
00:13:16,360 --> 00:13:20,273
But, you know, the true truth is
that you hate Christmas

192
00:13:20,360 --> 00:13:24,239
so you just spout out all these facts
and you ruin it for everyone else.

193
00:13:24,320 --> 00:13:26,117
I ruin the true truth with facts?

194
00:13:26,200 --> 00:13:29,476
You ruined it for the squint squad
by making them work on a case

195
00:13:29,560 --> 00:13:33,348
about a guy who's been sealed up
in a fallout shelter for 50 years.

196
00:13:33,440 --> 00:13:35,317
How should I spend my Christmas?

197
00:13:35,400 --> 00:13:41,953
Christmas is the perfect time
to re-examine your standing with... you know.

198
00:13:43,080 --> 00:13:46,197
- A helicopter pilot?
- Oh, right, right.

199
00:13:46,280 --> 00:13:50,512
You can't measure the man upstairs
in a beaker so he can't possibly exist.

200
00:13:50,600 --> 00:13:52,989
- The man upstairs?
- Hm.

201
00:13:53,080 --> 00:13:57,471
You don't know if you're sick,
but you're willing to take drugs just in case.

202
00:13:57,560 --> 00:14:01,473
Seems to me you could give the man upstairs
the same benefit of the doubt

203
00:14:01,560 --> 00:14:03,790
that you do an invisible fungus.

204
00:14:07,880 --> 00:14:09,677
Hm.

205
00:14:17,320 --> 00:14:20,630
In some cases of valley fever
suppurating skin lesions appear.

206
00:14:20,720 --> 00:14:24,395
Could someone in responsibility
please order Zack to shut up?

207
00:14:24,480 --> 00:14:26,710
Coffee, coffee.

208
00:14:26,800 --> 00:14:30,076
- Good morning, Ms Montenegro.
- Where'd this come from?

209
00:14:30,160 --> 00:14:33,675
A hazmat team brought it over this morning.
Very appetising.

210
00:14:33,760 --> 00:14:36,638
- Are you back with us?
- Yeah, think so.

211
00:14:36,720 --> 00:14:40,554
Since we're stuck together for Christmas,
we should make the most of it.

212
00:14:40,640 --> 00:14:43,916
- How?
- Decorate, and exchange handmade gifts.

213
00:14:44,000 --> 00:14:46,434
- An excellent idea.
- I can get behind that.

214
00:14:46,520 --> 00:14:48,238
- I'm in.
- As am I.

215
00:14:48,320 --> 00:14:50,311
- How about Bones?
- <i>(all)</i> Hm...

216
00:14:50,400 --> 00:14:52,789
What's the deal with Bones and Christmas?

217
00:14:52,880 --> 00:14:57,635
Last night I spun a little story
about two young lovers running off to Paris,

218
00:14:57,720 --> 00:15:00,792
but the man never shows up
and the woman is left wondering.

219
00:15:00,880 --> 00:15:04,031
And I say, "Imagine
what that must have been like."

220
00:15:04,120 --> 00:15:06,998
And Brennan says, "I don't have to."

221
00:15:07,080 --> 00:15:08,832
I still don't get it.

222
00:15:08,920 --> 00:15:11,673
- Oh, my God.
- What?

223
00:15:11,760 --> 00:15:15,230
Brennars parents disappeared
just before Christmas. She was 15.

224
00:15:15,320 --> 00:15:19,393
- And she never knew what happened to them.
- Oh, God. That explains a lot.

225
00:15:19,480 --> 00:15:22,711
- <i>(all)</i> Yeah.
- We need a way to choose our secret Santas.

226
00:15:22,800 --> 00:15:26,713
- I could build a random generator.
- Wouldrt it be better to match people?

227
00:15:26,800 --> 00:15:30,918
I got five numbers and five letters.
Tell me the number, I tell you the letter.

228
00:15:31,000 --> 00:15:34,709
- Are letters sequential?
- Sequential. We'll go oldest to youngest.

229
00:15:34,800 --> 00:15:36,153
- Six.
- There's no six.

230
00:15:36,240 --> 00:15:39,277
- A through E and one through five.
- <i>(clears throat)</i>

231
00:15:39,360 --> 00:15:42,909
Just pick a name
and if you get your own put it back in.

232
00:15:43,560 --> 00:15:46,028
- That could work.
- Good idea.

233
00:15:46,120 --> 00:15:49,157
Feds seized the house
from a man named Gil Atkins.

234
00:15:49,240 --> 00:15:52,391
Proceeds of crime from fencing,
dealing in jewels, art.

235
00:15:52,480 --> 00:15:57,873
Atkins built the fallout shelter in '51, sealed it
in '58, died in '83. What have you got?

236
00:15:57,960 --> 00:16:01,839
Nothing much special about our victim.
You know about the toupee?

237
00:16:01,920 --> 00:16:05,833
Below average height, below average weight.
A little frail. Bad back.

238
00:16:05,920 --> 00:16:09,595
- He had a hunch, maybe from paperwork.
- So basically a wimp.

239
00:16:09,680 --> 00:16:13,434
- Contents of his pockets.
- Compass, penknife, some change.

240
00:16:13,520 --> 00:16:15,954
I got Goodman for this secret Santa and...

241
00:16:16,040 --> 00:16:19,510
Anthropologically,
gifts assert dominance in a group.

242
00:16:19,600 --> 00:16:24,594
Imagine a holiday devoted to self-promotion,
especially in this materialistic culture.

243
00:16:24,680 --> 00:16:27,638
How can you expect me to get behind that?
How can you?

244
00:16:27,720 --> 00:16:31,713
Wow. That's deep.
That's a very deep pile of crap.

245
00:16:32,160 --> 00:16:34,833
You came to me with information,
a peace offering,

246
00:16:34,920 --> 00:16:40,677
but it was to make you feel better, not me.
Proves my point. Any idea what this is?

247
00:16:40,760 --> 00:16:43,752
- No.
- Me neither. Try Dr Goodman.

248
00:16:43,840 --> 00:16:48,311
You know, Bones, you make it
very, very hard for me to be nice to you.

249
00:16:50,040 --> 00:16:51,917
We have to be extremely creative.

250
00:16:52,000 --> 00:16:55,117
A bunch of test tubes
filled with luminescent liquid.

251
00:16:55,200 --> 00:16:57,634
- Very festive.
- Probably give us cancer.

252
00:16:57,720 --> 00:17:02,032
- That would be fitting this Christmas.
- Tidings ofjoy, gentlemen. Joy.

253
00:17:02,120 --> 00:17:05,396
Decorations do not a Christmas make,
family and friends do.

254
00:17:05,480 --> 00:17:07,994
We're friends.

255
00:17:08,080 --> 00:17:12,232
- Or not friends.
- We are colleagues, friends, co-workers, yes,

256
00:17:12,320 --> 00:17:15,471
but for a father like myself, like Agent Booth,

257
00:17:15,560 --> 00:17:18,393
test tubes don't make up for
missing the children.

258
00:17:18,480 --> 00:17:20,391
- Excuse me?
- Be kind, rewind.

259
00:17:20,480 --> 00:17:22,675
- Booth has a kid?
- Ah...

260
00:17:22,760 --> 00:17:25,718
Well, not common knowledge, I gather.

261
00:17:28,520 --> 00:17:31,796
I see you've decided
to help Dr Brennan with the case.

262
00:17:31,880 --> 00:17:36,078
Oh, you know, if Angela's right, sure.
Why not? I mean...

263
00:17:37,080 --> 00:17:40,390
A little something for Bones.
Call it Christmas spirit.

264
00:17:40,480 --> 00:17:43,916
My thoughts exactly. Um...

265
00:17:44,000 --> 00:17:47,390
I thought I might look at
the contents of the suitcase with you.

266
00:17:47,480 --> 00:17:49,232
Why?

267
00:17:49,320 --> 00:17:52,949
It beats making decorations
out of pipettes and cylinders.

268
00:17:53,040 --> 00:17:55,713
I mean, what makes you qualified
to look at clues?

269
00:17:55,800 --> 00:18:00,271
I'm an archaeologist.
I'm good with artefacts. Do you mind?

270
00:18:00,360 --> 00:18:03,830
No. Archaeologist.
I thought you were an administrator.

271
00:18:03,920 --> 00:18:07,799
I didn't start out that way. He was fastidious.

272
00:18:07,880 --> 00:18:12,556
Everything neatly folded
as though by a trained valet.

273
00:18:12,640 --> 00:18:18,476
This man was by no means wealthy.
All the clothing is well-used and mended.

274
00:18:18,560 --> 00:18:21,597
Look, Blackman and Ball,
fine tailors, Washington, DC.

275
00:18:21,680 --> 00:18:25,309
The rest of his clothes
are all labelled from Tulsa, Oklahoma.

276
00:18:26,280 --> 00:18:28,669
- Female handwriting.
- How'd you get that?

277
00:18:28,760 --> 00:18:31,320
After cuneiform, handwriting is a snap.

278
00:18:31,400 --> 00:18:34,597
- "Dearest Lionel."
- No envelopes, no return address.

279
00:18:34,680 --> 00:18:37,399
No signature either,
just this drawing of a leaf.

280
00:18:37,480 --> 00:18:43,919
They seem to be dated from the summer
of 1957 through to early winter of 1958.

281
00:18:44,000 --> 00:18:46,150
- With permission, I'll read these.
- Yeah.

282
00:18:46,240 --> 00:18:49,277
Bones thought you might know
what this is here.

283
00:18:49,360 --> 00:18:51,794
<i>(phone rings)</i>

284
00:18:53,000 --> 00:18:54,149
Oh.

285
00:18:54,240 --> 00:18:56,356
Hey, Rebecca.

286
00:18:56,440 --> 00:18:59,079
Thanks for calling.
You heard what happened?

287
00:18:59,160 --> 00:19:02,948
- It seems to be some kind of a pouch.
- You don't have to see me.

288
00:19:03,040 --> 00:19:05,235
Sid agreed to bring him by.

289
00:19:07,320 --> 00:19:10,392
Don't make me beg.

290
00:19:13,760 --> 00:19:15,751
Thank you.

291
00:19:15,840 --> 00:19:18,115
- Everything all right?
- Yeah.

292
00:19:24,160 --> 00:19:27,232
- Puparia show Lionel had valley fever.
- We knew that.

293
00:19:27,320 --> 00:19:29,959
Wow. Was that a shot? Because I apologised.

294
00:19:30,040 --> 00:19:34,556
Goodman can't see his family. Zack can't see
his kids. Booth can't see his son.

295
00:19:34,640 --> 00:19:37,473
I'm an accidental grinch.
You're the Grinch on purpose.

296
00:19:37,560 --> 00:19:42,236
- I have no idea what you're saying to me.
- The Grinch is a creation of Dr Seuss.

297
00:19:42,320 --> 00:19:44,231
I got Angela for my secret Santa.

298
00:19:44,320 --> 00:19:48,029
What I want to do is blow up
a microscopic imagery of a toxic mould.

299
00:19:48,120 --> 00:19:51,908
She's interested in fractals.
That might appeal to her. Do you agree?

300
00:19:52,000 --> 00:19:55,709
I'm not really who you want to talk to
about gifts. Booth has a kid?

301
00:19:55,800 --> 00:19:57,836
- You didn't know?
- No.

302
00:19:57,920 --> 00:20:00,593
I wasrt the one who told you.

303
00:20:00,680 --> 00:20:04,434
Fall 1958, heavyweight suit.

304
00:20:04,520 --> 00:20:09,150
Kinda small, wool, black.
First name Lionel. That's all I got.

305
00:20:09,240 --> 00:20:13,028
Thanks. I appreciate it,
it being Christmas Eve and all. I'll hold.

306
00:20:13,120 --> 00:20:15,554
Lionel had a suit here made in town.

307
00:20:15,640 --> 00:20:18,757
The tailor's still exists.
His grandson owns it. Get this.

308
00:20:18,840 --> 00:20:21,798
They kept records.
We may find Careful Lionel's name.

309
00:20:21,880 --> 00:20:24,348
- Careful Lionel?
- Yeah. Little guy, toupee.

310
00:20:24,440 --> 00:20:28,991
Drank a vitamin tonic. Carried his own
compass. All his stuffjust so. Careful Lionel.

311
00:20:29,080 --> 00:20:32,311
- What was he worried about?
- Considering how he ended up...

312
00:20:32,400 --> 00:20:34,152
You have a son?

313
00:20:34,240 --> 00:20:36,276
- Yeah.
- You've never mentioned that.

314
00:20:36,360 --> 00:20:39,716
Nothing brings people together
like a Christmas lung fungus.

315
00:20:39,800 --> 00:20:42,360
Yes. That's great. When?

316
00:20:42,440 --> 00:20:44,590
Great. Thank you. Merry Christmas.

317
00:20:44,680 --> 00:20:49,151
Lionel Little. OK? He picked up
his new suit on November 7, 1958.

318
00:20:49,240 --> 00:20:52,789
He paid cash. He was supposed
to come back the next day for a shirt.

319
00:20:52,880 --> 00:20:57,556
But get this, he never showed up.
It was his wedding shirt.

320
00:20:57,640 --> 00:21:00,074
Whoa! Bless you.

321
00:21:00,880 --> 00:21:03,633
Uh-oh. Is that valley fever?

322
00:21:05,160 --> 00:21:07,720
Bones?

323
00:21:13,760 --> 00:21:14,909
<i>(laughter)</i>

324
00:21:15,000 --> 00:21:19,676
So if Lionel was a coin collector, that might
explain the levels of lead and nickel.

325
00:21:19,760 --> 00:21:22,593
When do they insert
the needle into your brain?

326
00:21:22,680 --> 00:21:26,514
I sneezed because the air is dry.
It's not valley fever.

327
00:21:26,600 --> 00:21:31,071
- Any other symptoms? Headache?
- Any foul-smelling pustules on your shins?

328
00:21:31,160 --> 00:21:33,799
She sneezed twice.
Anything about the letters?

329
00:21:33,880 --> 00:21:37,668
Quite a lot, yes.
They are very, very passionate love letters.

330
00:21:37,760 --> 00:21:40,479
- Careful Lionel had a girlfriend.
- In trouble.

331
00:21:40,560 --> 00:21:43,996
- Pregnant in trouble?
- Careful Lionel wasrt so careful.

332
00:21:44,080 --> 00:21:47,072
Unmarried pregnant girl
in Oklahoma in the late '50s.

333
00:21:47,160 --> 00:21:49,515
Lionel came up here to procure an abortion?

334
00:21:49,600 --> 00:21:52,034
This isn't a very Christmas Eve-type story.

335
00:21:52,120 --> 00:21:56,238
Of course it is. The Christ myth is built upon
the travails of an unwed mother.

336
00:21:56,320 --> 00:22:00,950
OK, stop bringing up the Christ myth thing.
Some people believe it's more than a myth.

337
00:22:01,040 --> 00:22:04,794
- Who besides you?
- That'd be me. I'm a deacon at my church.

338
00:22:04,880 --> 00:22:06,916
I do. Christmas and Easter, anyway.

339
00:22:07,000 --> 00:22:11,869
Although I believe organised religion is
just another movement to control the masses,

340
00:22:11,960 --> 00:22:14,872
it doesn't mean God doesn't love me.

341
00:22:14,960 --> 00:22:17,315
I'm a rational empiricist all the way.

342
00:22:17,400 --> 00:22:19,516
Unless you talk to my mother.

343
00:22:19,600 --> 00:22:21,875
Then I'm Lutheran.

344
00:22:21,960 --> 00:22:27,273
I can understand why you'd be sensitive,
Booth. You have a child out of wedlock.

345
00:22:27,360 --> 00:22:29,590
- Sweetie...
- What?

346
00:22:29,680 --> 00:22:30,999
<i>(Goodman)</i> Um...

347
00:22:31,080 --> 00:22:34,436
The letters display a combination
of both block and cursive.

348
00:22:34,520 --> 00:22:36,715
A combination of printing and writing?

349
00:22:36,800 --> 00:22:39,678
It would indicate she left school
in the second grade.

350
00:22:39,760 --> 00:22:43,639
Most white children then would attain
at least an eighth grade education.

351
00:22:43,720 --> 00:22:46,837
- She was African-American?
- I believe so, yes.

352
00:22:46,920 --> 00:22:50,833
- Was Lionel an African-American?
- No. He was definitely Caucasian.

353
00:22:50,920 --> 00:22:54,959
A white man and a pregnant black girl
in 1958 Oklahoma.

354
00:22:55,040 --> 00:22:57,110
- That was bad?
- It was illegal.

355
00:22:57,200 --> 00:22:59,873
- In Oklahoma?
- Notjust Oklahoma, here in DC.

356
00:22:59,960 --> 00:23:02,349
- Then why come here?
- They were running away.

357
00:23:02,440 --> 00:23:06,797
Lionel had tickets to Paris. Where else in 1958
could a white man and a black woman

358
00:23:06,880 --> 00:23:09,110
get married and live together?

359
00:23:09,200 --> 00:23:11,634
Visiting hours, folks. Who's first?

360
00:23:11,720 --> 00:23:14,598
As director of this institution,
I claim that right.

361
00:23:14,680 --> 00:23:16,238
OK, brief announcement.

362
00:23:16,320 --> 00:23:21,110
You guys might recognise my dad, but I don't
really wanna talk about it, so... thanks.

363
00:23:21,200 --> 00:23:23,760
OK? That's all.

364
00:23:28,320 --> 00:23:32,199
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Have Yourself A Merry Little Christmas"</i>
<i>by Tori Amos)</i>

365
00:23:39,120 --> 00:23:46,834
♪ <i>Have yourself a merry little Christmas</i>

366
00:23:48,160 --> 00:23:53,712
♪ <i>Let your heart be light</i>

367
00:23:55,400 --> 00:24:05,036
♪ <i>From now on our troubles</i>
<i>will be out of sight</i>

368
00:24:10,640 --> 00:24:17,716
♪ <i>Have yourself a merry little Christmas</i>

369
00:24:18,760 --> 00:24:25,836
♪ <i>Make the Yuletide gay</i>

370
00:24:26,840 --> 00:24:35,396
♪ <i>From now on our troubles will be miles away</i>

371
00:24:39,920 --> 00:24:45,916
♪ <i>Here we are as in olden days</i>

372
00:24:46,000 --> 00:24:52,473
♪ <i>Happy golden days of yore</i>

373
00:24:53,720 --> 00:24:59,317
♪ <i>Faithful friends who are dear to us</i>

374
00:24:59,400 --> 00:25:07,671
♪ <i>Gather near to us once more</i>

375
00:25:09,520 --> 00:25:19,316
♪ <i>Have yourself a merry little Christmas</i>

376
00:25:21,520 --> 00:25:25,718
♪ <i>Now</i>

377
00:25:41,920 --> 00:25:44,912
- You like it?
- It's very beautiful.

378
00:25:45,000 --> 00:25:50,597
It's not done yet. We can put our presents
under there and we can...

379
00:25:50,680 --> 00:25:53,672
- You think it's stupid.
- No, Ange.

380
00:25:56,920 --> 00:25:59,275
What were your Christmas plans?

381
00:26:00,280 --> 00:26:06,594
My dad and I get together somewhere quiet,
exchange gifts, just the two of us.

382
00:26:06,680 --> 00:26:12,038
Since I was a kid, getting some time alone
with my dad was always difficult.

383
00:26:12,120 --> 00:26:15,317
So what is it with you and gifts, anyway?

384
00:26:17,640 --> 00:26:22,031
I know your parents disappeared
just before Christmas.

385
00:26:25,720 --> 00:26:30,510
My brother Russ was... 19,
and we were still in the house.

386
00:26:31,360 --> 00:26:34,636
That must have been strange.

387
00:26:34,720 --> 00:26:40,431
Russ found our presents in my parents' room,
and Christmas Eve, when I was asleep,

388
00:26:40,520 --> 00:26:44,877
he snuck down and made Christmas,
trying to do the right thing for me.

389
00:26:44,960 --> 00:26:48,032
Christmas for his little sister.

390
00:26:50,240 --> 00:26:54,028
But when I came down
and saw the lights and the presents...

391
00:26:54,120 --> 00:26:59,672
- You thought your parents were back.
- I just expected to see them sitting there.

392
00:26:59,760 --> 00:27:03,036
Drinking their coffee,
watching Russ and me open presents.

393
00:27:03,120 --> 00:27:07,113
- Oh, my God.
- I kind of lost it.

394
00:27:07,640 --> 00:27:11,918
I refused to open the presents
until they came back.

395
00:27:13,680 --> 00:27:17,309
It was like I told Russ
he wasrt enough family for me.

396
00:27:17,400 --> 00:27:22,633
Before New Year's
he went out West to work and...

397
00:27:24,280 --> 00:27:26,748
I was in the foster system.

398
00:27:27,960 --> 00:27:31,555
Excuse me.
We have Lionel's missing persons file.

399
00:27:36,040 --> 00:27:41,068
The tree is really, really beautiful, Ange.

400
00:27:41,160 --> 00:27:42,593
Really.

401
00:27:47,200 --> 00:27:50,749
<i>(Booth)</i> Lionel Little was born May 19, 1934,
Tulsa, Oklahoma.

402
00:27:50,840 --> 00:27:53,274
- <i>(Goodman)</i> Aged 24.
- <i>(Bones)</i> Fits the remains.

403
00:27:53,360 --> 00:27:56,830
<i>(Booth)</i> According to the report
lodged by his boss in January 1960,

404
00:27:56,920 --> 00:28:01,755
Lionel Little worked as a lease inspector
for Silver Cloud Petroleum out of Tulsa.

405
00:28:01,840 --> 00:28:05,310
- An accountant.
- You were right about his coin collection.

406
00:28:05,400 --> 00:28:10,030
When Lionel vanished, so did most of his
coin collection. That was attached to the file.

407
00:28:10,120 --> 00:28:13,795
- Did the coins show up?
- Yeah. Maryland, Virginia, Pennsylvania.

408
00:28:13,880 --> 00:28:19,273
The sales were traced to Gil Atkins.
He made out about $8,000 selling those coins.

409
00:28:19,360 --> 00:28:21,920
Atkins killed Lionel for a coin collection?

410
00:28:22,000 --> 00:28:26,312
$8,000 in 1958 translates to roughly $64,000.

411
00:28:26,400 --> 00:28:29,119
Careful Lionel gets
a young black girl pregnant,

412
00:28:29,200 --> 00:28:33,955
he sells his coin collection so he can move
them to Paris and they can live together.

413
00:28:34,040 --> 00:28:39,512
He offers the coins to Atkins, who figures
it'd be easier to kill him and steal the coins.

414
00:28:39,600 --> 00:28:45,835
Also, the last person to see Lionel was a
woman who cleaned his office. Ivy Gillespie.

415
00:28:45,920 --> 00:28:51,472
- <i>(Goodman)</i> What's the significance of that?
- Does this look like an ivy leaf to you?

416
00:28:51,560 --> 00:28:54,757
Ivy Gillespie. Race: Negro.

417
00:28:54,840 --> 00:28:57,513
- Oh, my God.
- <i>(Angela)</i> You have to find her.

418
00:28:58,880 --> 00:29:01,394
- Ivy.
- <i>(Goodman)</i> She may not even be alive.

419
00:29:01,480 --> 00:29:06,349
And if she is, this could be a reminder of
a painful time. What would we accomplish?

420
00:29:06,440 --> 00:29:11,036
You have to find the girl
and tell her what you know. Don't you see?

421
00:29:11,120 --> 00:29:14,510
- You can give her the answer you never got.
- Angela...

422
00:29:14,600 --> 00:29:18,718
I'm sorry, sweetie, but it's true.
You have a chance here.

423
00:29:18,800 --> 00:29:24,079
To say what? "Merry Christmas, Ivy. Your
fiancé was murdered and your life was ruined,

424
00:29:24,160 --> 00:29:26,833
but at least you get to know
what happened to him"?

425
00:29:26,920 --> 00:29:30,196
Don't you wish somebody
had said that to you?

426
00:29:33,800 --> 00:29:34,949
Yes.

427
00:29:46,880 --> 00:29:51,590
I realise it's Christmas Eve, but it's extremely
important that I find Ms Ivy Gillespie.

428
00:29:51,680 --> 00:29:55,878
We know that she was a cleaning lady
at Silver Cloud Petroleum

429
00:29:55,960 --> 00:29:59,350
in 1958 and 1959. After that, we don't know.

430
00:29:59,440 --> 00:30:04,514
I wouldn't interrupt your Christmas except
this is very very important to a friend of mine.

431
00:30:04,600 --> 00:30:10,914
I don't wanna take time from your family, but
I have important news regarding a loved one.

432
00:30:11,000 --> 00:30:16,950
Do you have an address,
or place of work, or... anything?

433
00:30:17,040 --> 00:30:23,309
I've made dozens of calls in an effort
to track this woman down. It's that important.

434
00:30:25,200 --> 00:30:28,795
Assisted living?
Is her last name still Gillespie?

435
00:30:28,880 --> 00:30:32,873
Yes. Yes. Merry Christmas to you too.

436
00:30:32,960 --> 00:30:34,757
Hello?

437
00:30:34,840 --> 00:30:41,109
Yes. I was wondering if you could tell me
if you have any guests there, first name Ivy,

438
00:30:41,200 --> 00:30:45,478
born January 21, 1934.
She'd be African-American.

439
00:30:46,240 --> 00:30:51,030
Yes, I apologise. I should have started
with "Merry Christmas".

440
00:30:52,000 --> 00:30:56,755
Date of birth is January 21, 1934.

441
00:30:56,840 --> 00:31:02,073
She's African-American.
Yes, Ivy. Her name is still Gillespie.

442
00:31:02,160 --> 00:31:04,230
Yes, if her granddaughter's there.

443
00:31:04,680 --> 00:31:10,232
Yes, hello. I'm Dr Temperance Brennan
from the Jeffersonian Institution in DC.

444
00:31:10,320 --> 00:31:14,313
I have information that might
be very interesting to your grandmother.

445
00:31:14,400 --> 00:31:18,757
I can be reached through
the medico-legal lab here at the Jeffersonian.

446
00:31:18,840 --> 00:31:21,718
And tell her "Merry Christmas".

447
00:31:24,520 --> 00:31:26,988
You found Ivy Gillespie.

448
00:31:28,040 --> 00:31:31,316
In an assisted living facility near Bethesda.

449
00:31:31,400 --> 00:31:33,391
I spoke to her granddaughter.

450
00:31:33,480 --> 00:31:36,358
Thank you.

451
00:31:36,440 --> 00:31:38,795
She might not get in touch with us.

452
00:31:38,880 --> 00:31:41,838
She will.

453
00:31:41,920 --> 00:31:44,115
Because it's Christmas?

454
00:31:44,200 --> 00:31:45,553
Yes.

455
00:32:04,160 --> 00:32:07,994
- Did you find something?
- Two things that fit together.

456
00:32:08,080 --> 00:32:10,878
- Angela sent me. She says it's Christmas.
- OK.

457
00:32:10,960 --> 00:32:15,078
You still think there's more to learn
about Lionel Little and Ivy Gillespie?

458
00:32:15,160 --> 00:32:18,357
There's always more to learn. Hey.

459
00:32:19,320 --> 00:32:24,553
I'm sorry you didn't get Christmas morning
with your little boy.

460
00:32:24,640 --> 00:32:26,790
Thanks.

461
00:32:36,200 --> 00:32:38,873
Good. OK, everybody.

462
00:32:38,960 --> 00:32:41,428
Stand over here.

463
00:32:41,520 --> 00:32:43,511
Close your eyes.

464
00:32:45,240 --> 00:32:47,913
Open your eyes.

465
00:32:50,400 --> 00:32:55,394
- <i>(Angela)</i> Merry Christmas.
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> Angela! Merry Christmas!

466
00:32:55,480 --> 00:32:59,189
♪ <i>Sleigh bells ring, are you listening?</i>

467
00:32:59,280 --> 00:33:03,671
♪ <i>In the lane snow is glistening</i>

468
00:33:03,760 --> 00:33:08,117
♪ <i>A beautiful sight, we're happy tonight</i>

469
00:33:08,200 --> 00:33:11,237
♪ <i>Walking in a winter wonderland</i>

470
00:33:13,560 --> 00:33:17,553
♪ <i>Gone away is the bluebird</i>

471
00:33:17,640 --> 00:33:20,837
♪ <i>Here to stay is a new bird</i>

472
00:33:20,920 --> 00:33:25,914
- <i>(Angela)</i> Look at all these gifts.
- <i>(Hodgins)</i> We should be drinking eggnog.

473
00:33:27,840 --> 00:33:31,992
Oh, my God! It's beautiful. What is it?

474
00:33:32,080 --> 00:33:36,198
- It's prettier if you don't know the details.
- <i>(Goodman)</i> That is beautiful.

475
00:33:36,280 --> 00:33:39,477
- Thank you.
- I wonder what it is.

476
00:33:41,200 --> 00:33:44,351
- <i>(Angela)</i> What did you get?
- Very impressive.

477
00:33:44,920 --> 00:33:46,956
- You made this?
- Yeah.

478
00:33:47,040 --> 00:33:48,996
- Thank you.
- I'm next.

479
00:33:50,360 --> 00:33:52,555
It's from me.

480
00:33:52,640 --> 00:33:56,315
It's my family. And me.

481
00:33:56,400 --> 00:33:58,277
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.

482
00:34:01,400 --> 00:34:03,994
- <i>Scarabaeus sacer</i>.
- A sacred scarab.

483
00:34:04,080 --> 00:34:09,552
- That is excellently rendered, sir. Thank you.
- You're very welcome.

484
00:34:09,640 --> 00:34:10,914
Wow!

485
00:34:11,400 --> 00:34:12,992
Zack, that's, uh...

486
00:34:13,080 --> 00:34:16,356
- <i>(Zack)</i> Self-propelled nonautonomic unit.
- <i>(Goodman)</i> Well!

487
00:34:16,440 --> 00:34:18,237
- It's a robot.
- <i>(Goodman laughs)</i>

488
00:34:18,320 --> 00:34:22,438
I thought if we get out of here in time today,
you could give it to your son.

489
00:34:22,520 --> 00:34:25,637
- Merry Christmas.
- <i>(Angela)</i> Ah, Zack.

490
00:34:25,720 --> 00:34:28,632
- Thanks a lot.
- You're welcome.

491
00:34:28,720 --> 00:34:32,838
♪ <i>We'll frolic and play the Eskimo way</i>

492
00:34:32,920 --> 00:34:36,196
♪ <i>Walking in a winter wonderland</i>

493
00:34:37,920 --> 00:34:42,277
Bones, here's the thing. What if a gift
goes both ways? What's wrong with that?

494
00:34:42,360 --> 00:34:44,191
- Look at this.
- It's a penny.

495
00:34:44,280 --> 00:34:48,034
It's notjust a penny.
It's a 1943 bronze one cent piece.

496
00:34:48,120 --> 00:34:52,830
All I'm saying is maybe the real gift is when
you accept something with a little grace.

497
00:34:52,920 --> 00:34:55,388
Over a billion pennies were minted in 1943,

498
00:34:55,480 --> 00:34:58,631
most of them in steel
to conserve copper for World War II.

499
00:34:58,720 --> 00:35:03,350
But a handful were struck
in an old-style bronze planchet.

500
00:35:03,440 --> 00:35:05,749
Only about 12 of them exist today.

501
00:35:05,840 --> 00:35:07,717
Whoa. Huh.

502
00:35:07,800 --> 00:35:10,473
- And this is one of 'em?
- Yes.

503
00:35:10,560 --> 00:35:11,993
Huh.

504
00:35:12,080 --> 00:35:15,834
- How much is it won'th?
- Over $100,000.

505
00:35:16,840 --> 00:35:20,310
Lionel never showed Gil Atkins
the best part of his collection.

506
00:35:20,400 --> 00:35:24,996
Atkins murdered him,
never knew there was a fortune in his pocket.

507
00:35:25,080 --> 00:35:27,514
Looks like Careful Lionel got the last laugh.

508
00:35:27,600 --> 00:35:29,636
Ready?

509
00:35:29,720 --> 00:35:31,597
It's time for our test results.

510
00:35:42,400 --> 00:35:48,077
Oh, green, green. Is that green as in "Go",
or green as "Stick a needle in your brain"?

511
00:35:52,400 --> 00:35:54,960
- Merry Christmas.
- Oh.

512
00:35:55,040 --> 00:35:57,395
<i>(Hodgins)</i> Yes!

513
00:35:58,160 --> 00:36:02,153
We are outta here.
Merry Christmas, everyone.

514
00:36:04,200 --> 00:36:06,714
Go. Go have Christmas.

515
00:36:07,440 --> 00:36:10,398
Wish your boy a merry Christmas from me.

516
00:36:10,480 --> 00:36:13,711
I'm at Wong Foo's
if you decide you want company.

517
00:36:18,080 --> 00:36:20,674
Merry Christmas, Bones.

518
00:36:34,240 --> 00:36:36,879
<i>(woman)</i> Excuse me.

519
00:36:43,280 --> 00:36:44,713
Hi.

520
00:36:44,800 --> 00:36:49,157
My name is Lisa Pearce,
and this is my grandmother, Ivy Gillespie.

521
00:36:49,240 --> 00:36:52,471
- Are you Dr Brennan?
- Yes.

522
00:36:52,560 --> 00:36:58,874
I gave birth to a half-white child
in Oklahoma, 1960. Lionel's daughter.

523
00:36:58,960 --> 00:37:02,270
Raised her myself. No education.

524
00:37:02,720 --> 00:37:04,870
I got her to college.

525
00:37:05,880 --> 00:37:10,271
- She died eight years ago.
- And Grandma raised me after that.

526
00:37:10,360 --> 00:37:13,989
Her mother was a nurse
and Lisa's gonna be a doctor.

527
00:37:14,080 --> 00:37:17,516
Grandma, I can't afford college.

528
00:37:19,120 --> 00:37:21,918
So Lionel was murdered?

529
00:37:22,000 --> 00:37:25,356
In 1959, yes, by a man named Gil Atkins.

530
00:37:25,440 --> 00:37:30,355
And you can figure that out all this time later?

531
00:37:30,440 --> 00:37:32,431
He had these.

532
00:37:41,080 --> 00:37:43,230
Huh?

533
00:37:46,960 --> 00:37:49,952
Tickets to... Paris!

534
00:37:50,480 --> 00:37:54,268
Grandma, isn't that what he promised you?
A life in France?

535
00:37:54,360 --> 00:37:58,638
I thought the worst of him.

536
00:38:05,400 --> 00:38:07,118
Thank you, Dr Brennan.

537
00:38:07,200 --> 00:38:10,158
I have something even better.

538
00:38:14,560 --> 00:38:17,472
What could be better?

539
00:38:17,560 --> 00:38:20,677
You've given me back my life.

540
00:38:24,240 --> 00:38:26,276
It's a penny.

541
00:38:26,360 --> 00:38:30,638
There's something
you ought to know about that penny.

542
00:38:34,960 --> 00:38:37,952
<i>(</i>♪ <i>"Jingle Bells" by Brian Setzer)</i>

543
00:38:45,960 --> 00:38:48,315
- Drinks?
- Ah, yes.

544
00:38:48,400 --> 00:38:50,755
Christmas spirits come in many a guise.

545
00:38:50,840 --> 00:38:52,831
Cheers.

546
00:38:55,640 --> 00:39:01,112
Ivy Gillespie came to the lab after you left,
with her granddaughter.

547
00:39:01,200 --> 00:39:02,235
Mm-hm.

548
00:39:02,320 --> 00:39:04,390
Don't you wanna know what happened?

549
00:39:04,480 --> 00:39:06,471
I know what happened.

550
00:39:06,560 --> 00:39:09,472
You told her about Careful Lionel.

551
00:39:09,560 --> 00:39:13,109
You showed her the letters,

552
00:39:13,200 --> 00:39:16,829
the tickets, and she cried.
But you made her happy.

553
00:39:16,920 --> 00:39:21,630
Not to mention I gave her a penny
won'th over $100,000.

554
00:39:21,720 --> 00:39:24,188
She won't care about that today.

555
00:39:24,280 --> 00:39:29,195
You just gave somebody
the best Christmas gift they could ever get.

556
00:39:30,360 --> 00:39:33,909
- Who's the secret Santa now?
- Stop.

557
00:39:34,000 --> 00:39:35,797
Whoa.

558
00:39:39,600 --> 00:39:45,755
And that weirdo assistant of yours
just made me the coolest dad in the world.

559
00:39:45,840 --> 00:39:48,718
Daddy! Daddy!

560
00:39:51,000 --> 00:39:53,389
- Hey, look. Look at this thing.
- Can it flip?

561
00:39:53,480 --> 00:39:57,712
How cool. It can flip, trip, swim,
whatever you want.

562
00:39:57,800 --> 00:40:00,234
- Say "Merry Christmas".
- Merry Christmas.

563
00:40:06,120 --> 00:40:08,156
OK, big guy.

564
00:40:19,760 --> 00:40:27,474
♪ <i>Have yourself a merry little Christmas</i>

565
00:40:28,800 --> 00:40:34,352
♪ <i>Let your heart be light</i>

566
00:40:36,040 --> 00:40:45,676
♪ <i>From now on our troubles</i>
<i>will be out of sight</i>

567
00:40:51,120 --> 00:40:58,674
♪ <i>Through the years we all will be together</i>

568
00:41:00,200 --> 00:41:05,672
♪ <i>If the fates allow</i>

569
00:41:07,560 --> 00:41:17,549
♪ <i>Hang a shining star upon the highest bough</i>

570
00:41:19,600 --> 00:41:26,153
♪ <i>And have yourself</i>

571
00:41:26,240 --> 00:41:31,553
♪ <i>A merry little Christmas</i>

572
00:41:33,840 --> 00:41:35,831
♪ <i>Now</i>

573
00:42:04,200 --> 00:42:08,955
Visiontext Subtitles: Adrian Isaac

574
00:42:17,200 --> 00:42:18,553
What's that mean?

575
00:42:19,280 --> 00:42:21,271
ENGLISH SDH

