1
00:00:03,560 --> 00:00:06,791
Come on, honey. If we don't leave,
we won't get into the club.

2
00:00:06,880 --> 00:00:09,519
- I'm just finishing up a few emails.
- Oh, what?

3
00:00:09,600 --> 00:00:14,310
- My publisher wants to schedule a book tour.
- That can wait, sweetie.

4
00:00:14,400 --> 00:00:18,632
A student needs help with the cause
of a fracture on a lateral epicondyle.

5
00:00:18,720 --> 00:00:22,156
- TGIF. You heard of that?
- Yeah. It's some kind of acronym.

6
00:00:22,240 --> 00:00:24,470
- But my inbox is full.
- That's not true.

7
00:00:24,560 --> 00:00:27,870
There's a TV show that needs research.
Not that they listen.

8
00:00:27,960 --> 00:00:30,520
- We're going.
- I should catalogue that skull.

9
00:00:30,600 --> 00:00:33,273
It's in the exhibit on the French Revolution.

10
00:00:33,360 --> 00:00:37,592
Yeah. Pepé Le Pew is more important
than booze... and boys.

11
00:00:37,680 --> 00:00:39,591
I don't think that's his name.

12
00:00:43,520 --> 00:00:46,876
<i>(announcer) All right, everybody.</i>
<i>Keep it crunking here.</i>

13
00:00:46,960 --> 00:00:51,795
<i>Tonight the Basement Club brings to you</i>
<i>the number one DJ around town: DJ Rulz!</i>

14
00:00:51,880 --> 00:00:54,440
<i>Give it up!</i>

15
00:00:54,520 --> 00:00:57,592
Feels good, doesn't it?
Being with people who are alive?

16
00:00:57,680 --> 00:01:01,468
- It's stimulating, I have to admit.
- We are so gonna tear it up tonight.

17
00:01:01,560 --> 00:01:03,357
- That's slang, right?
- Right.

18
00:01:03,440 --> 00:01:08,309
- Is my costume all right?
- It's not a costume, it's an outfit. Yes, perfect.

19
00:01:08,400 --> 00:01:10,595
I know, it's very warm in here.

20
00:01:10,680 --> 00:01:12,875
No, because it looks great.

21
00:01:13,520 --> 00:01:16,830
- We are so getting checked out.
- I love this music.

22
00:01:16,920 --> 00:01:19,832
<i>(Angela)</i> DJ Rulz - he is so hot.

23
00:01:19,920 --> 00:01:21,638
<i>(</i>♪ <i>raps)</i>

24
00:01:24,120 --> 00:01:26,554
- It's so tribal.
- Don't say tribal, sweetie.

25
00:01:26,640 --> 00:01:29,473
Why? Oh, because of all the black people?

26
00:01:29,560 --> 00:01:32,154
Sweetie, have fun. Stop dissecting, take part.

27
00:01:32,240 --> 00:01:35,710
African-Americans
aren't the only ones with tribal heritage.

28
00:01:35,800 --> 00:01:39,998
- You saying we're natives of some tribe?
- Anthropologically speaking, we all are.

29
00:01:40,080 --> 00:01:41,672
You better shut your mouth.

30
00:01:41,760 --> 00:01:46,709
I just meant hip-hop mirrors the visceral
connection you see in tribal communication.

31
00:01:46,800 --> 00:01:48,028
- Oh, man!
- What?!

32
00:01:48,120 --> 00:01:52,477
After the Can'tesian split,
we separated our minds from our bodies.

33
00:01:52,560 --> 00:01:57,156
- The numinous from the animalistic.
- Are you calling me an animal, fool?

34
00:01:57,240 --> 00:02:00,994
No, fool. She's using Descan'tes' philosophy
to say she's down with the music.

35
00:02:01,080 --> 00:02:03,230
Who you calling a fool, fool?

36
00:02:03,320 --> 00:02:04,992
Get out my way.

37
00:02:07,000 --> 00:02:10,629
- We're going. We're going.
- You shouldn't have done that, bitch!

38
00:02:12,520 --> 00:02:14,317
<i>(music stops)</i>

39
00:02:19,720 --> 00:02:23,395
- <i>(man)</i> That's what I'm talking about.
- Uh-oh.

40
00:02:24,000 --> 00:02:27,549
- <i>(man)</i> Yo, check this out.
- <i>(woman)</i> Look in the wall. What is that?

41
00:02:27,640 --> 00:02:30,154
<i>(man)</i> Look at that fool, man.

42
00:02:30,240 --> 00:02:32,993
<i>(man #2)</i> What the hell is it?

43
00:02:33,080 --> 00:02:36,755
- Can she handle this?
- No one in our lab can deal with a mummy.

44
00:02:36,840 --> 00:02:40,628
- I'd have to call her in anyway.
- She assaulted two agents.

45
00:02:40,720 --> 00:02:42,676
They were compromising the remains.

46
00:02:42,760 --> 00:02:46,753
A cloud of meth covered the dance floor.
I think they've inaled quite a lot.

47
00:02:46,840 --> 00:02:49,354
- You two high?
- By accident. It doesn't count.

48
00:02:49,440 --> 00:02:51,829
Why bring Tessa? This isn't a great date.

49
00:02:51,920 --> 00:02:56,277
We were out to dinner when he got your call.
Your pupils are the size of saucers.

50
00:02:56,360 --> 00:02:59,238
- Get away from the remains!
- Bones, simmer down.

51
00:02:59,320 --> 00:03:01,880
- How long is this gonna take?
- Who wants to know?

52
00:03:01,960 --> 00:03:04,713
He works for me.
I'm Randall Hall. I run this place.

53
00:03:04,800 --> 00:03:08,395
You run this place? Interesting,
cos we found some drugs on this...

54
00:03:08,480 --> 00:03:11,677
- Found them. We found them.
- We found drugs on the dead guy.

55
00:03:11,760 --> 00:03:14,194
- We wanna know where they're from...
- Why...

56
00:03:14,280 --> 00:03:18,273
...why he had them. Any idea who he is?
- Why he had them.

57
00:03:18,360 --> 00:03:20,920
- Any idea?
- Guy barely looks human.

58
00:03:21,000 --> 00:03:23,389
What makes you think I'd recognise him?

59
00:03:23,480 --> 00:03:26,153
Bones? Bones, how does
something like this happen?

60
00:03:26,240 --> 00:03:30,438
The Egyptians would give the body
a cedar-oil enema and cover it with salt.

61
00:03:30,520 --> 00:03:32,988
- That didn't happen here.
- You are wasted.

62
00:03:33,080 --> 00:03:35,469
Zack! Zack! Zack!

63
00:03:35,560 --> 00:03:40,315
Come here! Come here! Isn't this
a beautiful specimen of mummification?

64
00:03:40,400 --> 00:03:42,709
- What's going on?
- Your boss inaled.

65
00:03:42,800 --> 00:03:46,793
See how preserved the skin is?
You don't find something like this every day.

66
00:03:46,880 --> 00:03:49,075
Hey, Tessa, have you seen it?

67
00:03:49,160 --> 00:03:52,835
It's hard to believe you two'd be a couple -
cop and lawyer. Touching.

68
00:03:52,920 --> 00:03:56,117
- I'm gonna grab a cab.
- Oh, no. OK, hold up.

69
00:03:56,200 --> 00:03:58,953
Sorry. Sorry. I apologise.

70
00:03:59,040 --> 00:04:03,113
Here. I'm gonna make it up to you.
I promise. OK? Ice cream later?

71
00:04:03,200 --> 00:04:06,192
- Take care.
- I'll talk to you later.

72
00:04:07,360 --> 00:04:08,839
(both) Awwww...

73
00:04:08,920 --> 00:04:10,911
Can we just stick to business?

74
00:04:11,000 --> 00:04:16,358
I'm gonna need a list of your employees. We'll
run it and see if any have a drug conviction.

75
00:04:16,440 --> 00:04:21,639
- How long before you can ID him?
- I'm not tired. I'll stay up all night and work.

76
00:04:21,720 --> 00:04:25,076
We have to be careful removing him.
He's very dry and brittle.

77
00:04:27,480 --> 00:04:30,153
My first modern mummy.

78
00:05:06,040 --> 00:05:10,033
Crystal meth is made from cold medicine,
lye and strike pads from matchbooks.

79
00:05:10,120 --> 00:05:13,430
- The body was not designed to deal with it.
- So I'm finding out.

80
00:05:13,520 --> 00:05:16,398
- Camomile tea?
- No. I just need your results.

81
00:05:16,480 --> 00:05:20,712
- A stick to pry the monkey off your back?
- Are you sure you need me here?

82
00:05:20,800 --> 00:05:22,836
Payback for showing me the good life.

83
00:05:22,920 --> 00:05:26,799
- OK. So how is my man, the Tut?
- In better shape than I am.

84
00:05:26,880 --> 00:05:31,795
The meth in his lungs and nose matches the
meth thatjuiced Angela and the good doctor.

85
00:05:31,880 --> 00:05:33,871
Can you please keep it clinical?

86
00:05:33,960 --> 00:05:36,679
So, uh, he died of an overdose.

87
00:05:38,280 --> 00:05:43,593
Asphyxiation. Meth coated the alveoli
in his lungs, making breathing impossible.

88
00:05:43,680 --> 00:05:46,877
So he overdosed with his meth
behind the wall.

89
00:05:46,960 --> 00:05:50,635
The space was too narrow
to squeeze through. He got stuck, bag broke.

90
00:05:50,720 --> 00:05:53,314
When he gasped for air
he died instantaneously.

91
00:05:53,400 --> 00:05:57,791
The dry-air convection behind the wall
removed most of the moisture from his body.

92
00:05:57,880 --> 00:05:59,472
How long was he in there?

93
00:05:59,560 --> 00:06:02,791
Judging from the acrid mites in his ears,
I'd say six weeks.

94
00:06:02,880 --> 00:06:05,235
Hey, didn't he have hands?

95
00:06:06,480 --> 00:06:12,669
They're easier to work with dismembered. I've
rehydrated them so we can get fingerprints.

96
00:06:13,520 --> 00:06:15,795
- Off that?
- Sure.

97
00:06:19,040 --> 00:06:22,828
- You ever been to Costa Rica?
- I was flown down once.

98
00:06:22,920 --> 00:06:26,913
They found a human skull, 12,000 years old.

99
00:06:28,640 --> 00:06:31,234
- Why?
- I get some vacation time.

100
00:06:31,320 --> 00:06:34,596
I was gonna head off on Thursday.

101
00:06:35,560 --> 00:06:38,791
- I heard Costa Rica was beautiful.
- Mm.

102
00:06:38,880 --> 00:06:41,997
Fascinating wildlife. Lots of parrots.

103
00:06:42,080 --> 00:06:47,598
Oh, I don't like parrots. No.
People should really... really do all talking.

104
00:06:47,680 --> 00:06:49,272
You know, maybe I should...

105
00:06:49,360 --> 00:06:51,191
Oh, God! What are you doing?

106
00:06:51,280 --> 00:06:56,798
The Aztecs would flay people and then...
wear their skin as a bodysuit.

107
00:06:57,800 --> 00:07:02,874
I guess you won't be needing mittens
for Christmas, huh?

108
00:07:06,640 --> 00:07:09,916
- Did the FBI find a match?
- Yep. His name was Roy Taylor.

109
00:07:10,000 --> 00:07:14,232
Roy Taylor? You're kidding?
That's DJ Mount.

110
00:07:14,320 --> 00:07:18,074
- I don't know who that is.
- Mount is one of the best DJs in DC.

111
00:07:18,160 --> 00:07:22,915
He used to play at the club. Everyone
was wondering what happened to him.

112
00:07:23,000 --> 00:07:24,991
His album'll take off after this.

113
00:07:25,080 --> 00:07:27,071
<i>(</i>♪ <i>rap song plays)</i>

114
00:07:30,600 --> 00:07:33,717
- I never knew this side of you, Bones.
- It's DJ Mount.

115
00:07:33,800 --> 00:07:35,791
Doesrt this make your head explode?

116
00:07:35,880 --> 00:07:41,238
I got a couple hours of sleep on my couch
and showered in the decontamination room.

117
00:07:41,320 --> 00:07:42,719
Really know how to live.

118
00:07:42,800 --> 00:07:46,475
Angela said rap artists
sometimes kill each other over the music.

119
00:07:46,560 --> 00:07:49,870
Jam Master J, Tupac, Biggie.

120
00:07:49,960 --> 00:07:54,750
- D'you even know who you're talking about?
- Yeah. I've done my Googling.

121
00:07:54,840 --> 00:07:57,115
Listen.

122
00:07:57,200 --> 00:08:00,112
You can hear the alpha male
asserting himself.

123
00:08:00,200 --> 00:08:01,474
<i>(beatbox noises)</i>

124
00:08:01,560 --> 00:08:05,792
"Fill your ass up... <i>(beatbox noises)</i>
...with lead." Always a nice lyric.

125
00:08:05,880 --> 00:08:11,034
I'm heading back to the club
to meet the FBI forensics team.

126
00:08:11,120 --> 00:08:14,032
<i>(sighs)</i> I'm getting facts.

127
00:08:14,120 --> 00:08:17,396
<i>(Hall)</i> DJ Mount. He was starting to break,

128
00:08:18,120 --> 00:08:20,554
finally making some money.

129
00:08:20,640 --> 00:08:24,155
Someone who's never had anything,
it can go to your head.

130
00:08:24,240 --> 00:08:26,435
So he gets involved with drugs.

131
00:08:26,520 --> 00:08:31,150
You didn't know who he was hanging with
or who might've been chasing him?

132
00:08:31,680 --> 00:08:36,629
Dude like Mount, he had a lot of enemies -
other artists, rivalries.

133
00:08:36,720 --> 00:08:38,711
Everyone wants to be number one.

134
00:08:38,800 --> 00:08:43,078
I mean, you have to know
who the rivals are, Mr Hall.

135
00:08:43,160 --> 00:08:45,196
Affects your bottom line.

136
00:08:45,280 --> 00:08:47,874
Wait for me by the elevator.

137
00:08:56,720 --> 00:08:58,790
- Rulz.
- What rules?

138
00:08:58,880 --> 00:09:02,759
That's his name. He performs at the club.

139
00:09:04,840 --> 00:09:11,439
I try to keep my crew together, but I always
had to run interference between those two.

140
00:09:11,520 --> 00:09:14,830
- Why?
- Ask Rulz.

141
00:09:21,240 --> 00:09:25,711
- <i>(Zack)</i> Was it fun coming to the club?
- Yeah. Before the drugs and the dead body.

142
00:09:25,800 --> 00:09:27,597
Tilt... tilt down.

143
00:09:28,560 --> 00:09:33,315
Seems so primitive - being in
a crowd of strangers, gyrating to music.

144
00:09:33,400 --> 00:09:37,154
- You've never danced?
- I'm told I look like a marionette in a storm.

145
00:09:37,240 --> 00:09:40,277
- You would've fit right in last night.
- Really?

146
00:09:41,240 --> 00:09:44,755
<i>(Bones)</i> Footprints...
in the dirt and the termite shavings.

147
00:09:44,840 --> 00:09:49,675
- Someone was on the other side of him.
- Light. This leads to the outside.

148
00:09:49,760 --> 00:09:53,594
- We need to get inside that wall.
- Or take it down.

149
00:09:53,680 --> 00:09:55,671
One last look?

150
00:09:57,800 --> 00:09:59,791
Take 'em in, show 'em around.

151
00:10:04,680 --> 00:10:06,955
- Agent Booth?
- Yeah?

152
00:10:07,640 --> 00:10:11,394
I'm Roy Taylor's father.
Maybe you know him as DJ Mount.

153
00:10:11,480 --> 00:10:14,790
- Mr Taylor, please come in.
- Thank you for seeing me.

154
00:10:14,880 --> 00:10:16,757
Please sit.

155
00:10:18,840 --> 00:10:21,274
You the one looking into my sors murder?

156
00:10:21,360 --> 00:10:26,354
Investigating his death, yes, sir.
I'm... sorry for your loss.

157
00:10:27,440 --> 00:10:30,591
- I have some information you need.
- About your sors death?

158
00:10:30,680 --> 00:10:32,671
No, sir.

159
00:10:33,880 --> 00:10:36,189
About his life.

160
00:10:36,280 --> 00:10:39,750
I've read in the newspaper
how my son was part of the meth scene,

161
00:10:39,840 --> 00:10:44,152
how he was killed by drugs
behind a wall like that.

162
00:10:48,520 --> 00:10:54,595
What my son did was graduate third
in his class from high school.

163
00:10:55,080 --> 00:11:00,393
He would've graduated first,
except he... he worked a full-time job.

164
00:11:02,120 --> 00:11:05,192
Track-and-field medals,

165
00:11:05,280 --> 00:11:07,635
baseball.

166
00:11:07,720 --> 00:11:11,349
Roy never drank and he never did drugs.

167
00:11:11,440 --> 00:11:13,670
- Do you understand me, sir?
- Mr Taylor...

168
00:11:13,760 --> 00:11:17,594
How they are portraying my boy
in the newspapers is wrong.

169
00:11:17,680 --> 00:11:20,353
If his mother was alive, it would kill her.

170
00:11:21,000 --> 00:11:24,549
I taught him a relationship with Jesus.

171
00:11:25,560 --> 00:11:28,154
Do you understand, sir?

172
00:11:28,240 --> 00:11:31,118
A personal relationship with Jesus.

173
00:11:31,200 --> 00:11:34,829
With all due respect, sir,
sometimes when kids grow up they change,

174
00:11:34,920 --> 00:11:38,390
they move away from what they were taught.

175
00:11:42,480 --> 00:11:45,074
Five years old, he made this.

176
00:11:47,920 --> 00:11:52,038
And a lady who reads palms,

177
00:11:52,120 --> 00:11:54,714
she looked at it and she said...

178
00:11:55,840 --> 00:11:59,435
She said my boy
was going to be a great man...

179
00:12:01,440 --> 00:12:03,635
a good man.

180
00:12:03,720 --> 00:12:04,709
<i>(sniffs)</i>

181
00:12:04,800 --> 00:12:08,509
She read no evil in that boy's hand.

182
00:12:14,320 --> 00:12:17,517
I can see that now, sir.

183
00:12:25,960 --> 00:12:28,554
Some iniquity killed my boy.

184
00:12:31,440 --> 00:12:33,237
<i>(sobs)</i>

185
00:12:34,360 --> 00:12:38,717
Do you know that word, Agent Booth?
It's from the Bible.

186
00:12:38,800 --> 00:12:42,793
"Deliver me from the workers of iniquity...

187
00:12:46,280 --> 00:12:48,953
and save me from bloody men."

188
00:12:54,200 --> 00:12:56,589
You know your Psalms, sir.

189
00:13:04,680 --> 00:13:08,229
I can trust that you will find out
what happened to my boy?

190
00:13:08,320 --> 00:13:10,151
Yes, sir.

191
00:13:11,800 --> 00:13:13,597
Good.

192
00:13:16,000 --> 00:13:18,389
Then I'm glad I came by.

193
00:13:25,320 --> 00:13:28,198
<i>(man)</i> Can we conform to
as much protocol as possible?

194
00:13:28,280 --> 00:13:31,909
<i>(Zack)</i> We're better at this than you think.

195
00:13:32,000 --> 00:13:33,433
<i>(squeaking)</i>

196
00:13:33,520 --> 00:13:35,715
- You know what those are?
- <i>(Bones)</i> Rats.

197
00:13:35,800 --> 00:13:40,157
Scaring us with rats? We've been to places
where rats eat the laces out of our boots.

198
00:13:40,240 --> 00:13:42,595
Take it easy there, Willard.

199
00:13:44,760 --> 00:13:46,955
<i>(Zack)</i> There are the footprints.

200
00:13:47,040 --> 00:13:49,873
There are marks on the wall. It's scraped.

201
00:13:55,960 --> 00:13:58,520
<i>(Bones)</i> Blood smear. Dried.

202
00:14:04,240 --> 00:14:06,071
I see something.

203
00:14:06,160 --> 00:14:07,991
Can I retrieve?

204
00:14:08,080 --> 00:14:09,877
Yes.

205
00:14:21,440 --> 00:14:25,797
Apparently there's a rivalry between Mount

206
00:14:25,880 --> 00:14:28,952
and this guy... Rulz.

207
00:14:29,040 --> 00:14:31,713
We saw him perform last night.
Did you talk to him?

208
00:14:31,800 --> 00:14:33,995
Oh, no. I don't have enough yet.

209
00:14:34,080 --> 00:14:36,116
I go in too soon, he could run.

210
00:14:36,200 --> 00:14:39,237
Wow, that's a beautiful piece.
Zirconium or diamond?

211
00:14:39,320 --> 00:14:42,790
I'm more focused on the dried blood
and flesh at the moment.

212
00:14:42,880 --> 00:14:46,873
- Do you buy Tessajewellery?
- I don't wanna talk about that right now.

213
00:14:46,960 --> 00:14:50,873
Too much of a commitment. I just thought
because you two were going away...

214
00:14:50,960 --> 00:14:54,714
- Do you have anything yet?
- Given the rate of air convection

215
00:14:54,800 --> 00:14:59,510
and the degree of dehydration of the flesh,
I'd say they were there at the same time.

216
00:14:59,600 --> 00:15:02,956
Must hurt to get that thing
ripped out of your bellybutton.

217
00:15:03,040 --> 00:15:06,077
- I thought it was an earring.
- Look at the size of the stud.

218
00:15:06,160 --> 00:15:10,870
I had one of these
before they became totally Miami divorcée.

219
00:15:10,960 --> 00:15:14,396
Good news.
I was able to pull some particulates.

220
00:15:14,480 --> 00:15:17,392
- Are... are those...?
- Eyeballs? Yeah.

221
00:15:17,840 --> 00:15:19,671
Two foreign materials -

222
00:15:19,760 --> 00:15:23,309
low density polyethylene residue
and methamphetamine crystals.

223
00:15:23,400 --> 00:15:26,278
- Polyethylene?
- From the plastic bag holding the meth.

224
00:15:26,360 --> 00:15:28,954
This can be cleaned now.

225
00:15:30,800 --> 00:15:32,836
Yeah, that's a real diamond.

226
00:15:32,920 --> 00:15:36,913
Hey, why not get her a bellybutton ring?
That's not too much of a commitment.

227
00:15:37,000 --> 00:15:41,437
The inside of the lips was damaged by
the teeth. It was not an accidental inalation.

228
00:15:41,520 --> 00:15:46,389
The meth was pushed against his face with
force. Someone was trying to smother him.

229
00:15:46,480 --> 00:15:51,235
- That's how the particulates got into the eye.
- So he didn't OD. He was murdered.

230
00:15:51,320 --> 00:15:54,949
So we just have to find out
who owns this bellybutton ring.

231
00:15:56,120 --> 00:15:58,998
<i>(Angela)</i> Look at this. "Luv Rulz."

232
00:16:00,440 --> 00:16:03,238
At least we know who to ask.

233
00:16:05,960 --> 00:16:08,349
<i>(</i>♪ <i>rap song plays loudly)</i>

234
00:16:10,120 --> 00:16:11,519
Hello.

235
00:16:11,600 --> 00:16:15,070
- Yeah. It's open.
- Yeah, it's open. FBI Special Agent Booth.

236
00:16:15,160 --> 00:16:18,596
What? Is the FBI recruiting from
<i>America's Top Model</i> now?

237
00:16:18,680 --> 00:16:20,910
I'm a forensic anthropologist.

238
00:16:21,000 --> 00:16:23,753
- She works for the FBI.
- I could live with that.

239
00:16:23,840 --> 00:16:26,832
Dr Brennan also discovered
that Roy Taylor was murdered.

240
00:16:26,920 --> 00:16:29,309
- So?
- So, murder is wack, see?

241
00:16:29,400 --> 00:16:32,039
Cos those are the rules, Rulz.

242
00:16:32,120 --> 00:16:34,076
Maybe he had it coming to him.

243
00:16:34,160 --> 00:16:37,550
Oh, so you and Roy Taylor don't get along.

244
00:16:37,640 --> 00:16:42,156
That sucker ran me down, man. Tried to slam
me in one of his tracks. Ain't nobody do that.

245
00:16:42,240 --> 00:16:45,437
And, uh, what happens when they do?

246
00:16:45,520 --> 00:16:48,080
I take a piece of 'em.

247
00:16:48,160 --> 00:16:50,833
I saw him at the Basement,
told him to disappear

248
00:16:50,920 --> 00:16:55,198
and I ain't seen him since
cos he knew to follow the Rulz. <i>(chuckles)</i>

249
00:16:55,280 --> 00:16:56,679
<i>(sardonic laugh)</i>

250
00:16:56,760 --> 00:17:03,233
And maybe your girlfriend made sure
that your "problem" just went away.

251
00:17:03,680 --> 00:17:06,638
She ain't my woman.
I kicked her sorry ass out months ago.

252
00:17:06,720 --> 00:17:10,110
- What is her sorry-ass name?
- Eve Warren.

253
00:17:10,200 --> 00:17:13,954
- What was she doing with Mount?
- Take a guess. I guess it was his turn.

254
00:17:14,040 --> 00:17:17,396
- She kept your ring?
- It's a diamond. Why'd she get rid of that?

255
00:17:17,480 --> 00:17:21,678
- Any idea where she is now?
- Probably ripping somebody else off.

256
00:17:21,760 --> 00:17:25,275
That girl don't care about nobody but herself.
She got a kid.

257
00:17:25,360 --> 00:17:29,433
Don't care about her neither.
Let her brother shoulder that. Bitch.

258
00:17:29,520 --> 00:17:33,672
- What happened to your hand?
- I got shot through the wrist a few years ago.

259
00:17:33,760 --> 00:17:35,955
Shattered the lower radius.

260
00:17:36,040 --> 00:17:40,477
- Yeah. I got some nerve damage, too.
- It's impressive.

261
00:17:40,560 --> 00:17:43,757
I got shot in the back and leg, too.
Wanna see the scars?

262
00:17:43,840 --> 00:17:47,435
Thanks anyway.
Let us know if you hear from Eve.

263
00:17:48,800 --> 00:17:52,349
That's all I got for y'all.
I wanna get back to work. That's it.

264
00:17:52,440 --> 00:17:55,318
You let us know if you hear from her.

265
00:17:56,760 --> 00:17:59,069
- <i>(turns up volume)</i>
- Bones?

266
00:18:01,800 --> 00:18:03,791
I like this music.

267
00:18:06,160 --> 00:18:10,199
<i>(Booth) OK. DJ Mount trusted Eve</i>
<i>because they were sleeping together.</i>

268
00:18:10,280 --> 00:18:13,113
She meets him in the wall, takes the drugs,

269
00:18:13,200 --> 00:18:15,839
kills him for Rulz, then he takes off.

270
00:18:15,920 --> 00:18:18,753
- Hey, you should write fiction.
- It's reasonable.

271
00:18:18,840 --> 00:18:20,956
It's not based on evidence.

272
00:18:21,040 --> 00:18:23,838
I'm positing a scenario.
We've been through this.

273
00:18:23,920 --> 00:18:27,833
And it always seems to be a waste of time.
Now, finding a marker on a bone...

274
00:18:27,920 --> 00:18:31,037
No. I think I need a vacation.
I think you do, too.

275
00:18:31,120 --> 00:18:35,716
- Well, I'm not the one who's snippy.
- "Snippy"? What are you? Like, 70?

276
00:18:35,800 --> 00:18:40,669
See what I mean? I think you should find
a nice, relaxing place to go on that vacation.

277
00:18:40,760 --> 00:18:43,558
Somewhere where you can
get a massage, do some yoga.

278
00:18:43,640 --> 00:18:48,794
- I don't do yoga. I do push-ups, sit-ups.
- That's cardiovascular. Yoga deals more...

279
00:18:48,880 --> 00:18:52,270
- Why exactly are we talking about this?
- Because you're tense.

280
00:18:52,360 --> 00:18:55,955
- Because we're talking.
- <i>(</i>♪ <i>rap song)</i>

281
00:18:58,440 --> 00:19:00,829
You switched my music?

282
00:19:06,520 --> 00:19:09,114
- Roy Taylor?
- Yes.

283
00:19:09,200 --> 00:19:11,714
Anything pop out now the bones are clean?

284
00:19:11,800 --> 00:19:15,952
Some damage to the facetjoint and foramen
on C4 on the right side of the neck.

285
00:19:16,040 --> 00:19:18,429
That suggests his head was forced that way.

286
00:19:18,520 --> 00:19:21,671
One other thing.
I looked at the skull through the microscope.

287
00:19:21,760 --> 00:19:25,639
Came across a slight depression,
barely discernable.

288
00:19:25,720 --> 00:19:27,950
A slight indentation.

289
00:19:28,040 --> 00:19:33,114
- Could it be congenital? Or a bone anomaly?
- Yeah, probably.

290
00:19:35,640 --> 00:19:40,191
- Do you ever go on vacation?
- I take my vacation when you take yours.

291
00:19:40,280 --> 00:19:44,910
- What do you do?
- Go back home to Michigan, see the family.

292
00:19:45,000 --> 00:19:47,309
I have three brothers and four sisters.

293
00:19:47,760 --> 00:19:50,228
- Do you enjoy that?
- God, no.

294
00:19:50,320 --> 00:19:54,393
I made the mistake of telling them
I work with corpses and skeletons.

295
00:19:54,480 --> 00:19:57,358
- They think I'm a freak.
- Then why do you go?

296
00:19:57,440 --> 00:19:59,431
It's my family.

297
00:19:59,520 --> 00:20:02,239
They love me.

298
00:20:02,320 --> 00:20:08,316
Take a closer look at the anomaly under
the microscope. See what made that mark.

299
00:20:09,760 --> 00:20:13,070
- That's right. Good, good, good.
- <i>(</i>♪ <i>rap music)</i>

300
00:20:13,160 --> 00:20:15,754
Yeah, let's work. Let's work!

301
00:20:19,360 --> 00:20:21,954
- What do you want?
- Special Agent Booth, FBI.

302
00:20:22,040 --> 00:20:25,271
- This is my associate, Dr Brennan.
- What do you call this?

303
00:20:25,360 --> 00:20:27,476
Krump.

304
00:20:27,560 --> 00:20:31,758
The kids, they come here, they dance,
they don't gangbang.

305
00:20:31,840 --> 00:20:34,957
So what do you want?
You didn't come here for a dance lesson.

306
00:20:35,400 --> 00:20:38,790
Hey, Maya. How you doir, baby?

307
00:20:39,760 --> 00:20:44,914
Come on now. We're gonna go outside and
you gonna play with the rest of the kids, OK?

308
00:20:45,000 --> 00:20:49,039
- There you go.
- I'd like to ask you about your sister Eve.

309
00:20:49,120 --> 00:20:50,633
<i>(sighs)</i>

310
00:20:50,720 --> 00:20:54,474
- What's she done now?
- When was the last time you saw her?

311
00:20:54,560 --> 00:20:57,472
About six weeks ago
when she dropped off Maya.

312
00:20:57,560 --> 00:21:00,313
- OK. That's fine.
- Just dropped her off and left?

313
00:21:00,400 --> 00:21:03,392
She needed me to watch her for a while.
Left me some money.

314
00:21:03,480 --> 00:21:09,669
Do you happen to have a, I don't know,
recent photo that we could take?

315
00:21:10,760 --> 00:21:16,312
Evie said she had cleaned herself up.
She was turning her life around.

316
00:21:16,400 --> 00:21:18,960
And I believed her.

317
00:21:19,040 --> 00:21:21,918
She never came back.

318
00:21:22,480 --> 00:21:25,711
That little girl out there, that's her daughter.

319
00:21:26,560 --> 00:21:29,233
She's like a daughter to me, too.

320
00:21:30,240 --> 00:21:35,109
Didrt it bother you that Eve never came
back? I mean, didn't you go look for her?

321
00:21:35,200 --> 00:21:36,997
I learned to let her go.

322
00:21:37,560 --> 00:21:41,633
Eve, she's had a lot of problems -
drugs, hanging out with the wrong people.

323
00:21:41,720 --> 00:21:45,759
If I track her down and
she takes Maya before she's ready...

324
00:21:45,840 --> 00:21:49,116
I'm not letting nothing happen
to that little girl.

325
00:21:50,080 --> 00:21:52,913
- Did you know Roy Taylor?
- Met him.

326
00:21:53,000 --> 00:21:55,958
DJ Mount. I like his stuff. Play it for the kids.

327
00:21:56,040 --> 00:21:58,395
We think she was there
when he was murdered.

328
00:21:58,480 --> 00:22:00,710
Murdered?

329
00:22:01,200 --> 00:22:03,760
- You can't find Evie?
- No.

330
00:22:05,800 --> 00:22:08,439
Oh, man.

331
00:22:08,520 --> 00:22:11,114
She told me she loved him...

332
00:22:12,080 --> 00:22:16,437
and that she and Mount
were gonna take Maya away, out of DC,

333
00:22:16,520 --> 00:22:18,909
give her a better life, one we never had.

334
00:22:19,000 --> 00:22:23,039
- You said she left you some cash.
- Yeah. For Maya.

335
00:22:23,120 --> 00:22:26,590
I'll buy what you have, two dollars to one.

336
00:22:26,680 --> 00:22:29,877
- Sure. Whatever, man.
<i>- (Maya giggles)</i>

337
00:22:34,880 --> 00:22:39,749
You may want the stooges at the FBI, who
are experts due to your so-called "drug war",

338
00:22:39,840 --> 00:22:45,551
to run a comparison, but I'd say the meth on
these bills matches that found with DJ Mount.

339
00:22:45,640 --> 00:22:50,953
Yeah. My guess is that Eve was with Mount
at the time that he was murdered.

340
00:22:51,040 --> 00:22:53,508
How about this, huh?

341
00:22:53,600 --> 00:22:57,513
DJ Mount rejects Eve
because of a questionable past.

342
00:22:57,600 --> 00:23:01,957
So, hey, she gets mad,
she wants to leave with some money, so...

343
00:23:03,960 --> 00:23:06,838
- What?
- Yeah, I don't really think about that stuff.

344
00:23:06,920 --> 00:23:11,198
- I'm more about bugs and minerals. Sorry.
- Come on, Hodgins. You're a smart guy.

345
00:23:11,280 --> 00:23:16,638
Look up from your microscope. These are
real people we're trying to figure out here.

346
00:23:17,080 --> 00:23:19,594
- OK.
- Maybe she was just using Mount.

347
00:23:19,680 --> 00:23:22,353
- Setting him up to get his drugs and money.
- Nice.

348
00:23:22,440 --> 00:23:24,715
- Yeah?
- Yeah.

349
00:23:25,800 --> 00:23:29,395
- Real question is where does she go next?
- You're on fire, man.

350
00:23:29,480 --> 00:23:33,473
After she left her brother's place.
That is where she met her untimely end.

351
00:23:33,560 --> 00:23:36,199
I'm gonna turn you into an investigator yet.

352
00:23:36,280 --> 00:23:40,114
No, no, no. Bugs and slime, dude.
That is where I'm happy.

353
00:23:50,160 --> 00:23:54,631
The damage to his C4 vertebra was the result
of his head being twisted so far right.

354
00:23:54,720 --> 00:23:57,518
He was moving this way, toward Eve.

355
00:23:57,600 --> 00:24:00,319
<i>(Booth)</i> My bet is he was chasing her.

356
00:24:00,400 --> 00:24:03,995
- And that's based on?
- Money and meth.

357
00:24:04,080 --> 00:24:07,993
She left carrying money
saturated in the same meth that killed Mount.

358
00:24:08,080 --> 00:24:11,629
- She was moving fast.
- She didn't stop when her ring got ripped out.

359
00:24:11,720 --> 00:24:17,636
Money's a good reason to get chased, hm?
Only question is why wasrt he facing her?

360
00:24:17,720 --> 00:24:21,679
It got tight back there. 15 centimetres.

361
00:24:21,760 --> 00:24:25,514
Eve ripped out her bellybutton ring here
and then left a smear of blood

362
00:24:25,600 --> 00:24:28,034
until the corridor widened, here.

363
00:24:28,120 --> 00:24:29,951
Oh, God!

364
00:24:30,040 --> 00:24:32,474
<i>(exhales in pain)</i>

365
00:24:32,560 --> 00:24:36,678
- What?
- Thatjust... makes me a little sick.

366
00:24:36,760 --> 00:24:40,833
You pick bodies out of graves. Yanking out
a bellybutton ring makes you sick?

367
00:24:40,920 --> 00:24:42,512
OK. Move along.

368
00:24:42,600 --> 00:24:47,037
I've shot a lot of people, and I admit that
bellybutton thing makes me nauseous, too.

369
00:24:47,120 --> 00:24:51,511
- Thank you.
- Mount must've looked back, but kept going.

370
00:24:51,600 --> 00:24:56,435
Then the passageway narrowed,
so he couldn't turn his head back toward Eve.

371
00:24:56,520 --> 00:25:01,230
Then there's no way she could've shoved
the meth into his face. Eve didn't kill him.

372
00:25:01,320 --> 00:25:03,595
A third person surprised him. He turned.

373
00:25:03,680 --> 00:25:07,355
Mount prevented this third person
getting to Eve, so she escaped.

374
00:25:07,440 --> 00:25:11,069
But he got to Mount,
shoved the meth in his face and killed him.

375
00:25:11,520 --> 00:25:16,878
But the real question is
who the hell is this third person?

376
00:25:24,000 --> 00:25:28,915
- <i>(man)</i> Why the hell you pick me up, man?
- <i>(Booth)</i> You know why I brought you in.

377
00:25:29,000 --> 00:25:33,312
I waited for you to contact me,
explain your situation, but you didn't do that.

378
00:25:33,400 --> 00:25:35,436
That's not polite.

379
00:25:35,520 --> 00:25:39,559
What are you? DEA? Metro cop?

380
00:25:40,400 --> 00:25:43,153
I'm Special Agent Ronald Oakes.

381
00:25:43,240 --> 00:25:47,279
- One of us?
- My orders were not to break deep cover.

382
00:25:47,360 --> 00:25:51,069
Out of deep regard for my FBI brother,
I gave you the nod.

383
00:25:52,920 --> 00:25:54,911
That's bull.

384
00:25:56,200 --> 00:25:59,670
I made you. Now you're making excuses.

385
00:26:00,240 --> 00:26:02,231
You got any keys for these cuffs?

386
00:26:02,320 --> 00:26:04,595
Fine. Your way.

387
00:26:05,600 --> 00:26:10,151
I need more than a nod, man. You know,
I'm conducting a murder investigation.

388
00:26:10,240 --> 00:26:12,834
Now I need to know what you know.

389
00:26:13,760 --> 00:26:19,835
15 months investigating the links between
the urban music business and gang activity.

390
00:26:19,920 --> 00:26:23,515
- That's why you got next to Hall.
- That's a clean alias. You ran him?

391
00:26:23,600 --> 00:26:25,716
- Yeah.
- Came back clean?

392
00:26:25,800 --> 00:26:28,997
His real name is Terrance Baskin.

393
00:26:29,480 --> 00:26:34,713
We know he's pushing meth through that
club, but we can't get enough to touch him.

394
00:26:34,800 --> 00:26:38,634
Our informants disappear.
They either get bought off or killed.

395
00:26:38,720 --> 00:26:41,837
- What about this murder?
- The night Mount disappeared,

396
00:26:41,920 --> 00:26:44,434
Hall got ripped off for meth and a ton of cash.

397
00:26:44,520 --> 00:26:49,355
- DJ Mount ripped off Hall?
- No. It doesn't scan. Mount was into Jesus.

398
00:26:49,440 --> 00:26:54,833
- Hall killed DJ Mount?
- Nah. Hall's people do that stuff for him.

399
00:26:55,760 --> 00:26:59,639
So if anybody asked,
why did you have me arrested?

400
00:26:59,720 --> 00:27:01,472
Weapons beef.

401
00:27:03,120 --> 00:27:06,874
- So I don't get my gun back?
- <i>(chuckling)</i> No. No.

402
00:27:07,920 --> 00:27:12,596
We meet up again,
if you get an excuse, hit me.

403
00:27:12,680 --> 00:27:15,478
Oh. That, uh...

404
00:27:15,560 --> 00:27:17,915
Count on it.

405
00:27:20,560 --> 00:27:25,315
I've been investigated for years. Why
do you think they never got me on anything?

406
00:27:25,400 --> 00:27:27,789
Because you're so smart?

407
00:27:28,640 --> 00:27:31,791
Because Terrance Baskin is my past.

408
00:27:31,880 --> 00:27:34,394
I am 100% clean now.

409
00:27:35,480 --> 00:27:39,439
This is my life now.
This and my record label.

410
00:27:39,520 --> 00:27:42,751
Not crystal meth, not gangbanging.

411
00:27:42,840 --> 00:27:48,233
Yet much of the iconic quality of urban music
lies in the perceived or actual rivalry

412
00:27:48,320 --> 00:27:50,834
between the principal artists.

413
00:27:52,160 --> 00:27:55,118
- Where did you find her?
- Museum.

414
00:27:56,440 --> 00:28:01,753
Was the rivalry between Mount and Mr Rulz
strong enough to lead to murder?

415
00:28:01,840 --> 00:28:03,432
Sure. They were both capable.

416
00:28:03,520 --> 00:28:07,513
Add in the fact that Mount
was sleeping with Rulz's girlfriend, Eve.

417
00:28:07,600 --> 00:28:09,955
- Yeah, in fact...
- Yeah?

418
00:28:10,040 --> 00:28:13,350
...Rulz built himself a studio around that time.

419
00:28:13,440 --> 00:28:16,318
Poured cement for the pad
a day after they disappeared.

420
00:28:16,400 --> 00:28:18,391
- So?
- I'm saying...

421
00:28:18,480 --> 00:28:22,075
Mount's dead, Eve's gone missing.

422
00:28:23,640 --> 00:28:26,154
You might want to consider that.

423
00:28:27,120 --> 00:28:31,079
- Let's go.
- What do you think?

424
00:28:31,160 --> 00:28:34,675
What do I think?
I think we need to find a way

425
00:28:34,760 --> 00:28:38,719
- to find a body buried under a slab of cement.
- Can't you get a warrant?

426
00:28:38,800 --> 00:28:43,078
A look around the premises maybe,
but no way to tear it up.

427
00:28:43,160 --> 00:28:45,151
Let me make a phone call.

428
00:28:47,720 --> 00:28:53,158
- Tootie travels the world finding dead bodies.
- Does Tootie always drool like that?

429
00:28:53,240 --> 00:28:56,835
What? I'm gonna hurt her... <i>his</i> feelings?

430
00:28:56,920 --> 00:29:00,230
Tootie is the best cadaver dog in the world,
Agent Booth.

431
00:29:00,320 --> 00:29:05,075
It's true. If you were a dead body,
you'd want Tootie looking for you.

432
00:29:06,280 --> 00:29:09,477
- How can it smell anything under a building?
- He can.

433
00:29:09,560 --> 00:29:15,635
Once I saw Tootie find a dead body wrapped
in plastic, under concrete, after four years.

434
00:29:15,720 --> 00:29:19,156
Tootie can smell decaying blood on a tooth
six feet underground.

435
00:29:19,240 --> 00:29:22,277
So what he drools a little?
What's up with that?

436
00:29:22,360 --> 00:29:26,751
You know, your eyes are kinda close together,
but I don't comment.

437
00:29:26,840 --> 00:29:29,149
I apologise.

438
00:29:29,240 --> 00:29:31,754
- Is he sincere?
- Yeah.

439
00:29:31,840 --> 00:29:34,400
All right, then. We accept.

440
00:29:36,160 --> 00:29:37,878
<i>(growling)</i>

441
00:29:37,960 --> 00:29:41,157
- Good boy. Tootie found something.
- Or he's just lazy.

442
00:29:41,240 --> 00:29:43,959
Lying down is his indicator.

443
00:29:44,040 --> 00:29:47,316
Tootie found it. There's a body under here.

444
00:29:47,400 --> 00:29:52,599
You should get a warrant
to bring in ajackhammer for the floor.

445
00:29:52,680 --> 00:29:55,240
I'd start digging here.

446
00:29:58,240 --> 00:30:00,435
Dental records confirm this is Eve Warren.

447
00:30:00,520 --> 00:30:03,398
Insect activity confirms
she died the same time as Mount.

448
00:30:03,480 --> 00:30:06,472
- Where did Booth go?
- His girlfriend brought him a shirt.

449
00:30:06,560 --> 00:30:09,313
- They're up in the lounge.
- Zack, clean the bones.

450
00:30:09,400 --> 00:30:12,119
We've already got cause of death and identity.

451
00:30:12,200 --> 00:30:15,670
It might be grasping,
but that odd mark on Mount's skull,

452
00:30:15,760 --> 00:30:18,558
see if you can find anything like it
on Eve's remains.

453
00:30:18,640 --> 00:30:21,518
Jamaica? God, that's incredible.

454
00:30:21,600 --> 00:30:24,398
It's a bed and breakfast.
There are coral cliffs.

455
00:30:24,480 --> 00:30:27,278
Snorkelling, kayaking.

456
00:30:27,360 --> 00:30:32,593
Oh, you two are so ready
for the pre-shacking-up test vacation.

457
00:30:32,680 --> 00:30:35,831
- What do you mean?
- You have keys to each other's places.

458
00:30:35,920 --> 00:30:40,471
You've done the weekend away a couple
times. It's time for the ten-day vacation.

459
00:30:41,000 --> 00:30:46,438
Jamaica's like a dry run for living together,
only with rum punch and steel drums.

460
00:30:46,520 --> 00:30:49,034
Yeah. See you later.

461
00:30:49,120 --> 00:30:51,270
Living together? Silly.

462
00:30:51,360 --> 00:30:53,351
Thanks for bringing me a shirt.

463
00:30:53,440 --> 00:30:55,431
Yeah, OK. I'll talk to you later.

464
00:30:55,520 --> 00:30:57,715
Yeah.

465
00:30:57,800 --> 00:31:00,598
- Hi, Tessa.
- Yeah, OK. Bye.

466
00:31:02,000 --> 00:31:05,470
- It's Eve Warren.
- Eve Warren. OK. Cause of death?

467
00:31:05,560 --> 00:31:07,357
- Same as Mount.
- Meth overdose.

468
00:31:07,440 --> 00:31:10,671
Pushed in the face,
but I don't think Rulz killed her.

469
00:31:10,760 --> 00:31:14,469
- She was buried under his studio.
- But her wrist was broken.

470
00:31:14,560 --> 00:31:20,556
Bone damage indicates that Eve was taken
from behind and smashed into a wall.

471
00:31:23,600 --> 00:31:28,515
Her skull shows damage to the infra- and
supraorbital margins and zygomatic process.

472
00:31:28,600 --> 00:31:31,672
Zygo-zu...?
You said she was killed by crystal meth.

473
00:31:31,760 --> 00:31:36,038
She was. She would've been stunned
by the blow, but not killed. Not immediately.

474
00:31:36,120 --> 00:31:42,036
A bag of crystal meth was placed over her
face, ground into her wounds, into the airway.

475
00:31:42,120 --> 00:31:45,032
Wait. Rulz couldn't have
smashed her into a wall?

476
00:31:45,120 --> 00:31:48,874
Her radius was separated
from the scaphoid and trapezium.

477
00:31:48,960 --> 00:31:51,315
Her right wrist was twisted behind her back.

478
00:31:51,400 --> 00:31:54,437
There's damage
to both the elbow and shoulder.

479
00:31:54,520 --> 00:31:59,116
For that to happen, Eve's attacker would've
had to twist her arm up with his right hand

480
00:31:59,200 --> 00:32:01,998
while jamming the meth into her face
with the other.

481
00:32:02,080 --> 00:32:04,116
Both with a great deal of force.

482
00:32:04,200 --> 00:32:08,830
Rulz had been shot twice in the right hand.
I got it. He had nerve damage.

483
00:32:08,920 --> 00:32:12,993
There is no way
he had the strength to kill Eve Warren.

484
00:32:20,640 --> 00:32:22,915
You did not murder Eve Warren.

485
00:32:23,360 --> 00:32:27,990
This is a weird kind of interrogation, huh?
Cops telling me what I didn't do.

486
00:32:28,080 --> 00:32:32,153
Then do me a favour. Tell me Bones is wrong
and confess to a murder, huh, pal?

487
00:32:32,240 --> 00:32:37,155
- Hell, no. You think I'm some type of idiot?
- Well, do me a favour. Deny it.

488
00:32:37,240 --> 00:32:40,630
See, you got tricks.
You're gonna twist all my words around.

489
00:32:40,720 --> 00:32:44,235
- So I better not say anything.
- But you didn't kill Eve Warren.

490
00:32:44,320 --> 00:32:47,392
So you say. The Rulz says, "Say nothing."

491
00:32:47,480 --> 00:32:49,516
- He wants us to hold him.
- Why?

492
00:32:49,600 --> 00:32:54,230
Because every time a rapper gets murdered,
his business goes through the roof.

493
00:32:54,320 --> 00:32:58,154
Why should DJ Mount get the bump, huh?
Maybe it's my turn.

494
00:32:58,240 --> 00:33:01,118
I tell you what. I'll make you a better deal.

495
00:33:01,200 --> 00:33:05,079
Tell us what we need to know
and I'll have those charges laid against you.

496
00:33:05,160 --> 00:33:07,594
- Put you in the remand centre?
- For how long?

497
00:33:07,680 --> 00:33:11,559
- Depends on what you tell us.
- You're negotiating to put him in jail?

498
00:33:11,640 --> 00:33:14,712
I'll sweeten the pot,
charge you with Mount's death, too.

499
00:33:14,800 --> 00:33:21,353
But you hire one of those moron lawyers and
you'll be thrown in lockup for maybe a month.

500
00:33:21,440 --> 00:33:24,750
- Sweet. All right.
- Where am I? In backwards world?

501
00:33:24,840 --> 00:33:28,389
- What have you got?
- I can tell y'all why Mount got killed.

502
00:33:28,480 --> 00:33:32,951
- Figure out the rest on your own.
- We have to figure it outjust from motive?

503
00:33:33,040 --> 00:33:37,875
OK, look, Bones, this is,
you know, sort of my thing.

504
00:33:37,960 --> 00:33:42,078
- Mount was gonnajump.
- You mean commit suicide?

505
00:33:42,160 --> 00:33:44,799
- Where did you find her?
- Museum.

506
00:33:44,880 --> 00:33:47,553
I mean labels. Jump labels.

507
00:33:47,640 --> 00:33:53,317
Wait. <i>(laughs)</i> You're saying that DJ Mount
was gonna leave Basement Records?

508
00:33:53,400 --> 00:33:57,552
All he needed was the money
to buy himself back. That's why he got killed.

509
00:33:57,640 --> 00:34:02,668
If Hall even finds out I told y'all that much,
I'm gonna end up some mummy in a wall.

510
00:34:02,760 --> 00:34:06,548
- And what about Eve?
- Man, Eve couldn't kill nobody.

511
00:34:06,640 --> 00:34:10,838
You know, sex 'em to death maybe,
but that's about it.

512
00:34:10,920 --> 00:34:13,150
Oh, there was one more thing.

513
00:34:13,240 --> 00:34:17,233
The next day Hall built me a new studio.

514
00:34:17,320 --> 00:34:19,959
He took it out of my money, too.

515
00:34:23,480 --> 00:34:28,918
- So you gonna put me in jail?
- Well, you know, hey, it's the least we can do.

516
00:34:30,840 --> 00:34:34,150
Hall's got motive to kill Mount
because he's jumping labels

517
00:34:34,240 --> 00:34:39,917
and he's running away with some girl
who's stealing Hall's meth and money.

518
00:34:40,000 --> 00:34:42,992
I'm starting to see
how this whole motive thing works.

519
00:34:43,080 --> 00:34:46,629
- Thank you.
- It's still murky psychological guesswork.

520
00:34:47,840 --> 00:34:50,559
Dr Brennan, I found a mark on Eve Warren.

521
00:34:50,640 --> 00:34:54,394
Here, on the manubrium.

522
00:34:54,480 --> 00:34:57,153
- Compare it to the mark on Mount.
- OK.

523
00:34:57,240 --> 00:34:59,549
Eve tells Mount she wants a new life,

524
00:34:59,640 --> 00:35:04,191
so she rips off the dope and the cash,
thinking she can build a new future with him.

525
00:35:04,280 --> 00:35:06,077
That's a story, Booth.

526
00:35:06,160 --> 00:35:09,391
- You need to find something real.
- Why? It feels real to me.

527
00:35:09,480 --> 00:35:11,835
I mean, Eve is a woman in love

528
00:35:11,920 --> 00:35:16,357
who is trying to escape a world
that's just crushing her. Hm?

529
00:35:19,920 --> 00:35:25,119
All right, Mount finds out how much trouble
the woman he's in love with is in,

530
00:35:25,200 --> 00:35:28,192
so he gives up his own life to protect her.

531
00:35:28,280 --> 00:35:30,555
That's not enough.

532
00:35:32,840 --> 00:35:37,630
They were hoping for a better life,
and they wound up dead.

533
00:35:45,040 --> 00:35:47,315
Looks like a match.

534
00:35:49,400 --> 00:35:51,868
Thanks. Good job.

535
00:35:51,960 --> 00:35:55,669
- What the hell's that?
- I'm not sure. It's a bone dimple.

536
00:35:55,760 --> 00:35:57,990
They both have it so it can't be genetic.

537
00:35:58,080 --> 00:36:01,117
Something external caused it,
but I'm not sure what.

538
00:36:01,200 --> 00:36:03,156
Randall Hall.

539
00:36:03,240 --> 00:36:07,153
He's behind this. Randall Hall, OK?
He killed these two people.

540
00:36:07,240 --> 00:36:09,595
We know it. He did it.
We just can't touch him.

541
00:36:09,680 --> 00:36:13,878
And there's no evidence linking him
to the drugs, the cash, or either body,

542
00:36:13,960 --> 00:36:16,349
except for a couple of damn bone dimples.

543
00:36:16,440 --> 00:36:20,752
I'll keep looking at the remains,
maybe find the evidence we need.

544
00:36:20,840 --> 00:36:22,512
- I can't let it stand.
- What?

545
00:36:22,600 --> 00:36:26,388
I'm gonna spread the pain, OK?
That's my new motto.

546
00:36:26,480 --> 00:36:29,790
Wait! I can help spread pain! Wait!

547
00:36:29,880 --> 00:36:32,758
<i>(</i>♪ <i>rap song plays)</i>

548
00:36:32,840 --> 00:36:34,592
- We know you did it.
- What?

549
00:36:34,680 --> 00:36:37,148
Killed Mount so he wouldn't leave your label.

550
00:36:37,240 --> 00:36:41,438
- You killed Eve Warren.
- And buried her under Rulz's studio.

551
00:36:42,280 --> 00:36:46,034
Meantime, this is gonna have to remain
an active crime scene.

552
00:36:46,120 --> 00:36:49,271
It's harassment. I'll sue.

553
00:36:49,360 --> 00:36:52,989
And I'm gonna harass you every chance I get.

554
00:36:54,760 --> 00:36:58,355
I'm not somebody you wanna mess with.

555
00:37:00,560 --> 00:37:03,199
Did you just poke me?

556
00:37:06,040 --> 00:37:09,157
Did he just poke me with his little stick?

557
00:37:09,240 --> 00:37:13,711
This is my place.
I wanna poke someone, I do it. Come on...

558
00:37:18,640 --> 00:37:21,916
All right. How easily do you think I scare?

559
00:37:22,000 --> 00:37:24,309
Hey, Booth! Don't break the cane.

560
00:37:24,400 --> 00:37:26,914
Arrest him
and confiscate the cane as evidence.

561
00:37:27,000 --> 00:37:30,549
- I need the cane.
- Arrest him for what? <i>He</i> pointed the gun.

562
00:37:30,640 --> 00:37:35,111
Harbouring threats, smelling bad,
or anything. It's the cane we want.

563
00:37:35,200 --> 00:37:37,760
Well, then here. Randall Hall,

564
00:37:37,840 --> 00:37:42,516
I'm placing you under arrest
for the assault of a federal agent.

565
00:37:43,600 --> 00:37:47,354
- This'll never go to court.
- Oh, let's go find out, huh?

566
00:37:48,120 --> 00:37:50,918
Next time I take your gun,
I'll shoot you with it.

567
00:37:51,000 --> 00:37:54,879
Well, then I better not let you
get my gun again.

568
00:37:54,960 --> 00:37:57,428
<i>(Booth)</i> Come on. Let's go.

569
00:38:05,240 --> 00:38:10,473
Get this. I called Tessa to tell her a couple
places she should check out in Jamaica.

570
00:38:10,560 --> 00:38:12,596
- She's not going.
- What happened?

571
00:38:12,680 --> 00:38:16,229
She said something came up at work,
but I know the truth.

572
00:38:16,320 --> 00:38:20,632
- How many times you want me to poke Zack?
- Just once, but as hard as you can.

573
00:38:20,720 --> 00:38:23,439
As hard as he can?
Why don't I hit him as hard as I can?

574
00:38:23,520 --> 00:38:26,193
Because you have arms like noodles.
I am burly.

575
00:38:26,280 --> 00:38:30,478
- What truth?
- Argh! Is that all you got, burly boy?

576
00:38:30,560 --> 00:38:34,712
- They got freaked out by stage six.
- What's stage six?

577
00:38:34,800 --> 00:38:38,076
One: Spend the night.
Two: Spend the weekend.

578
00:38:38,160 --> 00:38:41,869
Three: Exchange keys.
Four: Sexy weekend getaway.

579
00:38:41,960 --> 00:38:46,351
Five: Extended vacation
inevitably followed by six: Move in together.

580
00:38:46,840 --> 00:38:50,594
I'm an anthropologist. I know the stages
of everything. You made those up.

581
00:38:50,680 --> 00:38:55,800
- I did not! They got to stage five and balked.
- Not Booth. Booth did not balk.

582
00:38:55,880 --> 00:38:58,269
- It's always the guy.
- Booth is not a balker.

583
00:38:58,360 --> 00:39:01,670
Hey. The mark on Mount
and the mark on Eve are the same.

584
00:39:01,760 --> 00:39:04,832
He can't resist hitting them
with that stupid cane.

585
00:39:04,920 --> 00:39:09,357
The end of the cane - it's a fit for both marks.
Hall is the killer.

586
00:39:09,440 --> 00:39:13,797
Send the cane, the photos and the medium
to the FBI. Let them confirm the match.

587
00:39:13,880 --> 00:39:16,952
- What? Let them have all the glory?
- My chest hurts.

588
00:39:17,040 --> 00:39:19,429
Yeah. All the glory.

589
00:39:21,680 --> 00:39:25,309
<i>Here's what we know.</i>
<i>Evidence linking rap producer Randall Hall</i>

590
00:39:25,400 --> 00:39:28,676
<i>with the death of rising hip-hop star DJ Mount</i>

591
00:39:28,760 --> 00:39:31,638
<i>led to charges being filed</i>
<i>by the district attorney.</i>

592
00:39:31,720 --> 00:39:35,759
<i>Information coming to us slowly,</i>
<i>but as soon as details...</i>

593
00:39:40,000 --> 00:39:42,673
Getting yourself in the mood?

594
00:39:42,760 --> 00:39:44,671
Trying.

595
00:39:45,680 --> 00:39:49,719
You know, this really isn't gonna be
the type of vacation I was hoping for.

596
00:39:49,800 --> 00:39:51,631
Oh?

597
00:39:51,720 --> 00:39:55,429
Tessa's not going.
Something came up at work.

598
00:39:55,920 --> 00:39:59,310
That's too bad. I'm sorry.

599
00:40:01,040 --> 00:40:04,271
Hey, I like going on vacations by myself.

600
00:40:04,360 --> 00:40:07,955
- Really?
- Sure. Nothing wrong with being alone.

601
00:40:08,040 --> 00:40:13,797
- No. I mean, you like to go on vacation?
- Yeah. I go places all the time.

602
00:40:16,840 --> 00:40:21,630
Do you everjust, you know, sit on the beach,
pretend there's no such thing as skeletons?

603
00:40:21,720 --> 00:40:23,790
Is that in any way fun?

604
00:40:24,360 --> 00:40:27,670
- When was the last time you got away?
- Got away from what?

605
00:40:27,760 --> 00:40:29,990
<i>(chuckles)</i>

606
00:40:30,080 --> 00:40:35,359
Oh, Bones, you know,
because what usually happens to me...

607
00:40:37,040 --> 00:40:40,396
- I think about not coming back.
- Seriously?

608
00:40:40,480 --> 00:40:43,552
Yeah. You know, you go with someone,

609
00:40:43,640 --> 00:40:47,872
you joke about
not going back to your real life,

610
00:40:47,960 --> 00:40:50,235
the two of you laugh.

611
00:40:50,320 --> 00:40:55,235
But, when you're alone,
the world is full of possibilities.

612
00:41:01,040 --> 00:41:03,759
See you next week.

613
00:41:37,240 --> 00:41:40,869
Visiontext Subtitles: Natasha Cohn

614
00:41:45,920 --> 00:41:47,239
What's that mean?

615
00:41:48,000 --> 00:41:49,991
ENGLISH SDH

