2
00:00:05,470 --> 00:00:07,280
Previously on Prison Break

3
00:00:07,290 --> 00:00:08,840
Did you ask for a recent photo

4
00:00:08,850 --> 00:00:10,700
of LJ and Sara? Yeah.

5
00:00:11,290 --> 00:00:13,200
Where is i She showed me the pictures,

6
00:00:13,210 --> 00:00:14,560
but she wouldn't let me keep them.

7
00:00:15,730 --> 00:00:16,610
All right.

8
00:00:16,620 --> 00:00:18,140
I want to know who this guy is.

9
00:00:18,170 --> 00:00:19,750
Said his name was Sullins.

10
00:00:20,670 --> 00:00:22,680
Alex, thanks for coming in.

11
00:00:23,610 --> 00:00:24,610
Hello, Lang.

12
00:00:24,620 --> 00:00:26,580
What's going on? There's all kinds

13
00:00:26,590 --> 00:00:28,390
of suits over here going through your office.

14
00:00:28,560 --> 00:00:29,780
I know you, huh?

15
00:00:30,070 --> 00:00:30,370
Afraid not.

16
00:00:30,380 --> 00:00:31,550
Yeah, yeah, yeah.

17
00:00:32,140 --> 00:00:33,340
You're McFadden.

18
00:00:33,360 --> 00:00:34,500
You've confused me with someone else.

19
00:00:34,510 --> 00:00:36,080
You were with the ambassador.

20
00:00:36,130 --> 00:00:38,270
You don't know me, I don't know you,

21
00:00:38,280 --> 00:00:40,060
but it's your job to get me out of here.

22
00:00:40,070 --> 00:00:41,480
You break out tomorrow. By 3:00 p.m.

23
00:00:41,490 --> 00:00:43,270
You mean a.m. No, I mean p.m.

24
00:00:43,280 --> 00:00:45,750
We're doing this tomorrow... in the middle of the day.

25
00:00:54,290 --> 00:00:55,420
Give me the ring.

26
00:00:56,930 --> 00:00:58,280
Wise decision.

27
00:01:02,610 --> 00:01:03,780
Want the rin brother?

28
00:01:03,980 --> 00:01:05,560
That's more your style, man.

30
00:01:15,510 --> 00:01:17,220
It's all right, it's all right.

31
00:01:20,310 --> 00:01:22,090
You all go on back. Go ahead.

32
00:01:22,900 --> 00:01:23,980
No, go ahead.

33
00:01:26,840 --> 00:01:28,010
A word.

34
00:01:33,470 --> 00:01:35,540
You should try and be more careful in the future.

35
00:01:35,570 --> 00:01:36,700
Yes, sir.

38
00:02:00,810 --> 00:02:01,850
What's your name?

39
00:02:03,720 --> 00:02:04,800
Tyge.

40
00:02:05,050 --> 00:02:06,160
Michael.

41
00:02:06,680 --> 00:02:07,760
The Australian.

42
00:02:07,770 --> 00:02:09,300
You said you knew him from Nice.

43
00:02:09,510 --> 00:02:10,590
Is that true?

44
00:02:10,800 --> 00:02:12,110
You calling me a liar now?

45
00:02:12,120 --> 00:02:13,540
He says you're full of it.

46
00:02:13,930 --> 00:02:15,640
He said he was never an ambassador.

47
00:02:16,430 --> 00:02:18,140
No, not anambassador,

48
00:02:18,440 --> 00:02:19,860
TheAmbassador.

49
00:02:20,160 --> 00:02:22,680
I was concierge at the Ambassador Hotel.

50
00:02:23,650 --> 00:02:25,990
I could've sworn he worked there for a few months.

51
00:02:28,430 --> 00:02:29,690
Who the hell knows, huh?

52
00:02:29,810 --> 00:02:31,300
I was high half the time.

53
00:02:31,690 --> 00:02:33,260
Kind of why I got fired.

54
00:02:34,050 --> 00:02:35,470
Kind of why I'm in here.

55
00:02:35,480 --> 00:02:36,920
What was he up to in Nice?

56
00:02:37,400 --> 00:02:38,500
What?

57
00:02:38,510 --> 00:02:39,910
You writing a book?

58
00:02:40,560 --> 00:02:42,500
We're leaving at 3:13-- that gives us three hours

59
00:02:42,510 --> 00:02:45,000
41 minutes. And we still don't have a way into no-man's-land.

60
00:02:45,010 --> 00:02:45,620
ll take care of that.

61
00:02:45,630 --> 00:02:47,980
I just need to check it out first. And the fence?

62
00:02:47,990 --> 00:02:49,590
Your grave digger friends only sprayed the thing once,

63
00:02:49,600 --> 00:02:51,290
And I'd just as soon not get electrocuted today.

64
00:02:51,300 --> 00:02:53,490
Would I feel better if Sucre had sprayed the fence again? Yes.

65
00:02:53,500 --> 00:02:55,510
Is that an option? No.

66
00:02:55,700 --> 00:02:57,770
Unless he had another reason to be there.

67
00:02:58,070 --> 00:02:58,640
What are you going to do?

68
00:02:58,650 --> 00:03:00,740
Kill someone to get more spray on the fence?

69
00:03:00,900 --> 00:03:03,420
I'd think about killing you if it helped us get out of here today.

70
00:03:04,030 --> 00:03:05,630
You know what'll help us get out of here?

71
00:03:05,640 --> 00:03:06,640
A ladder.

72
00:03:06,840 --> 00:03:07,750
Michael...

73
00:03:08,670 --> 00:03:10,790
where are we gonna go once we get through that fence?

74
00:03:12,060 --> 00:03:13,410
Just get me a ladder.

75
00:03:18,180 --> 00:03:19,600
This hammock's shorter than the last one.

76
00:03:19,610 --> 00:03:21,220
Well, we might need something to extend it.

77
00:03:21,230 --> 00:03:22,980
All right, I'll take care of it.

78
00:03:24,090 --> 00:03:25,660
I've never been to Nice.

79
00:03:26,010 --> 00:03:27,400
I hear it's beautiful.

80
00:03:27,970 --> 00:03:28,910
I wouldn't know.

81
00:03:28,920 --> 00:03:30,720
I don't care if this guy knows you or not.

82
00:03:30,730 --> 00:03:31,890
But what I do care about is

83
00:03:31,900 --> 00:03:34,530
his apparent fixation with watching you at all times.

84
00:03:35,050 --> 00:03:37,030
Scofield.Visita.

85
00:03:37,230 --> 00:03:38,650
We'll be out of here soon enough.

86
00:03:38,660 --> 00:03:39,790
He won't be a problem.

87
00:03:40,830 --> 00:03:43,070
Scofield, you have a visitor.

88
00:03:50,060 --> 00:03:51,380
Hey, buddy, check it out.

89
00:03:51,390 --> 00:03:53,010
Do they roll bones in your country?

90
00:03:53,040 --> 00:03:54,690
Come to my cell, I'll teach you.

91
00:03:55,530 --> 00:03:58,400
You want me to come back to your cell and "roll bones"?

92
00:03:59,080 --> 00:04:00,340
Real subtle.

93
00:04:00,360 --> 00:04:01,480
Hardy har-har.

94
00:04:01,830 --> 00:04:03,370
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's hilarious.

95
00:04:03,380 --> 00:04:04,290
Tell me,

96
00:04:04,450 --> 00:04:06,750
are you this friendly with all the shirtless guys in Sona?

97
00:04:07,000 --> 00:04:08,190
I gave you food yesterday.

98
00:04:08,200 --> 00:04:09,960
I gave you a place to sleep.

99
00:04:09,970 --> 00:04:11,040
I wonder why.

100
00:04:11,880 --> 00:04:12,610
What the hell is your problem?

101
00:04:12,620 --> 00:04:15,760
Look, I just don't want to have sex with you, okay?

102
00:04:18,170 --> 00:04:19,570
Is that so hard to believe?

103
00:04:29,250 --> 00:04:30,360
Get a plate.

104
00:04:33,130 --> 00:04:35,020
To make it across no-man's-land,

105
00:04:35,130 --> 00:04:37,240
we're going to have to disable two of the tower guards.

106
00:04:37,690 --> 00:04:38,880
I've already taken care of one of them.

107
00:04:38,890 --> 00:04:40,790
With the other one, we're going to need your help.

108
00:04:41,490 --> 00:04:43,000
Every day between 1:00 and 2:00,

109
00:04:43,010 --> 00:04:43,620
he takes his lunch break.

110
00:04:43,630 --> 00:04:44,980
He gets a cup ofoffee.

111
00:04:45,100 --> 00:04:48,160
You need to find out where and put something in that cup.

112
00:04:48,170 --> 00:04:50,030
Make sure he's unconscious during the escape.

113
00:04:50,040 --> 00:04:52,060
You're dropping this on me with three hours to go?

114
00:04:52,770 --> 00:04:55,020
I don't know what to tell you. 3:13?

115
00:04:55,130 --> 00:04:56,710
3:13 is when it starts.

116
00:04:56,940 --> 00:04:58,750
We'll be on the beach by 3:25.

117
00:04:58,760 --> 00:04:59,940
In broad daylight.

118
00:04:59,950 --> 00:05:01,730
The Company still thinks we're doing this at 9:00

119
00:05:01,740 --> 00:05:02,270
tonight, right?

120
00:05:02,280 --> 00:05:04,640
Listen, I can't lie to these people anymore, Michael.

121
00:05:04,650 --> 00:05:06,610
We need time to survey the transfer site,

122
00:05:06,620 --> 00:05:08,740
to figure out if we can get LJ and Sara out of there

123
00:05:08,750 --> 00:05:10,240
in case they try something.

124
00:05:11,340 --> 00:05:13,270
You got the gun? Yeah, I got the gun.

125
00:05:15,670 --> 00:05:17,210
How's LJ? How's Sara?

126
00:05:17,590 --> 00:05:18,540
They're fine.

127
00:05:18,950 --> 00:05:20,300
What about the pictures?

128
00:05:21,180 --> 00:05:22,470
I can't get pictures.

129
00:05:22,950 --> 00:05:23,690
I need them, Linc.

130
00:05:23,700 --> 00:05:25,250
I can't get the pictures.

131
00:05:25,260 --> 00:05:26,480
How do we know they're still alive?

132
00:05:26,490 --> 00:05:28,080
They're the only reason I'm doing this.

133
00:05:28,090 --> 00:05:28,930
Susan says they're fine.

134
00:05:28,940 --> 00:05:30,980
Just trust her. You're the one who's always telling me

135
00:05:30,990 --> 00:05:31,920
we can't trust anybody.

136
00:05:31,930 --> 00:05:34,250
Now you're... you're vouching for this person?

137
00:05:34,260 --> 00:05:36,110
There isn't enough time.

138
00:05:38,250 --> 00:05:41,950
Listen, if I don't see pictures of LJ and Sara by 2:30

139
00:05:41,960 --> 00:05:43,230
this afternoon,

140
00:05:44,470 --> 00:05:45,830
I'm not going anywhere.

141
00:06:33,580 --> 00:06:35,890
Can't seem to find American cheese down here.

142
00:06:35,900 --> 00:06:37,510
I hope you like Asadero.

143
00:06:38,210 --> 00:06:40,100
Yeah. It's perfect.

144
00:06:41,300 --> 00:06:44,490
A couple of years ago, I was serving in Mosul.

145
00:06:45,740 --> 00:06:47,500
And I was taken prisoner.

146
00:06:48,160 --> 00:06:49,180
A few nights later,

147
00:06:49,190 --> 00:06:52,740
I could hear the sound of U.S. Army helicopters.

148
00:06:52,990 --> 00:06:54,480
Two clicks and closing.

149
00:06:56,520 --> 00:06:57,930
My hands were still tied behind my back,

150
00:06:57,940 --> 00:06:59,500
and I... I ran.

151
00:06:59,920 --> 00:07:01,540
It didn't occur to me

152
00:07:01,650 --> 00:07:03,630
that if this was a rescue mission,

153
00:07:04,060 --> 00:07:06,270
my captors could hear the choppers.

154
00:07:07,380 --> 00:07:08,290
It didn't occur to me

155
00:07:08,300 --> 00:07:11,220
that this was actually a hostage exchange,

156
00:07:12,910 --> 00:07:13,900
and that

157
00:07:14,250 --> 00:07:16,900
jumping would be viewed

158
00:07:17,240 --> 00:07:19,000
as a hostile act.

159
00:07:22,020 --> 00:07:24,000
I got recaptured immediately.

160
00:07:25,330 --> 00:07:26,990
Six Rangers died

161
00:07:27,630 --> 00:07:28,760
in the firefight.

162
00:07:30,900 --> 00:07:32,600
And for the next three weeks...

163
00:07:39,680 --> 00:07:40,940
Let's just say

164
00:07:42,220 --> 00:07:43,440
men are pigs.

165
00:07:48,390 --> 00:07:49,650
Let's be clear.

166
00:07:51,340 --> 00:07:53,270
This is an exchange.

167
00:07:54,240 --> 00:07:55,990
If you don't try to be a hero,

168
00:07:56,060 --> 00:07:57,820
you and your father will be okay.

169
00:07:58,650 --> 00:08:00,540
Okay? Okay.

170
00:08:00,880 --> 00:08:01,870
Good.

171
00:08:05,850 --> 00:08:06,780
Eat.

172
00:08:11,250 --> 00:08:13,820
Norman? Norman?!

173
00:08:13,890 --> 00:08:14,590
As you can imagine,

174
00:08:14,600 --> 00:08:15,880
he prefers Lechero.

175
00:08:15,890 --> 00:08:16,920
Norman?

176
00:08:17,310 --> 00:08:19,720
He kill you before or after he does your taxes.

177
00:08:21,580 --> 00:08:24,150
Kill you when he pleases.

178
00:08:24,530 --> 00:08:25,970
I'm feeling thirsty.

179
00:08:26,000 --> 00:08:28,200
Why don't you go fix us something to drink, boy?

180
00:08:28,210 --> 00:08:29,850
Maybe you ain't got the memorandum,

181
00:08:29,860 --> 00:08:31,440
but I've been promoted.

182
00:08:31,600 --> 00:08:32,720
Boy.

183
00:08:36,310 --> 00:08:37,490
What did you say to me?

185
00:08:38,440 --> 00:08:39,520
What's the problem?

186
00:08:40,540 --> 00:08:42,180
Stumpy herand his mouth.

187
00:08:42,190 --> 00:08:43,200
That's the problem.

188
00:08:43,210 --> 00:08:44,920
I'm calling him out right now!

189
00:08:45,310 --> 00:08:47,690
I'll talk to him. Leave.

190
00:08:50,990 --> 00:08:51,570
This isn't over.

191
00:08:54,780 --> 00:08:55,750
Leave!

192
00:08:59,410 --> 00:09:00,340
We was just, uh...

193
00:09:00,350 --> 00:09:01,430
No, no, no.

194
00:09:01,770 --> 00:09:03,010
The favor you owe me...

195
00:09:03,020 --> 00:09:04,470
What have you found out?

196
00:09:04,540 --> 00:09:06,390
A thing like this takes time.

197
00:09:06,500 --> 00:09:08,960
I can't just walk up to them and say, "Hey, whoever's been

198
00:09:08,970 --> 00:09:11,220
betraying Lechero, raise your hand." You know?

199
00:09:11,500 --> 00:09:13,540
I asked you to be my ears in this prison,

200
00:09:13,550 --> 00:09:14,920
and you hear nothing?!

201
00:09:14,930 --> 00:09:17,030
All I know is every time I try and sit down and begin

202
00:09:17,040 --> 00:09:19,810
sussing things out, Sammy always changes the subject.

203
00:09:19,820 --> 00:09:21,440
Not that I'm saying he's the guy, but...

204
00:09:21,450 --> 00:09:23,970
I don't want to hear your theories.

205
00:09:24,670 --> 00:09:25,970
I want results.

206
00:09:45,760 --> 00:09:46,930
Is everything okay?

207
00:09:47,090 --> 00:09:48,810
Is James all right? Yeah, he's fine.

208
00:09:49,900 --> 00:09:50,800
Where is this from?

209
00:09:52,200 --> 00:09:53,690
Uribe's, the roadside

210
00:09:53,700 --> 00:09:55,490
 Bodega a few kilometers away.

211
00:09:55,500 --> 00:09:57,500
If I needed you to ID a specific guard--

212
00:09:57,500 --> 00:09:58,900
a tower guard-- could you do it?

213
00:09:59,900 --> 00:10:01,400
I just don't want to get busted.

214
00:10:01,400 --> 00:10:02,400
Could you do it or not?

215
00:10:02,900 --> 00:10:03,800
Yes.

216
00:10:08,500 --> 00:10:09,700
Lincoln? Yeah.

217
00:10:09,900 --> 00:10:11,500
What is it? I need something.

218
00:10:38,800 --> 00:10:39,790
Teodoro's harmless, man.

219
00:10:39,800 --> 00:10:42,400
He's a... he's clown. He's a dead clown.

220
00:10:48,800 --> 00:10:50,190
Hey, man, I wasn't going to say anything,

221
00:10:50,200 --> 00:10:52,700
but, uh, last night,

222
00:10:53,800 --> 00:10:56,400
I was looking for my playing cards and guess what?

223
00:10:58,100 --> 00:10:59,100
I found these.

224
00:10:59,600 --> 00:11:00,700
You're holding out on me.

225
00:11:01,500 --> 00:11:02,390
Take 'em.

226
00:11:02,400 --> 00:11:03,500
They taste nasty.

227
00:11:03,800 --> 00:11:06,700
Man, you cannot get a better cigar than this.

228
00:11:06,800 --> 00:11:08,800
Where'd you get these? Augusto?

229
00:11:09,600 --> 00:11:10,590
I can't make him stop sending them in to me,

230
00:11:10,600 --> 00:11:12,600
but I don't work for him, you understand?

231
00:11:14,900 --> 00:11:15,900
You re you don't mind?

232
00:11:50,500 --> 00:11:52,300
I was in the neighborhood.

233
00:11:56,800 --> 00:11:58,500
You came all this way to visit?

234
00:11:59,100 --> 00:12:00,500
I came to get you out of here.

235
00:12:01,000 --> 00:12:02,690
I can have you in Schaum Correctional Facility

236
00:12:02,700 --> 00:12:03,900
in 48 hours.

237
00:12:05,000 --> 00:12:06,100
In St. Louis.

238
00:12:06,500 --> 00:12:07,990
Sullins wanted a medium security,

239
00:12:08,000 --> 00:12:10,000
but, uh, talked him down.

240
00:12:10,400 --> 00:12:12,000
What sort of deal is he getting me?

241
00:12:12,200 --> 00:12:13,600
25 years?

242
00:12:13,900 --> 00:12:14,900
Life?

243
00:12:15,000 --> 00:12:16,890
The director's giving us a lot of latitude

244
00:12:16,900 --> 00:12:18,790
in exchange for testimony against the government

245
00:12:18,800 --> 00:12:20,400
in the Lincoln Burrows conspiracy.

246
00:12:21,300 --> 00:12:22,300
So...

247
00:12:23,700 --> 00:12:25,200
how does eight years sound?

248
00:12:26,800 --> 00:12:28,500
Soon as Sullins finishes up,

249
00:12:28,500 --> 00:12:29,900
we can have a van ready...

250
00:12:30,600 --> 00:12:31,800
I don't think so.

251
00:12:32,600 --> 00:12:33,600
What?

252
00:12:34,300 --> 00:12:35,890
I appreciate the effort,

253
00:12:35,900 --> 00:12:39,900
your effort, but, um, I can't do eight years.

254
00:12:40,100 --> 00:12:41,600
You're doing ten now.

255
00:12:43,200 --> 00:12:45,300
The government is calling in some favors.

256
00:12:45,300 --> 00:12:47,890
Once you're in the U.S., if you don't cooperate,

257
00:12:47,900 --> 00:12:48,990
they're going to charge you with everything.

258
00:12:49,000 --> 00:12:50,900
That's multiple homicide counts.

259
00:12:55,700 --> 00:12:56,890
Without this deal,

260
00:12:56,900 --> 00:12:59,200
you are gonna be in prison for the rest of your life.

261
00:13:01,800 --> 00:13:03,300
I appreciate the effort,

262
00:13:03,900 --> 00:13:05,000
your effort.

263
00:13:06,000 --> 00:13:07,000
But I can't.

264
00:13:08,500 --> 00:13:09,500
Alex.

265
00:13:12,800 --> 00:13:14,300
While we're getting out of here, and...

266
00:13:16,100 --> 00:13:17,500
if I don't make it,

267
00:13:18,300 --> 00:13:20,600
will you make sure this gets to my girlfriend?

268
00:13:23,600 --> 00:13:24,700
All right.

269
00:13:28,400 --> 00:13:31,490
You know, uh... I could do the same for you.

270
00:13:31,500 --> 00:13:33,000
Tie an anchor bend there.

271
00:13:34,800 --> 00:13:35,490
I was just offering.

272
00:13:35,500 --> 00:13:37,600
You know what, if I'm the one who doesn't make it,

273
00:13:37,700 --> 00:13:39,200
and you really want to do me a favor,

274
00:13:39,200 --> 00:13:40,800
just hold up your end of the bargain.

275
00:13:42,500 --> 00:13:43,900
I'll do everything I can.

276
00:13:44,000 --> 00:13:45,100
I hope that's true.

277
00:13:46,300 --> 00:13:47,500
How's that knot coming?

278
00:13:49,300 --> 00:13:50,400
There.

279
00:13:51,800 --> 00:13:53,200
Did I pass your test?

280
00:13:54,200 --> 00:13:55,800
I told you I'm a fisherman.

281
00:13:58,000 --> 00:13:58,790
Where are we?

282
00:13:58,800 --> 00:14:00,890
I found a cell that'll get us into no-man's-land.

283
00:14:00,900 --> 00:14:03,090
It's a longer run to the fence than my old one,

284
00:14:03,100 --> 00:14:04,300
but it's gonna have to do.

285
00:14:04,500 --> 00:14:06,000
Which one? Who liveshere?

286
00:14:06,600 --> 00:14:08,700
Papo, Cheo and Sammy.

287
00:14:09,200 --> 00:14:10,600
Look, I know what you're thinking,

288
00:14:10,700 --> 00:14:12,390
but it's the only other cell on the second floor

289
00:14:12,400 --> 00:14:14,990
with a direct line to the fence, where we won't be seen

290
00:14:15,000 --> 00:14:16,590
the other tower guards. And how do we

291
00:14:16,600 --> 00:14:17,990
guarantee that they won't be there?

292
00:14:18,000 --> 00:14:19,990
By 2:00, everyone should be out in the courtyard

293
00:14:20,000 --> 00:14:21,800
for the lunchtime soccer game.

294
00:14:23,400 --> 00:14:25,100
You sure it hasn't started already?

295
00:14:33,900 --> 00:14:36,600
Someone went outside the ring to settle a dispute.

296
00:14:38,200 --> 00:14:40,990
Now, anyone who affronts our justice system

297
00:14:41,000 --> 00:14:43,100
in this way must be punished.

298
00:14:43,800 --> 00:14:46,500
Now, I know the coward won't come forward.

299
00:14:46,800 --> 00:14:50,000
But if anyone has information about this shameful act,

300
00:14:51,100 --> 00:14:52,600
I demand to know.

301
00:15:02,100 --> 00:15:03,790
Let's go, Menudo. Why?

302
00:15:03,800 --> 00:15:05,900
Lechero wants you. Move your ass.

303
00:15:07,800 --> 00:15:09,690
Now, every day I see you out in the yard,

304
00:15:09,700 --> 00:15:10,790
you play your American sports

305
00:15:10,800 --> 00:15:12,090
and wear your American clothes.

306
00:15:12,100 --> 00:15:13,090
I don't think I've heard you

307
00:15:13,100 --> 00:15:15,000
speak one word of Spanish since you've been here.

308
00:15:15,100 --> 00:15:17,000
I like to practice my English.

309
00:15:17,100 --> 00:15:18,300
And why shouldn't you?

310
00:15:19,400 --> 00:15:20,800
America is a great nation.

311
00:15:21,900 --> 00:15:25,190
"One nation, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all."

312
00:15:25,200 --> 00:15:26,100
Is that right?

313
00:15:26,600 --> 00:15:27,390
Yes.

314
00:15:27,400 --> 00:15:28,500
Yes.

315
00:15:29,100 --> 00:15:30,500
Justice for all.

316
00:15:31,000 --> 00:15:34,200
Justice for you and justice for me.

317
00:15:35,700 --> 00:15:37,300
And justice for...

318
00:15:37,600 --> 00:15:39,700
whoever killed that blanquito in the yard.

319
00:15:41,000 --> 00:15:43,300
Now, I know why you didn't say anything out there.

320
00:15:43,800 --> 00:15:46,690
But you play your silly American games all day long,

321
00:15:46,700 --> 00:15:49,200
right in front of the stairs where the body was found.

322
00:15:51,000 --> 00:15:53,500
Now, if you don't tell me what you saw,

323
00:15:55,200 --> 00:15:56,900
there will be consequences.

324
00:16:02,700 --> 00:16:06,100
Well, I-I saw one person go into the stairwell.

325
00:16:08,500 --> 00:16:12,100
A-And then maybe a minute later, I heard an argument.

326
00:16:12,900 --> 00:16:14,700
Who did you see?

327
00:16:18,400 --> 00:16:20,100
So after we tie the cord off...

328
00:16:21,700 --> 00:16:23,590
we dig out the bar, we pop open the grate,

329
00:16:23,600 --> 00:16:24,690
and we're, and we're down, right, Michael?

330
00:16:24,700 --> 00:16:25,790
Does anyone want to say anything

331
00:16:25,800 --> 00:16:27,500
about what we just saw out there?

332
00:16:29,000 --> 00:16:29,890
What is there to say?

333
00:16:29,900 --> 00:16:31,290
Well, for starters, an hour ago,

334
00:16:31,300 --> 00:16:32,590
you say maybe we should kill someone

335
00:16:32,600 --> 00:16:33,690
and then someone gets killed.

336
00:16:33,700 --> 00:16:35,290
I didn't say that, and this is exactly

337
00:16:35,300 --> 00:16:36,590
what we should be focusing on right now.

338
00:16:36,600 --> 00:16:37,890
Let's spend a couple of hours worrying

339
00:16:37,900 --> 00:16:40,200
about another dead body in this hellhole.

340
00:16:40,600 --> 00:16:41,700
What do you want?

341
00:16:42,500 --> 00:16:43,400
What are you doing?

342
00:16:43,500 --> 00:16:44,690
Lechero wants to see you.

343
00:16:44,700 --> 00:16:45,990
I don't have any information.

344
00:16:46,000 --> 00:16:47,400
He doesn't want information.

345
00:16:47,400 --> 00:16:48,700
He wants a confession.

346
00:16:54,300 --> 00:16:55,600
I didn't do anything.

347
00:16:55,600 --> 00:16:57,000
Listen to him; he's innocent.

348
00:16:58,500 --> 00:16:59,700
You want to confess?

349
00:16:59,800 --> 00:17:01,400
You can easily switch places.

350
00:17:06,000 --> 00:17:07,190
Maybe now we should start worrying

351
00:17:07,200 --> 00:17:08,900
about who the real killer is, huh?

352
00:17:09,600 --> 00:17:11,590
Yeah, but in this place,

353
00:17:11,600 --> 00:17:13,090
there could be a hundred people on that list.

354
00:17:13,100 --> 00:17:14,790
Except I'm thinking a single stab wound

355
00:17:14,800 --> 00:17:17,100
to the base of the neck looks pretty professional, Alex.

356
00:17:17,300 --> 00:17:18,690
I was in visitation, Kojak.

357
00:17:18,700 --> 00:17:21,300
And what makes you so sure that Whistler didn't do it?

358
00:17:21,300 --> 00:17:23,090
He's the one that had the run-in with the guy.

359
00:17:23,100 --> 00:17:24,590
No, he's got too much to lose. Well,

360
00:17:24,600 --> 00:17:25,690
Whistler's gone, and if not now,

361
00:17:25,700 --> 00:17:27,490
he probably will be soon, so it's you and me.

362
00:17:27,500 --> 00:17:28,800
There's no you and me.

363
00:17:29,100 --> 00:17:30,500
We're not leaving here without him.

364
00:17:30,800 --> 00:17:33,090
In two hours, I'm going out that window and through that fence.

365
00:17:33,100 --> 00:17:34,890
Oh, yeah? Yeah, that's right.

366
00:17:34,900 --> 00:17:36,190
And where are you going to go to, Alex?

367
00:17:36,200 --> 00:17:37,290
Anywhere but here.

368
00:17:37,300 --> 00:17:38,700
There's only one road out,

369
00:17:38,900 --> 00:17:40,990
and the jungle is under constant patrol by police 24-7,

370
00:17:41,000 --> 00:17:43,100
so, again, where are you going to go to, Alex?

371
00:17:43,100 --> 00:17:45,200
3:13, I'm gone.

372
00:17:51,100 --> 00:17:53,000
I told you I know nothing about this.

373
00:17:53,400 --> 00:17:54,600
I shouldn't...

374
00:17:54,900 --> 00:17:56,090
I shouldn't be here.

375
00:17:56,100 --> 00:17:58,700
I can promise you I, I did not kill that man.

376
00:17:58,700 --> 00:18:00,500
Someone saw you go down the staircase.

377
00:18:00,700 --> 00:18:02,900
Stai.. is there any other proof?

378
00:18:03,200 --> 00:18:04,500
My men will find something.

379
00:18:04,600 --> 00:18:06,200
Well, do you see a weapon on me?

380
00:18:06,200 --> 00:18:08,090
I didn't expect to see a weapon on you.

381
00:18:08,100 --> 00:18:09,890
Well, w-why don't they look for that?

382
00:18:09,900 --> 00:18:11,590
You find that, you'll find the real killer.

383
00:18:11,600 --> 00:18:13,490
Or maybe they find where you planted it.

384
00:18:13,500 --> 00:18:14,990
So, what, I'm framing someone?

385
00:18:15,000 --> 00:18:16,190
Well, did it ever occur to you

386
00:18:16,200 --> 00:18:18,590
that someone might be framing me? Who would bother?

387
00:18:18,600 --> 00:18:19,690
You know the reason I'm here.

388
00:18:19,700 --> 00:18:20,890
You know I have powerful enemies.

389
00:18:20,900 --> 00:18:23,200
You think my judgment is swayed by the mayor's friends?

390
00:18:23,400 --> 00:18:24,900
Sit your ass down.

391
00:18:26,000 --> 00:18:27,200
When I was 13,

392
00:18:29,400 --> 00:18:31,500
my mother worked for a wealthy man as a maid

393
00:18:32,600 --> 00:18:33,900
until one day...

394
00:18:35,500 --> 00:18:37,300
...she was alone in the house...

395
00:18:39,200 --> 00:18:40,600
with him and he...

396
00:18:46,100 --> 00:18:47,700
Everybody knew what he did,

397
00:18:50,600 --> 00:18:52,300
but because he was rich

398
00:18:52,600 --> 00:18:54,500
and we were immigrants,

399
00:18:55,700 --> 00:18:57,800
the police wouldn't even take a report.

400
00:19:00,000 --> 00:19:02,400
So, a week later,

401
00:19:02,500 --> 00:19:04,500
to gain access through his gates,

402
00:19:05,500 --> 00:19:08,700
I dressed as a milkman-- a Lechero --

403
00:19:09,800 --> 00:19:13,300
and I madeure that fair punishment was rendered.

404
00:19:14,500 --> 00:19:16,900
Now you want to tell me how I favor the rich.

405
00:19:19,800 --> 00:19:23,500
I understand the rules here, and I respect them.

406
00:19:24,800 --> 00:19:26,600
But why the rush to judgment?

407
00:19:27,200 --> 00:19:29,790
Is there a rule saying you must convict a suspect

408
00:19:29,800 --> 00:19:31,000
within ten minutes?

409
00:19:34,800 --> 00:19:35,800
No.

410
00:19:40,600 --> 00:19:42,100
We have all the time in the world.

411
00:19:44,500 --> 00:19:45,400
Thank you.

412
00:19:45,800 --> 00:19:47,700
Now, obviously, I'm not going anywhere.

413
00:19:47,700 --> 00:19:49,900
If you need to talk again, I'm gonna be in my cell.

414
00:19:50,000 --> 00:19:50,900
No.

415
00:19:51,300 --> 00:19:53,500
You'll be right here in this chair.

416
00:20:09,650 --> 00:20:11,140
What the hell do you want?

417
00:20:11,150 --> 00:20:12,150
I don't like you.

418
00:20:13,150 --> 00:20:15,050
I certainly don't respect you.

419
00:20:15,350 --> 00:20:16,640
Stop. You're hurting my feelings.

420
00:20:16,650 --> 00:20:18,740
I've seen at you're capable of,

421
00:20:18,750 --> 00:20:19,950
but I got to say

422
00:20:19,950 --> 00:20:21,650
I never pegged you as a murderer.

423
00:20:22,950 --> 00:20:24,450
You think I killed Tyge?

424
00:20:24,950 --> 00:20:28,540
I saw the two of you in the courtyard this morning.

425
00:20:28,550 --> 00:20:29,840
I was trying to be Nice to him.

426
00:20:29,850 --> 00:20:30,940
He started with me.

427
00:20:30,950 --> 00:20:32,450
Well, if you didn't kill him, who did?

428
00:20:32,950 --> 00:20:33,650
Not me.

429
00:20:33,650 --> 00:20:34,850
Come on, Brad.

430
00:20:35,350 --> 00:20:36,850
Who wanted him dead besides you?

431
00:20:36,850 --> 00:20:38,450
You really think I killed that frog?

432
00:20:38,750 --> 00:20:41,050
How many times have I had you at gunpoint?

433
00:20:41,350 --> 00:20:43,150
You think I didn't want to pull that trigger?

434
00:20:47,350 --> 00:20:47,950
Hell...

435
00:20:49,650 --> 00:20:51,450
I can't even kill myself.

436
00:21:01,550 --> 00:21:04,450
Hey, you seen anyone see Whistler go down the stairway?

437
00:21:04,750 --> 00:21:06,250
We only been out here a minute.

438
00:21:06,350 --> 00:21:07,540
Well, hurry up, then.

439
00:21:07,550 --> 00:21:08,950
The sooner Whistler dies,

440
00:21:09,750 --> 00:21:11,650
the sooner I can give you the chicken foot,

441
00:21:11,850 --> 00:21:14,040
or if you prefer, you can give me the chicken foot--

442
00:21:14,050 --> 00:21:16,150
you know, try and go out like a man.

443
00:21:16,850 --> 00:21:19,550
Either way, you're getting in the ring with me today.

444
00:21:28,950 --> 00:21:32,250
Zylafol. It's used to anesthetize dogs.

445
00:21:32,250 --> 00:21:34,550
Two drops, and the guard should be out within an hour.

446
00:21:35,750 --> 00:21:37,850
I was expecting Whistler's girlfriend to join you.

447
00:21:37,950 --> 00:21:39,640
Where is she? Around the corner in the car?

448
00:21:39,650 --> 00:21:40,750
She came to me.

449
00:21:41,150 --> 00:21:42,340
I don't mind that she's helping you.

450
00:21:42,350 --> 00:21:43,950
I mind that you kept it from me.

451
00:21:44,550 --> 00:21:45,640
What difference does it make?

452
00:21:45,650 --> 00:21:46,740
I mean, we're done by tomorrow, right?

453
00:21:46,750 --> 00:21:48,650
No more surprises, Lincoln.

454
00:21:50,850 --> 00:21:51,850
What? Say it.

455
00:21:52,250 --> 00:21:53,950
Can you get any more pictures of Sara?

456
00:21:54,750 --> 00:21:56,550
Alive? No.

457
00:21:59,650 --> 00:22:00,750
You didn't tell him.

458
00:22:01,550 --> 00:22:03,650
You didn't tell Michael that Sara's dead.

459
00:22:04,850 --> 00:22:06,150
Can we get pictures or not?

460
00:22:06,850 --> 00:22:08,540
I'm sure we can cobble something together,

461
00:22:08,550 --> 00:22:11,350
but smart move not telling your brother.

462
00:22:11,450 --> 00:22:13,250
He seems a little sensitive to me.

463
00:22:15,550 --> 00:22:17,640
This is the exchange point-- LJ and I will be waiting.

464
00:22:17,650 --> 00:22:19,240
You, Michael and Whistler will meet us there.

465
00:22:19,250 --> 00:22:22,450
Everything goes as planned, you'll have your son back by 9:00.

466
00:22:23,550 --> 00:22:24,150
Lincoln?

467
00:22:25,250 --> 00:22:26,150
9:00.

468
00:22:42,150 --> 00:22:43,350
Which one is it?

469
00:22:43,550 --> 00:22:44,840
I don't know, I think it's the taller one.

470
00:22:44,850 --> 00:22:47,150
The other one is always drinking orange juice. You sure?

471
00:22:47,150 --> 00:22:48,640
I think so, I'm not completely sure,

472
00:22:48,650 --> 00:22:49,440
but they all look the same. Hey!

474
00:22:50,150 --> 00:22:51,440
We've been trying to reach you.

475
00:22:51,450 --> 00:22:52,850
There's another dead body in Sona.

476
00:22:52,950 --> 00:22:53,640
I was just...

477
00:22:53,650 --> 00:22:55,250
Come on.

478
00:22:58,250 --> 00:22:59,750
You want a coffee?

479
00:22:59,850 --> 00:23:01,050
Get me a juice.

480
00:23:01,150 --> 00:23:02,150
Orange juice.

481
00:23:05,950 --> 00:23:08,950
One orange juice and one coffee, please.

482
00:23:21,150 --> 00:23:22,250
Watch where you're going!

483
00:23:22,350 --> 00:23:23,140
Here, look, uh...

484
00:23:23,150 --> 00:23:24,740
this is a buddy's, please.

485
00:23:24,750 --> 00:23:26,050
Please, I insist.

486
00:23:26,950 --> 00:23:29,050
Captain Hurtado!  Here's a new coffee.

487
00:23:29,150 --> 00:23:29,640
No really.

488
00:23:29,650 --> 00:23:30,550
Toma, Toma .

489
00:23:31,850 --> 00:23:32,550
Toma.

490
00:23:32,850 --> 00:23:33,650
Gracias.

491
00:23:33,850 --> 00:23:36,350
Man, I...

492
00:23:36,350 --> 00:23:37,250
Thank you anyway.

493
00:23:38,250 --> 00:23:38,840
Excuse me, Señor.

494
00:23:38,850 --> 00:23:40,550
I need to go to Sona.

495
00:23:40,650 --> 00:23:41,440
I...

496
00:23:41,450 --> 00:23:43,240
my car's run out of gas and-- Sorry.

497
00:23:43,250 --> 00:23:45,540
I'm-I'm heading in the wrong, wrong direction.

498
00:23:45,550 --> 00:23:47,040
I really need to go to Sona.

499
00:23:47,050 --> 00:23:49,650
I'll give you a ride.

500
00:23:49,650 --> 00:23:50,950
Come along.

501
00:23:51,350 --> 00:23:52,050
Thank you.

502
00:23:56,050 --> 00:23:57,850
Watch the lid.

503
00:24:12,350 --> 00:24:14,050
My condolences.

504
00:24:14,650 --> 00:24:17,140
You finally make a friend, and now he's about to die.

505
00:24:17,150 --> 00:24:18,250
Damn shame.

506
00:24:18,950 --> 00:24:20,350
You can stop it, you know.

507
00:24:21,350 --> 00:24:22,440
If you hadn't noticed,

508
00:24:22,450 --> 00:24:25,150
my position enables me to hear things.

509
00:24:29,550 --> 00:24:30,350
I'm listening.

510
00:24:30,750 --> 00:24:32,440
The only proof Lechero's got is

511
00:24:32,450 --> 00:24:34,340
that your man went down that staircase, t?

512
00:24:34,350 --> 00:24:35,440
What if you had more compelling

513
00:24:35,450 --> 00:24:37,050
evidence? Well, I don't.

514
00:24:37,150 --> 00:24:38,250
But if you did...

515
00:24:38,550 --> 00:24:40,040
You're suggesting I make something up?

516
00:24:40,050 --> 00:24:41,840
If it makes your conscience feel better,

517
00:24:41,850 --> 00:24:43,340
then blame it on somebody who deserves it.

518
00:24:43,350 --> 00:24:44,440
Someone who's killed before

519
00:24:44,450 --> 00:24:45,340
and gone unpunished.

520
00:24:45,350 --> 00:24:46,650
Yeah, like you maybe.

521
00:24:48,150 --> 00:24:49,050
Sammy.

522
00:24:53,150 --> 00:24:54,340
You want me to tell Lechero

523
00:24:54,350 --> 00:24:56,050
that his right hand man should die?

524
00:24:56,850 --> 00:25:00,150
You don't tell Lechero squat.

525
00:25:00,850 --> 00:25:01,740
Lechero knows

526
00:25:01,750 --> 00:25:03,150
this is Sammy's ring.

527
00:25:03,850 --> 00:25:04,540
If you drop it

528
00:25:04,550 --> 00:25:05,940
in the blood by the staircase,

529
00:25:05,950 --> 00:25:07,940
then yell up to Lechero what you've found...

530
00:25:07,950 --> 00:25:09,440
the whole entire

531
00:25:09,450 --> 00:25:11,440
prison will hear clear-cut evidence

532
00:25:11,450 --> 00:25:12,850
of Sammy's guilt.

533
00:25:13,050 --> 00:25:16,250
Lechero will have no choice but to comply.

534
00:25:21,750 --> 00:25:23,550
This is Sona.

535
00:25:24,750 --> 00:25:26,740
Don't worry your pretty little head about it.

536
00:25:26,750 --> 00:25:29,240
All you have to do is drop the ring in the blood

537
00:25:29,250 --> 00:25:30,640
and say it was Sammy.

538
00:25:30,650 --> 00:25:31,850
I'll take care of the rest.

539
00:25:35,550 --> 00:25:37,450
You want to save your friend's life?

540
00:25:38,250 --> 00:25:39,950
Someone else has to die.

541
00:26:27,050 --> 00:26:28,850
Explain your disagreement with this Tyge man.

542
00:26:29,250 --> 00:26:30,140
From what I just heard,

543
00:26:30,150 --> 00:26:31,350
he knew something about you?

544
00:26:32,450 --> 00:26:34,050
He thought he knew something about me.

545
00:26:34,550 --> 00:26:35,640
Opportunity and a motive.

546
00:26:35,650 --> 00:26:36,750
That's not a good combination.

547
00:26:36,850 --> 00:26:38,240
You must know there's discontent

548
00:26:38,250 --> 00:26:40,550
from many prisoners over how you run Sona.

549
00:26:40,850 --> 00:26:42,750
Now would not be a good time to insult me.

550
00:26:43,550 --> 00:26:47,740
you execute me, you get your swift justice

551
00:26:47,750 --> 00:26:49,040
and you may placate the masses.

552
00:26:49,050 --> 00:26:50,650
But when they find out who really did it...

553
00:26:51,250 --> 00:26:53,150
they will know you killed an innocent man.

554
00:26:53,150 --> 00:26:54,850
You're still not answering my question.

555
00:26:54,850 --> 00:26:56,440
What was your disagreement with Tyge?

556
00:26:56,450 --> 00:26:57,240
He was a nosy guy.

557
00:26:57,250 --> 00:26:58,450
He got into my business.

558
00:26:58,850 --> 00:27:00,440
I'm sure he did the same with someone else,

559
00:27:00,450 --> 00:27:01,650
and that's what got him killed.

560
00:27:01,750 --> 00:27:03,540
Would you just admit that you had an argument?

561
00:27:03,550 --> 00:27:04,450
This is prison.

562
00:27:04,450 --> 00:27:06,640
If someone makes false accusations, I can't back down.

563
00:27:06,650 --> 00:27:07,940
You must respect that.

564
00:27:07,950 --> 00:27:09,850
Look, I've answered every one of your questions.

565
00:27:10,150 --> 00:27:11,740
I've acquitted myself the best that I can.

566
00:27:11,750 --> 00:27:13,650
Now what can I do to make you trust me?

567
00:27:17,850 --> 00:27:18,950
I don't trust anybody today.

568
00:27:24,450 --> 00:27:26,050
You must get this a lot, but...

569
00:27:26,350 --> 00:27:27,650
You're very pretty.

570
00:27:28,850 --> 00:27:30,950
I mean very, very pretty.

571
00:27:55,150 --> 00:27:56,850
What's the trouble?

572
00:28:01,350 --> 00:28:05,750
You probably don't know this, but...

573
00:28:06,150 --> 00:28:07,950
There is a special visitation

574
00:28:08,050 --> 00:28:09,650
for special people...

575
00:28:10,150 --> 00:28:12,950
I could arrange for you to go inside Sona

576
00:28:13,650 --> 00:28:17,450
and have some private time with your love.

577
00:28:19,050 --> 00:28:21,050
And everything you would need

578
00:28:22,850 --> 00:28:24,350
to assure your entry

579
00:28:25,650 --> 00:28:26,950
could be performed right here in this car.

580
00:28:37,850 --> 00:28:38,850
Yeah.

581
00:28:39,050 --> 00:28:40,350
We have the picture.

582
00:28:40,650 --> 00:28:41,750
How does it look?

583
00:28:41,950 --> 00:28:43,350
It looks like Sara.

584
00:28:44,650 --> 00:28:45,840
I'll be at Sona in half an hour.

585
00:28:45,850 --> 00:28:47,250
Meet me in the parking lot.

586
00:28:48,050 --> 00:28:49,250
Is everything okay?

587
00:28:49,450 --> 00:28:50,950
Hold on, hold on, hold on.

588
00:28:53,550 --> 00:28:55,150
Don't you love your man?

589
00:28:57,250 --> 00:28:58,340
I don't know if you know this, but

590
00:28:58,350 --> 00:29:00,950
Norman has a terrible temper.

591
00:29:01,850 --> 00:29:03,950
Norman? Norman St. John?

592
00:29:04,350 --> 00:29:05,250
S?

593
00:29:06,150 --> 00:29:07,840
You're one of Lechero's girls?

594
00:29:07,850 --> 00:29:08,750
S?

595
00:29:29,150 --> 00:29:30,550
I'm waiting.

596
00:29:30,950 --> 00:29:32,750
There was a complication with the guard.

597
00:29:33,550 --> 00:29:35,550
Complications drugging the guard?

598
00:29:35,650 --> 00:29:37,150
Yeah, but it's been taken care of.

599
00:29:38,450 --> 00:29:39,440
Well, that's encouraging,

600
00:29:39,450 --> 00:29:40,740
but why are you drugging the guard

601
00:29:40,750 --> 00:29:42,450
now when you're escaping tonight?

602
00:29:42,750 --> 00:29:44,040
Well, it takes that long for the drugs to work...

603
00:29:44,050 --> 00:29:46,350
They take an hour, like I told you.

604
00:29:54,050 --> 00:29:54,850
Alex...

605
00:30:44,300 --> 00:30:45,390
for walking into the wrong stairwell.

606
00:30:45,400 --> 00:30:46,390
I'm thinking this is enough

607
00:30:46,400 --> 00:30:47,890
to get you guys to switch places.

608
00:30:47,900 --> 00:30:48,900
You know what I mean?

609
00:30:49,100 --> 00:30:50,590
What does that mean, huh? What does that prove?

610
00:30:50,600 --> 00:30:51,500
It proves everything!

611
00:30:51,500 --> 00:30:53,500
I'm gonna make sure Lechero thinks so, too.

612
00:30:53,500 --> 00:30:54,200
Michael.

613
00:30:55,100 --> 00:30:56,790
Michael, I did not kill that man.

614
00:30:56,800 --> 00:30:58,700
I did not kill the man.

615
00:31:06,900 --> 00:31:08,100
What's, what's going on?

616
00:31:09,200 --> 00:31:10,200
Is everything okay?

617
00:31:13,200 --> 00:31:14,400
What the hell you doing?

619
00:31:16,200 --> 00:31:16,990
What's that for?

620
00:31:17,000 --> 00:31:19,100
Your father tried to be a hero.

621
00:31:20,000 --> 00:31:20,900
No, no.

622
00:31:21,000 --> 00:31:22,590
Hey, please, please.

623
00:31:22,600 --> 00:31:23,300
Please.

624
00:31:23,400 --> 00:31:26,490
Please, no, stop! Stop!

625
00:31:26,500 --> 00:31:28,590
Once I cut the spinal cord and the sever nerve endings,

626
00:31:28,600 --> 00:31:29,590
you won't feel a thing.

627
00:31:29,600 --> 00:31:30,290
No, no.

628
00:31:30,300 --> 00:31:32,300
No, no!

629
00:31:38,400 --> 00:31:39,690
Susan, I'm sorry.

630
00:31:39,700 --> 00:31:41,100
We didn't mean to do that.

631
00:31:41,400 --> 00:31:43,200
Dad, they're gonna kill me.

632
00:31:43,300 --> 00:31:44,600
What? LJ?

633
00:31:44,600 --> 00:31:46,500
Yeah, they got a knife to my throat.

634
00:31:46,700 --> 00:31:47,500
LJ!

635
00:31:48,100 --> 00:31:49,090
Susan, don't you hurt-- Dad...

636
00:31:49,100 --> 00:31:50,300
The truth.

637
00:31:50,700 --> 00:31:51,400
Truth.

638
00:31:54,600 --> 00:31:56,590
Michael's getting out at 3:13.

639
00:31:56,600 --> 00:31:58,800
We're meeting at the exchange point at 3:45.

640
00:31:58,900 --> 00:32:00,090
Susan, please, we did this

641
00:32:00,100 --> 00:32:02,500
because we wanted to make sure the site was safe.

642
00:32:02,600 --> 00:32:04,700
That's it, that's the only reason why we did it.

643
00:32:04,700 --> 00:32:06,890
Sounds to me like you're planning another end round.

644
00:32:06,900 --> 00:32:08,100
Another rescue.

645
00:32:08,100 --> 00:32:09,100
No, no.

646
00:32:09,200 --> 00:32:11,200
We're not, we're not planning,

647
00:32:11,300 --> 00:32:13,000
re not planning another end round.

648
00:32:13,300 --> 00:32:15,400
No. Please, just...

649
00:32:15,500 --> 00:32:16,400
let my son go.

650
00:32:16,600 --> 00:32:17,400
Leave my son.

653
00:32:41,400 --> 00:32:42,700
Living the good life, huh?

654
00:32:44,400 --> 00:32:45,500
Is that what this is?

655
00:32:46,400 --> 00:32:47,590
Having too good a time here

656
00:32:47,600 --> 00:32:49,200
to contemplate leaving?

657
00:32:51,600 --> 00:32:53,400
I needed some time to think.

658
00:32:53,600 --> 00:32:54,990
Well, I needed some time

659
00:32:55,000 --> 00:32:57,090
to finalize our agreement with the Panamanians,

660
00:32:57,100 --> 00:32:58,990
but instead I get dragged down here.

661
00:32:59,000 --> 00:33:00,090
Yeah, I'm sure it was really hard

662
00:33:00,100 --> 00:33:01,600
to convince you to come down here.

663
00:33:03,900 --> 00:33:05,100
I'm gonna be honest.

664
00:33:06,300 --> 00:33:07,490
I was looking forward to seeing you

665
00:33:07,500 --> 00:33:12,400
dowI, uh, wouldn't wish this but now thaon anyone.

666
00:33:15,700 --> 00:33:17,590
Can we just save all this till after...

667
00:33:17,600 --> 00:33:18,490
I don't know if we can or not.

668
00:33:18,500 --> 00:33:20,200
Made up your mind yet, Alex?

669
00:33:20,300 --> 00:33:22,100
Eight years, minimum security.

670
00:33:22,300 --> 00:33:23,600
I got 'em down to four.

671
00:33:24,500 --> 00:33:26,090
And I leave for the US tonight?

672
00:33:26,100 --> 00:33:26,690
Once the special

673
00:33:26,700 --> 00:33:28,090
prosecutor clears you,

674
00:33:28,100 --> 00:33:28,690
you'll be on your way.

676
00:33:30,600 --> 00:33:31,790
What about a special prosecutor?

677
00:33:31,800 --> 00:33:33,190
You stand in front of a guy,

678
00:33:33,200 --> 00:33:35,190
you, you tell your story and he determines

679
00:33:35,200 --> 00:33:37,290
if you're gonna be a useful and credible witness.

680
00:33:37,300 --> 00:33:38,400
It's a formality.

681
00:33:39,100 --> 00:33:40,100
"It's a formality"?

682
00:33:40,800 --> 00:33:42,100
This is just a formality?

683
00:33:42,100 --> 00:33:44,000
You know, if it were up to me,

684
00:33:44,600 --> 00:33:46,100
you could rot in here for the rest of your life.

685
00:33:47,400 --> 00:33:48,490
But the Justice Department

686
00:33:48,500 --> 00:33:51,000
is extremely motivated to get to the bottom

687
00:33:51,200 --> 00:33:53,100
of this President Reynolds business.

688
00:33:54,000 --> 00:33:56,200
Alex, this is a hundred percent abovboard.

689
00:33:56,500 --> 00:33:58,200
You've made a lot of mistakes in your career.

690
00:33:58,400 --> 00:33:59,590
You know it and I know it,

691
00:33:59,600 --> 00:34:01,090
intentional or otherwise.

692
00:34:01,100 --> 00:34:04,600
I've got eight files in my office attesting to that.

693
00:34:04,800 --> 00:34:07,100
And if you don't take this offer,

694
00:34:07,500 --> 00:34:09,090
then I assure you it would be

695
00:34:09,100 --> 00:34:10,600
the biggest mistake of your life.

696
00:34:19,000 --> 00:34:19,890
I know who killed that man.

697
00:34:19,900 --> 00:34:20,800
I'm sure you do.

698
00:34:20,800 --> 00:34:21,600
Lechero!

699
00:34:27,400 --> 00:34:28,400
What do we have here?

700
00:34:28,500 --> 00:34:29,500
I found this

701
00:34:30,100 --> 00:34:31,800
in Alexander Mahone's cell.

702
00:34:52,000 --> 00:34:53,000
Convenient!

703
00:34:53,100 --> 00:34:55,400
To blame this on a man who can't even be questioned.

704
00:34:56,900 --> 00:34:58,700
Enough of this already. Cheo!

705
00:35:01,600 --> 00:35:02,700
Get the prison up.

706
00:35:03,300 --> 00:35:04,400
this time

707
00:35:15,500 --> 00:35:16,890
You kno Whistler didn't do this.

708
00:35:16,900 --> 00:35:19,000
He just said he found the shank in Mahone's cell?

709
00:35:19,000 --> 00:35:20,090
Doesn't that prove I'm innocent?

710
00:35:20,100 --> 00:35:20,900
You're a joke!

711
00:35:21,900 --> 00:35:22,790
You talk about equality.

712
00:35:22,800 --> 00:35:24,290
You talk justice, but at the end of the day

713
00:35:24,300 --> 00:35:26,490
you're a dictator, and just like any dictator

714
00:35:26,500 --> 00:35:28,190
you're terrified of losing your power.

715
00:35:28,200 --> 00:35:30,290
It'd be very unwise to go any further.

716
00:35:30,300 --> 00:35:31,690
You don't care who the real killer is

717
00:35:31,700 --> 00:35:33,490
just as long as you get to string somebody up.

718
00:35:33,500 --> 00:35:35,190
That's all that matters to you, isn't it?

719
00:35:35,200 --> 00:35:38,090
I've determined who's guilty, and the punishment is death.

720
00:35:38,100 --> 00:35:39,690
You're making a mistake. This is murder!

721
00:35:39,700 --> 00:35:41,100
You know it and I know it!

722
00:35:41,300 --> 00:35:42,690
At least have the guts to admit it!

723
00:35:42,700 --> 00:35:43,500
You're right!

724
00:35:44,700 --> 00:35:45,400
It's murder.

725
00:35:49,400 --> 00:35:50,100
Don't!

726
00:36:06,300 --> 00:36:07,500
I found this in the yar

727
00:36:11,300 --> 00:36:13,500
Augusto used to give them to me as tribute.

728
00:36:14,000 --> 00:36:15,600
And now you reek of them.

729
00:36:27,500 --> 00:36:28,300
Go.

730
00:37:01,900 --> 00:37:02,800
Everything okay?

731
00:37:03,400 --> 00:37:04,700
It's sad...

732
00:37:06,000 --> 00:37:07,800
one wrong move and a stranger

733
00:37:07,800 --> 00:37:09,800
is throwing dirt on top of you.

734
00:37:29,300 --> 00:37:30,300
He will be okay.

735
00:37:48,300 --> 00:37:50,200
I question your love for your son.

736
00:37:51,000 --> 00:37:53,500
He was two seconds away from being decapitated

737
00:37:54,100 --> 00:37:55,000
because of you.

738
00:37:55,400 --> 00:37:56,300
I told you the truth.

739
00:37:56,900 --> 00:37:57,700
Maybe.

740
00:37:58,200 --> 00:37:59,490
But if you have anything else planned,

741
00:37:59,500 --> 00:38:00,600
now it's scrapped.

742
00:38:00,800 --> 00:38:03,100
Because, what happens if you try something?

743
00:38:04,700 --> 00:38:05,400
I know.

744
00:38:05,500 --> 00:38:06,300
Oh, good.

745
00:38:14,200 --> 00:38:16,390
This is the same newspaper she was holding in the last picture.

746
00:38:16,400 --> 00:38:17,890
That's what my guy could get.

747
00:38:17,900 --> 00:38:19,090
You didn't give me a lot of time.

748
00:38:19,100 --> 00:38:21,000
You think Michael's not going to Nice this?

749
00:38:21,000 --> 00:38:24,100
Yeah. "Hey, Michael, here's the pictures."

750
00:38:24,200 --> 00:38:25,900
He's going to want to see this close up.

751
00:38:26,100 --> 00:38:27,800
I'm done doing favors for you.

752
00:38:27,900 --> 00:38:28,800
Get out.

753
00:38:29,000 --> 00:38:30,100
I'll see you in an hour.

754
00:38:56,600 --> 00:38:57,900
No football today?

755
00:38:58,400 --> 00:38:59,900
No, no football today.

756
00:39:05,200 --> 00:39:06,500
You're my brother, Sammy?

757
00:39:10,000 --> 00:39:10,900
Of course.

758
00:39:33,300 --> 00:39:34,000
It's done?

759
00:39:34,600 --> 00:39:36,100
The guard will be asleep in a half hour.

760
00:39:36,200 --> 00:39:37,100
So we're good.

761
00:39:38,000 --> 00:39:38,800
Not quite.

762
00:39:40,300 --> 00:39:42,800
They, uh, they know we're breaking out this afternoon.

763
00:39:46,400 --> 00:39:47,200
You told her?

764
00:39:47,900 --> 00:39:48,790
Man, she worked it out...

765
00:39:48,800 --> 00:39:50,700
Why didn't you lie? She workedout.

766
00:39:50,800 --> 00:39:53,000
So what are we gonna do to get the upper hand here, Linc?

767
00:39:53,700 --> 00:39:55,090
Nothing. You think they're just going to turn over

768
00:39:55,100 --> 00:39:56,990
LJ and Sara? This is too dangerous.

769
00:39:57,000 --> 00:39:58,290
If we try anything, they're just going to...

770
00:39:58,300 --> 00:39:59,400
What, hurt them?

771
00:40:01,500 --> 00:40:03,900
No, not if they want us to deliver on Whistler, they won't.

772
00:40:04,900 --> 00:40:06,100
We're playing this one straight.

773
00:40:06,200 --> 00:40:07,890
No games. No surprises.

774
00:40:07,900 --> 00:40:08,600
All right?

775
00:40:10,800 --> 00:40:12,000
Show me the pictures.

776
00:40:15,800 --> 00:40:17,400
Show me the pictures, Linc.

777
00:40:17,800 --> 00:40:18,600
Come on...

778
00:40:20,100 --> 00:40:21,100
The pictures.

779
00:40:21,400 --> 00:40:22,900
I can't show you the pictures, man.

780
00:40:27,800 --> 00:40:28,900
Why not, Linc?

781
00:40:37,700 --> 00:40:39,000
She's dead, Michael.

782
00:40:44,500 --> 00:40:45,500
I lied to you.

783
00:40:45,800 --> 00:40:46,800
I'm sorry.

784
00:40:48,700 --> 00:40:50,700
If you don't break out today, they're going to kill my son.

785
00:40:51,800 --> 00:40:53,100
They're going to kill LJ.

786
00:40:54,800 --> 00:40:56,100
Michael, we've got to do this.

787
00:40:57,100 --> 00:40:58,500
Michael, we've got to do this!

788
00:40:59,300 --> 00:41:00,100
Michael!

789
00:42:08,500 --> 00:42:09,600
Sara's dead.

790
00:42:13,000 --> 00:42:14,100
They killed her.

791
00:42:17,800 --> 00:42:18,900
Oh, man, I'm so sorry.

792
00:42:22,500 --> 00:42:25,800
I loved her and... now she's go.

793
00:42:28,000 --> 00:42:29,500
And it's all because of you.

794
00:42:30,700 --> 00:42:31,400
What?

795
00:42:34,000 --> 00:42:35,400
Hey, take it easy.

796
00:42:41,300 --> 00:42:42,500
Wh... What?

797
00:42:43,000 --> 00:42:44,300
This is your fault.

798
00:42:44,500 --> 00:42:45,000
Huh?!

799
00:42:45,600 --> 00:42:46,900
He's told me his grievance.

800
00:42:47,700 --> 00:42:49,000
This fight is going to happen.

801
00:42:50,600 --> 00:42:52,300
Just think about what you're doing.

802
00:42:52,800 --> 00:42:54,800
I have.
